Are you bullying Samantha again?
Please don't misunderstand. Richard was just giving me some new health supplements this company is developing.
He really cares about me and wanted me to try them.
I just spilled them all just now.
Okay, well that's good then.
By the way, tomorrow we're going to have a small wedding ceremony for Carrie and I.
I hope both of you come.
Are you really going to marry the maid? My mother's in a fucking coma?
Can you wait? Do you have any fucking remorse?
Your mother and I were divorced two years ago, please.
So carry a little respect.
Don't act like you fucking care about me.
Richard, can't you be nicer to me?
You're not disgust to me.
If you knew that I will die soon,
put your heartbreak even just a little.