Hi, you're awake so you stay here watching over me all night Samantha
What made you cough up blood? It's just
My old stomach is just acting up. You see that's the thing. I
Haven't really heard about your stomach is just before so I'm glad you're doing well. I'm leaving
He was a little boy, but now every time he sees me he looks at me like I miss a worst enemy
Don't say that
Well tomorrow is my wedding to Gavin and I will find you a rich fiance from the wedding attendees
Just forget about Richard. You're pitiful act fooled me again. You and your mother's scheme makes me sick
I won't let this wedding go smoothly
Well, no
You can't do this
Richard will never forgive me. Don't forget about him
I'm the woman of Gavin's household now. Remember you can only ever be Richard's step sister