No, I don't know. I don't know. I went to get medicine and when I came back she was, you don't know
Samantha boss here has been really really good to you lately
You're the only one who's been with madam Helen. So what happened?
Hmm our
Initial judgment is that madam Helen was murdered
Cause of death was poison injected into her IV drip. Samantha. You are so cold-blooded
You know what I get it
You were afraid that if madam Helen regained her memory that she would ruin your relationship with Richard
You just finished her off
Is what she said fucking true, huh? Answer me
Richard you have to believe me. I did not do that
I don't believe fucking lies anymore, and I'm gonna make sure that you pay for fucking with my mother