Ethan, baby, your call was a lovely surprise. I missed you too.
Only only once. If you heard Stella again, you'll not like what happens next.
What are you talking about?
I saw you at the bakery. The shop manager confessed everything to me. There's no point in line.
Ethan, why are you talking to me like this? I'm your wife.
Ex-wife.
Ethan, please. This is all just a big misunderstanding. I didn't mean any of it, and Stella and you aren't meant to be together.
What about what we had? Do you remember that night three years ago at the Dean Hotel? Don't you love me?
The night was a mistake. And let me remind you, I saw the option to press criminal charges against you and your father.
No, please, don't do that. You and Stella aren't meant together. She's just a waitress. I'm so much more. We should have a life together.
Shut it. Stella's everything that you're not. She's kind, she's pure.
So just stay away from us or all the dude with you personally.
Just you wait, Ethan. Nothing comes from a dirty whore like Stella.