Actually, my father here is a modest company driver,
and my mother here is a very humble cleaner.
The company offers long-term benefits, meal plans,
but they struggle like the rest of us.
Oh, I see, so you all work together
for the Smith Company.
Wow, such loyalty.
Yes, very loyal indeed.
What's going on here?
Just play along, I'll tell you later.
Come, dear.
Have a seat.
Elise, make yourself at home.
This isn't right.
Oh, nonsense.
Does the leather feel nice on your skin?
I can make one phone call
and have the company shoot you the exact same one overnight.
Thank you so much,
but this really must be violating
some sort of company policy.
So really, we should all get out of here
before someone discovers us.
Because then you need to get your parents out of here
before they get fired.
Okay, what about you?
We can't just lean you here.
Why don't you come with us?
No, I have to deliver this to the CEO, personally.
Why don't we just see what's inside?
What are you doing?