Are you okay? Just breathe.
I'm so sorry, Ethan. I'm meant to hit him up.
I told you time and time and again not hurt Stella. You don't listen.
Please, you're choking me. Stella, Stella.
You can stop us not worth it.
Get out of here. I don't want to see you again.
Is that what Darcy says you have a remote enclosure?
You need to rest. Please don't do it stupid like that again.
The thought of losing you, I can't live without you. I love you.
You love me?
I know why marriage was really fast, but...
I think I've fallen in love with you.
I love you too.
For all I...
Did we pay the electric bill?
Nothing's more important than this right now.
You're out wide though. We Stella, Stella, Stella. I'm everything she's not.
I'm prettier. I'm taller. I'm smarter.
You're useless.
Dad, how can you say that?
It's your financial decisions that are getting us into debt, and now I'm an accessory to fraud and embezzlement.
As if you didn't enjoy spitting our money, it's too late now.
The Smith Group is going to come out as just everything they got. We're done for. Unless we got quick.
I can't get Ethan back, but what if Stella leaves Ethan?
That's the stupidest idea I've ever heard. Who in the right mind would leave a billionaire?
That's preposterous, childish, idiotic!
Naive? And who's Naive?
Time we show Stella who her husband really is.
I'm hanging up now.
I found him. The guy from the end.
Who?
The company's annual gal is in three days, and Stella is to accompany me.
But here's my dilemma. She has no idea who I am.
And I fear what may happen if she finds out.
But this charades.
She's a smart girl, and she's going to find out soon enough.
So don't let it get to that.
Ethan, my Ethan, a humble security guard is the CEO of this Smith company.
What are you scheming? Smells like bullshit.
Here, take a look at this.
Look familiar? Oh, what humble beginnings?
I bet you're his new plaything. Just wait till he gets tired of you like he got tired of me.
It's none of your business. You don't know anything about my husband.
What if I told you he already tossed you aside three years ago?
Put the pieces together, Stella.
That man who ruined your life? Who spread all those rumors about you?
No. No, that's not possible.
He wasn't at the hotel. His name wasn't on the list.
Do you really think a CEO would put his name on the list?
No. He has an assistant for that.
You know John.
John Will. Ethan's assistant.
Hey, I need you to cross-reference my name for me from three years ago.
John Will.
Okay, one sec. I'm checking.
Yeah.
Well, they require photo ideas at check-in right now.
Ethan Smith. Stella.
This is Tim.
No one can.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me. I'm sorry.
Please forgive me. I love sincerity.
Come on, man.
The light of my life. The spark that gives me purpose.
The world would be nothing without you in it.
From the bottom of my heart, I apologize.
Please forgive me.
Say you admit it.
What are you? What are you crying?
I know everything.
Shit, I'm sorry. I was going to tell you.
What else is a lie?
This rented house.
Your feelings? Your fake identity?
And your family? You brought your family in on all of your lives?
Do you think I'm that gullible?
No, I'm sorry. It's just my first marriage failed, so I just assumed you were...
Oh, God.
I can understand that.
Really?
Ruined your life?
I want a divorce.
What?
Let it out. You're defoisting my tears.
For who? For a liar who ruined my life?
The nerve of this man.
Playing with your feelings like this?
If I had known that I was him, then none of this would have ever happened.
And no one just hurts.
Bonjour!
Ever dream of being a world famous pastry chef?
Study in putty.
Find yourself.
Shake your future.
Call now.
Ruined your life?
Did I hurt you that much?
Pearl, I'm...
Mrs. Smith.
I mean, Stella just closed down the bakery.
Apparently she's going to France to study, and she signed us right before leaving.
There's something else.
We recovered the rest of the footage from that night.
How it plays out is you heavily inebriated.
Go into Stella's room.
Ruby then enters the next morning, right before you wake up.
So Stella's the one that hooked up with that night?
There's more.
The video shows Ruby bribing the staff to spread false information about Stella's promiscuity.
That's why she thinks you're behind it.
So that's why she said her...
I only left Ethan.
To miracles.
To miracles?
These are back on track with what he'd never do.
Don't mess it up.
Not in a million years.
Ethan!
For three years, you've been posing as Stella and even duped me into a marriage.
That's not even the worst of it.
You fabricated lies, smeared her reputation, gutted her life and left her with nothing.
Not anymore.
It's clear now, and on camera, courts are going to love you.
Ethan, we got off on the wrong foot.
Stella or Ruby, either way you see.
I'm still your father-in-law, you're still my son-in-law.
Stella made back to different, so do I.
He felt a realizeness or four that cutting ties with your daughter means that you and I are no longer related.
And a few hours, all four assets will cease to exist.
Every last fucking one of them.
You'll have nothing.
No.
I know I lied to you, but I still love you.
You make me sick.
And a few minutes the authorities will be here.
Do it freedom you have left.
Three years ago, I impersonated my step-sister, Stella Ford, and concocted a one-night stand with the Smith Group CEO, Ethan Smith.
I continued to slander her name and reputation through fake social media accounts, fictitious videos and testimonies.
Doing so led to her immediate exit from educational institutions and future job opportunities.
I sincerely apologize and seek forgiveness from all associated parties.
I was wrong about Ethan.
Go to grandma.
Come home ASAP.
I got a big surprise for you.
It's not good to go to bed without a bite to eat, bro.
I like dreaming.
You know.
Why?
What do you think?
How did you get in?
Wait, you're my big surprise.
I made your favorite.
I even cut it too.
Don't think that cooking me a steak will make me forgive you.
You still lied to me, Mr. CEO.
I know what to do is wrong.
I've been beating myself up about it ever since.
I told that lie from the first place.
If I can go back to the beginning, I would.
I'm not asking for forgiveness.
I'm just asking for a second chance to earn a trust.
I take it back.
Maybe cooking me a steak every day for the rest of my life will make me forgive you.
Anything from my parole.
You know what make this steak taste even better?
Sharing it with you.
Is that so?
Taste your flavor.
Taste your lips.
I'll be the judge of that.
Please, I misjudged you.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too, girl.
I'm not okay.
It looks, please.
Everyone, enjoy yourselves. Everything is half off.
Thank you so much for helping me with all these renovations.
I did some stuff here and there, but it was your money that did the work.
Congratulations, parole. I'm so proud of you.
It's adorable.
You know, I can start saving for an ex-expansion.
I actually have a gift for you, too.
Oh, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Wait, you?
I could have never imagined this moment.
My life being so complete, so loved that a future could be possible.