I say that's the Clark family business from you, you, you, you've just disgusting, spoiled,
infected, rat, didn't even bother.
They tell me before the wedding, I, they, they, they, no, people, how many more excuses can you make?
Ricky, did you ever love me?
What, how insulting?
How could I love someone who is such a nightmare every day of my life?
How could I love someone who can make me sick?
You're at the end and all you care about is frecky love too.
What you should really be worrying about is how a drug-free virgin like you ended up like
since you're dying, I figured I'd let you in on a little sick. Someone was hired to inject you
with this disease. It's a price you didn't figure it out for yourself or jump off of a
building to save the world when you're disgrace.
Do that, Ricky.
It was Ricky. The love of your wife didn't believe you. 20 bucks to a drugie, he's free,
and you're the dirty slut. He'd be even treatment? Well, that was my act. I wanted to watch you soon.
And he'd get to see past you.