This is college? How can this be? I've been reborn ten years ago.
I thought it would be great to meet her.
I would be good.
I told you to buy lunch for Karen. Not some trash that you and your people leave. Something edible.
Ricky tracks, in my previous life I gave you everything only for you to betray and murder me.
This time, it'll be different.
Are you deaf? Go! Now!
Ricky, it's just best if I go myself.
Don't even go.
She feels more value, serving people like me and you as compared to her people that she calls for family.
Am I right? Ken?
Let this meal start my revenge.
Fetching lunch for your master again?
With brilliant girls like Karen around?
Ricky won't waste a glance on your kind.
You know that, right?
Yeah, and what is my kind?
The, you're the daughter of his maid?
Kind?
That follows him to school every, the wishes.
She can marry a rich kind.
The, if you're lucky, you can make his bed, sweep his floor and scrub his toilet kind.
You know, you're kind.
Then Ricky tracks, tell you that?
Did he tell you that his maid back?
Is my family car? And that he is the son of...
My driver?
What a psycho!
Barking like a chihuahua just because Ricky won't look at you?
Hurry up.
Your master's lunch is getting cold.
The driver's son is saying I'm his maid.
Ricky tracks, you're gonna pay for that.