I told you to buy a lunch for Karen and you ate it, mine too?
God, you are just such a... Hey, aren't you?
I spent this with my own money.
Two meals or twenty meals.
What's it to do with you?
Your money?
Even if you spend it, it still tracks as money.
Duh.
Oh, is that so?
It was money, isn't it?
I think getting lunch when you're told to, from your boss, is a
simple task.
And you came with me with something so simple, that you just got to be fucking stupid.
You want to use my boss first?
A completely fabled Bonnie Woman too lazy to get her lunch?
I think she deserves the tummy ache.
You?
You are a tracks family maid.
Taking care of his girlfriend is literally your job.
How?
Is that so hard to comprehend?
Tricky tracks.
Am I your maid?
All right, Chad.
I don't know what game you're playing, but I'm not doing it.
Don't cause any trouble, otherwise I will not forgive you no matter how hard you'd
die.
Daddy?
Oh, why would I?
What did I do?
You think you're so tough, don't you?
It's crazy how quickly you just lost a seat in the car.
I could care less if you welcome.
Your car?
It was never yours, and it's time you learned your place.