After insulting Riki and Karen, she still has a nerve to keep freeloading rides.
Unbelievable.
A maid's daughter acting like a princess.
Riki is too quiet.
If it was me, I would have kicked around already.
Drive.
Let's, uh, wait for Riki.
Mr. Trax, uh, you work for my father and me.
I think I can safely wait on him.
Do you guys have a fight or something?
Look, I'll have a word with him for sure.
But could you try to be a little nicer to him?
I mean, I know you like to look down on him.
Mr. Trax, can you just drive?
I don't want him in my car. I don't want him at my house.
I just, I don't want to see him anymore.
Well, let's just, let's just be.
Drive or not?
She's usually so scared of Riki.
What's going on today?
Did you forget on her future father-in-law?
Or the fact my son will take over her father's business?
Mr. Trax, I asked politely.
Look, they're coming right now.