Even Ricky's driver respects the maid's daughter?
It does not make any sense.
Why is Ricky getting out?
Shannon, was it really necessary for you to bother your father like that?
I mean, he's a very busy man.
Oh, from now on, those two are not allowed in this car.
That's a little childish, Shannon?
Thank you.
Not that close to you's my name.
Remember who pays you?
Plus, I think a driver being asked to drive is a simple task.
If you can't handle it, feel free to quit.
You're right. I was wrong.
I am driving right now.
Shannon, that's enough.
It looks like the young master is mad.
Shannon, I get it if you don't like me, but you don't have to be a bully to Ricky.
He's always been so nice to you.
You even have the driver come back just for you.
You don't have to be so mean.
You know what? You don't even have to explain yourself to her.
She has never learned a single thing of gratitude in her entire life.
And you just continue to keep crossing the line every time.