Yesi, I expect you to be respectful and shut your mouth.
Shannon has moved up 253 places. That is amazing.
What? 200 places? A professor found us in a mistake because
your grades are so poor, there's no way she could have...
I made no mistake. Shannon, you have done a great job. Keep up the good work.
Thanks professor.
What was?
Did you forget about a little black?
You got lucky this time.
So what?
Luck or no luck, you lost the bet.
So you better start running and then kneel down and beg.
Unless you want to beg now.
Shannon, I'm acting all high and mighty.
Moving up 200 places is not that impressive.
Ricky is right first and Karen the second.
You don't see them acting all high and mighty.
Girl, why are you even yapping?
Ricky placed a bet that I couldn't move up 100 places.
And guess what? I moved up 200.
So it's time to pay up Ricky tracks.
Karen's a lap dog and you dream of Nancy's heart.