You're being unreasonable, the teacher told you to retake the exam, so stop arguing.
This retake is a chance to clear your name.
You don't want people doubting you behind your back, do you?
Professor, I'm sorry.
The reasoning behind this is absolutely absurd, but for you, I will retake the exam.
Shannon, it's no big deal.
There's no need to feel guilty.
Who says to feel guilty?
Still making excuses.
Stomach?
Yes, you shut up.
You're always trying to find something to bitch about because you're so boring for Karen's approval.
Professor, since she accused me without any evidence, should there be consequences?
What did you say?
Professor, Yancy has accused me of cheating without any proof and that has targeted me repeatedly
for weeks.
If I retake the exam and prove that I didn't cheat, I think she should drop out.
You want her to drop out?
Seriously?
How could she be like this?