You want her to drop out?
Professor, she made a stupid rumor about me cheating.
Even if I prove my innocence, I will always be known as the girl who was accused of cheating.
Wouldn't that ruin my reputation?
What if I can't handle the pressure and I do something drastic, like, kill myself?
Suicide? What should we do then? Maybe she is letting go.
Alright, alright, Shannon, we get it.
Yeah, and see, didn't she insist I cheated?
Or, are you scared of your own words?
I'm not afraid. Fine, but if I'm right then you have to drop out because I'm not going to be the same.
Do!
Professor, can I take the exam?
And can you make sure Ricky keeps his word as well?
Do you really want to do this right now?
I mean, when they do catch you, they will kick you out of school.
Just confess I'll help give you a kiss to the boy.
Okay?
We'll do better a little bit.
I won't make you up.
Thanks, Ricky.
But you will have to know that I'm ready for getting this.
Whatever.
When I pass this test, it'll be your dignity on the line.
So you better start warming up those calves, not just for running but for kneeling as well.
Thank you.