Shannon, I'm giving you one last chance to come clean.
Karen, this is your final warning.
Back up or don't come to playing when your face hurts more than Nancy's.
As I've said before, this test is much harder than the previous exam,
and I'm happy to say that Shannon scored higher than before.
So it is clear that she did not cheat.
Who is this possible? How could you not have cheated?
Professor, you must have miscalculated the scores.
We're getting back!
Shannon, you had made incredible progress, and I am very impressed.
What have you done to continue this progress?
It's quite simple, Professor.
I had a bad tutor, and we have a good one.
It feels really good doing, Will.
Well, this incident right here proves how toxic this classroom environment is.
And I will do everything in my tower to make sure that Shannon's name is clear
and that anybody that falsely accused Shannon of cheating shall be punished as well.
Nancy, you said if I don't cheat, you will drop out.
So are you gonna stick to your word?