Please, whatever it takes.
Oh, since you're someone who spread false accusations and doesn't want to drop out,
you can run 20 miles around the track.
But now you're running.
I want you to chant, I'm falsely accused, Shannon.
Shannon didn't cheat.
Okay.
She passed on the exam.
There is no need to do this, I thought.
Ricky tracks thinks it's time to lecture me.
Why don't you kneel down and beg until I forgive you?
Thank you.
Ricky!
Take me!
Yeah!
It said you'd kneel.
I'm just helping.
Now beg.
Shannon, perhaps you shouldn't ruin friendship over a text.
Oh, Professor, these people aren't my friends.
If they don't keep their word, I'll never let it go and I'll drive them out of school.
Oh no.
It's 10 miles.
I'll run 10, also, 20.