That's my mum. She was quite the beauty, wasn't she?
So you've got her eyes?
I'm sure you've, er, heard the story of my parents' death.
Heard some rumours.
I don't really believe them.
Who keeps the photo of someone they'd hung right by their bed?
What? Me smiles.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
I'm sorry.
Get out.
Get out, get out, leave me alone.
The last night, he loved the bosses from at like 3am.
I told you, the boss keeps on his shoulder leave.
The bitch.
Don't worry.
You son of a bitch!
Fucking cunt!
Shut your fucking mouth!
I don't touch human trafficking.
Robert, who the fuck would do something so disgusting?
There's all money at the end of the day, innit?
I don't need to feel like that in my life.
Look at the fuck out.
You fucking prick!
Does it need me to call a doctor?
No.
Nothing serious.
Robert's words upset you.
Why?
I'm here to protect you.
It's my job.
But I hope it protects you.
From me.