Should I keep going?
Smile.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, just texting Jack.
See, I'm sending Jack a fake address in your name.
I'm telling him where he can find his work.
No, don't do that!
I just had a brilliant idea.
Why don't you send the message yourself?
Don't do that to me.
Would you sleep with me?
You're getting jealous of Jack now.
When I set this trap together,
I want to make it that easy for you, you snitch.
So, so long.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, don't be hasty.
Much better.
Now, I hear the generous.
Blackjack is...
It's gifting me by an end casino, right?
Fuck you, Ace.
You fucking psycho.
How dare you?
You have ten seconds.
Oh, wait, that's your line, isn't it?
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Three.
Two.
Deal.
Good.
Is that in the contract?
You're even more of a cunt than I thought.
Thanks for the compliment.
Everything's perfect now.
Oh!
By the way, I got you a gift!
That's Jack, gentlemen.