I got you a gift, ha ha!
How about I have some jackets, isn't it?
Sorry.
In useless fucking bastard!
Stop, stop!
Well, I leave for 10 seconds, and this hot guy is crying.
Mmm! Oh, Jack, I've changed my mind.
That fuck is wrong with you, twisted psycho.
Psychos?
My dear sir, we don't need a reason.
I keep it useless, dog.
It's a new verse, sir.
Shite, huh?
It's fine.
I thought you were a lot tougher than that.
It's all right.
All right, all right, stop crying.
You're safe now.
Didn't ask me to save me.
Jack has completely abandoned you.
You are no value to him anymore.
I won't betray him, but even if I die.
Stand up, come and see your potential.
I owe him.
The kindness he once showed me.
That means a lot to me.
Your life, the drawers anymore.
See, I just saved you.
Remember?
So your life belongs to me now.
And I'll repay you too.
Just take it if that's what you want.
Dying is too easy.
I have something else in life.
Your face took quite a hit too.
We can't have that.
Stay still.
Why did you save me?
Take a guess.