I'm sorry, Mum.
I'll go now.
You should rest.
Alex?
Is that you?
Where is this place?
Where are we?
It's okay.
That's me.
It's me.
You're safe here.
Don't worry.
One minute to convince me not to.
I won't tell anyone.
How can I trust you?
You trust me this time?
Don't leave me.
I'm here now.
You're so good.
Let me go.
Leaving tomorrow?
Ace has arranged everything.
You're safe now.
I'm one of Ace's closest friends.
I came here specifically.
It's important you get your rest though.
To save your strength for the journey tomorrow.
I'll be here.
To protect both of us.
You promise?
What about my Alex?
It's still just a gift.
Alex is coming with us.
We're all going to start a new and good life together.
And let's get back into bed.