That's what happened to you, Mum.
I was only 15.
Where do you think you're going, darling?
I'm very pleased.
I'm making you.
Oh, Dao, what's going on, Alex?
Come in.
This bitch is just about all badness.
Don't you go near him!
Alex, go back to your room!
You know what happens to traitors, right?
I want you to tell them.
Are you going to betray me as well, Alex?
I took over the business from my father and moved my mother here to fit safety,
but she was never the same.
You see, the trauma just never left her.
People love to gossip about me, but only I know the truth.
And now you.
I blame you as well.
You feel your bleeding, Cher?
Yes, I know.
So what's your story?
My dad, he was a violent drug.
And after his neck and dad's.
Every time he came home drunk, he would beat me and my mum.
He even forced her to sell herself to pay his debts.
Once he almost killed me, my mum tried to stop him.
And he, you know.
So she grabbed me and we ran.
No, I'm sorry.
Oh, my dear.
Don't fall asleep.
I love you, Max.
I live a good life.
No.
Don't fall asleep.
She, she pissed her.
Jack, I am.
I met him that time.