It's up with the leg boss.
Get the boys together.
We're pretty nice to visit tonight.
Sorry, Ace.
On time, Ace.
Nonetheless, you promise not to hurt yourself again.
Why do you even bother?
You know, Ace, even if a guy loses his strength,
you can always tie on a new one.
Stop talking.
Just leave.
Isn't that what you've always wanted to leave?
It's not that simple.
Jack isn't just gonna back off.
Let me stay.
All right.
I wanna help.
My mum did die for me again.
Fuck off.
I'm not going anywhere.
No matter what you say to push me away,
I'm not leaving you alone.
Don't need your pity.
It's not pity.
I like you.
What did you just say?
Ever since you saved me from tracks?
Maybe even before that.
You're not as messed up as you think.
Maybe you are, but to me you're incredible.
I think about you all the time.
Dream about you.
I mean, these are my shit here.
Look at me.
Look at my eyes.
Say it again.
Don't push me away, Ace.
I gave you the chance to leave.
And you chose to stay.