Get up.
Max, you want to be trying me for this fuck.
We always loyal before that,
so I'll offer you a way out.
Kill Ace,
and I was forgiven.
I'm willing to overlook this.
Tram's crush.
Otherwise,
they both die.
Together.
Life for life.
Take mine and let him go.
Life alone isn't enough.
Do it now.
I don't want to wait.
Kill him.
You turn to being my beating kid, you want to wait.
You're nothing my body got full of lies to me.
We mean nothing to each other.
Oh, Max, don't be a cunt.
Shoot me and return to your real fucking master.
I could drown in rats.
Would be a delight.
This is rigged to blow.
I die within Max.
You can't save it.
My boys have the place around it.
Ha, ha, ha.
Shoot it!