Stop worrying, baby.
Everything's going to be fine.
What if our plan doesn't work?
What if Marco escapes?
Let's stop worrying about Marco.
Have you thought about tonight?
Do you know what dress you're going to wear for our date?
Why is there something special about tonight?
No.
No, no.
Yeah, I just thought maybe it would help you take your mind off things.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
I should just focus on our date.
Miguel.
Where's Dominic?
Why isn't he here yet?
Uh, no, the boss is running late.
He just had some things he had to take care of.
Have you noticed how empty the place is?
We're the only ones here.
Something's off, maybe we should go.
No, Madam.
Would you like to try tonight's special?