This deal is to have priority. I'll oversee it myself.
Sir...
Here's your home cart, and a glass of black paint.
Why isn't the bathroom cleaning up the cuz it's going to be here soon?
You know there's only one person per floor. It's impossible to keep everything in charge.
Okay, well I will see to it that we get more staff on board in the future.
That's why, seriously, you need to let it go.
I know you haven't been back here long, but it's impossible to beat Dolores.
Dolores has been sleeping for ages.
First she ships me off to boarding school, and then she's trying to take the hotel right out from under me.
Don't worry mom, I will get the hotel back.
No matter what it takes.
All right.
You're really beautiful.
Let's get you back too.