Mom, plan fail.
What? Henry slept with some slut.
What are you talking about?
You. You're always screwing around.
You never take anything seriously.
What kind of airhead did I raise?
Mom, I haven't even told you the best part.
That clueless slut got scared after sleeping with Henry.
You thought it was me?
Look. Oh my God, a black car?
Yes, it's limited edition.
Henry gave it to me.
Good job. You are my daughter.
Mom, don't underestimate me.
I know exactly what kind of women men want.
All it took was an act of innocence and he believed me.
He even said he'd compensate me.
Excellent.
But who is it that he slept with?
Huh. Don't worry, Mom.
I'll take care of that little slut.
It doesn't matter.
As long as you stay with him and bear his child,
then what would this lousy hotel be worth?
You'll be the envy of everyone.
Oh, don't you worry, Mom.
The title of Mrs. Wilson will be mine.
I'm gonna head upstairs.
I'm exhausted.
Go ahead. You earned it.
Elizabeth, you just watch from your coffin
how I kick your daughter out.
Let me see who this bitch really is.