That bitch never endures your phone.
Well, she probably won't show up again.
Still trying to save the hotel?
It's none of your business.
Well, I'm just worried about you.
I mean, you've seen the financial situation of the hotel.
Bankruptcy is just a matter of time.
I won't ever let the hotel go bankrupt, Emily.
Oh, really?
It's just a matter of time before the hotel will change its name.
I wonder what my mom will rename it to.
You know what? You just keep trying your best.
I cannot wait to see you get kicked out of here.
Mm-hmm.
Looks like we'll have to secure partnership with the Wilson group after all.
Long time, let's see.
What are you doing here?
You clean up nice.
It smells familiar?
Hey, what are you doing at the Wilson group?
Did you see you ascend you here?
God!
Sending an escort this early in the morning.
You must have, like, a thing for male escorts or something.
Maybe, like, a fetish.
Escorts?
A fetish?
Yeah.
Is this how you plan on getting my attention off?
What?
What is it with escorts these days, God?
Do they not recognize a client?
The one who's got her.
Ooh.
Wait.
Is that the CEO, Mr. Wilson?
Yes, of course. What do you mean?