Mr. Wilson, who is that woman?
The hotel surveillance system has been reported as malfunctioning,
but I got information on Emily White.
Her mother is the current vice of light up a hotel.
Her background seems quite ordinary.
Keep digging.
Hi.
Do I have an appointment today with Mr. Wilson?
Thank you, see, we'll call you on his run.
Thanks.
Was the escort really, Mr. Wilson?
God, did I really ask the CEO of the Wilson group
for his smart donation?
Henry, take a look at what you've done.
We have a press conference in three days,
and now all of a sudden we're without a venue.
You've only been a CEO for a short time,
and now it's just become a complete mess.
Who are you to boss me around?
I'm the CEO of the company now.
Sorry to interrupt you.
Mr. Wilson, here is the arrangements
for the press conference venue.