Mr. Wilson, here is the arrangements for the press conference venue.
Who are you?
Hi, I'm Sarah White. I am the manager at White Hotel.
I heard you two talking about the venue and came in to see how I could help.
Mr. Wilson, the arrangements for the venue are here.
You can check it out and see if anything needs changing.
Remember, you're just a manager here, so do your job.
I'm not as easy going as my grandfather.
If I hear that you've been talking to my grandfather,
this will not be the last time you hear from me.
Get up.
It's pretty clever of you.
Taking advantage like that.
Mr. Wilson, I'm so sorry. I didn't see her as a kid.
You get out of the room.
Mr. Wilson, I'm sorry I didn't mean to eavesdrop,
but it seemed like you urgently needed a venue,
and I can provide that venue, Mr. Wilson.
I promise you'll be very satisfied.
What are you doing?
Mr. Wilson, don't worry. I'll get her out of here.
Leave.
You heard him. Get out of here.
I meant you.
Me?
This woman, she...
I said leave.
Okay.
You're determined, but too much determination can be annoying.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wilson, but it is very important to me,
and I had to take that approach.
Have we met before?
Uh, sorry, I think I mistook you for a friend of mine earlier.
You have friends that are our sports?
Yeah, a lot of different friends, actually.
Let's go.
Go where?
Cafe downstairs.
Unless you'd like to talk business like old men.
Mr. Wilson just left with that woman.
I can't believe that.
That's the first time he left with a stranger.
What's so special about her?
She thinks she gets to do with him?
With her looks? What a joke.
There's no way he could go for someone like that.
She's gonna get dumped.
From what I can tell, the situation at the hotel is not good.
With your experience, I know you can go to greener pastures tomorrow.
Why stick around and potentially ruin your reputation?
I can't leave.
The white hotel is founded by my mother.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Wilson, I need to secure a partnership with your company for the sake of the hotel.
You can trust me, okay? I will give the Wilson Group the best possible deal,
and I will handle all of the activities.
You show me your determination.
And the proposal is very well written.
The tech launches in three days. Can you make it?
You can count on me to our first deal.
To our first deal?
Not that our business is squared away.
Let's talk about our personal matters.
Huh?
We've cross-passed before.
I noticed when you glanced at me, sometimes when you look at me in the eye,
there's a glimmer of concern. What's going on?
Mr. Wilson, about that day, I'm so sorry, I'm just really confused, I'm truly sorry.
Sis, what are you doing here?
You two? And raise my boyfriend.
Your boyfriend?
Henry's my boyfriend.
You two are sisters?
Yeah, sisters.
Now she's more like my dad's love child.
Oh, Henry, please don't take it to heart.
Sarah has been off at boarding school for years and has not graded socializing
or being diplomatic in her speech.
Mr. Wilson, I wish you and your girlfriend a lifetime of happiness,
yeah, no need to dwell on what happened in the past.
What are you two talking about?
I'm gonna leave, but don't worry.
I will handle the press conference venue, okay?
How did you say you're my girlfriend?
Aren't we an item now?
Look, I'm sorry about what happened. Now make it right.
I can't make you my girlfriend.
You promised to take care of me.
Can't you imagine how thrilled I am? That someone won't leave me?
Listen, I thought that my behavior towards you in the past month would make things pretty clear.
What about you, Spill? Do you get off on this charade you're putting up?
I just, I didn't want you to dunk me, okay? That's why I acted like that.
Please, don't leave me Henry. Give me three months and if you don't like me by then,
I won't bother you anymore.
Fine by me. I'll give you anything you want. I don't know if I can love you.
Excuse me, can you please contact Waitstaff and tell them to deliver fresh flowers tomorrow?
Hold it, hold it, stop. You, come with me.
Jones, what are you doing?
Sarah, we need manpower elsewhere. Dolores said we don't take on collaboration.
It's your problem now that you took on the collaboration with Mr. Wilson.
Um, Jones, you've been working here for a decade, but deciding what to lose now?
Sides, who cares about sides? All I know is the hotel's gonna be rebranded in a few months.
Sarah, if you ever need help, come find me. I'll be sure to lend you a hand for all times sake, okay?
Let's go. Sarah, what the hell? You think you could compete with the Wilson Partnership?
Emily's the future Mrs. Wilson. You think you could compete with her? Let's go.
Mom, you won't lose, okay?
We're here.
Okay, thanks. Yes, please just have the flowers delivered to the White Family Gate Hotel tomorrow.
Okay, yeah.
You've been pastoring me all day.
Miss White, you're back so late. You've been set for a bit.
Can that bitch be you?
Careful. Careful.
What are you doing here?
This conference is kind of a big deal for the Wilson group, so you're gonna combine and check it out.
You hear along?
Mr. Wilson.
Hey, Sarah, manage to handle it all by yourself, huh?
Oh!
Too bad even if you do.
The hotel will have a new owner soon anyway.
Mr. Wilson, what are you doing here?
I wouldn't want to miss the drama here, would I?
Misunderstanding, misunderstanding.
Pick it up and get out.
Yes, sorry.
Mr. Wilson, I'm really sorry you had to see that.
I've seen a lot of the sort of things since I took over.
Just snapping pics of your purse, huh?
Meanwhile, Mr. Wilson's cozin' up with Sarah in the banquet hall.
What? What did you just say?
What did you just say?
I saw it in my own eyes.
They're getting all cozy in the banquet hall.
Not here.
They'll be trouble if anyone sees us.
The hotel is already a done deal.
I don't care why you're trying to bother and cozy up to Henry on top of all that.
You don't understand.
This rundown please hesitating over a decade ago.
It's nothing compared to the Wilson group.
Fine. Suit yourself.
But don't come crying to me when Sarah steals the prize from under your nose.
She really do that conniving?
No.
I won't let her have Henry.
Quite impressive.
I didn't anticipate you managed the entire banquet hall by yourself.
Well, Mr. Wilson, I have to thank you for all your help.
Cheers to successful conference care.
Thank you for the good wishes.
Can that bitch be you?
Hello?
Hello, Miss speaking.
Something wrong?
No, just a wrong number.
Mr. Wilson, I can promise you you wholeheartedly have my support tomorrow.
I think you'll do well.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Mom, something's not right.
Sarah was the woman who suffered Henry.
What?
I tried calling a phone that was left and it was her.
You know, if you weren't fooling around with that Jones loser, this wouldn't happen.
I know.
But what do we do now?
If Sarah wins over Henry, we'll have nothing.
No rush.
If Sarah hasn't told Henry, she doesn't plan on telling Henry.
Make sure you stay as close to him as you can.
Sarah has never liked us.
Turn her into a home wrecker if she dares to reveal this.
Knowing Sarah, she'll keep this to herself.
Mom, you're so smart.
Remember, John.
When we want something, we get it.
Henry warned everyone not to do business with one screw group.
He still managed to secure a venue.
Is there something I can help you with?
Just got some water for the host?
Oh, I could do that for you.
Yeah.
Henry, anyone still blame it yourself?
I always a lead candidate for that position.
You chose to loop me all over me.
That's going to lead you back off.
Mr. Wilson, looking forward to our future collaboration.
And rest assured, I'll ensure the best for the Wilson group.
I've seen your capabilities.
I trust you won't disappoint me.
Mr. Are you involved with Henry?
Uh, you're mistaken. We were just discussing work.
Well, that's good after all.
Henry is my boyfriend.
When am I your boyfriend?
Mr. Henry, something's happened.
What happened?
I don't know.
He said he had bad stomach pain and needed to use the restroom.
And then halfway there, he collapsed and started foaming at the mouth.
Okay, did you call 911?
I already did.
Does anyone else smell bleach?
Leach, I just gave him a glass of water.
How could it be bleach?
Oh, my God.
What is happening here?
Mr. Wilson, we literally have to conference in 10 minutes.
What are we going to do about this whole situation?
Jess, I don't know.
They're saying the host drank bleach, but I just gave him water.
The host will struggle enough this.
Enough.
Get in with the hospital.
Make sure he's okay immediately.
Jason, check her to the lounge.
Mr. Wilson, let me handle this.
Okay, this is obviously due to the hotel's negligence.
You?
Mr. Wilson, please.
Okay, I studied this in hotel management.
All right.
I'll leave you to it, okay?
Mr. Wilson, I heard something happening to the host of the event.
You just taken over the range of Wilson Group,
and you're already messing up the most important press conference.
You might be facing it peacefully by the board.
How'd you hear about the host?
I just already know.
You should be worrying about how to handle this.
Oh, I'm prepared.
On to today's press conference.
It is my honor to introduce the theme for today's event.
Henry, where did you find this beautiful host?
This host is amazing.
She's beautiful and well-spoken.
She represents Wilson Group well.
Yeah, she's impressive.
I didn't think Wilson Group was going to reach new heights under Henry's rule.
Hopefully that means my money for us, right?
Yes.
The Wilson Group will continue to thrive in renewable energy.
Thank you, everyone.
You look stunning.
You do it, Mom.
Let's do this on over here.
Send out the pictures I gave to you.
Max, where are you off to?
Henry, I have submerged your matter at home immediately now.
Hold tight.
Police want to ask you a couple questions.
What police?
You can't accuse me.
The host being poisoned had nothing to do with me.
I didn't say anything about poison.
Yeah, kind of sound like you just confessed right there.
Henry, it's best you let me go.
This won't be good for you if this escalates.
Max, you mixed bleach with water.
Did you not think anyone would get hurt?
What on earth are you talking about?
Bleach?
Oh, I get it.
You're trying to turn this on around me so you could secure Wilson Group.
You think you're going to get away with this?
I don't know what you're talking about, but I got to go home.
Oh, not so fast.
You were saying something about no evidence?
The glass is still bare, Max.
Why not have the police inspected?
You're despicable.
These are responsible for the bleach.
You okay?
Yeah.
Henry, our photos have been leaked.
What are we going to do?
The reporters will be here any minute.
You played your role perfectly.
You don't think I know who leaked the photos?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stay away from me.
I don't want to see you again.
What are you thinking?
You don't belong with Henry.
I didn't edit tonight.
I should go to the hospital tomorrow.
Man, you're over a month.
I'm going to go to the hospital tomorrow.
I should go to the hospital tomorrow.
Man, you're over a month pregnant.
You know, during the early stages of pregnancy,
you shouldn't engage in any vigorous activities.
Nint, pregnant.
Sarah?
Dylan?
Oh, my God.
It's been a while.
Oh, wait.
Why don't you tell me you were back in the country?
No, I just got back and just haven't had the chance to find you.
What?
What is this?
Well, I'm going to attend a physician at this hospital now.
Wow.
Are you okay?
Why are you at the get a college department?
I'm fine.
It was just a checkup.
What are you doing tonight?
Can I treat you to dinner?
Sure.
I would love that.
Great.
Mr. Wilson, the online news and photos have been taken down.
Also, the venue fee for the White Hotel has not been paid yet.
Sarah has not come to sign.
She's not even proactive about collecting money.
The fee can wait.
I'll sign it myself.
Okay.
What's there?
Come find me.
Do you remember when we were kids and you used to just follow me around everywhere?
I know.
I remember.
This has just been your shadow, huh?
Yeah.
And now that shadow, it's just grown up so much.
Remember?
Okay.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
You really grew into a man who knows how to take care of a woman.
Mm.
Confidence.
Thank you.
Well, I had to finally grow up.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Still, you know, you've really been through a lot these past few years.
Haven't you?
Oh, yeah.
So have you.
I mean, I heard that from your mom passed away that your dad got married to your family's
maid.
Oh, remember when my parents and your mom were still around?
Mm-hmm.
And he once told them that you.
Yeah.
You wanted to be my bride.
Haha.
Well, yeah.
We were kids.
I mean, it was just, it was just okay.
Right?
Well, Sarah, listen.
I haven't forgotten.
Dylan, right now, my only priority is saving my mom's hotel.
Okay.
I am just, I'm not in the place for anything romantic or-
Don't worry.
I understand.
I'll wait.
I have to go.
Hey, let me walk with you.
No.
It's, it's no need.
Dylan, you really deserve someone who truly loves you.
Why are you, Sarah?
Hey, Sarah.
Hi, Anna.
I'm here to pick up the signatures from the bills for Mr. Wilson.
Mr. Wilson told me you can go straight in.
Thanks.
Hey, did you trip yourself?
Maybe you should go home and lie down, sweetie.
Who told Mr. Wilson?
Bitch!
Mr. Wilson, she hit me.
Sorry for hitting you, but some people deserve it.
Come in.
Mr. Wilson, you don't need to sign these papers yourself, do you?
You can just leave it to one of your employees.
What, are you just going to use me then and discard me?
No.
How could I?
No, I just don't want to get too close to you and upset your girlfriend.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Right, right, because the media exposed that the scandalous photos of the CEO Wilson were fake.
You jealous?
No.
Justin, we're going to need your access card back.
Right, what's happening?
It's a direct order for Mr. Wilson.
Mr. Wilson's not going to find me.
Yes, he would.
Now you're going to leave on your own, or do we need to take action?
Oh, look whose job just flew out the window.
You know, maybe you should go home and lie down.
Sarah, are you seeing Henry again?
What's this?
Sarah is pregnant?
That child must be Henry's.
Emily.
What are you up to?
You look like you just committed a crime.
Sarah, I'm warning you.
Stay away from Henry.
He's mine.
You know, last time I heard, Henry doesn't have a girlfriend.
Mom, Sarah's pregnant.
Sarah's pregnant?
Thinking letting those photos out.
Now we've lost all communication with Henry.
I was scared that Henry would find out Sarah was the girl who slept with him.
Oh.
Now that she's pregnant, the will isn't a fact.
Didn't you say that the mammoth group wants to partner with us?
Uh, yes, the CEO said he would.
And he likes women, and no one comes away unscathed.
Mom, you're not suggesting that.
I'm going to talk to Jones and have him sign up a meeting with the mammoth group.
Sarah is pregnant, but she'll lose the baby.
And if there's photos to prove it, all the better.
The mammoth group is a major client of our hotel.
You have to secure a partnership with them today.
Okay, I didn't know the mammoth group was a client of ours.
How would you know?
You're just a junior manager.
So naturally, you're not really aware of everything.
If you don't go, it's the hotel that will suck.
Not me.
You're doing a great job like Big Strong Manager, man.
Of course.
How else do you think I became a manager of this place?
Sarah.
What's she doing here?
We're the rooms in the back door.
The room's for private parties.
Two meets and clients needs, you know.
Some people just can't resist getting it on.
Really?
This woman is mine to play with all night.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Great.
You guys know exactly what I want.
I'm Sarah White.
I'm the manager at the White Hotel.
Good.
Have a seat.
It's like a drink?
No, actually, I can't.
I'm pregnant.
Pregnant?
That's great.
I've never been with a pregnant woman.
Oh, my God!
What the fuck?
The real one where I was just about to do.
I can't explain.
She asked for it.
Ask for it.
You're a tall, ugly freak.
I would never ask for you.
You're ugly and your family's ugly.
Henry, I can't explain.
I wouldn't have for doing anything that she didn't want.
I received a phone call personally from the manager.
The hotel manager called me and told me that she was going to accompany me for the night.
What manager?
Was it Jones?
Go me!
Yes!
Get out.
Great.
I'll leave.
Do you know how foolish it was coming here alone?
It's not your business.
Do you know what would happen if I didn't show up?
Why are you playing these games?
I'm not.
I can't.
I'm pregnant.