It's hot. I can't. I'm pregnant.
Pregnant? Who is...
I was never using you or anything.
It's not safe here.
I have to go handle something on my own. I'm sorry.
I never thought she would play me.
Mm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm.
Piece of job?
Mm-hmm!
Ms. White, what are you doing here?
Excuse me. Can you please stop damaging company property?
It's this machine that's broken.
Really? Maybe you should check your email.
Email?
Dismiss or notice?
How dare you have the right to dismiss me?
Well, I am also one of the company directors,
but it seems like you might be in bigger trouble.
Jones! You have a lot of nerve. How dare you scheme against me?