Well, what should I do?
How did I raise such a stupid daughter?
It's no wonder why you always lose to Sarah.
Jones has arranged the drug.
He's also taking the photos.
So our hands are clean.
So do you want us to pin everything on Jones?
I mean, what if he does something about it?
Let him come back first.
If not, then we go directly after him.
You know, I used to think that if Sarah could fly,
she couldn't save the hotel,
I have severely underestimated her.
And as for Sarah, I'll let her father handle her.
Because a father-daughter conflict in the White family,
she proved to be very interesting.
Sarah?
Dylan, what are you doing here?
What is this?
Well, I remember how much you used to love Rose as so.
Hey, but you know my situation now.
I know, I know.
It's not what you think it is.
This is just a token of appreciation for a good old friend.
Your boyfriend, I presume.