So who's a person just now?
It's just this business partner at our hotel.
Yeah, she's okay.
Henry, why are we at this restaurant?
We only have one table.
Would you mind sharing it with these couples?
This couple?
Sarah, should we meet?
No, let's say, let's eat.
So, you're the youngest of the master family, right?
And you grew up Sarah, what a shame.
You know, remember when your family went bankrupt?
Never thought I'd see you again.
Good memory of yours.
Well, then, you must also remember when you were just as simply
me as daughter.
You call me Sarah your sister.
We have dasities commendable.
Emily?
Don't blame me if I slap you later.
Sit.
Henry!
Oof, you better take care of your companion tonight.
You might want to put Alicia on her so she doesn't bite.
Oh, she can't.
She's pregnant.