What are you doing?
I... I really like you.
When the first moment I saw you, I fell in love.
Can you please hold me the way you did that one day?
Just one more time?
Mommy!
Why won't you accept me?
You are the first man I've ever slept with and you will not take that responsibility!
I told you I would!
Really?
How will you take responsibility?
Do you even like Sarah?
She's already pregnant.
Do you want her to cuckold you?
But I don't care about Sarah.
I told you that, alright?
And don't involve me in your hotel drama.
Just know that in the future, whether it's you or Sarah,
either one of you.
Know this.
Trying to get over on me will not serve you.
Henry, I know my sister used you.
But I really like you.
I'm sorry for today.
It won't happen again.
Just count.
Sarah, you have nothing to do with Henry anymore.