Good night.
Sarah, are you really going to embrace a child on your own?
Dylan, I know this baby is going to come into the world in unconventional way,
but I still want to keep it.
It's not that easy being a single mother, you know?
I think it'll be okay.
I mean, imagine I won't have a husband bossing me around.
I mean, maybe we'll keep that back.
When I have this child, remember to bring a gift as the child's godfather.
It's getting late. Get home safe.
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
Me too.
Sarah, don't just want to be the child's godfather.
First off, I want to welcome everyone to today's meeting with the board of the directors of the hotel.
As you know, we've seen a downturn in business recently,
and it's time that we consider the bankruptcy reorganization,
and I want to get plans from each and every one of you
before that bankruptcy reorganization, which is going to occur in two months.
Why do we need to restructure?
We just secure several partnerships.
I mean, haven't the numbers improved?
We got in there talking about the business.
We're lucky that we tell them to go bankrupt with you in the head.