Okay, seriously, none of you would have any of your jobs here if it wasn't for my mother's support.
And now you're just gonna throw her under the bus?
This way, you will also deal with facts.
And the facts are that the hotel is losing money and intro.
It's time to do your organization, get new financial growth into the system.
Okay, but we just secured a partnership with the Wilson group, so why do we need to restructure?
Anyone?
Okay, yes, so Dolores has really gotten into your heads.
Dolores, what about Emily?
If the worker heard help with Wilson gone so easily on you?
Sarah, I mean, Wilson, it's canceled our partnership.
It's not possible.
How could it not be possible?
You always talk about the Wilson group because you mention it every day.
The notice of cancellation was delivered directly to my desk.
So without Wilson's cooperation, this whole partnership would not exist.
I know you are reluctant to let go of your mother's hard work,
but we have to accept our faith.
You don't have to say so much.
Restructuring.
I'm gonna join the meeting now.
Sarah, no matter how hard you try, you'll never beat me.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see Mr. Wilson.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wilson, that he doesn't want to see.