Wait, this will be you, okay?
It's fine. Just relax.
Henry, please don't cancel our partnership.
Sarah, was it not you who deliberately used me for the hotel?
No, no, no, I promise. I didn't take advantage of you.
Sarah, I like you.
What?
No, no, that's not possible.
You want the partnership reinstated?
I want you to be my girlfriend.
No, no, I'm not just gonna be the other woman
and ruin someone else's relationship.
The other woman?
How are you the other woman when we're in relationships?
No, aren't you an Emily dating?
No, no, no, we're not.
Okay, so then why do you keep going on dates with her?
The only reason I keep taking Emily out is because I don't want to see you with Dylan.
So why ask Emily out out of all people?
I'm sympathetic for Emily. I am.
There wasn't my intention.
What do you mean?
I still may stay at the hotel.
I slept with Emily and I may have taken her virginity.
What?
No, the white hotel.
I know you only stayed that one night and it was that day.
Henry, was it that day?
I was busy with the group and I had a drink.
It's not what I wanted.
Are you sure?
It was just the alcohol.
Whatever it was, the fact of the matter is
I slept with Emily.
It was not my intention.
Was Emily the one who told you she was the one you had a relationship with that night?
What?
Okay, I know what happened.
You were drugged by Jones.
Jones?
Emily said she was threatened by a man named Jones.
No, she lied to you.
Emily and Jones have been in cahoots from the very beginning.
Who you actually had sex with that night was.
Sir, how are you?
I worry the nurse mentioned your name didn't expect it to be you.
Why didn't you sell me fate?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
What is it, Dylan, huh?
Dylan?
It was Henry who brought me to the hospital.
Last time you embarrassed you and now he's being so attentive.
Sorry.
No, I should be apologizing to you.
Listen, everything Emily says to you is a lie, okay?
Don't believe her.
It wasn't Emily you slept with that night.
I think you should rest for now, okay?
Let's not forget that you're pregnant.
Mr. Wilson, I think it's for the best if you let her rest for now
and then you can talk about the matter later.
What do you say?
He's right.
Get some rest.
Discuss the partnership later.
I'm about to confess to Henry that he's the father of your child.
Yes.
I completely misunderstood him and put the blame all on him.
We're gonna do now.
Are you gonna confess to him?
I don't know.
If I want to save the hotel, I have to secure a partnership with him
but I don't want to ruin her relationship.
Don't tell him now.
Just for now, just to avoid conflict, okay?
That thing's settled for a little bit, okay?
And then you can decide whatever to do with the baby.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll do that for now.
Hey, I will take care of you, okay?
I will take care of you and the baby.
Thank you, Dylan.
It's okay.
You don't need to thank me.
I am the child's godfather after all, all right?
You rest for now and I'll check out later.
Forgive me, Sarah.
You're not for all these years again.
I got my feelings for you.
You actually came back.
I didn't think you cared about this family anymore.
Of course I came back to my mom's house.
I am surprised you were back.
I thought you were afraid of retribution and
wouldn't dare show your face again.
You still love me as your father?
Well, I think that love died for you
right along with mom.
Now you're just a devil in my dad's skin.
What, did I say something wrong?
Well, you shipped me off to boarding school
for over a decade for them.
And now you want to talk about father-daughter love.
Richard, come here.
Listen to what you said.
Sarah, he still is your father.
Why don't we just sit down as a family and talk?
Dad, look at her.
Sarah, apologize to me.
Oh, what an amazing act.
Richard, her mother passed away when she was you.
She's difficult to discipline.
She's impossible to control.
She's just like her mother.
No manners.
Don't you dare mention my mother, Richard.
Who are you to talk about mom?
When mom was sick, you were the one who was fooling around
with the shameless slut.
He didn't even bring her home three days after mom died.
Your mother was very sick at the time.
She didn't have many days left.
Is it so wrong for me to see happiness elsewhere?
How dare you say that?
We both know that mom got worse after you started seeing her.
Let's not talk about the past.
Yeah, yeah, let's not talk about the past.
Let's talk about now.
And how you want to take the hotel.
How about that, huh?
Are you man enough to talk about that?
The hotel is on the brink of bankruptcy.
If we don't seek financing in reorganization,
the hotel will close down.
I am saving the hotel.
Saving the hotel.
Wow, yes, you make it sound so noble.
No, you were just trying to rush to change the face
of the hotel before the will sets it, right?
Oh my gosh, saving the hotel.
You are even worse than I thought you were.
You were so afraid of me taking over the hotel,
but you just had to tamper with mom's will.
Tamper with the will.
You know, it doesn't matter though,
how you treat me or what you do,
because I'm already pregnant.
Pardon?
Who's child?
Who's child it is?
There's none of your business.
And by the way, I have already registered the child's affairs.
So if you try to interfere,
which I know you will, it won't work.
The will is already in effect.
So, let the best man or woman win.
What's the matter with the will?
I don't know.
Why did you hit her?
It's my fault.
It's my fault, okay?
Your daughter with her attitude,
it's like you don't care.
You're not going to be here sooner or later.
What can happen to you?
Richard, we've been together for over 10 years.
I've never asked for anything from you.
All I want is a happy family.
I mean, I don't care if we live in a hotel or not,
but I just don't want to be on the streets.
But you can't go tamper with the will.
She's my daughter after all.
You treat her like a daughter,
but she doesn't treat you like a father.
I mean, just look at her attitude.
Look at the fight you guys just had.
She couldn't admit to you
whose baby she was carrying
because she wants to inherit from the will.
You don't care about what happens to you.
You don't care about what happens to me.
You don't care about what happens to Emily.
I mean, if you're not going to do something,
I'm going to do something about it.
All right, the two of you settle this.
Just pretend that I don't know anything.
Sarah, do you get some time?
I want to take you somewhere.
Sure, let's go.
So how much do you make here?
Is it starting at 100 or higher?
Okay, I'm just thinking about a couple of things.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go.
How may I assist you?
Hey, how's it going?
Which area did they go to?
This gentleman reserved a VIP lounge.
He's going to propose to his girlfriend.
Propose?
You mean the woman that just walked through here,
General?
Yes.
Let's go out of here.
I didn't see exactly what type of woman
could picture my brother like that.
Let's go, come on.
Now I see why you brought me here.
Well, we used to come here all the time when we're kids.
Yeah.
Remember?
His friends are still open.
Sarah, I, uh...
What? Hello?
Is this he taking?
Mr. Wilson.
Hi.
I'm Matthew, but you can call me Matt.
I'm Matthew.
I'm Sarah.
You know, this is nice.
I would never expect for a guy.
So handsome to also be so romantic.
I mean to actually plan.
Hold this out like this, I mean.
That is truly stunning.
Hey, pal.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Oh, I mean, do you want to be a man
and actually have a fair fight?
Hey, pal.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Oh, I mean, do you want to be a man
and actually have a fair fight?
Henry, what is your friend doing?
Sorry.
We'll go.
What do you have?
Okay, well, that was strange.
What's going on?
You're not even going to fight for her?
There's no need.
If she likes them, she'll be with them.
Man, that's heartbreaking.
What are you going to need to do?
You know what?
Forget it.
I got you.
You want me to drunk tonight?
Mm?
You need me to be drunk tonight.
Sarah?
Yeah.
I love you, Sarah.
I want to protect you and the child.
Will you marry me?
Dylan, I have told you,
I don't see you like that.
I don't have.
Dylan's for you, eh?
I can't accept your proposal.
Can't you, Sarah?
I won't have ever thought about who's you and me.
I want to be here, your side, Sarah.
For the rest of our lives.
Dylan, I see you as my family.
I'm like a brother.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
I can't say this.
Want to hook up?
Desert.
Does tell?
You think you deserve, Sarah?
You're fucking crazy!
Listen to me.
If you plan on playing her, do not propose to her.
Pose.
You rejected me!
She's fucking rejected me!
You got it?
Foxy, Henry.
You think you sent a chance because she rejected me?
You were being delusional.
Sarah only loves the father of her child.
I suggest to you, you better not embarrass yourself.
You don't really want to keep going after this girl, Sarah, do you?
I mean, she's already pregnant.
I'm into her, man.
I don't really care.
I didn't expect you to have such a hard time when she started dating again.
That's right.
There's somewhere to go flowers for yums.
For me?
Oh, no. I'm sorry. They're for Sarah.
Wow.
You got her flowers.
He's actually still waiting if you want to come along the team.
Henry.
Impossible.
Those flowers definitely weren't sent by Henry.
These are for you.
These flowers are for me?
Yeah, but I'm sorry about my friend the other night.
Well, thank you.
Is there something else you have to say?
Look, I know a lot's been going on.
I want to be with you.
What?
I am.
I have a lot of work that I need to do in Boston.
And I actually need to leave soon.
Right.
So.
Why, I just Sarah always get everything.
Sarah, I don't just die.
If you die, you won't be able to take away my things.
Yes, go die.
Sarah, go to hell.
Go to hell.
Marie, you really don't need to keep following me like this.
You haven't given me an answer yet.
Ooh, you shouldn't drive.
It's not safe for the baby.
You think I'm good with me?
And you were just joking back there, right?
I mean, pursuing me.
Like, you wouldn't want to pursue someone who's actually pregnant.
No, I wasn't kidding.
I don't even care that you have a child.
I just, I just like you.
Well, watch out.
Henry, only wake up.
Henry, wake up.
Henry, do you wake up?
Henry, you can't die yet.
I still have so many things I didn't tell you.
Mom, please keep me safe.
Henry, you asshole, you can't die yet.
I still have so many things I need to tell you.
I love you.
And you're the father of my child
and I want you to be in their life.
And I want you to be in their life.
Now, this is a woman.
Henry's a woman?
Henry, you're not.
What were you saying about me being a father?
That's the thing is,
I didn't know Emily was pretending to mean me
and told you that she was the one she slept with.
But I won't pester you anymore.
And if you're not happy, I will just forget about it.
Were you taking my child?
Mommy's face.
She sure is a tomato.
You're right as a tomato.
Sarah, I'm happy.
I love you.
I know I haven't properly proposed to you.
Well, not to let him do so.
No.
You don't want to marry me?
No, it's just, I can't stop thinking about the car accident.
I think Emily and her brood had something to do with it.
There's something strange about it.
I haven't investigated.
Well, the board meeting is next week.
I have a plan.
Can you help me?
Of course.
Maybe a little reward would help.
Oh, really?
Henry, you know, I really didn't take you to be the villain.
Just using me to secretly empty out the hotel.
And what kind of person are you manipulating me like that?
I hope you know you have no relationship with me in the future.
Oh, that's fine because I never want to see you again.
What's going on with you and Henry?
Both you and Henry are despicable.
Yeah, you, the child of a mistress, just colluding with him,
to take our biggest business partner.
I didn't expect Sarah and Henry to break up.
Let's see you save your hotel now, Sarah.
Sarah, I've already told the reporters to release the photos.
How about your aunt?
Emily fell for it.
The board meeting is the day after tomorrow.
And we can finally expose their true colors.
Oh, I have a surprise.
Dr. Jones don't.
And he provided me some pretty interesting info.
Well, that's great.
But in order to pull this off, we can't see each other.
I'll miss you.
I'll miss you too.
The white family's property is ours now.
Wait, what?
Henry and Sarah broke up.
Really?
Oh my God.
So the white family property is all ours now.
So that board meeting in three days will be such a success.
Yes, you did.
The white hotel has been in operation for more than 20 years.
As a private entity, we have done very well.
But recently, we have been operating in the red.
We are seeking refinancing and restructuring within a week.
And it's okay to rebrand.
They didn't have the hotel go under.
Hm, he who goes with the wind.
Oh, sorry.
Did I say something wrong?
I just remember over 10 years ago, you guys all begging my mom for a job.
And now, um, life.
You know, flatter Dolores and now you're a member of the board.
It's outrageous.
What do you mean?
I've worked hard to get this position.
I've not been a browner.
Calling your brown loser?
I've gotten this on my own abilities.
You know, Sarah, it's about restructuring.
Don't stir up trouble.
Oh, sorry.
Am I stirring up trouble?
Haven't you already sensed my attitude?
I clearly disagree with the reorganization.
Dolores?
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
I know what you're doing.
You're doing this so my shares are invalid.
And then the will isn't valid.
And then you can take over the hotel.
Right?
Sarah, how can you think that I would do that?
You have already taken away my home.
I won't like to take over.
What can you say?
You only have 40% of the shares.
Combined, we have all others.
What about me?
Henry, didn't you and Sarah break up?
See, I'm awfully happy about that.
I guess you can probably consider this the official announcement
of my relationship with my wife.
Sarah, your scheming has gone deeper than I thought.
Well, how about that?
Mr. Wilson, this is a hotel board meeting.
Must I really ask you not to interfere?
As far as I'm concerned,
neither you nor your daughter
have a single share in this company.
Who are these people?
Board members?
You.
Mr. Wilson, you want to take charge of it.
I need you to listen to Sarah.
You have feelings for the hotel,
but I need you to think about survival.
Otherwise, we will lose everything.
So let's reach a decision together
with a refinance and organized for the operation of the hotel.
Of course, I can't bear to see this hotel go out of business.
Don't worry.
This is where it gets fun.
What do the rest of you think?
Mr. White,
there's an internal board meeting,
which means we have to leave.
My name is you.
This means they're no longer a part of the board.
How about a vote for the hotel not to change its cards?
Mr. Wilson, this is an internal matter for them.
Tell what do you want to do?
I do ask.
Have a look at that.
I've acquired the shares from the board,
and I'm interested in them to my wife.
Thank you.
Wow.
Well, now that I have hold of all of the shares,
I hope you have no objections.
Beautiful.
Henry promised me compensation.
Don't get to share with him to me, please.
She wants to be compensated.
Look, you'll be accounted for.
Bring him in.
It's not my business.
It was all her.
It was Emily who asked me to drug you.
And her, this bitch,
she's the one that made me make Miss White's life difficult.
Miss White, I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
Shut up, Henry.
Don't believe a word he says it.
It's not for this person.
I recorded our time in bed that day.
I will kill you.
Please.
Emily and do us white.
Get on the russet, or come and murder.
Sarah, you dad always knew you'd be successful.
It's very sweet of you,
and I already told you.
My dad died right along with Mom.
Very easy.
I would forget I'm Bob.
You were my father until he brought galore silver
and while we know what happened.
And I think that's when he stopped being my dad.
You hear that?
Look, the way I see it,
you have a couple options.
You send the shares back.
You sit on them, but just so you know,
once I'm finished,
the shares in your possession will be useless.
So?
They'll sell.
How'd I do it, baby?
Amazing.
Henry, I'm sorry about the incident at the bar the other day.
It's okay.
I should thank you for helping me chase my wife.
Pastor.
Let me tell you this.
You better be taking care of her.
I'm going to snatch my daughter and Sarah away from you.
Sarah, I always want you to be happy.
Thank you, Tom.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You haven't even taken your vows yet.
Young people so impatient.
Okay, you're ready?
Please repeat after me.
We stand here today before all of you.
To declare my love and willingness.
As we enter into this most holy matrimony.
Now you can kiss the bride.