Shut up, young lady!
Mr. Taurus, I need you to leave my wife alone.
Mr. White, there's been a horrible misunderstanding.
It's been a long day, and I'm sure you and Charlotte are very tired.
Maybe you should go home and get a nice, good night's rest.
And tomorrow we can meet, and we can talk about the partnership between the White family and the Taurus family.
How's that sound?
Mr. Taurus, I don't listen to the likes of you.
Charlotte makes the calls. I'll do whatever she wishes.
I bet you will. Get out of my way.
Charlotte, are you all right? Do I need to cancel the magazine interview happening in 10 minutes?
No, I'm all right. This would be a good opportunity to clear any lingering rumors and fix their stock prices.
Good.
I'm sorry. I can explain everything that just happened.
The partnership between the White and Taurus families will guarantee to raise both of our stock prices.
And it's just a matter of time till these silly little rumors fade.
I promise you will have the freedom to do as you please for the rest of your life.
This is only about the Taurus group. It has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with me? You're my wife. You're a problem.