We're legally married. It's wrong with living a gun.
Right. This is a deal. I can't just take the money and give nothing in return.
I can get myself to work. And I'll be back on time, it's me.
Oh, Lisa. You're finally mine.
I'm so sorry. It was a great day in emergency.
Oh, no worries. It's fine. Can I have your name?
Oh, Lisa.
Never knew Mr. Hawthorne would have such a silly smile moment.
All right. It's real? If your mom finds out you married a Cinderella.
All right, I give it to her. They want your mom.
You really married Mr. Hawthorne? It's just a contract marriage.
Shh, it's a pay-to-tay.
Next is the Lisa Hawthorne.
You are the CEO's wife. So where is my favorite?
We've known each other since medicine.
I don't think he actually likes me.
Plus, everyone in the company knows who he actually wants to be a man.
Heart is back.