Hello, everyone. Please, help yourself to have some cake.
Thank you, Ms. Hart. You are so very kind.
It's really such an honor to work with.
Please, don't flatter me.
I have to go see Mr. Hawthorne right now. He must want to see me right now.
Save a slice for me.
When do you think they will make their own relationship public?
I'll please see him.
Last time I asked when I saw Mr. Hawthorne unlock his phone,
the code of 090 is for its birthday, and isn't that looking too on you?
Well, I never knew Mr. Hawthorne would be so romantic, and using puts on a poker face.
Amelia, my relationship with Mr. Hawthorne is still talking about you.
Okay.
090 3. At summer's birthday again.
They love each other so much that it's okay, whatever it is.
It's just not getting as many things.
Why aren't you coming up?