Did you forget about your unexcused absence last time?
That's because something unexpected happened at home,
but I called in for a leave of ask.
So, what?
We needed you last minute and you weren't there.
Now that the project has failed,
if you're not to blame, who else would it be?
I was absent that day, yes,
but I prepared the initial budget ahead of time
so there is no way that my absence
would have affected the negotiations.
Wouldn't have affected the negotiations?
Elisa, take a closer look.
What did you write in a project budget?
No, no, no, this isn't right.
I wrote 50 million.
How did it become five million?
For a professional budget analyst,
you've made such a sloppy mistake.
Elisa, do you have anything else to say for yourself?
Well, it's like Elisa isn't trouble.
Elisa always strikes me as a professional.
How could she make such an error?
Keep it down, can't you see?
It's just trying to find something to your responsibility.
Wait, I have evidence to prove that my budget was correct.