You should have seen the look on Summer's face when she tried to swipe her card.
It was hilarious.
Oh my gosh, today we finally showed her who's boss.
I know, but I feel like everyone knows that Summer is Lucian's dream girl.
When he finds out, I, the placeholder wife, am totally getting the...
Legally, you are Mr. Hawthorne's wife.
You are literally the President's wife.
You have the high ground, what are you so afraid of?
Come on.
Let's go drink and celebrate.
You actually don't need your drink right now?
Yes.
No.
Okay.
Emilia.
Be honest with me.
Okay.
What is it?
I don't understand why Lucian wanted to marry me.
I don't know.
It's just...
I'm starting to feel like maybe he...
Like...
See, actually someone really...
Hey, Lisa.
I have something I have to attend to, so I'm going to be leaving now.
What?
Wait, no.
Are you gossiping about me behind my back while you're drunk?