What is it?
Everyone knows that Mr. Hawthorne is devoted to his mother.
If we tell her about Elisa seducing Mr. Hawthorne, then...
Good idea. Mia is the matriarch of the Hawthorne family.
She's very clever, but she never got involved in the family business and
she's lived in seclusion abroad for years. Even I haven't spoken to her.
All we need to do is send an anonymous text message to Mrs. Hawthorne.
Then we just need to wait for Elisa to be expelled from the Hawthorne family.
I went through great lengths to get this, but I never contacted her,
because I didn't have a reason. Do it for me. When Elisa is dealt with, you will be rewarded.
It's my pleasure to help you, Miss Hart. I just hope that when you become the president's
wife, you won't forget me. Of course not.
Be sure, Hawthorne, you received an anonymous message on your phone.
What does it say?
It says, as a fixed singer, Mr. Hawthorne, she charming so much that he's been
ignoring his or through good fears.
Book me a flight. I need to go back immediately.