How did the matter about matriarch Robinson go?
Rest assured, Ms. Hart, it's said that matriarch Robinson was furious upon hearing the news and returned home immediately.
Really?
Let me leave, so we'll be out of here soon.
Yes.
Congratulations in advance, Ms. Hart.
Let's go.
There's a weekly meeting of the Business Department, and there should be there personally.
We can't afford to make a mistake.
Amelia's gone on a work trip, so you can sit in her spot while she's gone.
If you get bored, you can just put on my phone.
I don't know what therapy, and we have to keep our voices down, because people are working.
Okay, I just want to know if I can say this to everyone.
A weekly meeting is about to begin.
Alyssa, why did you bring a cleaner to work?
Alyssa really treats the company as her home being anyone she likes.
Seriously, so filthy. It's disgusting just working at them.