Elisa, our entire department has showed up with work, and you?
If we have to delay our work, are you going to take responsibility for that?
Ms. Hart, this woman might have some trouble with her memory, so I'm only bringing her here temporarily.
I was going to help her find her family after work, and if she could just sit here for the time being, I'd promise that she won't disturb anybody.
Do you mean you brought this old hag in off the street, and she's also sick?
I think you're crazy. Picking up an old hag like this, reading of poverty, stinking up the whole office.
Where did you find her in a sewer?
What if this old hag isn't just mentally ill, but also could infect us all with some disease?
Yeah, Ms. Hart really think we should call a female later to disinfect every of this, ladies and men.
How could all of you be so cool?
Don't you all have families, too?
What if one of them had lost their memory, and needed your help?
Ms. Poole, she's interesting.
I'm not the one who's sick.
You're sick!
Disgusting, Alyssa.
Our company has rules and regulations.
It's not a place for you to show your kindness.
Get this old hag out of here now.
Ms. Hart, there is nothing in our company policy that discourages helping somebody in need.
In fact, it encourages us to do so.
Oh, there isn't.
Well, now there is.
Do you have a problem?
Ms. Hart is a senior leader in our company.
She can represent our president, and now she just happened to add another company rule.
Even if she asks security to drag you out, there's nothing you can do.
Understand.
How come you employees of a business department like this?
Lucian will be here soon from the business department.
Alyssa, you have two minutes.
If you don't get this old hag out of here, I will fire you.
You can go back on the street with her.
Maybe then you'll make more money than you do now.
So, Summer, you are really pushing it.
Tell me, what else can you do besides flaunt your authority?
I'm reporting you to Mr. Hart Ford.
As a well-level employee, you have contradicted me one too many times.
And now, you dare go see Mr. Hawthorne?
You're fired.
Two years.
Two years away from this company, and I never thought that the business department
at the Hawthorne group would decay into the state.
Alyssa will not be fired.
You will.
Okay, did I just hear this egg say she's going to fire us?
She has a problem with her brain.
That's why she's talking crazy.
It's hard to sell her president's wife to be firing her to ridiculous.
Besides memory loss, is she also crazy?
Why are they saying president's wife?
Isn't it you?
Are all of you quite finished?
Can't believe how shallow you are.
You are kind and righteous.
Do you never use Alicia's identity to gain power?
But you?
Okay, ma'am, it's okay.
I'm going to help you find your family.
Let's go.
Why do we need to leave?
Why don't they leave first?
Fine.
Since you're determined to cling to us.
At you, get this old hag out of here right now.
You've got guts.
I'll see who dares to kick me out of here today.
You actually dared to hit me.
Ms. Hart?
Alyssa, this woman attacked my subordinate.
I could have her sent to a mental hospital.
You don't have the authority.
Of course I do.
She hit my subordinate.
I can reasonably deduce she has some mental issues.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Yes, this woman is clearly sick,
but naturally I'm going to find her family to let them handle it.
If you and Matthew haven't instigated this,
none of this would have happened.
This woman's actions can only be described as self-defense.
Yeah, I think you're the one who's crazy.
You don't respect the elderly.
You're not qualified to be a leader.
I don't know why your company's higher ups even chose you.
Oh, are you angry?
To disappear from my sight!
Security!
Go both of them on a path on group.
With me here, I can't drive you away.
I'll tell you, I am.
Sorry, what are you doing here?
Oh my god, why does Lucian come to the business department every day?
Fine.
I guess we'll have another show then.
Just wait.
Well, it's like this.
Alyssa brought this woman in off the street,
who's most terrible and insisted on having her in the office,
which was disrupting everyone's work,
so I'm only thinking of the company.
Yes, Mr. Hawthorne.
What if she has some contagious disease and infects everyone?
I take full responsibility for this incident.
If the company wishes, I can handle my resignation.
Hawthorne Group is not an impersonal company.
Alyssa's done well.
From today forward,
we'll be promoted to team leader,
and oversee projects as a reward.
Mr. Hawthorne, I'm afraid I'm not qualified for this position.
I believe everyone here knows your abilities well.
As for you, you can go to HR,
and they'll handle your resignation.
He is the backbone of the business department.
If you fire him, there'll be no elites left.
Summer, you manage the business department into a mess.
You're responsible for that.
I promise to manage the business department better.
If this won't happen again,
Matthew, why have you not apologized to this madam and misfailient?
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Why are you apologizing first?
This one almost just put me into a mental hospital.
Who owns time?
Who dare you ask me to apologize?
Miss Hart?
Apologize.
Sorry. I'm sorry. I can't hear you.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
And you guys?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Have I been misunderstanding him all this time?
Could it be?
Well, that's the end of that matter.
I'll take care of this lady and help her find her family.
Listen, why did you call me over?
What police have find out?
Well, what exactly are you trying to do?
I want to test my daughter-in-law.
How can you test at her enough today?
She's great. You saw that.
Oh, listen.
You're quite loyal, aren't you?
It's enough.
Fine.
Look, um, Alyssa is a very good girl,
but it seems she doesn't even know that you like her.
Nor does anyone else know that she's your wife.
Why are you keeping this marriage so?
Secretive.
I don't know how to tell her.
I'm afraid that if we make our relationship public,
pressure will be too much for her.
Lucian, when didn't you become such a coward?
Look, if you like her, just confess boldly.
You don't want to wait until Lisa falls for some other guy before you feel regret, do you?
Regret what?
Nothing.
Please, come sit.
Alyssa, I'm sorry, I deceptive earlier.
I'm actually Lucian's mother.
What?
Please, let me explain.
Um, a few days ago I got an anonymous text saying that some woman was trying to seduce Lucian,
and I got afraid that he might get tripped.
Anyway, Alyssa, can you please forgive me?
Yes, Mrs. Hawthorne, I understand.
You're just looking out for your son.
But I am concerned that the person who sent that text must have had that intentions.
I have an idea who sent it.
Go ahead.
Good.
And Alyssa?
I heard that Lucian plans on taking you to a very fancy dinner tonight.
Okay.
There's actually something I want to talk to you about.
How should why aren't you eating?
Yeah, Alyssa, what do you want to ask me?
If you wanted to force, it's not going to happen.
Why would you think I wanted to force?
I've been meaning to ask you.
You've liked summer for 10 years.
Ben, why would you marry me?
Why protect me at every turn?
Well, what?
You think I've liked summer for 10 years?
Judging by his reaction, he must have been caught off guard.
Alyssa, you're being too presumptuous.
Seriously, why would I have liked her for 10 years?
Alyssa, I've liked you for 10 years.
How could that persevere?
Today we met.
I've helped for you.
But because of the conflict between our parents, I chose to get them.
I wanted to show you that I cared for you, but I couldn't.
I was afraid that it would put you in danger.
I'm really sorry, Alyssa.
All these years, I've suppressed my feelings for you.
I fought tooth and nail to be the head of the whole of our family.
And now it's taken me a decade to
fully stand by you like this.
So why now?
And now it's taken me a decade to fully stand by you like this.
I was afraid if I told you, you didn't like me,
but you wouldn't even be calling anymore.
So what's wrong?
So when you sat next to me, all those years ago,
it wasn't because you didn't like your food?
Hey, I don't really like this.
I'm really sorry I shouldn't
couldn't show you my feelings and the problem.
But then why did you raise some of that love letter back then?
Well, I love that.
I remember delivering a party invitation tour from my parents.
Well, why are all your passwords somewhere's birthday?
You mean 0903?
What was that have to do with summer?
I don't even know her birthday.
So then what 0903 do you?
Alyssa 0903, September 3rd, was the day of my first month.
So it was, I was all just misunderstanding?
So it was such a misunderstanding?
Listen, I love you.
I know, I tricked you into marrying me.
The feelings for you are absolutely true.
So can you try to accept me?
I know that our marriage started as a contract,
but it feels real to me now.
I want to be with you.
I want to be with you now, and I want to be with you when we're all done.
And finally on.
Hey, true husband and wife.
We don't have to give our relationships secreted from our colleagues anymore.
Lucian, I see you.
Summer, I'd like you to meet my wife.
What?
Alyssa and I have actually been married for a long time.
So you don't have to send out the list of text messages to my mom anymore.
We all like Alyssa.
So no matter how much we try to sow discord between us,
it's never going to work.
What text messages I have?
I have the evidence, Summer.
Now, considering the relationship between our families,
I'm going to ask you to go ahead and submit your resignation from your team.
That's for everyone else.
You all get off an hour early today.
And you're invited to dinner with my wife.