We are finally married, my missus.
I don't know if it feels like a dream.
I know.
Nothing feels, um, wrong or anything.
No. No. Everything is perfect.
You should. Maybe shower first.
Oh. Are you joining?
You're funny.
This is not what I agreed to.
You said I would never have to even meet him.
And now, not only am I married to the Miles Kipling,
but I have to live with him.
Our huge Dr. Hardy is finally back.
Doctors without borders must have been a blast.
I bet you didn't miss me at all.
Lane, my snarky sunshine.
I always do so much.
Oh, you shouldn't face that anymore.
My idiot sunflower.
Hey, I heard about your engagement.
Congratulations.
Oh, about that.
I just kind of have a favorite task here.
You.
The richest woman in LA.
Have a favorite to ask me.
Well, and only you can help me.
You owe me one. No questions asked. Remember?
Alright, I did spit it out.
I'll be a great-dyed mother.
What? You want me to marry your fiance in your place?