Not only am I married to the Miles Kipling, but I have to live with him?
Not a big deal. Okay, I'll be back in a month. Miles, he had accident years ago.
He can't really tell people's faces apart, so it should be easy to convince him.
So that's why.
He's the only one donating and volunteering around here. I'm like some rich jerks.
He actually cares.
He doesn't remember me. That's why he asked me to marry him.
Bigger wife, do you think suspicious? Or, you know, do what you need to?
I know, I know, right, right. Bestie code, I will not lay a hand on your man.
I mean, that's not really what I am trying to say.
Oh, I gotta go, he's back.
And, Clara, hold on.
Are you planning on surprising me, my missus?
You know, I've been waiting for this for a very long time.