I've been waiting for this for a very long time.
No, uh, I can't.
You can't? Why?
Um...
I just started my period.
My cramps hurt really bad.
I just swore to Elaine.
I can't break my promise.
Ooh, I cramps with so much pain.
I gotta go. Sorry.
No, no, no. No, you stay here, okay?
Get some rest.
I'll get you some money.
Okay.
I have done my research,
and this is the best medication for menstrual cramps.
I can't take painkillers.
I can't take...
Are you allergic?
Or are you faking those cramps?
What? Why would I lie about something like that?
Elaine is allergic, but I am.
I have to spit it out later when he's not looking.
She'll give me some honey, lemon, water.
I drink some before bed every night.
Of course.
Honey, lemon, water. Yeah.
Sure.