When exactly did you grow a prostate?
Shit, I packed the wrong report.
I can't wait to hear how you're going to explain this.
I did have surgery, okay? I had an appendectomy.
If you say so, let me see the wound. It's probably...
You're gonna pull the wound again.
Let me see it.
See, I told you I wasn't lying.
I'm sorry.
I must have just gotten the report to mix up.
You sure it's not like a sticker or a tattoo or something?
I got the sticker from her friend in the plastic surgery department.
It cost me $100 for God's sake.
I'm your wife, and I love you.
But it hurts that you don't believe me.
I'm to wake up, my missus.
My house, we can't be intimate right now.
No, no, no, no. It's not about that.
I wanted to wake you up and get ready because my grandma invited us to go celebrate Jesse's return from England.
What? Lunch with grandma and Jesse?
I ate this arranged marriage with Elaine.
Now he's changed all of a sudden.
It's weird, grandma.
Well, Jesse, it happens.
My husband and I were arranged too.
And once we married, we fell in love.
This is different.
It's a scheme.
I'll show you when they get here.
If you've got to stop watching this soap opera.
You don't have to be nervous. My grandma's nice.
Elaine says they've never met.
It should be fine.
I'm not joking. I have proof.
Oh, what were you proving?
I agree, my. This is Elaine, my wife.
Elaine, grandma, Joyce.
Joyce, I'm so happy to meet you.
So lovely to meet you too.
Let's help lunch.
This is my seat.
I'm sorry, I thought this was a family gathering.
Why is a stranger here?
My family has been friends with the Kipling's for decades.
How dare you call me a stranger?
And how dare you sit beside Milesy?
When you're not even Elaine, Kipling.
How dare you sit beside Miles?
I'll show you the proof.
Here is a picture from the engagement party.
Elaine Priestley doesn't have a birthmark on her neck.
She does.
Birthmark, what birthmark?
Elaine made sure no photos from the engagement party were left behind.
I bet she snatched it.
Who are you?
Why are you pretending to be Elaine Priestley and marry my Milesy?
Well, can I have a look?
Sure, but it's not a birthmark.
It's actually a new tattoo that I got.
Messing with my wife, Jessie.
No, no buts.
If you do this again, I'll have to ask you to leave.
She says it's a tattoo.
Then it's a tattoo.
Why aren't you sleeping together then?
That's on.
Clearly, she's hiding something.
Wait, what's going on?
Are the two of you not in love?
Because if you're not, you can get a divorce.
This is all just so ridiculous.
Miles and I actually can't keep our hands to ourselves.
We do it like every day.
Fine.
Impossible.
I asked your housekeeper.
They said you weren't intimate at all.
Housekeepers know.
Nothing, because Miles sends them away so that we can have some privacy.
She's just making up stories again.
Tell me the truth, Miles.
You've never lied to me.
Grandma, we are.
We're perfectly fine.
See?
There's nothing to be worth.
Covering for her.
Why?
What do you want to watch us do it, just to be sure?
He's covering up to save the marriage.
He must really like Elaine.
Enough of this nonsense.
Let's have lunch and peace.
Don't mind her.
She's been a friend of the family for so long.
We've definitely smelled her too much.
My Ayurveda practitioner recommended this liquor.
He said it's good for a young people's health.
You know what I mean.
I don't think that'll be necessary, grandma.
Sounds a little anti-science, Joyce.
Miles, if it's true, but Elaine said, I think you need this.
Dr. Gupta says it supplements the soul's energy and heats up the mud.
Are you sure it's not just purely an aphrodisiac?
I'm not really struggling in the energy department, grandma.
In fact, I'm in more need of demand than supply.
What?
What do you mean was Elaine lying?
I live once now.
Here's to a wonderful night.
This is going to be a wonderful night.
Let's get you to bed.
Okay.
It's a nice and cozy.
Have a good night.
I've liked you for a long time.
No, no. Get some rest, okay?
We don't go. I want a hook.
I really should be going.
You smell so good.
Thank you.
I should be going before this gets messy.
What is this?
Miles, I can explain.
Miles, you lied to me.
Didn't you?
I hate when people lied to me.
You drive me crazy.
Elaine's husband, what are you thinking?
Hey, where are you going?
I'm sorry, Miles. I apologize.
Apologize for what?
Until Miles.
It hurts.
It still hurts.
Yes, it still hurts.
How about when I do this?
Yes, it hurts worse there, please.
Well, if it hurts wearing them, you don't have to hide it.
You don't have to wear high heels.
I know. I won't, again.
Well, I should probably call the family doctor.
Oh, I... it's... it's not that serious.
Leg injuries can be very serious, okay? It's just a precaution.
I'm a doctor myself.
Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
Well, you heard him.
No more high heels for a while, okay?
It's still avoiding me.
I'm not dumb.
If you don't have feelings for me, then...
You don't have to stay together. We can get a divorce.
I don't want a divorce.
A divorce you.
I'm just not ready yet. I know it's weird.
Miles, I... like you a lot.
And I've liked you for a very long time.
Longer than you'll ever know.
It just feels unreal being your wife.
I feel so out of place and everything happens so fast.
Okay. Okay. I get it.
You do?
What if we give it a month?
In the meantime, I'll do my best to make this easy for you.
And at the end, if you still don't want this, we'll get a divorce.
What do you say?
One month. That's just enough time, Burling, to get back.
Deal.
Could you wrap this up for me, please?
And a card too.
I'd like to make a message up to my best friend.
Okay.
Miles, wait for me.
Keep your distance, Jesse. I'm a married man.
I know you'd like me better, but Elaine would be so mad.
Miles? Miles?
This is not what it looks like.
Oh, I know. I saw Jesse throw herself on you.
I can't believe she thought that would work.
Elaine, Miles, how to me?
Shut up, Jesse.
And I don't want to hear any more of these childish games.
Okay. Do I have to send you back to England?
I hate the food there.
Good. Okay. Great.
Well, I don't want to hear one more peep from you, or else I'll lose my mind.
What are you doing here? Just shopping for something in particular?
She's your admin here. What about you?
I'm just browsing.
Your purchase, Miss.
As you ask, we've made the card out to Elaine.
Told you she is buying Elaine gifts and writing her letters she is not Elaine.
It's not illegal to buy yourself.
Is it the platinum VIP card?
Miles, see? Do something.
I can't be the only one thinking this is weird, right?
You are.
I believe my missus.
Welcome, our most prestigious guest, Elaine Priestley.
What the fuck is this?
This is all very unnecessary.
I'll just take my purchase and leave.
Your pre-orders have arrived.
We've been waiting for you to collect them.
This is the limited edition Barrow Wing Hills.
Box for a coat, only five worldwide.
Sunglasses from Volgary. They fit your face so well.
Why is she getting all this attention?
She's a fake.
Thank you very much for everything. I'm so grateful.
Here you go.
It really hurts.
Yeah, it looks swollen.
Well, let's get you to the hospital.
Rich girl buys heels and can't wear them.
I'll expose you eventually.
This is where I work. Someone will recognize me.
You know, I've heard horrible things about this place.
We should try another hospital.
No, this one's the closest. Just hang on tight.
My wife, St. Cole, is hers.
All right, I need to keep a lot of the form. What's her name?
Clara, you're back from Africa.
You're back from Africa.
Is he talking to you?
No.
It's Brooke, your ex-boyfriend.
What ex? I never agreed to date him. It's all in his head.
Hey, my wife says she doesn't know you.
You're married?
Oh, that explains it.
You didn't go to Africa to work with doctors without borders.
You got married. I knew nobody would give up residency for charity.
You're going back to doctors ready, Clara.
Let's go.
Clara, she said she doesn't know you.
That is Clara Hurty. Why is she pretending to be someone else?
You said she's your ex-girlfriend.
Here's three mil.
Prove it, and it's yours.
Well, it's easy.
Clara is allergic to painkillers.
She will have an immediate rash after taking any.
I'll give it to you once the liar is exposed.
Hey, you didn't ask for my name.
Did you just trick the information out of me?
You know, I really didn't know that guy back there.
I believe you.
And that hospital. I really don't think we should go back.
What are you doing?
Getting you into the shower.
What?
Come on.
Funny, Miles. You promised me a month.
And I'm keeping that promise.
Well, then why do you?
Because the doctor said that we have to soak your foot in cold water.
Okay, it keeps us swelling down. I'm just trying to help.
All right, I get it.
You just enjoy playing with me, don't you?
Maybe I do. My missus.
Joyce, I'll prove to you today that that bitch is not a lame priestly.
What are you doing?
Do you trust me?
Yes.
What do you want?
I'm here to prove her identity.
It's fake.
Not interested. You can leave.
Elaine, I dare you to take these painkillers now.
If you do, I don't believe you.
Painkillers.
Does she know who I really am?
Dare. What's there to be afraid of?
I need to take my meds anyway, so.
This watch, I already got the intel.
This bitch is allergic to painkillers.
So she swallows it.
Well, I've taken the painkiller.
Now, will you please excuse us?
Impossible.
How are you not affected?
You should be covered in hives right now.
What are you talking about?
Who told you I was allergic to painkillers?
Good thing I've been carrying into histamine since last time.
I took one earlier in the car.
Look at that. Nothing happened.
A lot of fuss over nothing.
Must be the dosage.
One pill isn't enough.
If you have the guts, I dare you to swallow the whole bottle.
Then and only then.
When is enough, ever enough with you, Jesse?
I promise that she is not late. I'll prove it to you.
Shut up, Jesse.
I've told you before.
You're not welcome here.
Leave.
I've got the dramatics.
Jesse, your tears aren't going to work here.
Get out of my house.
Sorry, Elaine.
It's not Jessica.
She had me bring her here tonight.
I didn't mean to ruin your time together.
Oh, a grandma. No need to worry.
I take plenty of good care of my wife.
Now, if you'll excuse us, you've got some business to get down to.
Right. Yeah.
Have a good night, grandma.
Sucking wet, my missus.
Better get a try before you catch a cold.
Because if you do, my grandma will never let me hear the end of that.
Yeah.
Well, you guys have a good day.
All right. You guys have a good day.
Okay. Bye.
Something I can help you with, Miss?
Nothing. Nothing. You remind me of Gabriel.
The angel. Gabriel?
Never mind. It's stupid.
No. Yeah.
You really are like Gabriel.
Did you just say Gabriel?
Like the angel.
Gabriel?
Like the angel?
What angel?
I meant like Gabriel walked the actor.
Well, you just said reminded me of someone.
Tell me why you said that.
Or is Jesse right?
Are you not actually Elaine?
It's my friend.
She has this really weird obsession with angel references.
She likes to imagine what they might look like.
Super nerdy, I know.
But she told me about this guy.
She had a crush on that reminded her of Gabriel.
And I was like Gabriel who? And she said the angel.
And maybe that's how it got mad.
A woman who likes angels so much shouldn't lie.
Right. Right.
You're tired.
I think it all crazy like that.
It's time for bed it's late and nature calls.
I'm just kidding. The mission going?
He hadn't figured it out.
What are you coming back?
I'm barely holding it together here.
Wait. Are you wearing a hospital gown?
Are you sick?
Yeah.
I got caught in the rain just a little fever.
Resting in the hospital for a couple of days.
What a coincidence.
I sprained my ankle so I guess I'll be resting for a few days too.
That bitch Clara keeps claiming she's not who I think she is.
Not Jesse girl is willing to pay $3 million for proof of her identity.
But if I go directly to Clara, couldn't I extort even more?
I know right.
Oh, hang on. I got a text. Let me check it.
Clara, I know what you're up to.
Transfer $5 million by midnight.
We're all telling your husband who you really are.
Elaine, alright. Something came up. I gotta go. Bye.
I can't let Brooke ruin Elaine's plan.
But we're gonna get that much money.
Elaine, you should really call for me.
I'm here to help. You don't have to walk around on your own.
Miles looks like you're gonna have to make a small sacrifice for the sake of your marriage.
Miles, look at that ring. It's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
You like that one? I'll have my assistant buy it for you tomorrow.
What?
Unless you wanted to buy it yourself.
No.
Oh, what's the matter? Do you not have the funds?
What's the matter? You don't have the funds?
Here, I'll send you some right now. Done.
Of course.
Money's been transferred. Don't bother me again.
Thanks to Miles, that asshole broke us out of my life.
Miles deserves to be rewarded.
Take the rest of the day off. I'll take care of things my husband drives.
Miles does home, really.
I knew it. You do know me.
Danger! Get out!
Clara, you were in such a rush to leave for Africa.
I didn't get the chance to sleep with you back then.
But now?
What are you doing?
I told you, Clara. You'll always be mine.
How dare you marry someone else behind my back.
Watch how I deal with you now.
Touch her and you'll regret it.