Get out!
I'm sorry, my husband. I thought it was you at the door. I really don't know that.
Still pretending, Clara.
You recognize me just now. Try to shut me out.
What do you want?
You still think she's your wife?
Let me tell you the truth.
She's not a lame.
Her real name is Clara. She's a doctor at the hospital. And also, my ex-girlfriend.
That's not true.
Enough. My wife says she doesn't know you. So get off my property.
You're impossible. This woman is a fraud.
If you don't believe me, I'll get her medical records from the hospital to prove it.
No. There's no need.
I love the woman standing here. No matter what her name is.
What?
Now leave before I call the police.
Now!
Your hurt. Let's get you fixed up.
I'm sorry.
Did you really mean what you said earlier?
I said a lot of things earlier. What are you referring to?
You're referring to.