Miles?
Dr. Hurty, where are you going?
Uh, what's happening?
Hey.
Why is Miles here at this hospital?
Doesn't he have a private family doctor or something?
Dr. Hurty, what's wrong?
My outfit should be convincing enough.
I shouldn't be exposed.
Ugh.
I just forgot your medical records.
I'm just gonna go back and get-
Oh.
There's actually no need.
Um, I'm not sick.
Then why are you here?
Well, um, I'm here to ask you a question.
Ask away.
Um, how do I get my wife to have sex with me?
What did you just say?
I know.
It sounds ridiculous, but I want to be intimate with my wife.
And so far, it just seems like she's not even interested.
Well, maybe your wife has some reservations.
You should talk to her.
Understand her concerns.
Talking to her.
That's the solution?
Yes.
Lemon can be sensitive about this topic.
But with patience, I believe your wife will open up to you.
Well, alright.
I think I understand now.
Great.
Problem solved.
Well, good luck.
Have a nice day.
There's the door.
I'll walk you out.
We need to talk.
See you.
No.
I don't know what it is that Mrs.
.