What are you doing?
Why are you pretending to be a lane?
Tell me, what's your game?
I don't know what you're talking about, just let me go.
Don't know.
Let me clarify.
You know, Jessie, right?
She came to see me, offered me millions.
Lara, if we weren't together for three years,
I would have revealed your identity to her long time ago.
Jessie, all right, fine, fine.
I'll tell you, but you have to let me go first.
Look, to be honest, I'm a lane stand-in.
But she asked me to do it, and she'll be back in a month,
and then everything will be resolved.
So you don't want to be married to that man?
OK, I'll help you in all the marriage tomorrow,
and then you can leave today.
Absolutely not.
I am not divorcing Miles.
What did you say to me?
I said that no matter what happens,
I am not divorcing Miles.
In this lifetime, he is my one and only husband.
He forced my hand.