So you don't want to be married to that man?
I know it.
Forcing Miles.
Did you say to me?
That no matter what happens,
In this lifetime he is my only husband.
Miles, now you believe me, right?
That woman is not Elaine.
So what if she isn't?
And what if she isn't Miles?
She lied to you. Aren't you mad?
Who cares what her name used to be?
She's my wife now.
I must have underestimated this woman.
Not only did she deceive Miles,
But she also completely enchanted him.
If that's a case, then I'll have to.
Fine.
If you won't handle this,
Then I'll just give this to her according to grandma
And let her deal with that woman.
You wouldn't dare.
Yes, I would.
But if you want to stop me,
Then let's make a deal.
What do you want?
I can't handle a date with you.