Grandma, yesterday this slut admitted to not being a lane and I recorded it
listen
to be honest, I'm
Elaine's
It's over. She asked me to do it and she'll be back in a month and
Sorry grandma reflexes. Miles, are you crazy? Are you really gonna side with her?
Why is Miles helping me? Could it be that he already knows everything?
Miles, what does Jesse mean by her not being a lane?
grandma
Jesse is just very jealous of Elaine and she's doing everything in her power to ruin her name
But Elaine has been nothing but kind to you and if she isn't my wife
Who could she be? Okay, that makes sense, but why are you here with her tonight?
Jesse threatened me
She said that if I didn't spend the night with her she would hurt Elaine
Jesse you conniving liar
We've been tried to harm my granddaughter in law
You have to believe me everything I said has been true
That bitch isn't a lane
Can you prove she deceived my grandson?