Why does he suddenly want a divorce?
He knows who I am.
Grandma, you seem to have tested my wife multiple times, right?
I suppose you're very unhappy with her, right?
Maybe a divorce would make you happy.
Is all this because of me?
I'm sorry.
I won't interfere in your marriage again.
Dear, I can see how much she and Miles truly care for each other.
Divorce is a serious matter.
You two should talk it out.
Miles, do you really want a divorce?
I'm finally afraid.
So have you checked it out?
I wasn't lying, right?
That woman is definitely not a lame.
Miles was right. You really are out of your mind.
Is Miles protecting Aline again?
I don't know.
Yes, I'll just have to handle it myself.
Miles, want a divorce? Not?
No, no, no. Don't play with me.
I'm not stupid.
You have always kept your distance from me, intentionally avoiding me.
You probably never even liked me from the start, did you?
So instead of watching you suffer, I figure it's better we just part ways.
So go, be free or whatever.
That's not true. Being with you hasn't been tortured.
You're not going to stand there and tell me that you're happy to be married to me.
Yes.
What was that? What did you just say?
It's getting late. We should go home.
Yeah, yeah, it's late.
Hey, in terms of the divorce, I figure we can wait.
I actually fall in love with me.
Miles, you idiot. I've already fallen for you. A long time ago.
Where are you? There's a lady here by the name of Jesse.
She said if she doesn't see you within the next half hour, she's going to print the orphanage down.
What?
Is something wrong?
Nothing. It has nothing to do with you.
Find out where my wife is going. Make it quick.
Miss White, Claire, it's her.
Now you're Clara?
What do you want? It's simple. Go to Miles.
Tell him you're not a lesson!
Chop, chop, Claire. If you don't divorce him within an hour, I'll burn this small shitty place.
Not that anyone cares.
Okay, stop, stop, stop, don't. We'll do it.
Any what's going on?
Miles, we found her. She went to the orphanage.
Jesse's there too.
Our suspicion might have figured it out.
Send someone to angel orphanage immediately. Don't let her hurt my wife.
You're back. What happened? You left without saying anything.
Miles, I need to tell you something.
The truth is, I'm not a lean.
Jesse was right. I'm an imposter.
You said you wanted a divorce.
And I can leave, but please don't divorce a lean. I promised her you two would stay married.
Say something.
Thank you for telling me.
What? Thank you?
You're not mad?
Do you want me to be mad?
No, no. Not at all.
I'm not a lean. Miles, at all.
I'm just someone who married you under false pretenses and now that you know the truth, you should be furious.
That would be your normal reaction.
I don't care. I don't care.
I don't care.
As the person I love is right from me.
Claire Hurty.
Or Elaine Priestley.
You. I'm in love with you.
It was all along.
You're kind of a bad liar, Claire Bear.
What is going on? Tell me everything. I'll explain everything.
Okay. Okay. I'll explain. Have a seat.
The relation's clear.
You're watching this video, eat me, say you have five silly girls.
I've known all along that you love him.
He was never meant to be my fiancé. He was always meant for you.
So, who knew I wasn't Elaine all along?
Yes.
And I wasn't the only one lying. You two were in on it together.
Yeah, we all lied a bunch. I'm sorry.
But the part that is true is that I've loved you since the second I met you.
Claire, before I could confess, you had already left the orphanage.
So, I thought Elaine was the only way that we could actually have a chance.
And if you don't believe me, feel my heart. It's racing right now.
The heart never lies.
Claire must have confessed everything by now.
Models must be furious.
What are you doing? What have you done?
What did you do this time, Jesse?
Miles, it was all for you. She is not the real Elaine.
You need to kick her out.
Jesse, what's wrong with you?
Those kids have no one. Miss White is their only family.
And to get to me, you would have to build innocent kids?
Don't you have a heart?
Miles, you let her hit me?
Compared to what you just did, a slap in the face is nothing.
I've called the police. You're going to jail.
Eddie, get her out of here.
No!
I promise. I will never. I'm so sorry.
Elaine, what? You want me to marry your fiance in your place?
I have my reasons. Just pretend to be me for a month and I'll be right back.
You should be easy to convince him.
Are you sick?
I've been so blind. I should have known something was wrong with Elaine
this whole time.
Miles, please help me. She's my best friend.
Don't worry. I'll get the jail ready. We'll be in Europe this quick as we can.
Let's go.
So happy I made it. You're still alive.
What are you talking about? Of course I'm alive.
Well, then why are you in the hospital? Aren't you supposed to be dying?
Isn't that why you tricked me into marrying Miles?
I just got a nose job. Who said I was dying?
You were just acting so mysterious.
And you practically handed Miles to me on a sofa platter to inherit.
With you being you, you would probably end up putting the only person you love in your cross-drawer for the rest of your life.
So I decided to help out a little.
Well, thank you, essentially.
That's more like it.
Have you slept with him yet?
Oh my God! How can you even ask that? I thought you were his wife.
I've been trying a whole month not to portray you.
All right, all right.
My bad. Now we can sleep with him any time you want. Enjoy.
Okay, we should go. I'll leave it to this.
That.
Have you a bad?
Of course. Hurry up. I don't want to miss my spa time.
I can actually call you my wife.
What? About to hang home.
I was worried about you working late, so I brought snacks.
Very kind of you, but I think the only snack I really want is standing right in front of me.
Someone's in the boss's office.
Doll pretend.
And now you know my feet. I'm actually a big bad man.