You are late, or have you forgotten you're not the big-shot journalist you used to be?
Is that alcohol I smell?
I'm so sorry bossy
There that should help by the way
I'm sending you back down to the entertainment desk that department is on the chopping block and I could use someone who can handle a diva
After last chance Kane don't screw this up
Listen up everyone
This is Lois Kane, your newest team member
Look who it is
Is she's my new boss?
I know you all have heard the rumors about the billionaire acquiring our magazine
Brace yourselves, buckle up
Are his doing it for his first love?
I wonder who the lucky girl is
Boss your dad
Boss your man
And now you're about to lose your job too
Must be tough, huh?
And once I turn the new boss
You'll be out of here for good