Hello.
I apologize Mr. Cavill, sorry, can you repeat the question?
My question was, what do you think the theme of love is in notebooks?
You're an entertainment journalist, so I figured you'd have some good insights, right?
Right, of course, yes.
The main characters, they go through a rough relationship, and their love goes through
their emotions are high and low, their love.
This all sounds pretty generic to me, don't you think?
Maybe you don't know what true love is or miss the point of it entirely.
What's me or just Clark have it out for her?
Why is she soaked?
Is she trying to seduce Clark or something?
Definitely some tension there.
I've never seen him like this.
I appreciate your advice.
But if I may, it's clear Ms. Kane is completely unprofessional.
She's nothing but an amateur who can't even recognize the genius of Mr. Cavill.
Let's get this incompetent reporter out of here.
Don't touch her.