Lois Kane, you're under arrest for libel and defamation.
That's insane, I didn't write that!
I am so sorry Mr. Cavilla, I had no idea Lois would stoop this lab.
You know I've never...
Say it for the judge, Lois.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, let her go.
No, I said let her go.
Sir!
I said let her go!
Party handle this.
Ladies and gentlemen, have an announcement.
As of today, Clark Cavill is the new owner of Daily Globe.
Holy shit, he's my boss now.
And, as the new owner, I will make sure that this gets thoroughly investigated.
As the new owner, I will make sure that this gets thoroughly investigated.
What the hell is he up to?
Check the timestamp on the article.
It says it was published around the same time Lois and I were trapped in the storage room.
Clearly, this is some sort of setup.
Maybe...
Maybe she's scheduled it in advance.
Well, let's check the security footage in that channel.
That'll look great things up.
Mr. Cavill, the security system has been compromised.
All of the footage is gone.
Hello?
Trace the IP address back to the publisher of this article.
I need answers now.
What?
The one who sent the photos into the article is Jim Kirby.
Jim?
It is Mistress.
Not again.
We miss Jim Kirby for questioning and clearly he's the one behind this smear campaign.
Wait, that's not necessary.
I mean...
Oh, I might have to involve the cops in this.
It'll just draw more attention to the article.
But I can issue a statement saying that we were hacked and the article is fake.
Fine, but make sure it's convincing.
One more thing.
Why exactly were Lois and I trapped in that storage room?
I went in there to make a private phone call and she happens to walk in.
But somehow the door locked behind her.
Clearly, somebody here is more focused on sabotaging their co-workers rather than doing their actual job.
Perhaps it's time for newly shipped to step in and tackle these issues.
But, Mr. Cavill, I swear.
Honey, I strongly suggest you get your staff under control.
This behavior will not fly under my room.
Understood.
That's all for now.
Been waiting.
Long time.
He's up to something.
And whatever it is, it's gonna turn my life upside down.
Podcatonic, please. Make it strong.
I'm sorry, Ennis.
We're closed for a private event tonight.
Sorry, Sam.
Excuse me.
So, thanks for the seat back there.
No problem.
So, uh, what's going on with you and that gym guy?
He cheated.
With my best friend.
We're divorced now.
I'm staying with Barney.
Just for now.
So, uh, go into another rich man to rework out.
Come as a bitch.
That's not what happened.
But, I have some money I'm fucking out to.
I could be a new sugar daddy.
So, I could be a new sugar daddy.
Go to hell, Clark.
I'm not some gold digging bitch.
Oh, really?
Do you need me to remind you how our breakup went down?
I remember every detail.
You don't know the half of it.
Then tell me, Lois.
Why did you throw everything away from that prick?
I can't tell him the truth.
It destroyed him and ruined his relationship with Barney.
That's what I thought.
You're just left, just like that.
You think that'd be a good idea?
You're everything between us.
I know.
I'm not asking for a serious relationship, okay?
Just something simpler.
No strings attached.
That's insane.
Lois, you owe me.
After everything we've been through?
But I didn't.
His body's couch really that comfortable.
What about the paparazzi?
Will they come sniffing around your place?
I'm under it right here.
I moved in for the exact reason no one knows who I am.
What about the paparazzi?
I'm sniffing around your place.
I'm under it right here.
Okay?
I moved in for the exact reason.
No one knows who I am here.
Alright.
Look, I'll move in with you.
But only temporarily.
You know, if people found out about us,
it could ruin your career.
You know what?
You're right.
I'll just give up this whole celebrity thing now and...
I'm sure to call Barney in fact.
Sorry, stop.
Be serious.
I thought you wanted me to put our relationship ahead of my family.
That's not what I meant, and you know it.
Look, I just...
I don't want to be the reason you lose everything that you work so hard for.
Get out.
I'm good at clown clicker maybe.
I just have one more question.
Just for fun.
I don't want to be the reason
you lose everything that you work so hard for.
You're good at clown clicker.
I just have one more question.
Just for fun.
What if I did while he back?
I'm not in the mood for games.
I need an answer, Lois.
Fine.
All.
I'll take you back the day you went in Oscar.
Happy now.
Challenge accepted.
Let me drive you to work at least.
No, it's fine. I'll get anywhere.
Lus, what the hell are you doing here?
None of your business get lost.
I saw you leaving that guy's house.
What are you shocking out with some random guy now?
I'm staying with a friend, you idiot.
Remember, after you so kindly kicked me out?
Right. A friend.
Once a cheater, always a cheater, Lois.
You've got some nerve-consuming of cheating you lying suck of shit.
You know what?
You're just so desperate to find anyone
and fake life your performance.
Shut the fuck up, Lois.
Sir, please step away.
Hey, why don't you become the idiot?
No, look what you made me do.
Me, you're the one who-
Fuck you, you guys, walk away.
Walk away.
So that's when you should get out of here, Lois.
Hey, sin.
I really appreciate you having my backup.
No problem.
It's not like you left me for a loser or anything like that.
Really, Clark?
You're gonna throw this in my face right now?
Lois, I'm just saying.
You made your choice, and this happened.
You know what, ever, please, I'm getting out.
Mr. Kavil, why would you say something like that?
If it's obvious, you still love her.
Follow her.
Make sure she gets to the office safely.
It's me.
I need you to look into Jim Kirby.
I need to know contacts, movements, everything, no stone left on turn.
Look who finally decided to show up.
I've got a special assignment for you, Lois.
What is it this time?
You're going to be interviewing that smoking hot new singer, Jase Hawthorne.
Oh, and it's live.
Well, look, I'm going to need some time to prepare.
No time.
Here's the list.
Live in five.
Don't screw this up.
Morning, everyone.
I'm Lois Kane, and today we're joined by singing sensation, Jase Hawthorne.
It's great to be here.
Adjust the camera, Lois.
I need a better angle on Jase.
A little lower.
This is perfect, girl.
Stella, are you serious?
I can't ask him these.
They're so inappropriate.
That's the list, Jase approved.
So get the fuck on with it unless you want to get fired or blacklisted from every media outlet
in this city.
So, Jase, rumors are spreading that your last album tanked because you were sleeping around
and partying too much.
Care to comment?
What the hell did you just say?
Why?
You need to see us now.
Did you know about this?
Was this your plan all along to humiliate me on live TV for ratings?
No, I would say.
Save it.
We all saw you messing with that camera.
This is slander.
Stella, please tell them it wasn't my idea.
Grab her.
We're not calling anyone until I get my answers.
Please, let me explain.
I stopped like that.
Mr. Cavill, I swear it was a mistake.
My assistant must have given her the wrong list.
You're fired.
I'm fired.
Grab your things and go.
Please.
Sir, I can't lose this job.
My mom's in the hospital.
That's not my problem.
Get out.
Wait.
It wasn't her fault.
Just give her another chance.
But if anything like this happens, get your both out.
Understood?
There you go.
Thanks again.
Close.
You need to be more careful.
You're way too trusting.
I can get you into some trouble.
Really?
That's what you're going with right now?
Look, I don't need another lecture.
Give us enough, everyone.
I've got an exciting opportunity to announce.
Mr. Clark Cavill will be filming a new documentary.
And he needs one of our journalists to shadow him.
Documenting every moment.
The chosen journalist will live in Clark's house and work alongside him 24-7 until the
documentary is completed.
Afterward, they'll write an exclusive piece on the entire experience.
The close are key to you for the last chance you've been getting heard.
I'll do it, Mr. Cavill.
I'm the perfect choice for this project.
Actually, I've already made my decision.
Lois.
I want you to be part of this project.
Mr. Cavill.
Lois's background is in finance.
I have far more experience.
My decision is final.
Stella.
Ms. Kane.
What do you say?
I know you're trying to protect me.
Do you really think it's a good idea?
Yeah, I do.
So Lois, what's it going to be?
The more time we spend together, the closer Clark might get to the truth about why I broke up with him.
It could destroy his attention with Barney.
I appreciate the offer, Mr. Cavill, but I don't believe I'm the right fit for this project.
Lois, if you don't take this opportunity,
I will hand it to your competition on the silver platter.
Lois, if you pass up this opportunity, I will have no choice but to let you go.
We don't.
We cannot afford to lose this opportunity.
First, the storage room incident, then last night.
There's definitely something going on between us two.
Alright everyone, back to work.
Jim, it's me.
I need a favor.
Get your paparazzi buddies to keep it close.
I'm Clark Cavill.
I think there's a juicy story brewing.