Is it true you do that on your nose?
No, it's not.
It's not what.
Can you explain it in these allegations?
Okay, okay, you guys.
Do you want the real scoop here?
How about the fact that little Mr. Kurt has been cozying up
with some married film industry big wake?
What? That's absurd!
Ms. Kane, is this true?
Who is the mystery guy?
How long has this affair been happening?
He's lying.
It's clearly an attempt to deflect his own infidelity.
Okay, Lois, is that so...
Life proof.
I got a photo of the two lovers caught in the act.
Here's the proof, everyone.
Here's the married big wake that's cozying up with Lois.
She's been sneaking around with the skis ever since we've been married.
Oh God, what if it's Clark?