Hey Clark, hurry up, the show's about to start.
I'm sorry, I got what you're doing.
I'll be fine.
Good luck in there.
Good luck.
I might want to watch the show from here.
Yeah, that would be awesome.
Listen, Lewis, I need to get something off my chest.
I'm sorry.
For what I did back then?
Convincing you to break up with Clark?
Barney, we don't have to do this.
No, please, let me finish.
I thought I was doing what was best for Clark's career.
I never realized how much I was hurting both of you.
Yeah, but look at him now.
He seemed to all work out in the end.
Maybe career wise, but Lewis, I've never seen him as happy as he was with you.
I know it's not my place, but you and Clark, you're meant to be together.