I know it's not my place, but you and Clark, you're meant to be together.
Yeah, but Barney, if he finds out the truth about our breakup, I mean, what will it
do to your friendship?
You're like a brother to him.
And that's exactly why you should tell him.
He deserves the truth, and you both deserve to be happy.
There were so many nights, he'd get drunk and just call out your name over and over.
And during the toughest times in his career, he'd always say, I'm gonna make it big for her.
For Lois, you were his motivation though, even when you weren't there.
Okay Barney, okay you're right.
Look after the ceremony, I'm gonna tell him, I'm gonna tell him, no more running, no more hiding.
Thank you Lois, for fixing the mistake that I made.