She doesn't love you stop lying to yourself. I don't know us once. I love my pride in
security is getting away. I lost her because of it. I will not let that happen again because
of it. I will not let that happen again. I'm choosing to believe in her. I will not let
you stand in the way or anything. Can you believe this guy Lois? He's actually doubling
down on this bullshit. Lois if you're watching this I love you. I always have and I always
will. I will find you. I love you too. Lois if you're watching this I love you. I always
have and I always will. I will find you. If I can't believe him I thought for sure he would
think that you'd run off of him again. You're wrong about Clark and you're wrong about me.
I'll never leave Clark again. Well if I can't settle for destroying your very
little ending with us. I guess I'll just have to settle for you and you. This is your last
chance. Where is Lois? If you don't tell me right now I swear I will never let you work
in this industry again. So I get it. You think you loved him but he's just using you just
like he did with Lois. This one's our hotel. Room 237. Clark Lake to know. Lois. Lois. There's
something you need to know. Last night the doctors came and they ran some tests on you
while you're unconscious and it turns out that I'm pregnant. After all these years I have
a question for you. Will you take me back for good? I hope I have one more question. Anything.
Lois Kate. Of course. Please try to understand Barney was only doing what he thought was good
for your career. Okay he was he never meant to hurt us. I'm gonna need a best man. You
man. Just like in Clarkerville has just been nominated for an Oscar. Sources close to
the bill have made shocking allegations. Although his rekindled romance was Lois
came. What the? Bond to the allegations that Miss Kate is only with you for your money. Those
allegations are completely false. If I mean I have to set the record straight. Years ago
when Clark was starting out I convinced Lois to break up with him. I thought I was doing
what was best for Clark's career. So Lois pretended to fall for a rich man to make Clark
let her go. But the truth is Lois did this out of love. She sacrificed her own happiness
for Clark's success. I've witnessed their love since high school. Please stop these hurtful
rumors. Let them be happy together. They deserve it. No way. No. Jim. Jim please. Let's talk
about this. Lois there's nothing to talk about. This man is just ruined everything. Look I hear
you. Jim this is not the way. Why don't we just discuss what you want. I want you to
work with me in my next movie. Lois. Okay you want to work with me? Let's make it official.
I got a collage rack right here. If you sign it we got a deal. It goes to Clark
Cavill. So much true to receive such a astounding recognition today. This is truly an experience
of a lifetime and it means a lot to me. Thank you. But none of this would have been possible
without one thing and that is the unwavering support of someone very special to me. And
that person and that person is my wife Lois. Lois you happen, my rock, my inspiration,
my everything. And on top of this I also have one more announcement to make tonight. And
that is that's as of today. I'll be officially retiring from acting and I've decided to move
into producing in order to spend more time with my loved ones, my family and overall focus
on the next chapter of my life. That also includes supporting my wife and her new career as a best
selling omelet. Thank you everyone again. Thank you.