So, do you have any questions about my resume?
We have a saying in the fashion world.
You wear who you are, and honestly with your presentation right here,
I feel like I don't even need to read your resume.
Does it remember me from last night? That's a good thing.
But I know I've not majored in fashion.
I apologize for not making myself presentable.
Today, due to personal reasons, but I'm a hard worker and I'm smart.
I graduated top of my class at CalArts.
I understand the creative process.
And I'm not applying for a designer job here, am I?
Isn't it better for your assistant to be more keen on learning and catering to your needs
as opposed to spending the day thinking about how to climb up the corporate ladder?
Unfortunately, wanting to be in the fashion world is a pre-work with it.
So, I am unable to extend you an offer today at this time, Miss.
McCartney, you can call me Nia.
Sure.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Yes. Wait, you drew this.
Today is your lucky day. You're hired.
Miss, wrinkly hoodie and dirty sneakers.