Miss wrinkled hoodie and dirty sneakers.
You know, I should be happy that I got the job, but...
Condescending tongue really gets on my nerves.
I mean, he's not wrong though.
Well, still.
Plus, you could take one look at him and you know he's a playboy,
that he sleeps with random women on a daily basis.
You know, you shouldn't talk about his private life.
He's our boss after all.
Yeah, I should probably tell you something.
I have a boyfriend now.
What?
When?
And most importantly, who is the unbelievably lucky bastard?
You don't know him.
But you're gonna introduce him to me in Qatar, right?
Hello.
Be at that.
Of course.
Mr. Lynn.
My presume.
Been sent here to pick you up on a date.
I was unaware of this, but sure.
Kind of boyfriend you got there, the Prince of England.
Where are we going?
What's wrong?
We didn't see him this last night.
I...
I'll just...
I'm sorry, I'm just a little clumsy.
Look, she's looking for you.