Yeah, we both tend to like the same things.
Nia, to dreams coming true.
To jobs that pay the rent.
Yeah, okay.
I wish you could have been there.
And the girls that work there,
they're all saline.
So beautiful, so fashionable.
You know, I'm not the insecure type,
but it made me feel really so conscious.
What are you talking about?
You are so beautiful, and you are fashionable,
and above all else, you are talented.
I mean, Nia means purpose, right?
And like you said, it's a job that pays the rent.
So you finish my graphic novel at night.
Yeah.
I always need you in my corner.
You're not unique.
Mr. Holzer, I thought you already found a girl
you might hear the other night.
I did.
Something just doesn't feel right.
I can't put my finger on it.
That's the new assistant you just hired.
It looks like we're not making the job demanding enough for her.
We got time for doodles and dates with our boyfriend.
Where is the pitch deck that I asked you to prepare?
I'm supposed to have advice.
Good evening, Mr. Holzer.
To be fair, you said you wanted it to be finished soon.
If you change your mind, I could go back to the office
and finish it tonight.
No, don't go to the office.
Go to my house.