Don't mess it up by dressing like an idiot. Again. How about this one?
No, it's too formal. I mean, you're not going to funeral, right?
No, it's too casual. I mean, it wouldn't even let you down a tennis court right now, huh?
You really don't know how to dress for the occasion, do you?
Hey, I'm just...
I want you to see this new fashion scene. I know. I know. Hey, look. Hey. Yeah
There we go. Oh
Well, it's a good thing that you've got like a natural eye for the beauty and photography and
literature, so you shouldn't think of fashion as this isolated island of a thing, right?
All art forms are connected and plus you look beautiful in everything
everything
Where's your ugly little friend who embarrassed by her pathetic style to show up?
I mean, this isn't really her scene, but she's trying. So I have to try a lot harder than she has.
Anyone want a cupcake?
James, is this part of your line? I love it. It's so modern-day Audrey had burned.
My daughters would wear the hell out of that and the model shall he say is dropped at gorgeous, too.
Oh, it is. It's not.
Mr. Brohem, this is merely one of the ideas Mr. Holzer is testing out.
If you already like this one, your mind will be blown by the rest of the collection. I
can see the seams on your dress. Did you make it yourself? I didn't know that you could sew.
Dumb beginner's luck. Did you change into a...
Let's go to the bathroom. It's gonna be okay. Look, let me just... I don't need you to come to my rescue.
I can do it myself. It is something wrong, Sleen. I'm sorry. It's just that I totally embarrassed myself and you. You just...
You don't even care about fashion. You didn't study it,
but you somehow pull off a modern-day retro scheme out of nowhere. I had help. Cut her healthy. Of course you did.
And of course
you're just always good at whatever you do.
I'm regretting recommending you to work here. I might just be lucky.
Somehow just...
worked. I don't even know what I'm doing.
That's not true. I know you work hard and you have killer instincts.
I'm sorry, okay? Like you totally deserve a thumbs up tonight. And goddamn, you really do look like a modern-day art recap.
How?
Let me help you.
Yeah.
I try.
Sometimes. Why is my heart beating out of my chest? Did I see it right? He thought that electric jolt, too.
I really didn't have to do all the streams.
Although I haven't been made. I've always wanted to come here. Of course.
Happy birthday, Sleen. Is that a new perfume that I smell?
Smells different than the last one.
Yeah. Yeah, I recently switched brands. Look, the old one. Me too.
I just ran out of my last one, but I'm gonna stop.
Sleen, you don't have to be so formal with me. We're not at work. We're all alone.
Where's that carefree girl that I met? Out of miss her. May I have one? Like, oh,
actually, I guess we'll have a bottle. We can handle it, right?
Yeah.
Long day, huh?
I mean, do you think Celine's coming home with a boyfriend though?
Like, who is that guy? If she tells you everything, why didn't she tell you about that?
I know, right? I just hope he's good to her.
Otherwise, he'll have me to answer too. I wouldn't even be here if it weren't for Celine.
I just want to say thanks, Celine, for organizing this awesome party.
You guys are the best present I could ask for.
Cheers.
Now, what do you want to do, birthday girl?
Oh, yeah. There it is.
Before we join them, can I talk to you first now?
Cutter, I've been thinking about this a lot and I want to tell you about it.
It's Nia's birthday. I don't know how to keep her waiting, right?
You okay? You went a little too wild there, birthday girl? You saved my life.
Shit. I'm going to have to repay you for your birthday next month.
You have energy to choke. You're okay.
Let's.
Whoa, okay.
Let's, we'll show you, you met.
Oh, okay.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
We should go.
Uh, check, please, let's go.
Let's wait, let's wait, let's go.
Okay.
Um, why don't you just take a seat?
Whoa, what, what, then you should take some rest.
I'm going to, I'm going to take a shot.
Here we go, shopping tomorrow and having a catch.
No, that spot is actually growing on me.
Out of here, before I kick you out.
God, Cutter, it's you, I'm so sorry.
It was just my reflexes. Why were you so close to me?
I was getting someone on your face, but I mean,
like, who did you think I was, like, out of James?
I'm sorry, Celine.
I feel really tired all of a sudden.
Maybe you should go home tonight,
and I want to make clear about one thing again.
We're still trying this thing out, okay?
Yes, of course.
I'm keeping it casual too.
No labels, just fine.
Good. Good night, Celine.
What did you think I was, like,
James?
Of course not.
Why would I think about James?
Because he's, like, all you ever talk about,
and, I mean, he's clearly into you.
What?
No, I know, he's campy.
Is he?
Great.
Next urgent situation.
Roxy had to drop out of the promo shoot with you today.
Her agent let me know this morning,
because her bill talks went all over.
Do we push it or?
No, no, we can't push it.
We have to get the sum for P Capital.
Is there anybody else that we can reach out to?
It's a simple modeling job.
The footage will be edited anyway.
Maybe we can get one of the girls from the office to do it.
How about Celine?
You're slender and pretty.
Yeah, that would be a great choice.
I remember one of our photographers
mistook her farm model on set once.
That's right, I was there.
Okay, do you think you can do it?
I think so.
You think so.
Okay, we have no time.
Can you please stand up so we can see if the outfits
will fit you like Roxy's body.
Do a spin?
Oh, excuse me, hey, hi.
Yes, you?
If you could please come in here, please.
Thank you.
Jocelyn, let's have her do it.
Mr. Broyam likes her already.
And as I can see, her waist is a little bit smaller.
Yeah, that'll fit better.
Okay, Celine, you're going to assist on the shoot.
Thank you for the spin.
Are you all right?
No, because she has a similar body tucked her up.
I understand.
And I also don't want special treatment just because I'm here.
My what?
Celine, we've talked about this.
I know, but you know that I'm not the kind of girl
that we took all night, like nothing.
I'm not the irresponsible type.
That's why I'm giving this us even a chance, aren't I?
I know, but hey Celine, the makeup people
and the photographer can't decide
on a good pair of earrings for you to wear.
Can I just borrow ears?
You know, good smile.
Of course.
Mr. Holzer, you're here too.
Did I interrupt something?
No, no.
Cut two shots from the list and it goes to the time.
Yes.
Got it, Mr. Holzer.
Come on.
We have a very tight spatula balloon.
Can we have the female model in her first alpha taker
position so we can test the light air in outfit, please?
Yeah, come here, just do this.
This is so crazy.
Can you imagine me, a model?
Go, go, go, go, talk after.
I just like that.
That's how it looks straight out.
My friend has underwear.
Well, I know we were going for provocative,
but I didn't think we were going this far.
I think this is my work, don't you think?
Absolutely smashing.
March is gorgeous.
Okay.
How about you strike a few poses for me?
Stunning.
Perfect.
I love that pose.
Perfect shot.
And James, she is such a natural.
Truly something fast.
Smile.
There we go.
Perfect.
I loved it.
Loving it.
How about James?
How about you join her?
This is just a one sequence,
and I'm looking for an old,
tiny, singing on a rain style dance.
It smiles and all, please, please.
Sorry.
No, no, no.
No, that was great.
Don't be sorry.
Just keep it going, keep it going.
Perfect, yes.
I love this.
Loving it.
Crash into each other.
I love that, yeah.
Okay.
How about one more final spin,
and then let's end on a classic pose.
You grab her by the waist, James.
You lean back near.
I'm loving this.
I really love that shot.
And cut.
Perfect.
So you do dance.
Do you also wear the same perfume as silly?
What?
Oh, that one was H-O-T.
Oh god, I could feel the electricity through the screen.
Now, you two aren't really dating each other in real life.
No, not because I don't want to.
Wait, wait.
I'm not saying I don't want to date him either.
Can we just get back to work?
Is there really nothing going on between the two of you?
Oh, did I just strike a nerve?
No.
Why don't we just go ahead with the second look?
Okay, let's get back to work.
Everyone back to work.
If we feel in a way to replace her placement, there's a way.
I know this wrinkled hoodie and dirty sneakers
is becoming a favorite of his bit too quickly.
Don't you think?
You know, she's supposed to be her friend in all of it.
All of Santa do is get ahead of you.
Yeah, you're supposed to be my friend.
Why do you keep stepping on me?
Let's get along with her, Jim.
I did.
Have you lit?
Now, give me a little jump, both of you.
Can I get an help, please?
Hey.
Okay.
Salim, what happened?
You fell down when you weren't set.
I'm sorry.
Did I ruin the shoe?
No, that's what you're worried about right now?
Well, yeah, it's very important to you, isn't it?
Well, don't worry about the shoe.
Okay, you got hurt pretty badly.
You suffered a mild electric shock and you have a concussion.
Right, look, look, I...
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hey, take it easy.
Here it is.
I'm just a little dizzy and I'm okay.
Salim.
Thank you, Mr. Hoser.
Look, you can call me James and don't thank me.
You just need to be less clumsy.
You can't be getting hurt.
You are very hurt.
I am what?
You're the face of the new collection and I'm going to need you more.
And there have been two instances where your instincts have proven pretty good.
The Audrey Hepburn outfit, the sash that you wore today.
So, I'll be promoting you on the design and editorial side of things.
I know that you never wanted to be in fashion and that you wanted to write your own graphic novel.
Right?
All this promotion will help you...
I'm going to let you cut and took a fall.
Is she alive? Where is she?
She's inside.
She's okay, I think.
She just woke up but I fucked up, cut her.
It's all my fault.
What does that mean?
Did you have something to do with this?
Personally, it's being a fall.
Maybe she would twist your ankle and can't do the shoot anymore.
That's all.
I didn't need to...
She's also a human boyfriend.
You elected you and your best friend for a guy?
I mean, that billionaire douchebag knows this.
It wasn't excellent.
I just wanted to give her a small lesson,
especially since she's openly seducing my boyfriend.
You rushed over here.
All worried about her.
You interrogate me,
writing on your freaking high moral horse.
You've always been in love with her but you're too chicken to tell her.
Now look at you.
You are finally where I was when I had a crush on you back in college.
The one not picked.
The one who stayed close with me just so you can get closer to Nia.
That's sweet, I'm sorry.
No, don't apologize now, okay?
I've moved on from you, cut her.
I'm glad now you know how it felt.
Because as long as there's Nia,
I'll always be reminded that some people are just born the stars of this life thing.
And you and me, somehow we're bound to be their supporting characters.
Can you blame me for trying to come into the foreground in my life?
I still can't let you work.
Selena, I can't let you do that.
Please try.
Have we kissed before?
I've seen that you have your ear spirits but you never wear any earring.
Nia, should I file an occupational hazard lawsuit against Mr. Holzer?
Because Selena just told me that it was an exposed wire that caused her fall on set.
No, Cutter, what are you talking about?
I trip, that's it.
Exposed cable or not, you know me, I trip walking on flat ground.
I'm not going to sue him.
Fine, but Mr. Holzer, she gets her in your eyes.
You won't.
I'm going to sue you.
Um, this is Cutter, my very good friend since college.
Cutter, James Holzer, you know, the boss.
She won't get hurt ever again, I can assure you.
Not on my watch and I will find out who's responsible if that exposed cable.
Okay, well you should go get on that then.
Having you been away from your super important office long enough.
Joss, yes, what is it?
So you knew this aggressive since our college team lost a Duke?
Well, I was worried about you and I felt unfair for you.
I mean, you've done so much for that job and you're in the hospital.
You're instantly too really care about me so much.
Trust me, I'm really fine.
I was actually having a lot of fun being a fashion model before you know this.
I saw you kissing.
Wasn't accident, I went for his cheek and he turned.
Don't you remember that he has a girlfriend?
You're right, but it really wasn't accident.
Did you want to kiss him for real?
I'm a really shitty person, aren't I?
No, we all make mistakes, don't we?
You're not a bad person, you could never be that.
You're actually the most incredible person I know.
Yeah, I wanted to tell you to.
Looks like I forgot my water.
Everybody knew that you had a reputation, a playboy, a heartbreaker and you might think
that that's a good reputation to have but I can tell you right now that it is not.
A good man stays true to the one that he loves and doesn't go around kissing other
people's girls when he already has a girlfriend.
Nia is not your girlfriend and I don't...
Celine is his girlfriend.