Send out a memo, I'm slowing down and no longer works here.
Hey, just wanted to come by and check on you,
and also to let you know that only Fansgate has been taken care of.
You were here.
Yeah, of course I'm here. I'm a friend.
What do you do a year on her day off?
Boss, man.
I'm feeling much better already.
Thank you both for checking in on me.
Weird though, I haven't heard from Celine. Is she working late?
The collection is starting up very soon.
The one that you're the face of.
And if you were up to it, there were a few things on the event plan
that I'd like your input on.
Right now?
No. Are you kidding me?
Nia, you don't have to go with them.
Do you want to go with them?
Maybe it will help me get my mind off things.
Oh, Nia, I hope you know that.
I'll always be there to protect you.
Always.
No matter if it's stalkers, creams, whatever they're writing,
I'll always be there.
What other varieties are there?