You're Celine's boyfriend. We we can't we we shouldn't Celine and I are not in a relationship
I mean we we only went out on two dates. That's it
But Celine seems to really like him though. I I don't know what's going on between you two
relationship or not what matters to me is
She likes you for real
And I promised her I'd stay away from you. So
Let's just keep things strictly professional. Okay, so you're not gonna hear my side of the story
That's fine and just
Do work
Jocelyn booked Tropicana for next week. It's it's party. It's nothing high-end, but because it has the outdoor pool
it
matches the energy of the collection
Okay, James focus on work
It's a very delicate and complicated situation with Celine
Find another time to explain it to her
She smells so good. She's wearing that perfume again
He's so easy so easy so easy
Yeah, get it together. You're here to work