My baby with Jane.
Then again, you guys were even out.
I came to say, this is by all that's happened.
You were my best friend in the whole world.
You helped me through so much.
You were always there for me.
And because I had you, I was too happy to.
And over my head, I never noticed how you felt.
I overlooked you feelings more than once.
I wasn't the best friend you deserved.
And for that, I was worried.
You shouldn't apologize to me and for what I should have done.
But for as bad of a friend as I was,
I still didn't deserve the way you treated me.
You almost electrocuted me.
You creeped on me.
You poisoned me.
You tried to defame me.
You pretended to be me.
I don't think I'll ever be able to forgive you.
And James in a plated boss kind of way.
It might not have been for love, but it was love.
And that's all I came here to say.
Goodbye, sleep.
Have a good one.
Yeah.
No.
I'm in my soul favorite.