What have I done?
Such a mess when you drink.
I remember you slept with me.
I am so sorry for me to do it.
Is it over?
Then I could just wall fight.
He would have on any other day, but he's late too, so, you know, it never happens.
What happened? Did you oversleep?
I went to this hotel room with this guy.
Oh.
Well, mine is, yeah.
It's so wild.
It's so hot.
Oh, God.
I was lost in the hotel room. Damn it.
Oh, well.
Those are custom-made friendship earrings.
I'm a shitty friend.
No, you're not. I get it.
Hot dudes before house.
I'm sure we can get your replacement.
He's here!
Oh.
Morning, Mr. Holzer.
This is Celine.
She had that design and that pitch meeting last week that you liked, and her ear instructions.
She is now in the junior design team.
Wait. It's you.