Don't mess it up by dressing like an idiot again. How about this one?
No, it's too formal. I mean, you're not you're not going to funeral, right?
No, it's too casual. I mean, it wouldn't even let you down a tennis court right now on us, buddy.
You really don't know how to dress for the occasion to you.
Hey, I'm just
Now what use to this new fashion scene? I know. I know. Hey, look. Hey. Yeah
There we go. Oh
Well, it's a good thing that you've got like a natural eye for the beauty and photography and
literature, so you shouldn't think of fashion as this isolated island of a thing, right?
All our friends are connected and plus you look beautiful in everything
everything
Right. Where's your ugly little friend who embarrassed by her pathetic style to show up?
I mean, this isn't really her scene, but she's trying. So I have to try a lot harder than she has.
Anyone want a cupcake?
James, is this part of your line? I love it. It's so modern day Audrey had burned. My daughters would wear the hell out of that
And the model shall we say is dropped it gorgeous too. Oh, it is. It's not
Mr. Broham, this is
Merely one of the ideas. Mr. Holzer is testing out. You already like this one. Your mind will be blown by the rest of the collection. I
Can see the seams on your dress? Did you make it yourself? I didn't know that you could sew
Dumb beginner's look to change into a let's go to the bathroom. It's gonna be okay. Look. Let me just I don't need you
To come to my rescue. I can do it myself. It is something wrong, Sleen. I'm sorry
It's just that I totally embarrassed myself and you you just you don't even care about fashion
You didn't study it
But you somehow pull off a modern day retro scheme out of nowhere. I had help cut her healthy. Of course you did and of course
You're just always good at whatever you do. I'm regretting recommending you to work here. I might just be lucky
Somehow just worked. I don't even know what I'm doing
That's not true. I know you work hard and you have killer instincts
I'm sorry. Okay, like you totally deserve a thumbs up tonight. Thank god damn
You really do look like a modern day article. How?
Here me help you Nia
Try sometimes
Why is my heart beating out of my chest? Did I see it right? He felt that I let drip Joel too. I didn't have to do all the streams
Although I have been mad. I've always wanted to come here. Of course. Have you heard that some blue perfume that I smell?
Smells different than the last one
Yeah
Yeah, I recently switched brands like the old one me too. I just ran out of my last one
So Lane you don't have to be so formal with me. We're not at work. We're all alone
Where's that carefree girl that I met out of miss her? I have one thing. Oh
Actually, I guess we'll have a bottle you can handle it, right?
Yeah
Long day, huh?
I mean do you think Celine's coming home with a boyfriend though?
Like who is that guy if she tells you everything why didn't she tell you about that? I know right. I
Just hope he's good to her
Otherwise he'll have me to answer to what I could be here if it weren't for Celine
I just want to say thanks Celine for organizing this awesome party
You guys are the best president I could ask for
Cheers
Now what do you want to do birthday girl? Oh, yeah
Before we join them can I talk to you for a second?
cover I
Thinking about this a lot and I want to tell you that it's it's Nia's birthday
I don't I don't think we should keep awaying, right?
Are you okay? You went a little too wild there or they girl save my life
I'm gonna have to repay you for your birthday next month
Choke you're okay
We'll show you you met okay
We should go check the least let's go this way this way okay, I want to just take a seat
What I think that you should take some rest. I'm gonna take a shot
Do we go shopping tomorrow and find any catch? No that spot is
Actually growing on me
Oh my god cutter. It's you. I'm so sorry. It was just my reflexes. Why were you so close to me?
I'm sorry Celine. I feel really tired all of a sudden
Maybe you should go home tonight, and I want to make clear about one thing again. We're still trying this thing out
Okay
Yes, of course
I'm keeping it casual too. No labels just on
Good good night, Celine
James of course not
Why would I think about James cuz he's like all you ever talk about and I mean he's clearly into you
Gampy is he great next urgent situation
Roxy had to drop out of the promo shoot with you today her agent
Let me know this morning because her boat talks went all right
Do we push it or no no we can't push it we have to get the sun for peak capital
Is there anybody else that we can reach out to simple modeling job and footage will be edited anyway?
Maybe we can get one of the girls from the office to do it. How about Celine you're slender and pretty
Celine would be a great choice. I remember one of our photographers miss took her farm model on set one
That's right. I was there
Okay, do you think you can do it? I think so you think so
Okay, we have no time. Can you please stand up so we could see if the outfits will fit you like Roxy's body
Do a spin
Oh
Excuse me. Hey, hi. Yes, you you can please come in here, please. Thank you
Jocelyn let's have her do it. Mr. Broyam likes her already and as I can see her waist is a little bit smaller
Yeah, that'll fit better. Okay, so we you're gonna assist on this shoot. Thank you for the spin
Are you all right?
Knee of the model because she has a similar body tucked her up. You understand and I also don't want special treatment just because I'm here
My what? Celine we've talked about this. I know but you know that another kind of girl who took all night
Like nothing. I'm not that you're responsible type. That's why I'm giving this
Us even a chance aren't I? No, but Celine on the makeup people and the
photographer can't decide on a good pair of earrings and you to wear. Can I just borrow your ears, you know?
Yes, of course
Mr. Holzer you're here, too
Did I interrupt something? No, no
Pat two shots from the list and
It was a time. Yes. Got it. Mr. Holzer. Come on. We have a very tight spatula
Can we have the female model in her first outfit take her position so we can test the light air in outfit, please
Yeah, come here. Can't you do this?
This is so crazy. Can you imagine me a model go go go talk after?
He makes eyes like that
That's how it looks straight out. My friend has underwear
Well, I know we were going for provocative, but I didn't think we're going this far. I think this is my work. Don't you think?
Absolutely smashing. March is gorgeous. Okay. How about you strike a few poses for me?
Stunning. Perfect. I love that pose. Perfect. She is such a natural truly something
Smile
Perfect. I love it. We're loving it. How about James? How about you? How about you join her?
This is just a one sequence and I'm looking for an
Old timey singing on a rain style dance with smiles and all please please
Sorry, no, no. No, that was great. Don't be sorry. Just keep it going. Keep it going. Perfect. Yes
I love this loving it crashing to each other
Okay, how about oh
one more
final spin and then let's end on a classic pose you grab her by the waist James you lean back near
I'm loving this. I'm loving this
And cut
Perfect
So you do dance do you also wear the same perfume as silly?
What?
Oh, that was H-O-T
Oh god, I could feel the electricity through the screen now. Are you two aren't really dating each other in real life? No
Not because I don't want to
Wait, wait. I'm not saying I don't want to date him either. Can we just get back to work? Is there really nothing going on between the two of you?
Oh, did I just strike a nerve? No
Why don't we just go ahead with the second look? Okay, let's get back to work everyone back to work
We
Feeling a way to replace her placement
There's a way
What? I know I know this wrinkled hoodie and dirty sneakers is becoming a favorite of his
I have to quickly
Don't you think? I mean, I know she's supposed to be her friend and all but all of saying her do is get ahead of you
Yeah, you're supposed to be my friend. Why do you keep stepping on me? Let's go home for him
I did
Give me a little jump both
Thank god, okay, so leave what what happened you fell down when you're on set
I'm sorry. Did I ruin the shoe? That's what you're worried about right now. Well, yeah, it's very important to you, isn't it?
Don't worry about the shoe. Okay. You got hurt pretty badly. You suffered a mild
Electric shock and you have a concussion
I'm all right. Look. Look. Hey, take it easy here. It's
I'm just a little dizzy. I'm okay
Celine
Thank you. Mr. Hoser. Look, you can call me James and
Don't thank me
You just need to be less clumsy. You can't be getting hurt. You are very
I am
What? You're the face of the new collection
And I'm going to need you more and there have been two instances where your instincts have proven
Pretty good the Audrey Hepburn outfit
The sash that you wore today
So
I'll be promoting you on the design and editorial side of things
I know that you never wanted to be in fashion
And that you wanted to write your own graphic novel, right? All this promotion will help you
It is
She got to let you cute and took a fall. Is she alive? Where is she? She's inside. She's
Okay, I think
She just woke up but I fucked up cuz
It's all my fault. What does that mean? Do you want this?
Personally to be a fall
Maybe she would twist your ankle and can't do the shoot anymore. That's all I didn't wait to
It's also your boyfriend
Celine
You elected you did your best friend for a guy. I mean that billionaire douche bagel
It was an accident. I just wanted to give her a small lesson especially since she's openly seducing my boyfriend
You rushed over here. All worried about her. You interrogate me writing on your freaking high moral horse
You've always been in love with her but you're too chicken to tell her
Now look at you
You are finally where I was when I had a crush on you back in college
The one not picked
The one who stayed close with me just so you can get closer to Nia
I'm sorry. No, don't apologize now. Okay. I've moved on from you cutter
I'm glad now. You know how it felt
Because as long as there's Nia, I'll always be reminded that
Some people are just born the stars of this life thing
And you and me
Somehow we're bound to be their supporting characters
Can you blame me?
For trying to come into the foreground in my life. I still can't let you work
Celine, I can't I can't let you do that. Please try. Have we kissed you?
I've seen that
You have your ears pierced but you never wear any earrings
Nia
Should I file an occupational hazard lawsuit against Mr. Holzer because Celine just told me that
It was an exposed wire that caused her fall on set
No
Cutter, what are you talking about? I trip. That's it
Exposed cable or not. You know me. I trip walking on flat ground
I'm not gonna sue him
Fine
But Mr. Holzer if she gets her in your office
I'm gonna show you
Um
This is
Cutter my
Very good friend since college
Cutter
James Holzer
You know
The boss
She won't get hurt ever again. I can assure you
Not on my watch and I will find out who's responsible if that exposed cable, okay
Well, you should go get on that then
Having you been away from your super important office long enough
Joss. Yes. What is it?
See you knew this aggressive since our college team lost a Duke. Well
I was
Worried about you and I felt unfair for you. I mean you've done so much for that job and
Now you're in the hospital
Here in Celine
Do you really care about me so much?
Trust me
I'm really fine
I was actually having a lot of fun being a fashion model
Before you know
This
I saw you kiss him
That
Was an accident. I
I went for his cheek and he turned. Oh, you remember that he has a girlfriend
You're right. I
But but it really was an accident
Did you want to kiss him for real? Oh
I'm a really shitty person, aren't I? No
We all make mistakes. Don't we?
You're not a bad person. You could never be that
You're actually the most incredible person I know
Yeah, I wanted to tell you to
It looks like I forgot my water
Everybody knew that you had a reputation
A playboy
A heartbreaker
And you might think that that's a good reputation to have but I can tell you right now that it is not
A good man
Stays true to the one that he loves
And doesn't go around kissing other people's girls when he already has a girlfriend
Nia is not your girlfriend and I don't
Celine is his girlfriend
I don't know