I feel like an old sickly lady.
Well, the last F in BFF is forever, isn't it?
So, when we're both old and sickly, we might end up talking here just like right now.
Celine, I really didn't know you and James were dating.
The kiss really was an accident.
When did you guys start dating the night at the bar?
I know accidents happen.
We don't have to talk about it.
I know about James' history and his reputation.
But, Nia, will you promise me one thing though?
Promise me you won't steal him from me.
He's everything I've always wanted.
Oh.
People actually like being here?
Apparently.
Welcome back.
There's no one else I'd rather see.
Could it be a cutter?
Nia, can you come here, please?