I was wondering how she got the promotion. There's our answer.
Slut.
And she has the quality of being a slut, but is she hot enough to have an only fancy?
I'm just gonna pay for average.
Hot me.
Mr. Holzer, I am so sorry about this, okay? I did not vet her enough when we hired her.
She's gonna make the entire JH brand look like a joke or worse, low class?
Wait, are we gonna start attracting strippers and prostitutes to our collection now?
I hired her.
And she's the face of the new collection.
So if you're laughing at her, you're laughing at all of us, and at me.
Is there any laughing at me? The investors probably haven't seen the email.
You need to go to tech to make sure that they wipe them all out.
And I won't get through the bottom of this because I know that you're doing it.
It's still taking your side.
Nia, it's not time to hide, so don't you want to figure out who did this to you?