Did you find her?
No.
It's like she disappeared off the face of the earth.
She won't return any of my calls.
James fired her so she won't be at work anymore.
I'm in such a conflicted state because she broke my fucking heart.
Yet at the same time, my heart is full because I'm with James.
Celine braided me too.
For being a coward.
For not telling you how I actually felt about you.
But truthfully, I think you've always known.
You want to stay friends?
You don't want things to get awkward.
And, you know, I want the same.
So no more awkwardness.
You know, no more one-sided feelings.
At least I'll try to stop them from now on.
Come on.
Come on, a big hug for an old friend.
That way we don't have to talk about this anymore.
I mean, God, that was painful.
I do love you, Patrick.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
You okay?
What's going on?
Oh, we should go.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Positive.
I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God.
Oh, there's my way.