I have another job for you.
You'll be needing this?
Laurent!
Major shareholder.
My father listens to him,
and Victor needs to gain his trust to solidify his status to see you.
He's having one of his private parties tonight.
All of the Garrison family big wigs will be there.
You'll be going with Victor.
Your job?
Get close to Laurent.
Find out all the big projects that Victor hasn't picked up on yet,
and in return,
I'll get you. You're two million back.
Hi, Victor.
I need you as my plus one tonight.
Laurent is hosting. I'll text you the details.
Be ready in an hour.
Yeah, sure thing. I'll see you there.
Just, uh, watch yourself.
Laurent has a reputation. He's not the most respectful guy.