What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm going to do the file, urgent.
The doctor said painting could help with your recovery.
You run a coma for so long that you'll need to rebuild your memories step by step.
Just paint whatever comes to mind.
I know. I kept having this dream of something when I was in the coma.
It had this, like, weird shape, like a symbol or something.
Can't look.
The Garrison family crust?
What did you say?
Jane, what is this that you just painted?
I don't know, actually. It just came into my mind.
I have a big sense of having seen it somewhere, but...
Do you know anyone from the Garrison group?
Which Garrison family?
You mean the one who owns the famous Garrison group?
Everyone knows them.
No.
Jane, be serious. Have you ever met anyone from the Garrison family?
Of course not.
Have you seen this anywhere?
Yes, but I think I know who it belongs to.
What were you thinking? Why would you jump in if you can't swim? Are you nuts?
Creating mom's oatmeal raisin cookies.
I miss mom and dad, but at least we have each other.
We just need to focus on looking forward.
I know. I'm so glad I have you, Kim.
You know what? Why don't I go down to the cafeteria and see if they have any cookies?
I'll be back in 10 minutes, okay?
It's only been 10 seconds, Kim.
Victor Garrison.
I have a man here who tried to kill my sister.
We've got him cornered at the central hospital.
He's also connected to a murder.
What are you doing here?
Need a place high from Olivia?
Seriously?
I haven't been keeping up. Very close. I am your sister.
I heard somebody tried drugging her.
It must have been Victor.
You need to find a safe place for your sister.
Jane is asleep.
Thank you.
What do you think about the accident?
I don't know all the details, but Victor is dangerous.
If he feels sorry, he'll do anything.
What makes you so sure of this?
I'm pretty sure he's the reason my mom died.
My mother wasn't what most people think.
Victor's mom had post-partum depression and after that, my dad got remarried and had me.
When I was 12, we got in a fight and she came out looking for me.
She was looking for me and she fell down a slope.
I was right there at the bottom and saw everything.
The rocks, and there was one more thing too.
There was a boy who was thick.
After that, my father had blamed me for my own mother's death.
It's reveal everything at the wedding.
It's my honor to present Victor Garrison as the new president of the Garrison Group.
Thank you, everyone.
It's an honor.
I'm ready to take this coming from new heights.
So as you all know, I've been involved with some financial fraud and even murders.
I, uh, script.
Why did you try to kill my sister?
I don't know anymore.
Stop acting so innocent, Victor.
You're a man confessed on the spot.
You sent him to kill my sister.
Victor Garrison, you're under arrest.
We found a Garrison family crest with your fingerprints on it in a wrecked car.
Don't come any closer.
I swear I'll kill her.
You may have spotted that car accident, but you're not going to get lucky this time.
You killed my parents and almost my sister because of me.
Why do you want me dead?
What?
You're dead.
So I was right about the family scandals.
Just let her go, Victor.
I'm right here.
I'll just let her go.
Shh.
Another pawn.
A real scheme.
Another woman whose life is in danger because of your existence.
What are you talking about?
Why do all of this?
Because I hate you, Damien.
Hey, you and your entire family and your mother?
I pushed me on that day myself.
Oh, it was you.
I knew it.
Yeah.
I was there that day.
I made sure she didn't come back in that fall.
Now another woman's life is in danger because of your existence.
Pushed her off the glue.
Kim get hurt because of me, Victor.
I'll give you everything my life, my fortune.
Please just let her go.
You think you can buy me off?
It's too late for that.
I know why you hate me.
It's because of your mother.
Today I talk about my mother.
You think your mother killed herself because of me?
I took her own life because of postpartum depression.
She loved you very much.
But she was unhappy.
My mother died because she had me.
Kim.
You're the true heir to our family's legacy.
I hereby declare Damien as the sole heir to the Garrison fortune.
Is it any chance for us?
Good things be different?
Are we asking that?
Look around.
What do you think?
All right.
I see that that was not really a competition.
I should have no better.
You know, Olivia, I never really saw it as a competition.
We all deserve better lives.
And I hope you find what you're looking for.
Thanks.
I'll set off our abroad.
Good luck to both of you.
You're doing great.
I mean, pretty soon you'll be walking just like you were before.
You couldn't have done this without you.
Thank you for everything.
Hey, what's up?
Kim.
How are you?
You know how I am.
I'm jobless and broke.
Stop joking.
You're a mega influencer.
Try logging into your account.
It was unlocked.
And check your bank account.
There's two million dollars coming in.
Thank you.
That is very generous.
Oh, Kim don't.
I was a jerk.
Sorry.
But really, you should thank Damien Garrison.
He's a real deal with a big heart.
Speaking of Damien, I'd like to invite him to my first show back.
It's time we clear the Garrison controversy once and for all.
To sum it all up, Victor Garrison has been arrested for falsifying financial reports.
And there are Damien's new leadership.
The Garrison crew is moving towards integrity.
If you're interested, come to Grandview Villa and find me.
I want you to be seen in front of the Garrison.
Together, we can make a huge impact.
How much do you offer?
Let's see if you'll get market rates.
That's my girlfriend.
You get anything you want to just ask.
Sounds like a plan.
And then...
We got there in my trust first.
I was the challenge.
You want me to throw myself into the pool again?
No.
I'll teach you as well.