Ladies and gentlemen, introducing our uniquely fashionable bride.
Mom, control yourself. She must have her reasons.
This is our wedding day, and an important ceremony for the Grayson family.
Let's keep our poise.
As matriarch, I make the first sacrificial cut.
Back on this porch.
I'm sorry if I was rude earlier.
I didn't know David had a brother.
I'm sorry, let me formally introduce myself to take the pancreas.
Formal introduction.
What? You already had an informal one?
Relax, bro. I'm here on a serial murder case.
Several clues led me here.
Oh, Julie, your new daughter-in-law is quite different.
Growing up in such an unsavory environment, it's not her fault.
She has this taste.
I want to wish you a choke on that cake.
Julie, are you all right?
Where'd somebody get her some jolly hoes?
Oh, but it's chocolate!