It's just me.
What's got the best bartender in the state so out of sorts today?
You weren't at my wedding yesterday.
Sorry, I just got my test results back yesterday.
The doctor said unless some sort of miracle happens,
I'll never be able to have kids.
Oh my God.
You went through all that alone yesterday?
I didn't want everyone here wedding.
Is there any chance that perhaps they mixed up
and gave you the wrong report?
Hello.
What?
Doctor, are you serious?
Hey, I found this.
My notebook. Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Something between you two.
Definitely.
Where'd you get that?
My mom gave it to me.
Hey Ian, the murder scene at your wedding had a pentagram
just like the one on this tarot card.
What are you saying?