I heard your mom got arrested. I waited up for you all night. Are you okay?
I'm better. No. Thanks Hank. He stayed up with me at the precinct. Sorry. I'm really tired. I just need to lie down.
Sure. I just think it's too bad. I wasn't the one there for you last night.
Who do you think reported my mom as a suspect?
What? Hank did mention that they received a call and had to be someone at the wedding.
Vivian, there's something you should know about Hank.
Hank didn't grow up with the gracens because of some issues between my father and his mother.
He's always had a habit of taking things from me. Like what?
Baseball caps. Even my first girlfriend. No matter what it is,
you would always show up around the things that mattered to me.
It sounds like Hank has issues. Interesting though that you would refer to your girlfriend's as things.
Hey, did you talk to me? Did you mind that you were with me last night?
Why are you so concerned about Davin's feelings? Am I just a pawn and your brotherly feud?
Hello?
My princess. That hasn't changed in a thousand years.
I'm downstairs. You have to let me know what's going on.
I promise I could explain everything.
Hey, I didn't think you'd show.
I need you to tell me about Davin's ex-girlfriend.
Are you sure you want to talk here? My cars are annoying.
No. If I don't like what you're saying, I can go right back inside.
Davin's first girlfriend came onto me without even mentioning him.
My family, the gracens, they're magical royalty.
The gracens legacy stretches on for centuries, a family known for their extraordinary power.
Legend says that the king gets his power from sacrificing his first bride in a dark ritual.
That's insane. How are they allowed to keep doing this?
Because mere legend, everything's hidden behind veils and sealed behind doors.
What about you? You're a gracen.
Yeah, the illegitimate son had no magical powers.
Davin's ex thought that I would be able to help her get what she wanted.
And then she dumped you.
Yeah. When she found out I had no powers, I never saw her again.
You don't seem surprised by this whole wizard thing.
Why would I be? I'm a witch who can speak her desires into existence.
Well, you have an admirer. Can you at least give me a little smile? A little one? For me?
So you happy with me lady witch?
You are my brother-in-law.
You must know now that your wedding was a sham.
Well, Davin has been acting different since the wedding, but I can't get into a new relationship while I'm still married to him.
So stop your wedding.
No, your wedding was actually a sham.
Oh my God! Davin, stop!
Gee, in my house with this bastard, you slut.
Watch your mouth when you talk to her.
She's my wife.
Always after what's mine. A rat scavenging for crumbs just like your absent mother.
I wasn't ever after anything that was yours. She was never yours.
Your wedding was a demonic ritual in disguise. Did you even want to marry her?
What? Our wedding was a demonic ritual?
My family business is none of your concern, outsider.
I played it straight with her, unlike you.
You're walking away with lies. Sure you won't do this.
What is that?
It's a wizard-dual talisman. In three days, we duel to the death.
Oh. So you do feel pain, big hero?
There's a lot you don't yet understand, Davin.
Oh, you wizards and your secrets.
All wizards know that to inherit power, there has to be a ceremony to sacrifice the bride.
It's no secret.
So my wedding day?
I heard you and Davin were getting married.
So I got drunk wanting to cause a distraction, but I ended up kissing you instead.
I guess I couldn't help myself.
Couldn't help yourself. Sounds like you planned the whole thing.
I wouldn't dare.
I still remember you telling me about kicking my balls into the back of my throat.
Since I can desire things into existence.
I'm beginning to feel a touch envy towards you.
That was, that was crazy.
Yeah.
The wish-granting witches indeed power.
Who are you?
An ally, much stronger than you foolish son.
Are you here to fight for her?
You can have her body for your sacrifice. I only need her power.
What are you? How can you absorb a witch's power?
Ready to die, bastard.
Bring in a wand to a duel, really?
Says the person who doesn't have one.
Just like your mother.
Always getting in over your head.
I'll leave my mother out of this, she worthless prick.
Join her and hell then.
Kill yourselves.
Make anything that threatens their lives disappear.
The legend is true. The chosen witch.
Alright, that's not the duel's over. Leave.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. I'm a powerful witch, remember.
Leave in your power, it is astonishing.
There has been very concern.
You're concerned about how powerful I am?
No.
About what others might do to take that power away from you?
Is it me you desire?
Or is it my power?
This game when you literally just woke up.
Didn't sleep much to begin with.
Does this mean where I'm off?
Keep dreaming.
Because I love this dream way too that much.
I'm here to get my things.
You're still my wife.
Our wedding was a demonic ritual.
Find another wife.
Well, look who's back.
The bastard and the cheating wife.
What a perfect match.
Enough, Mom.
As the future wizard king, you'll have your fair share of embarrassment.
Might as well get used to it with this...
HAG.
Goodbye, Julie.
Oh, you know that exclusive champagne that you just adore?
It's sold at a farm five miles up the road for a fraction of the price.
I believe the locals call it Hillbilly Bubbly?
Let's be civil, Vivian.
I believe we can make a deal that benefits both of us.
What deal did you have in mind?
They never pressed any charges, right?
I tell you what, use your power to help me become the wizard king.
And I'll get your mom out of jail.
Don't listen to their lies.
This has nothing to do with you, Hank.
I'm not going to stand here and let you expose your powers.
You know how dangerous that is.
If you weren't a contender for the throne,
then I would buy your act of self-righteousness.
What?
I thought you didn't have any magic powers.
You know what?
This family is nothing but liars.
Vivian, let me explain.
Vivian!
Once, Wizard World, picks you.
You shall never escape.
Get out!
I've had enough of you, you old witch!
Hank!
What are you doing?
What else do you think?
We are Wizard World.
Whoever you are, give me one reason not to kill you.
Whoa!
I thought you were.
Don't.
Oh yeah, and if your path to the throne is secure.
Oh, did I hurt your feelings?
That's too bad.
I thought Wizard Kings didn't have any feelings.
Hey, on that bun me!
Great!
What?
I know you don't want to help me become king,
or probably even see me,
but your mother is innocent.
Let's go bail her out together.
Why should I trust you?
You probably shouldn't.
But I promise I'm here in good faith.
Can you please give me a chance to make it right?
Vivian, what did you promise him?
Relax.
It doesn't matter what she promises me.
You'll never get the throne.
Will you two please just shut up?
You let spelled in work.
Are you not human?
Lives taken by demons can't be revived.
Alright.
Then I will abuse the prophecy and send this demon back into the abyss.
Then I will abuse the prophecy and send this demon back to the abyss.
Ready, add to an vernum, don't nail an ass!
Your powers work on demons?
Do you feel weird after using that curse?
I don't care.
If I had known how to handle that demon earlier,
my mother would not be dead.
Great magic.
Comes great side of my soul.
I'm tired of your advice.
I can teach you how to control your magic.
Use this.
And draw the pentagram from your mother's tarot cards.
Do this.
And you can kill whoever or whatever you so desire.
Vivian, is enough of that.
Get lost.
I live my own life.
And what are you to me?
Why do you care?
I'm your lover.
A lover.
I am alone in this world.
Hey, hot stuff.
Why so sad?
Why come with us?
We've got just what you need.
Fine.
Let's go then.
Vivian, let's go.
I'm so sorry for everything.
It was in your fault, Vivian.
Mom always said, don't rush into getting married.
Don't rush into getting married.
And I did it anyway.
Now that she's...
There's no way you could have known.
Vivian, I know what you're going through.
I know what it's like to lose a mother.
What happened to your mom?
My family's bound by the rules of wizard loyalty.
I was a child born out of wedlock.
And my mom.
She was killed by the wizard king, right?
My dad sacrificed her.
So that he could become king.
Hey, someone anonymously reports that Vivian may have committed murder.
And a state of mental disorder.
It's a lie.
Dear you.
What are you doing here?
Vivian, you didn't use that thing.
That thing I gave you yesterday, did you?
What thing?
That thing.
Oh, you mean that old wooden stick that you call a wand?
Old wooden stick.
That's an ancient heirloom.
A treasure of wizard royalty.
I used it as firewood.
One wizard's treasure is another which is trash.
But you had accepted the wand.
It means you still believe in me deep in your heart, doesn't it?
Boss, what are they talking about?
I think we could all see who's having the manic episode here.
Detective, will you please remove this trespasser from my home?
Is that so?
So the victims haven't been identified.
The victims have been found in question.
Slightly injured in a powerful clay attack.
They seem to be thinking they've fallen from drinking too much.
That's good news.
What are we?
Vivian, you have no idea how I worried about you.
Worried?
You were just trying to frame me.
You have to believe me.
I was trying to protect you from making a mistake.
I will wait for you to understand.
Alright, that's enough.
You want to wait?
You need to know the thousands of years.
Get out.
David, no one to quit.
Nobody wants this.
You show yourself.
Now I can avenge my mother's death.
A little girl.
You shouldn't hate me.
So you can talk.
Your mother said I was a demon.
Demons only kill witches if they've made a pact.
Then who?
Who did you make a pact with?
That doesn't matter.
What matters is that I'm here to take your life.
The dagger doesn't scare you, but a teeny tiny alcohol swab does?
As terrified of losing, you mean more to me than you look.
I've been trying to piece together my dreams.
My mom said they were my destiny.
Have you come to any conclusions?
No.
After you kissed me at my wedding, my life has been a mess.
I dreamt of it before it happened.
It was the same happening to you.
My ancestors were wizards.
My past life very well.
I missed you terribly today.
Art for a new life.
Feels like century.
We were lovers.
I'm sorry.
I...
I need to get away.
What?
Vivian.
Love for a thousand years is too much for me.
I don't want to get hurt again.
I can't wait.
I'm quite good at it.
What?
It's a pity you can't kiss on yourself.
You should trust your body.
It doesn't lie.
Did you really get hurt?
Because you seem strong and don't think now.
Only my pride would fit it.
The paper would come early?
It's not the paper.
Your prince put the spatula down first.
Your hands are better suited, wrapped around money.
Breakfast could be conjured up with magic.
Well, maybe I'll start with dessert.
What's wrong?
A damn letter, cut my hand.
This is a challenge from the Grayson family for you.
A challenge?
Will Devon and Julie ever stop?
I mean, didn't we just have a duel a few days ago?
A duel has winners and losers.
A challenge is about life and death.
Everyone in the wizard royal family is combative.
Peace can never be found in places away from the center of power.
What?
No wonder what?
No wonder Vivian left a thousand years ago to seek the power of true love far away.
She had.
In the Imperial city, her love was just a foolish joke.
Well, putting matters of a thousand years ago aside,
like it's important I stay by your side to keep you safe.
Consessive proofs.
Proof of what?
Your cohabitation application.
Okay.
I am going to buckle down and diligently practice my witchcraft.
Oh my God.
A witch calling out to a god holding a devil's book.
You know, the only one to do so.
I've always been a unique one, haven't I?
Vivian, you're talent shine brighter than you ever know.
Oh, I thank you, Hank.
But I still do not understand what those headache-inducing pentagrams were for at my wedding.
Wait.
That's not right.
Not right?
What's not right?
The pentagram and the book has a circle around it.
In police files of past pentagram murder serial cases,
there's always a circle around it.
But strangely...
What?
Strangely, the murder scene at your wedding didn't have a circle around it.
So the killer randomly decided to change his method on a whim?
Maybe the case that your wedding was specifically targeted for you.
They were after me, but why?
I mean, I may occasionally kick a random drunk guy at the bar in the nuts,
but I haven't even killed a spider.
Because Vivian, you're powerful and unique.
I think I'd rather be ordinary.
Don't kill yourself, you're far from ordinary.
No ordinary bartender would drop kick a drunk guy in the nuts
and then rip up her wedding dress and walk out in jeans.
You're far from ordinary.
I swear that wedding dress ripped by itself.
Right, F.
There's something I've been thinking about for a thousand years.
There must be a big thought.
Vivian, ages ago, you got the power of true love through sacrifice.
Now you get it from my kiss.
Maybe this is just another trap.
I don't understand.
How can a gift be a trap?
Because you could get it on your own.
You don't need any triggers.
Just like you deserve love without anyone's validation.
You have no idea what a jealous of me
because I was able to get a grace in you.
But no one has ever told me that I deserved it.
You deserve better.
Challenge-driven issues become new.
A challenge is all this ungrateful slung girl needed.
If you had listened to me earlier, she would have been sacrificed already.
I'm not interested in your challenge, Devon.
I'm just here to learn the truth about my mother's death.
I swear I'm completely innocent.
Still, I can't help but resent your magical prowess
and the way my stepbrother stole you.
Everyone has their own unique abilities.
Devon, you have your own strengths.
There is no need to hunger for others.
How profound.
I never knew a bar maid could be so wise.
Oh, that crewness before just an act.
I'm not here to argue with you.
I just want to know why a figure in a black cloak keeps trying to kill me.
I summoned it.
I signed a contract with it.
What?
Today, you're both doomed.
How complete, Devon's succession ritual.
So fast.
Banish the demon.
Or save your true love.
I always have improved, but you are no match.
What did you expect?
Mom, how could this be?
You.
How are you still alive?
Alive.
I'm not.
I clawed my way out of hell.
Where were you?
How...
You became a demon?
Years ago, the old wizard king tricked me into having me.
I didn't know he only wanted a child to sacrifice.
Couldn't let her once I found out.
So they threw me into the fire because they knew I wouldn't let that happen.
Crude rivalry is standard among the royal elites.
Sadly, your mailing example of what it's like to fail.
Respect him.
How about you taste if links yourself?
Go to hell!
My magic.
It's gone!
My mother is dead.
And all of you will join her.
Mom, what are you doing?
Killing the woman behind you.
Her energy will bring me back to life.
I deal with the devil.
Murdering my true love.
Have you ever stopped to think about me?
Your son?
Fine.
If I were a mistake, you'd think wish me.
But stay away from Vivian.
Yes.
I'd like to report some criminal activity.
Detective Hank, this better be important.
What?