So what is it, exactly that you want?
I want to be Davin's rightful queen.
That's impossible.
Why?
It was me who stood by you during the ceremony.
And it was me who followed the royal family.
Even the power that this child has, I got from that witch.
I earned the title of queen.
Young lady, the power of the witch is not something
that the wizard royal family is willing to forego easily.
However, should you give birth to the child,
we will gladly extend our favor to you.
And if I refuse, if you behave,
you might be able to keep the title of the prince's mother.
Otherwise, you will be left with nothing.
We've been looking in the wrong place.
What do you mean?
This whole time that we got Davin and his mother
were responsible for the murders at the wedding,
but we can never find any evidence.
What if it wasn't them?
Who else could it be?