Sorry to interrupt your honeymoon.
It's fine.
Why is the analysis taking so long?
Is this the evidence you brought from the Grayson ruins?
Yeah.
We've been there several times and we've
found nothing but broken stones.
Well, maybe it was just really well hidden.
Are the results done?
I think I need new glasses.
So, Linda's the murderer.
Her fingerprints were found at several crime scenes.
All weddings.
Does she seem to hate weddings or something?
I don't know.
She seems like a good job, man.
Let's go.
Vivian.
Congratulations, Vivian.
The evidence has emerged.
Even clear of all charges.
More like congratulations to Detective Hank
for getting his job back.
It's all right, man.
First day back, can you still have time to drop me home?
For you?
Mm-hmm.
It's me, Detective.
Stay here, bullets.
What happened?
Normally, it looks like a bear rampaged in through here.
Roll it.
What?
Do you want to make it get bad?
Stop.
I didn't realize you were so bad.
No, no.
Stop.
I, um, I did a good job cleaning.
Since when does Hell's messenger double as a cleaning lady?
Were you waiting for us?
I'm here to warn you.
What is this?
Is this what Linda really wants?
Linda's extremely dangerous.
The murder at your wedding was the last step of her plan.
What plan?
Linda completed this sacrifice and successfully conceived.
The power of Davenen's mother is flown to her.
And she's now the strongest wizard in the world.
And royalty at that.
Be careful.
Is it just me or is your mother suddenly seeming human?
Vivian.
She just tried to kill you, didn't she resent her?
What are you thinking about?
I just realized I haven't felt this comfortable in the long time.
People in my sadness were in a heat.
The heel with their magic is it.
What are you doing?
Cut it out.
Cool!
Serves you right for not wanting to take off your shirt.
Now we both have to change.
You can't worry about changing later.
One last thing.
If you are to become a wizard king, you might need this.
We'll help off.
Maybe a little warning next time.
If you don't like this, it will help you against Linda.
Without power.
I'm starting to think it really sucks to be king.
Don't worry.
I'm used to people trying to kill me.
Let's leave.
What?
Let's leave before things get messier.
We're already on the run to keep you from bringing branded as a fugitive on false charges.
Now that your name's cleared, let's just get out of here.
But Hank, you have a job here that you love and our memories.
You really want to leave all that behind?
Calm down.
It was a misunderstanding.
I'm happy Vivian's name is cleared.
A happy wizard prince who wanted me dead.
What do you want now?
Vivian, I'm about to become the king.
You don't have to be sacrificed by the royal family anymore.
I...
Commence that.
Just be my queen.
If you say yes, you can have anything you want.
Can I ask the wizard royal family for a different prince?
He's lying.
Do not trust those wizards.
Vivian, what happened?
Vivian, wake up.
She only suffers when she's with you.
Let her go.
Damn it.
What did you do to her?
I'm warning you.
You stay away from us.
Did you give in that voice?
Voice?
No.
I didn't hear anything.
What are you talking about?
What voice did you?
No, it was my voice except it didn't sound like me now.
It sounded far away like I don't know.
Could it be your past self trying to warn you?
We're not leaving.
Why not?
This place is dangerous.
Where else in the world isn't happened to my past self?
I need to get back my powers.
You're playing with fire, Vivian.
Fair enough.
We'll stay here in Batterton to see where the troops land.
Vivian, be my queen.
You'll get closer to the truth than you ever were.
If Vivian has to become a queen to learn the truth, then I officially challenge you to the throne.
Your act seems even more vicious than mine.
Women.
Hm.
With such a tough opponent, are you still going for the throne?
Absolutely.
Just for me.
And the throne on one's coveted.
I know you're no longer the closed book I met a few weeks back.
Well, being with you's made me realize I don't have to be shameful of who I truly am.
But what exactly is the wizard royal family and if we go for the throne, do we have a chance?
The wizard royal family is ruthless.
They sacrifice their own children and witches to trade for demons with power.
That seems overly cruel.
Yeah.
Unless selfish people who try to rise up by sacrificing others are recognized by the spirits,
and only the cold blooded and merciless can make them few.
Now, something doesn't seem right.
What do you mean?
If our memories are correct and a thousand years ago you married a queen who could bless
her people, why then should you still need to sacrifice others?
That is strange indeed.
Hm.
Let's stay around here and try and figure out what went wrong with the wizard royal family
over the past millennium.
I'm also curious about a queen for a thousand years ago, and what exactly happened to her.
Face Martos Tribon.
May time then has lacked us.
You crazy woman!
What have you done to me?
The mighty royal wizard didn't expect to be sacrificed, did he?
Face Martos!
You are useless to me.
Now it's time for my lovely bestie Vivian.
I can even smell the unending energy coming sweeter than the money.
Crazy evil middle.
You dare to provoke the chosen one.
Your doom is inevitable.
You want some milk?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
King ever rebelled against the absurd idea of sacrifice, not in all those years.
They say that when a prince ascends the wizard royal family bestows upon him and unknown.
Unknown power.
From where?
For what?
Oh, bastard.
Nobody tells me anything.
Does this power force the king to have to make a sacrifice?
No.
It's, uh, Vivian.
Not so fast, bastard.
She finished a thousand years ago without warning, and then she vanished into that damn
castle.
Don't forget that useless and despicable royal family.
I will create a new one, also part of the wizard royal family.
I would almost believe in true love.
What do you want?
You two just let it go off.
How ridiculous.
My ex talked big.
You couldn't protect the queen a thousand years ago, and you still can't protect Vivian
now.
Your concern is misguided.
Our royal power stems from conquest, not sentiment, wasn't this to our affection for
those commoners that led you into our trap?
If it was not for the medicine that gave me, I wouldn't have fallen for your scheme.
Yes.
I believe it was the elixir I had pursued so fervently.
If we were not consumed by love, how could he have brought harm to his own queen?
For me a thousand years ago, it's time to return.
The source of the mysterious royal power that was stolen from you, I bowed to my defeat.
I'm sorry.
It's still worthy of your kiss.
A pure kiss to my lover is the greatest reward there is.
What I feel to protect you.
About magic, and without the rules of fate, a genuine kiss is the symbol of my choice.
I love you without ever needing your protection.
Vivian, from this moment forward, I would no longer haunt you.
You will write all along, sacrifice as a coward's way.
How will you restore your human form?
I won't.
Being the way I am, suits me better than my powerless old self.
I curse you to heal, free of pain, and remain forever the perfect, grimly.
You want to adopt Linda's child?
We are the only ones who know his true identity.
Vivian, you're acting like the queen from a thousand years ago again.
I'm still me, and my love for you hasn't changed in a thousand years.
Too bad in my house?
Oh?
Really?
I love you even more than I did a thousand years ago.
Wizard princes are known for tricking women.
Honestly, I think the reason that Hank back then lost his queen was because he didn't understand
what love was.
But Hank back then had the courage to marry the woman he liked.
How could he not understand love?
I think someone else here doesn't get it.
So that's it.
You're just upset.
I was going to rebuild Grayson before properly proposing to you.
Well, don't think that's a sure yes.
My dearest Vivian, I've traveled a thousand years in wrong the vast lands, just to find
out that loving someone isn't about admiring a perfect image.
I just want the real you to accept the real me.
Can this come true?
The only type of love that is stronger than magic is the love for oneself.
Finally, I am free.
May you find eternal happiness.