This will be a very easy sign
This is a very long sign
This is a very easy sign
This is a very simple sign
Here we have the idea
Because I bought it a little bit
And we have the idea that we are not making something
You know, I'm waiting
Now they have the idea of the idea
And they have your idea
That would be an idea
I'd like to talk to you about this video already.
It's about killing us.
Bolou-chickani, nos.
Is she going to be a little bit more familiar?
It's like you're having a good time with us.
We don't know how to say it.
But it's not like you're doing it.
Because we don't know how to say it.
Nothing but like we said,
I'm not going to do that, I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do that.