Hello!
It's your favorite!
Welcome!
I'm here to consider you to do a little bit of good projects.
I really appreciate this project!
I'm here to introduce you to the original project.
I'm here to introduce you to the first one.
In my history, I'm from San Francisco.
I'm here to help myself and your chef.
M.E.M.I.
Chippo, modern attacks,
M.E.R.E.S.
Come on, Jissie.
Eliza,
Ewa Mullet,
the Satchta family legend.
Ella Poggins,
Nevado,
Prosimonito.
Who cares
Sandra Poggifasier?
Ella Sosa,
binin,
parboñez.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Do you give us
a stick, Enui?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Uprogette,
ou, sista la,
fu y migna, aye, tai, ha.
Puzzi, fie, a crocabes.
Teni, sab,
yu, ke, M.E.M.
Who knows
Eliza Varkredge?
Who can I just
log with
Keftnadora de M.E.M.?
Elsso,
Afnadora de M.E.M.E.
Hejipu,
what's
hefnadora de M.E.M.?
Elsso,
Afnadora de M.E.M.E.
Jashigasen,
para jivintares
as his stories.
What's that?
De chapralla,
what's the
word that you
think you
mean?
Eliza,
M.E.M.
M.E.M.?
Eliza,
ente,
a sore
eliza.
Pare,
Cinderella,
Maric Mengo survived,
which is
very
much
has a
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you next time.