We can put note that I don't know what it is.
Okay, we are not going to go online.
What next?
What are you doing?
No, I don't get it.
What's going on?
I'm going to get it here.
Is he going to be like this?
I don't have anything to say.
If he is going to leave his family,
you'll immediately have to tell the story of him.
He's going to be a friend of mine.
I'll tell you what he is.
A friend...
I'm not gonna let go of him.
I don't think he is going to leave at the moment.
If you don't know, I'm going to tell the story of him.
If he's going to leave him...
I should have been able to speak to my wife.
I'm a son.
And...
who is...
what is your name?
I'm a son.
I'm a son of your father.
I'm a victim of the truth.
I'm not a son of your mother.
I'm a son of your father.
It's Selenci, and I will see you in the next video.