bidding won'
of no boys
if I still don't think I could feel my type of skin
but if Iman
if I want to stay safely
prominent in some ways
I will continue to lower it
even to keep my stomach
I hang this corner
and navigate every other desert
that you cannot leave
How do I do with my fingers?
Why does that peculiar lie
that you don't realize I'm insecure
And I was very shy in the background.
I was so tired, but with today's video..
I was so tired and I couldn't explain it.
I was so tired too.
I was so tired.
But I was so tired.
I wanted to go back to my house.
I was so proud and I was so tired.
How deep was the room?
I'm very tired.
I'm not a fool, I'm a fool.
What are you doing?
I'm not a fool.
I'm a fool.
What are you doing?
I'm not a fool.