The house will be fixed, and they will take us to the future.
Also, there will be a new design on the configurations.
We will take all the parts from the top and the bottom of the floor.
We will get the plane to the back.
Let's go inside.
All right, this is going to be the end.
And you will go inside.
All right, you have to go inside.
There we have to go inside.
Yes, I'll give this to you today.
I'm going to tell you anything about this.
What is happening, where is the opposite side,
and here is the whole thing?
Here we are.
How long is this all over here?
Oh, that's a wild one.
It's the first one.
We're not supposed to be able to live.
Let's go.
I'm not going to live.
I can do so much.
I'll find a way to go.
Hello?
Congolores?
We can't have a great design sheet for this design.
It can be a simple design sheet.
I'm getting scared of the rest of the design sheet.
But I can see it's a good design for the original design.
I'll make sure that this work is secure.
Let's show you the design sheet.
I can see the inside of this design,
and I'll tell you that it's from that to that,
and I'll show you how to make this.
It also has the same skin,