You're behind me.
You're something i've done with your friends.
I'm very happy I had the opportunity to do this.
I've been doing this for over a long time.
Do you think you'd even know who you are?
Who's this guy?
We're on the edge.
I'm looking forward to a lot more.
I'm very happy, but I'm very happy.
I love that too.
And my friend, guys, is an vacant individual,
a small miles of the police.
I make a small videos of my family.
That's a crime.
Sosa bia calanon era comfia vio.
Fusi a si a si a regi para zerum pere faitur juntus?
Yela, justtru y oso casa meinto.
Moizela, mise ao ho dund sein jucomel y sabo de ria fazera guassin.
y eso vistido que hos se petu para con certa.
Obrigado.
Adir y ao por que a tante sco sturas.
Ej el tene fos grange.
No a, mo y to casin sperifase.
Si.
As in como me de los sonamés to concents.
What's the name of the country?
I'm not the one who is here.