But it is not going to do anything.
Time to go back.
All around you.
No problem.
All right?
I told Mar Gole to his car,
and I wasn't afraid.
But how can you take my car?
I think he will be the enemy.
But when you have a bond,
you will simply be a normal person.
The first thing is,
Tekin,
what are you doing here?
But even if you were a mother, you would mean if you were not looking for your father.
Are you looking for the love I have?
No, even if you were not in the house.
I was a son of a son of a son.
What about you, you must be like this?
A son of a son of a son of a son of a son?
I was adulthood.
No, I'm sorry.
This is the second course, the very most of the day.
So, you're the very most special in your identity?
You're great.
You're the most?
No, it's the best.
You're the best.