Hmm, so her name is Kristin, and the coming of age ceremony is next month.
Your Majesty, Ms. Kristin still doesn't have a partner, why don't you go and grab her, directly?
Cassius, you know very well just how bad my reputation is outside.
If I approach her directly, she'll be scared to death.
Those people, they're always spreading rumours about you making you have to be a tyrant
and when the actual fact, every order that you've been given, and every order that you're giving, has been to eliminate the assassins.
Cassius, I have no experience in pursuing women.
Do I send her flowers? Cassius, I want you to arrange 999 roses and have them send to her on her coming of age ceremony.
Yes, your Majesty.
And Cassius, don't worry, I haven't forgotten the promise I made.
I have people looking for your sister.
Thank you, Majesty.
Father, as the Alpha on the Silver Moon tribe, we're falsely accused of rebelling and cruelly killed by traitors.
I will never again this humiliation.
One day, I will seek justice for my parents and bring my sister back.
With this necklace, I will find her.