Dear, you refuse me. I'll take care of you now.
No, but just at least you can't. You have Amelia.
Amelia is my woman, and you, you cannot escape either. I will make you pay for everything that you've done.
Alice, what should I do?
Keep him a baby, Kristin. Tell him you want to wait until after your conversation.
I want you, Alpha. I've realized my mistakes.
Kevin, please just wait until after the coming of me.
I just don't want the first time to be in a place like this.
Since you're willing to admit your own mistakes, I'm not such a petty Alpha.
By then, you and Amelia, the three of us can have a good time together.
Bitch, I'll make the coming of age ceremony the most humiliating memory of your life.