Cassius, I'm just remembered.
It's Kristin's coming of age ceremony today.
Such an on-day, I've got to go and see her.
Your Majesty, Elder Roy is already waiting for you in the reception area.
I know, I know, look, you go over to the Blackwind tribe and take care of Kristin, okay?
The last time I saw her, she did not look happy.
I've got it.
In the meantime, I'm gonna go and see Elder Roy.
Once I've finished, I'll join you.
We've got this.
There are holes everywhere.
Oh my God.
This is my only dress.
It looks like I'll have to wear it to the queen of age ceremony.
Oh my God.
Everyone come and see, how can someone dare to dress like this for the coming of age ceremony?
Her dress is torn, so pathetic.
If I were her, I would rather be crying right now.
No, my dress was fine.
But someone just cut it right before the ceremony.
Stop pretending, Kristin.
Everyone knows you're an orphan.
Too poor to even afford a dress.
Hurry up and get out of here.
What do you mean this is my ceremony?
A she will flex you attending the ceremony?
It's embarrassing for our black wind try.