Kristen, I am so sorry. I didn't expect the elders to get agitated.
Because of what? Because you're not the alpha of a bloodline?
Look, I should have told you much sooner about the engagement.
I understand, really. I do. It's just all so sudden.
I'm so confused right now. I don't know what to do.
Calm down, Kristen. Alan doesn't seem to have any feelings for that woman.
The engagement is from the past generation.
But how can I not be upset? I don't have an alpha bloodline. And I almost became a long move.
Kristen, don't be sad. You have me, ain't it?
Thank you, Alice.
No matter what happens, I promise. I will not become Alan's mistress.
So, you are Kristen? Yes, Miss Anna. How can I help you?