Yes, Miss Anna, how can I help you?
A lowly she-wolf like you isn't worthy of Alan's attention.
If you know what's good for you, you'll leave him.
Alan is just passing a fancy for you.
I believe when he's done playing, he'll reject you and come back to me.
That's so.
Well, if you didn't know, me and Alan are partners, and we love each other.
Really?
But Alan once said that he wanted to marry me.
I was his first love after all.
What?
Like I said, you have no royal blood.
Alan would never take you for a wife.
Are you done?
If you love him so much, go tell him yourself.
Don't bother talking to me.
Hello, did it work?
Alan didn't suspect a thing.
Can a queen will be mine?
Don't be so confident.
All the documents forged by Justin if they're discovered.
We're all down for.
What's there to fear?
I'm the daughter of an alpha.
What can Kristen do against me?
I'll show Alan what a real woman is like.