Come in.
Your Majesty, you must be hungry. Please, if you saw before.
Miss Anna, why am I seeing you rather than one of the other servants?
Oh, please don't blame the servants. It's just that I wanted to do something for you to repay your kindness.
That's very kind of you. Please, just leave the soup there.
Oh, please, eat it quickly before it gets cold.
Miss Anna, please, you don't have to do this.
Your father already saved the king, and for that, I'm in your debt and I will take care of you.
But I shall not marry you as the queen. I already have somebody else in my heart.
Oh, no, Your Majesty. I just wanted to show how grateful I am.
Miss Anna, if there's nothing else, please, could you leave my office? I have work to do.
Strange. Why do I feel a bit feverish?
Your Majesty, am I not as attractive as her?
Miss Anna, please behave.
Your Majesty, but isn't it what you want?
Get out.
But your Majesty...
We're late tonight, so...
Could you?