Perhaps you should find a chance to explain it to Kristin properly.
You're right.
Cassius!
Majesty, what can I do for you?
I want this bowl of soup testing.
I'm pretty sure that something has been added to it.
Of course, Majesty.
Bring me the results as soon as you get them, OK?
And one more thing.
Tell Anna she's not welcome anywhere near my office ever again,
unless strictly ordered by me.
Of course, Majesty.
It seems the rumors are true.
His Majesty and Miss Kristin had a fight because of Anna.
Where have I seen this necklace before?
So familiar.
Miss Anna?
Cassius.
And I'm here on his Majesty's orders.
Open the door.
What now? I haven't done anything.
If his Majesty wants me to leave, I'll leave.
Miss Anna, when his Majesty gives you an order, you listen.
Otherwise you are disrespecting the royal family.
Do you understand it?
Fine.
What do you want?
I'm listening.
Isn't this necklace only for those of the direct bloodline of the silver moon tribe?
Could it be Anna?
Is the sister I've been searching for?
Always is.