What's going on here?
Your Majesty, I don't know what I've done to offend Kristen, but I just wanted to give her coffee, but you pushed me away.
What are you talking about?
I didn't even touch you! You just spilled it by yourself!
Alpha Cassius can testify for me. Your Majesty.
Cassius, can't you explain?
Alpha Cassius, you were right there. You saw everything. Please tell his Majesty the truth.
Perhaps as Miss Anna said, Miss Kristen accidentally bumped into her and spooked the coffee.
Why are you lying? You saw everything!
Then perhaps it was just an accident. Sit down and finish your meal.
I didn't push her! Why don't you believe me?
Like you didn't believe me last night, Kristen?
Alan, you don't have to be angry with me or Kristen. She just lost her temper of it.
You do not have the right to call me by my name, Miss Anna.
Do you really believe this woman of uncertain origin?
Of course not, but I can't let the elders find out they're investigating.