I haven't said really well that she just pops up.
Maybe accepting Alan in a first place was a mistake.
Oh, like Kristen. Don't think like that.
Alan misunderstood because Cassius lied.
After all, Cassius is his right-hand man.
You're right.
But why would Cassius help Anna?
Could it be...
He likes her. Not that's absurd.
And you can't give up on Alan like this, Kristen.
I thought woman not only was Alan's first love,
but she also got a reaction from him.
I feel like he's lying to me.
There must be some misunderstanding.
You can talk openly with Alan, Kristen.
You canceled this alone.
You're right. Okay, I'll go see him tonight.
Christine, if you want to know about your origins,
come alone to Blackmin tribe.
What? Justin claims to know about my origins.
Why he didn't tell me before.
Don't believe him.
Kristen, he's definitely trying to deceive you.
He's seen you going to the Queen and fears her retaliation.
What if he really has some clues about my parents?
I have been searching for mom and dad for so many years.
I just want to know the outcome.
Christine, don't act impulsively.
Why don't you ask Alan to send someone to four, you secretly?
No. This is my own business. I'll handle it myself.
Okay.
But don't find me tricks.
All in some Alan I can see.