Your Majesty, may I come in?
The test results of the suit.
The back.
Ah, take a look.
They're dared to add aphrodisiacs to the suit.
Your Majesty, is it true that it's possible and are tampered with your suit?
This necklace is identical to one Kristen while the other day.
You seem to care a lot about Anna.
She's so pitiful, I feel.
Sorry for her.
The suit is fine.
You may leave.
Your Majesty.
What?
Am I really betrayed his daughter?
No, I don't believe it.
I have to find Alan.
Kristen, look over there.
Aren't those palace guards?
Did Alan send someone to find you?
We're here on orders from King Alan to apprehend Kristen.
Have you seen her?
Oh, no. I haven't seen her.
What?