What is this guy I do not recognize you three as part of my guard service shut up. What are you now?
Are you the light and king get up
Unfortunately for you, I am the like in King
Sorry, I'm at his seat. We're late. Take these away for interrogation. Find out who's behind this
Kristen
Kristen I shouldn't have got angry at you the other night and about Anna. She put something in my soup
That's the reason that I I reacted the way I did
She also told me that she was your first love, Alan. It's that true. I haven't seen Anna since I was barely eight years old
So that's it. I shouldn't have doubted you. I
Went to the black wind trap to see Justin because he told me, you know something about my parents
He also told me that I'm a descendant of traitors. So I didn't dare come see you as to a friend. Kristen
Justin's words are not trustworthy and even if they were
It's not your fault. No, it is my fault as well. I shouldn't have doubted you