But there's one more thing. My abilities have seemed to weaken.
I had to know what they are yet.
Christian, that's great!
Congratulations!
You must be so tired. Why don't you go back to the castle and rest?
I'll come be in the council of Elders tomorrow. I will make you my queen.
No matter the outcome, I will stand by your side.
Cassius, what do you have a cup of tea before you leave?
Sir, may I suggest we go to sleep early tonight.
Tomorrow I'm presenting to the council of the Elders, and it's a very big day for us.
But if you insist.
Tonight, Majesty.
God, take this cup of contentation testing.
Find out if the DNA matches Christians.
Yes, sir.
I want to expose the true face of Anna as soon as possible.