Your Majesty, for this meeting, we are hoping that you may reconsider your choice for the future, Queen.
And if not Kristen, who else?
Your Majesty, there's something I need to say.
I am the son of the former Alpha of the Silver Moon tribe.
What? You? The king is the right hand of man.
I'm from a traitorous tribe. We are not traitors, and I'm here today to clear our family name.
We have gone to great lengths to protect the royal family.
And with his king's help, I've collected a knock evidence to clear our family's name once and for all.
It's all here, black and white. Take a look for yourselves.
Alpha Cassius, we never expected your silver moon tribe to have been falsely accused.
I am deeply sorry, and now that I've finally cleared our family's name, there is one more thing I'm here to announce.
Miss Anna is my biological long lost sister.