Ms. Anna is my biological, long lost sister.
My word! With Anna's merits and with his Majesty, Alan?
What? It's a match made in heaven!
No wonder he was covering up for Anna's lies earlier.
Cusius, do you have proof?
Of course I do your Majesty.
This token only loaves that our direct descendant of the silver moon tribe
can possess such a token.
The King knows this.
He also knows I possess one and who else possesses one.
Ms. Anna, my sister, it's identical.
Krista, what's the matter?
Oh, that's impossible. That's my necklace.
Kristan, how could you say that?
This clearly belongs to me.
I've had it for many years and Cassius just happened to see it a few days ago.
Ms. Kristan, please stop lying.
I'm not lying.
Do you think I wouldn't recognize a necklace?
I've been wearing my whole life and I actually lost it just yesterday.
I've been searching all over the palace for it.
And to my surprise, I find it on you, Ms. Anna.
Do you have any proof?
Everybody knows, Kristan, that you're from the Black Wind Tribe.
If you've been wearing it all this time,
people who know you should have seen it, right?
I happen to know someone from the Black Wind Tribe.
I can ask her.
You're Majesty Allen, esteemed elders.
I'm Amelia, the future lunar of the Black Wind Tribe.
I testify that this woman has been on our tribe for many years.
And I've never seen her with this necklace.