Don't please don't kill my father
Arnold you were my most loyal friend. This is the price you must pay for the train. Don please
It's been my children. If you care so much about your family, let's make a contract
Your daughter Alice will keep her purity until she's 18 and then she will marry my son Gertrude
with all your families
Will as for your son
We're good sir. We could no longer marry that the boss's permission
You'll work for the gang
Forever the plan to get in you has lasted for 15 years
Since then that moment I've been playing the traps in my hands
My dear Augusta, I'm finally going to marry you tomorrow Pietra today. I'm gonna take your place
Are you crazy?
I know you care about me as my brother, but for Christ's sakes, you're a man
I found a loophole in the contract. Pietra has to marry a child of the Caster of family
Doesn't have to be you. I can take your place
He's a monster and a playboy
God knows how many mistresses
Besides how could Pietra possibly want to marry a man to protect you have to try? It's too risky
He'll kill you
Kill who?