He'll hope.
Kill some stupid ideas.
Pietro, listen, you're not going to marry Alice today.
I'm going to take her place.
It's my duty as a child of the Castro family
to be your partner, the law permits it.
Do as I say, rewrite that contract.
But what if your father finds out?
You want to try me?
I can kill you right now.
Are you sure you want to take Alice's place?
There are certain obligations to be in my spouse.
Pietro.
Don't go along with his crazy ideas.
Neither your family nor the entire mafia world
will approve of this.
I don't care.
Are you serious?
You're not considering canceling the contract,
but you'd marry a man instead.
The only thing I care about is you giving your body
a soul to me and don't you dare play with me.
His body?
How can two straight guys?
I'll accept everything that comes along with the contract
as long as you leave Alice alone.
So I'll say yes.
Yes, I do.
If you were just doing this on a whim
to torture a gusto, I'd rather be a bro.
I'm the one that decides Alice stay in the dress
and await my instructions.
My groom, I've addressed this long-awaited wedding
that's about to start.