Pietro, I love you with all my heart, I must know what kind of cunt can take my place.
Welcome to Pietro and Augusto's wedding.
My son is the bride.
Same sex marriage in this city as an insult to the mafia.
He's gonna marry a man.
Then why can't I be the one?
Don't.
Do something to stop this.
Pietro.
Stop this nonsense.
Our gang will be the laughingstock of the city, our boss marrying a man and the man's
son of a traitor.
No matter what happens today, we are getting married.
The contract clearly states that I will marry a Castro child.
It is legal for me to marry Augusto.
When was this contract changed?
I am still the boss and I order you to stop this ridiculous wedding.
That would be great.
Father, you remember what happened three days ago?