Today we vote for a new leader of the Western Alliance.
So let's vote.
No one should have a problem with my re-election.
My family are dominant in this city.
I vote Pietro.
What?
Does anyone need reminding that I am still the boss?
Everyone knows your son's been rung shared the last five years.
I vote Pietro too.
I abstain if too young.
Although we could do with some fresh blood.
Arm and a matter of while always be your son.
My favorite heir.
I will hand over the business to you in advance.
Consider it a wedding gift.
I'm worried.
We'll get everything you wish for, Father.
So this was all part of your plan.
Plan?
Wasn't the wedding an impromptu decision?
Not very well that I'm in charge now.
You need to remember that this is just the white wedding by law.
The real ceremony for the mafia is the black wedding.
And without my blessing, he will never be recognized by the family.
This wedding's important to me.
I inherited the family in advance to make sure no one took advantage of the situation.
No matter what, I'm still your son.
And I want your blessing.