Do I scare you?
Scared.
Yeah.
I'm scared it's going to hurt.
I mean, I've never done this before.
Pietro, you can wait.
You want him to feel good for his first time.
You have to compensate me.
Do you embarrass me?
You're in our wedding kiss?
Yeah, for that, I'm sincerely sorry.
That's it.
An apology.
And what else do you want?
I expect you to pay me the interest.
Kiss me.
Try to please him until the marriage is over.
You have to keep your promise.
The family will only accept me after the black wedding.
I always gave my word.
And don't forget, you only have a month to take over the casino.
Otherwise, the contract is invalid.
A month?
Give me a week.
I've got you as my relation now.
Whoa.
How much so?
All these years.
We work together.
You've never been given a day this year.
Finally, I know why.
What are you trying to say?
Say it to my face.
Softly, I was the most.
It's so soft.