If it's my right to kill him, then it's my right to let him go.
But let it be said, me letting him go does not make me a merciful coward.
I'll go by Pietro's side on all future missions.
That's so sweet.
Maybe I can do something to delay the completion by joining this mission.
Then the marriage will be annulled smoothly.
Yeah, what are we doing here? Mission's not done yet.
Well, the black wedding is our formal night.
And you need a new suit for the occasion.
Yeah, isn't it a bit early for all this? Mission's not over yet.
Early. I actually can't wait to take your clothes off on one.
I'm not your pet, Pietro.
But I'll take you to the real destination.
Okay. Let's go.