Petra, I thought I was getting to know you.
But now it just feels like nothing's real between us.
You scare me.
You wanted to protect our list. I wanted to marry you.
The sooner you found out about the loophole, the better it would be for us.
I thought this would benefit the both of us.
Benefit? Oh, I see.
So you just care about the outcome.
You don't give a damn shit about my feelings.
Your feelings have not treated you well since we've been married.
Calm down.
I can make this up to you.
You almighty Pietro.
You say that you love me, but you know nothing for real lovers.
Did you ask Mark when?
Yeah, Dad, just forget about that.
Why?
You know how miserable I've been here for years.
Now we've got a chance to escape.
Yeah, and you think Pietro's going to let that happen?
Dad, Agasto's right. We can't make it.
Agasto.
You've totally become that monster slave.
Shame on you, you...
Dad!
How dare you hit my husband?