Pietro, you didn't kill Arnold.
Oh no, it was my fault.
You spare a traitor, and everyone will think you're getting weak.
You've been elected as the new leader.
The succession ceremony is being scheduled next week by the Western Alliance.
Yeah.
And as time these old girls has finally known their place.
They made the right choice.
But the election was before the wedding.
Your marriage broke the rules and offended them.
Told you I'm to blame.
Pietro, we're family.
I'm going to do this with you.
He finally considers me family.
Augusto, I want you to come with me to the Alliance meeting next week.
Well, but Augusto doesn't know anything in the Alliance.
He needs to see the impact your marriage has had on the family.
I can do it.
Well done, Augusto.
This is the second test of the Falcon at Program.