Relax. The wall is our guns.
We've got cover outside. Welcome everyone and thank you for joining
Pietro's ceremony to become the new Alliance leader.
Good one. I'd like to introduce you to my husband
Bogosto. I know there's been some concerns about our marriage
so I come bearing gifts. One apple equals one share in the
casino's profits. You think this is going to erase the
shame of marrying a man? Each apple represents my sincerity.
I do have a counter offer. I back down. I challenge you all
and only my family will survive. You're two arrogance.
Pietro, divorce this man. We can ignore all your faults.
I'd rather piss on all of your grays one by one.
Fucking monster. Ally or my enemy. So does anyone have any
objection to Pietro being the new leader? I object.
I, Miguel, calls air. Object to Pietro's election as leader.