Farber was almost taken out last time.
I can't wish putting you in danger again, okay?
Yeah, because of our marriage.
Yeah, you don't stay. Stop a gusto from leaving the man on.
No.
You said you were giving me a chance.
I'm not a softie.
I'm not your pet!
They're saving me that day.
You've been here for days now.
Do you still think Pietro really loves you?
I thought a lot.
Maybe we are never compatible.
I don't know if I can accept this kind of love.
Good. You're a real man.
Augusta.
I know you're smart like your father.
I could send you to university.
You could start a new life.
I can't even take a step out the door.
I know my son best.
He married you using a loophole.
And right now, you're the biggest loophole in his life.