If you're a tree, you always say that I'm your lover, not your prisoner.
I'm good, it's for your safety.
Don gave me these, and I think you should respect his wishes and mine.
Who is this?
You leave me, will you?
Did you?
Did you ever love me?
You always say that you want, it's not only my body, but also my heart, but I want
you.
I want you, I've always dreamed of you.
I'm not talking about you right now.
What about what I want?
I'm a normal guy.
Normal.
Okay, yeah.
All right.
What about what I want?
You just say that everyone else, you think I'm a monster?
Don't you?
Just say that everyone else, you're going to fucking abandon me.
Leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
You go.
Okay.
But I've got to pick the school, okay, and you go with my bodyguards, okay?