What a heart-wrenching story.
Augusto, do you really think a lawyer would make such a dumb mistake?
15 years ago, it was 12-year-old Pietro who forced him to change the contract.
15 years ago, he set me up to replace the hellies.
It's more than that.
15 years later, he forced Mark to let you know about the loophole so that you would volunteer to marry him.
I've got a story I fell in love with you 15 years ago.
I hit my sexuality for all those years and I worked my way up the ranks of the mafia
and become the most feared nimble.
Liar!
You wouldn't know how we had sex.
He fucked me hard while he was watching you having sex with Anne.
I was venting.
And that's why you're a psycho just like me.
That's why we're the perfect match.
You can just hold me all this after we were married.
He wouldn't dare because he has an even bigger secret.
The secret that Mark didn't finish before he left.
Well, good news, I found him abroad.
You want to hear about it?
Hey girl, if you stop here, I'll let you call him.
Asshole!
You really think you could still boss me around, Augusta?
Guess why you've been called a softie and who really made the contract?
He feared you'd get too strong and that you would rebel against him and then finally leave him.
Is all this true?
I don't want to lie to you, right?
I was trying to protect you and I don't want to lose you.
If the target was me, Pietro, for 15 years, why did Alice have to suffer?
So what are you waiting for?
This is your chance to get revenge.