What do you mean the sperm got mixed up?
Ms. Salvador, I am so sorry.
I mixed up your sample with the one meant for our VIP clients.
Then whose sperm is it, then?
You received Mr. Damon Green sample.
He donated it for research purposes three years ago.
Who?
Damien Green.
This is his donation record.
How could it be his?
No, him?
Yes, I do.
Damien Green is my ex.
Your ex? What are you going to do about the baby?
This is all your deadbeat dad's fault.
None of this would have happened if he had you run off with your engagement ring and pond it to pay his gambling debt.
Are you okay?
I'm just thinking about the baby.
Maybe you should tell him.
You know, he needs to know and you might even get back together.
Absolutely not.
He hates me.
You can never know that this baby is his.