Oh my god, this storm came out of nowhere,
cause are we gonna die?
No, no, we're not gonna die.
We just spotted her in a flight grant.
We're off force by 30 degrees
and our altitude's challenged at 25,000 feet.
Hold on.
North America's best captain.
You handled that emergency like a pro.
Again.
If you lose control like that again,
you won't be an LS copilot anymore.
Wait, Damien.
L-I-X organized a three month training program
to improve performance and as a leading airline,
LS is conducting the trainings.
But it's a small program.
I mean, even small tasks need attention,
but why specifically did you have to fly out
from Switzerland to superpowers?
This training program has garnered a lot
of attention from other airlines.
It's crucial for our reputation as an airline
that I attend.
That's for all and the charge.
Interesting.
Cause I thought it was all about her.
Her?
Please, she's not worth the effort.
Sure.
Drinks?
Five years and you're still within my reach.
I'll let you go to the stop.