Hey, asshole! The fuck do you think you're doing with my girlfriend?
Dang it! Dang it! Damn it! Get off of him!
What happened, Lucretia? How can you possibly explain this?
I can't, Damien. I love this man.
What about us? We've been together for three years! You've told me that you loved me!
Love to you? No, I used to you, you idiot. I'm leaving you, for someone richer.
No, I don't believe you. What does this man have that I don't have?
A hundred times better than you are. You're a dead man. Stop it!
I love you, Lucretia. I am going to make you a lifetime.
Lucky, the last time I saw you, I swore to ruin your life.
What happens today is just the start.
Not your stand, Damien. I did it all for you.