All these years I have been only one suffering.
Your lip has five years. All his dreams have come true.
He's a pilot, a CEO, and he has a gorgeous girlfriend.
He's moved on. Lucky. Now I know why you rushed in here.
What are you gonna do? I never expected Damien to hate me so much,
but still nothing changes. Can't know what this baby says.
I'm gonna ask Mr. Keller if I can skip illustrating.
Is the ever composed captain Damien losing his cool?
Admit it. Still have feelings for her. Just go and get her back.
Maybe you didn't hear me. She's married and pregnant.
So what? Just get her back and raise the kid as your own.
Prom sell. That's bullshit. Even if she wasn't married,
I don't want her. She shallow, vain, and a gold digger.
Sure. Sure. So what she used to. If you don't want her,
why are you so angry? It sounds like you need an open.
Isn't there a welcome party for the training tonight?
Use that to make your move. She'll be there.
Might have seen her name on the guest list. So you going?
You know I don't go to those things.