I was just wondering if there was someone else who could take my place at the LS training.
Lucky, no need to be so formal. Sit down.
Oh, that's okay.
No need to be so formal.
Which closest we were his childhood friends, right?
You know, it was pretty hard trying to stay in touch with you, transfer of schools, moving.
I remember good friends.
Brad, I'm really happy I got a job at your company, too.
It's my world, right? Okay.
In fact, why we're here. Can you explain to me why we'll do the LS training program?
I mean, it's a great opportunity and anybody who does it, they can promote it. You can be head attendant.
I know, it is a great opportunity, but I'm just feeling a little bit under the weather.
Okay, understandable. Definitely the woman you have to exhaust in.
How about this? I want you to do something for me. I'm going to make a phone call tomorrow.
I want you to attend. It's welcome.
And I did not expect you to come just for me.
You're overthinking this.
Why is he here? He always hated these months.
Is that grossed?