He's not your husband.
Of course not.
Pregnant. And sneaking around with your boss at parties.
You are as shameless as ever at the looker.
He noticed I'm pregnant.
But Tamey and C's clueless about the child.
Looks like the doctor kept it a secret.
Mr. Green, I am not married.
So I can attend parties with you ever.
Not married.
Then whose child is that?
It's one of your business.
Oh, I see.
You've been with so many men.
You don't know who the father is.
Fuck you. You make me sick.
I make you sick.
Of the two of us, you are both a gold digger and a cheater.
Do you even remember what you did to me?
Why are you dredging up the past?
Because it might be in the past for you, but not for me.
I've had to live with every day since then.