Hey, you need to stay away from your little friend. He's dangerous.
Who? Rad?
I think that you're the one that's dangerous. Stay away from me.
Lucky. I'm not joking. He's not as nice of a guy as you think he is.
I've known him for 12 years. That's longer than I've known you.
Yeah, but I know men better than you. You should see the way he looks at you.
I can't believe CEO has got captive to the simulation.
Isn't he so charming? It looks lucky to have a thing going on.
Have you just left a camera?
What are you talking about? I see the way he looks at you.
I mean, it's lucky you're looking too right.
No, not at all. Okay, well, if you're not going to go for it, then I will.
Let's say you're reassigned to another position. It's my chance.
Hope you don't mind. Not at all. Good luck.
Well, Chris, he's out of the door. Get in here.
You're the lucky one.