How did you know someone broke into my house?
My father's a general.
I heard him talking to his friends on the horseback.
Look very closely.
I got pregnant a month ago.
The break-in happened a few weeks ago.
Stop making baseless accusations
before I start questioning whether you're carrying Damien's baby.
Unless you've proof, of course.
Of course, my baby is Damien's.
Miss Green herself can confirm it.
You're pregnant?
When did that happen?
I've been pregnant for a while, Rad.
Okay, then.
Who's the father?
I mean, again.
She has probably been with so many men.
We didn't even know who the father is.
Mr. Keller, you seem to have some special interest in my Salvador.
Could you be the father?
So I'm dressed to stop.
Rad and I are just friends.
Lucky.
I don't care who the father is.
I'm willing to be there for you and your baby.
Rad, you don't have this.
Lucky?
Like you since we were kids, give me the chance.
I care of you and the baby.