Hey, Sonny, didn't.
Right?
We're back to arcade today.
No, he hasn't.
What happened?
Nothing.
It's fine.
Maybe I'm overthinking.
Rad has always been cheerful and optimistic.
He wouldn't do anything, Rad.
What are you doing here?
How did you get in?
I used the key.
Remember?
I thought he was just saying.
How do you have a key to my house?
You gave it to me for my birthday, remember?
You... you kept it?
After all these years?
I was going to ask you if you had something to eat.
Looks like I found my answer.
Are you trying to seduce me?
Remember?
Get over yourself, Damien.
We need to talk about the baby.
There's nothing to discuss.
I will raise the child as my own.
And you will stay by myself.