Okay? See, I'm here. Don't do anything stupid. Okay?
Do you care about me?
Of course I care about you. Your best friends.
Best friends?
You're important to me. I don't want anything to happen to you.
They were what about Jamie? Is he important to you?
Jamie and I are over. There's nothing happening between us.
But you're carrying his child.
My baby.
The pregnancy happened before I ran into him again.
I became a surrogate to pay off my dad's debt.
Why did you say so well?
It's not something I'm proud of.
Plus, I didn't want you to think of me any differently.
Look at the protection. You and your baby.
What?
Well, that's friends, of course. Not pressure.
Thank you so much, Rad.
But you can't do things like this to scare me.