Damien, can you remind me why you're not sleeping in your big, fancy house, and instead, why you're
crowding my small bed.
If you don't like it, sleep on the floor.
Hey, this is my house.
What's this?
Hey, don't touch my stuff.
Are we planning on proposing to love you?
No.
She chose someone else.
Brad, tell her.
Yes, they've been friend since chart time.
She wouldn't say yes, even if I were to propose.
You caught her in bed with another man, yet you still love her.
Then you get sent a photo of her hugging someone else and you...
What, you give up?
This is Damien I know.
Shut up.
Or I'll beat your ass.
Relax.
I'm kidding.
It was just a hug.
Didn't mean anything.
If she wanted to be with him, it would have happened longer.
Where are you going now?
It's pouring outside.