I can't believe I'm marrying a man I've only met once.
Take the car. The password is $6.60.
It's as bad as you like.
I'm going to hire you to get to Europe for business.
I'll contact you when I get back.
There is no need to. I've got enough money.
You can leave me money right after getting our marriage license.
This still does only to please his parents.
But does he or he want to spend the rest of his life with me?
Ginny, I failed to protect you three years ago.
Round your reputation and you couldn't go home.
I'm no longer healthy anymore.
And my greatest wish now is that you can marry a man that takes good care of you.
Houston is the grandson of my bestie.
He promised me to take good care of you.
I'll marry him, Grandma.
As long as it puts Grandma's worries to rest, does it matter who to marry?
We've got the license.
I'm so happy for you, Ginny. Wish you two a happy life and have children soon.
Guy ran away right after getting the license. What do you look like?
Mr. Mike, I heard the President Miller have been in Europe for a year for business and just got back today.
Yes. So she just got transferred from the subsidiary to the headquarters.
We have got a chance to be Mr. Miller.
Mr. President, Mr. Miller.