You've gone away, Mr. Miller. You're not having a thing for him, are you?
There was a girl from the secretary's office who attempted to hook up with Mr. Miller and was fired right away.
I'm not.
Ginny, where do you get the boss to leave your eyes on Mr. Miller?
Isn't that the weirdo who mess with you all the time after you've rejected his advances?
Right, you may not know. We're the nowadays. Like the punch above their weight.
The easy-on-the-eyes wines are all dreaming about marrying and the load of families.
Ignore the douche pack. I've got big news. The president will pick one from over 20 people in the secretary's office to join me, as a special assistant.
You gotta seize the opportunity.
Come in.
Mr. Miller, the two best candidates from the secretary's office are here.
Mr. Miller, my name is David and I've been working in the president's office for five years.
By the way, my uncle Jamie asked me to pause all his greetings.
I hate those who exploit connections the most.
I still feel like I've seen him somewhere.
What are you doing?
Hi, Mr. Miller. My name is Ginny and I...
Ginny?
Why does the name Ginny ring a bell?
Let her stay here and be my personal secretary.
Personal secretary?