With the $10 million dollar necklace in hand, you're already prepared.
Mr. Miller, it takes a young girl to know the interest of young girls.
Mr. Miller, I think girls would adore jewelry for sure, but I think the little things like
getting your wife at bouquet, taking her out to dinner, catching a movie together, are priceless.
Good. You go arrange these.
Remember, Mr. Miller really hates loose subordinates who have a secret crush on them.
Don't ruin your own career.
Thanks for the heads up, Mike. I only fancy to double pay, not himself.
I'm finally done with the grind.
These rich folks can do nothing without bossing others' room.
Who is it?
How can my own wife not even know my number?
Test him.
Who rings a bill?
Alokistan, is there anything I can help you?
My confused babe has even forgotten my name on the marriage license.
I'm your sweetie.
Come for dinner, if you are up.
How can there be another man's voice in my wife's house?
Turns out my so-called good wife is a slut.