Hanged up like that, it's such a weirdo, but how do you know my private number?
Come for dinner, Jeannie! Come for dinner, dinner's ready.
This looks wonderful, thank you so much!
So President of the top-notch conglomerate, M Group, the top-notch conglomerate, has never shown his face in the public media.
How does he look? Are you charmed off your feet?
He's got the looks for sure, but as far as it fits to the extent that Trump's feet off, that's for his wife to answer.
Oh, really? Oh, he's married!
And he loves his wife dearly. He does look familiar. I couldn't remember what I'd seen before.
Don't forget you married, lady.
Do you really expect Jeannie to spend the rest of her life waiting for that bastard, who vanished right after marrying her?
That irresponsible jerk? I swear, even if he gets down and begs me, I won't lay eyes on him.
Mr. Miller seems to be really upset today. You think maybe he didn't get what he wanted from his wife last night?
Is that something we can gossip about as subordinates?