I thought the rumors were true that Mr. Miller was completely celibate, now that Mr. Miller hasn't gotten tired of it yet, okay, I'll wait a little longer.
Mr. Thomas, I apologize to her right now.
Mr. Miller, we are partners. You wouldn't do this for this little slut.
What a little slut, seducing married man at this young age?
I didn't seduce him! He tried to rape me! I didn't seduce him!
No wonder you got in that good college. You must have slept with every man in school.
Why should I be humiliated like that just because I'm a girl, because I'm pretty?
Mr. Miller, we can have a thorough exchange about the art of flirting with women later. I'm a specialist in this.
Stop!
Get out!
Understand?
Mr. Miller, it was my mistake. For the sake of our partnership, please.
Mr. Miller, it's just a misunderstanding. I can explain.
From today onward, M. Group will never collaborate with Mr. Thomas U. Company.
Yes, sir!
Get out of here.
Mr. Miller, avenging me?