Um, Mr. Miller, I know that a last minute change to the partnering company will cause a great loss to Engroup.
I am really grateful for you for helping me out.
It's the main fault of the man who sexually harassed you, not you.
When you are bullied in the workplace, no matter what the occasion is.
And you gotta fight back, bravely.
And there's no need to hold your tongue.
Engroup will always be supporting you.
If somebody stepped forward to defend me,
when I was pushing around back in the old days,
it wouldn't have gotten back rep.
Thank you, Mr. Miller. I know what to do going forward.
You weren't backing off when you pushed you around, you know.
And look, now you are weeping.
Um, Mr. Miller, I'm going to shop around for some local specialties before we leave.
Do you want to bring your wife a gift?
Last time I heard a man's voice here with a phone call there.
Of course, it doesn't prove anything.
It might be just a misunderstanding.
Okay, I'll go with you. I'm taking my wife to dinner tonight.
You booked the restaurant ready, okay?
Yeah, no problem. Leave it to me, Mr. Miller.