Mr. Miller, their bracelet is in the bouquet, and I have arranged a restaurant as well as the after-dinner entertainment.
The details are sent to your phone.
Have a nice date.
Whoever the president's wife is, she's darn happy.
Finally, to call it a day.
Hi, Grandma.
Alice, do you have any idea that ever since you finished the paperwork and jet it off for work abroad, leaving your newlywed wife behind?
I haven't had the nerve to face her for this whole year.
You'd be driving me crazy if you don't go now to pick up Ginny and bring her home.
Grandma, what did you say your name is?
Oh, oh my goodness.
What am I going to do with you?
Ginny, her name is Ginny.
All right. You don't even remember what your wife's name is.
I can take no more of you.
Hi, Mr. Miller. My name is Ginny.