Why are you? Why don't you answer my message?
The man that disappeared after I married him was heard from Loughan that year later, looking for divorce.
And on the same day I was slender?
Ginny, is this happening to Ginny again, like three years ago?
How could you give it to those bastards?
It was that scumbag who tried to rape you.
And now since you've agreed to come with terms with them, everyone would assume that you seduced him.
Don't pressure Ginny.
They outnumber at her and have made a scene of the school.
Ginny almost got expelled. What could she do?
You're right.
Ginny, I'm sorry.
I'm just very touched by the fact that you and Jason were the only ones besides Grandma.
I've always trusted me when it happens.
Ginny, you still have your boyfriend. He has faith in you as well and he's coming to pick you up.
Yeah. And he loves you so much and his family is so well off.
He might even figure out a way to help you Ginny.
I'm here.
Ginny, I know all of your shitty things. We're done.