The Panos is a prestigious family in MC City.
We can't afford to take this shit.
If we meet again, please pretend you don't know.
Okay.
Burn and help, you asshole!
Jenny couldn't sleep well for a long time afterwards,
and was always woken up by nightmares in the middle of the night.
And Jenny's comeback, X, went at Europe to study,
and was never heard from again.
Jenny stopped believing in love since then.
That's why she promised her grandmother to marry a stranger.
Is Jenny running into another scumbag like three years ago?
I don't have time for a divorce today.
8 p.m. Monday night, you decide to place.
This woman is finally willing to come out.