Ms. White, it's past eight already. Why aren't you here?
I'm sorry, I've been rather busy lately. I can't see you now.
Well, then when will we meet? Give me an exact time.
Oh, Tony, go back. I'll get back to you when I'm available.
You don't have time? Oh, you don't have one to divorce. Please tell.
People allow me to rest.
Ginny, I see you feel uncomfortable, so I brought you some medicine.
Thank you, Sophia.
Can I have a few words?
What do you want to say?
Do you know that Mr. Miller is married?
Yes.
If that's the case, you should be more wary of your conduct and not drive any wedge between Mr. and Mrs. Miller.
Do you think there's something wrong with my conduct?
Not really.
Then what's your point of telling me this? Going to call it a day.
Mr. Miller's new assistant is indeed young and pretty, but I can see she doesn't have a thing for Mr. Miller.
In case she thought Mr. Miller won't keep her around without you asking.
Yes, I'll keep an eye on her in the days to come.
Sophia?
Mr. Miller, you...
That woman told you to spy on me and you had the balls to listen to her.