Mr. Miller, I think Madam was concerned.
Concerned about me?
Do I need her concern?
And what does that have anything to do with Ginny?
As you know, Madam likes the young lady from the Garcia family
and has always wanted you two to be together.
And so she's worried that you're
falling for other women.
Instead of worrying about my wife on paper,
she's concerned about my young assistant.
Madam knows that you married to appease your grandmother.
But Ginny is different.
She is young, beautiful.
And your personal secretary, the most important thing
is that you began to fight for divorce
shortly after Ginny became your secretary.
For whatever reason I married that woman,
as long as that marriage license is there, she's mine.
Your boss should be glad that she didn't touch that woman.
Or I will make her regret it for the rest of her life.
Mr. Miller, then I am.
And keeping your job at M. Group
is the greatest mercy I've ever shown.