In your theory, then, male doctors can't treat female patients?
It's not the same.
Mr. Miller, maybe you don't care about your reputation, but I do.
A man and a woman are judged differently when a man does something that's called playful.
But a woman does the same. She's slutty.
It could get even worse like what happened in office last time that stirred up all the rumors.
Sorry, I just wanted to get you back to the hospital as soon as possible to take care of your work.
I wasn't being thoughtful.
Can you walk on your own?
I hurt my arm, not feet.
Yes, I can walk.
Are you scared of me, Ginny?
I'm Mr. Miller. I'm not scared of you. I'm just afraid my husband will look at you a list.
You times like this, my happy does come into a handy.
I'm not going to get anyone to speculate ever again.
Mr. Miller! Mr. Miller, please get in the car now, and it will offer you a thorough examination.
Are you blind or what? Ginny's the one who's hurt.
Give her a thorough examination right now.
Make sure to cross every T and dot.
Holler if you're not feeling well. Don't hold back.
Uh, thank you, Mr. Miller. I'm fine now.
Okay, go to rest. I'll have dinner brought over later.
Mr. Miller, there's really no need to.
Mr. Miller, your wife made up an excuse for not showing up and even turned her phone off.
There's no place for losers at M Group.