Grandma, why are you still up at this time?
I couldn't get hold of you. I'd be worried sick.
Oh Grandma, I was too drowsy and passed out.
Did you have dinner, Ginny?
Have you been under a lot of pressure at work lately?
Get another job if it's too demanding. Don't wear yourself out.
I'm fine Grandma. Don't worry about me.
What about you? Are you two tutoring the students?
I've got plenty of time.
Tutoring is not just earning me money, but also keeping my mind active.
Ginny, it's been a year.
Is my husband in love still work?
I haven't had the chance to meet him at all.
Grandma, ever since I got married.
All you talk about is your grandson in line the phone.
Do you still care about me anymore?
Oh, how could your grandma not care for you?
I'm happy. I know you guys are busy with work and I'm going to go to New York.
To see you two and to drop by my long time BFF.
Shit, Grandma comes to New York City. There's no way to keep the divorce under wraps.