Ginny, I'm bad at you. You're the only one who can help me. If you don't see it for me, I'll kill myself.
Sofia, let go of my arm.
I'm not letting you go where I'm dead. Don't you understand that?
Let it go!
Mr. Miller, I've apologized to Ginny. Please forgive me. Don't kick me out.
Bruce?
No, no.
I need to call Dr. Mary. Dr. Mary, I need you here right now. Please come.
I told Sofia to leave M Group. It had nothing to do with you. Okay.
I know. I'm not as stupid as she is.
Sofia has been transferred to the West, not for long, but she's already lying her pocket pretty well.
Sofia looks like a decent person. I never thought that she would do it under your nose.
The situation here is quite complex. I'm gonna have to stay for a while. If you can't handle the climate, I'll have Bruce take you back first.
It's okay. I can handle it.
Ginny, don't be so stupid if this happens again.
I didn't want to be stupid. It was an instinctive reaction at the moment.
Does your husband know that you hurt?