Alice, Bruce said Sofia has had your mother in check, and she shouldn't be bothering
Ginny anymore.
Sofia said that Madam has been kinking up the notch lately because the lady from the
Garcia family is about to graduate and return home.
It's not her business.
I can do my own decision.
She's your mother after all.
Will it affect her reputation if you act like this in this situation?
Reputation?
Alice, you went this far for Ginny.
Are you having the thing for her?
Do you think I'll watch you and Bruce getting pushed around and not do anything?
You're treating Ginny like she's one of yours and no one can push her around.
Hello, Mr. Miller.
I really appreciate your offer, but I've got someone to pick me up.
You can go then?
How are their things prepared?
Alice, you have so many elite lawyers and M group.
Did you really get cuckoded by your wife?