What are you gonna do if I don't sign it this what sign the agreement and everything else is negotiable
Do I look stupid to you?
Tell kistan if he really wants a divorce
Let's make an appointment and go to civil affairs bureau if he wants to cheat money from me that I'm sorry
He won't get a dime
Any problems Alice your wife is stunning
You have half an hour
Your wife won't sign the divorce papers why is she acting like that?
Who the hell is she?
It's not that she's not willing to sign it. It's that she's not willing to pay the ten million dollars and damages
I don't care you take care of it
The compensation clause is taken out miss white. Would you check it again?
What else do I need to do?
You're in the dark about what your husband does for a living aren't you?
Does it have anything to do with me?
Seems like she does have no idea who Alice is
She's gonna cry over the spilled milk after Alice reveals it to her after the divorce goes into effect
I will now file the divorce petition with the court
And I will notify you and kistan to complete the procedures in one month
Okay