You can let that married woman go, okay?
What's the problem with being married?
Her husband is definitely not as good-looking rich as I am, but I really want her.
She won't be able to escape no matter what.
She's mine!
Don't try to lay a finger on her.
Is she yours?
What do you mean one of yours?
She's your assistant, not your wife.
I caught her, and she falls from me.
What does it have anything to do with you?
Alice, if you want her, go get her.
Regardless if she's married or not.
I don't believe there is a woman in this world who would say no to Alice.
Do I really want her? I don't know.
But it doesn't just be off to see her being so intimate with that guy.
Maybe because my marriage was a failure.
I envy her husband for having such a nice woman.
Ginny, your boss's wife is cheating on him,
and he's sobbing and heart broke.
You better come and take him home.
I've done everything I can to get a pretty ear, and it's up to Alice himself to make a move.
That's what happened to him. His wife cheated on him.