Mr. Miller, this is his schedule of activities for your birthday party.
Oh, such a perfect match.
If only Chinyu was his wife.
Ah, what a pity he married someone else.
Alias, I'm back. I missed you so much.
Who are you? What did you miss me?
That's a pretty director and brutal way to turn down a wall.
Alice, don't you remember me?
I'm Olivia Garcia.
You used to hug me, we were both kids.
You're Alice's wife?
Where did you get the balls to stay here?
You shameless bitch.
Have you not disgraced him enough? Get out.
What? What are you doing here?
Apologize to her right now.
Have you lost your mind?
You're being mean to me because of a woman who cheated on you?
This woman has slipped without the man.
Are you going to pretend nothing happened?
Ms. Garcia, I'm Mr. Miller's assistant.
And what does it have to do as Mr. Miller who I sleep with?
Chinyu's right. It's none of my business who she sleeps with.
Why am I feeling upset about it?