Alice, sorry.
I know that if I say I like you now,
it will make people think that you got divorced because of me
and overlooked the fact that that woman cheated on you first.
But I like you so much that I can't wait for the whole world to know.
I know. You don't have to like me.
But please don't hurt my heart.
First straight trauma it is, but I may work on men.
Don't play that game in front of me.
You think I got divorced because of you?
You think too highly of yourself?
You get the hell out of my house right now.
I don't want to waste another second with you.
It has always rejected women from his life.
I've tried so many ways to get close to him and he turned me down.
All along.
How did that woman come and go from his house as she pleases?
And get so close to him.