It's not that men can recognize a scheming woman, it's just that some men pretend dumb.
What are you laughing at?
Am I laughing?
I had nothing to do with that woman.
Mr. Miller, this is your private stuff, you don't have to tell me.
Mr. Miller, if there's nothing else...
Jenny, remember what I told you.
What?
Remember that you're my assistant, at or out of workplace.
Nobody gets to push you around because you're one of mine.
You don't have to be afraid of Olivia.
You're the Garcia family behind her.
Mr. Miller.
As long as you're still working for me.
I'm group. We'll protect you.
You got it?
I got it. Thank you, Mr. Miller.
Ms. White, somebody would like to see you. Please get in.
Who is that somebody?
Ms. White, you'll know when you get there.
Now she's here.
Leave us alone.
Ms. White, excuse me for inviting you here in this manner.