I am Mr. Miller's mom.
Mrs. Miller, what do you want to see me?
Miss Wyatt, have a seat.
You can just say it.
Why don't you sit down and have a cup of tea and we'll talk about it.
Are you afraid that I poisoned the tea?
Do I look like a bad person?
Well, not a bad person who might take a guess like this.
I just want to know what you think about Alice.
What do you feel about him?
Would any girls fancy him?
These years Mr. Miller has been at the top of the list of men in New York City would like to marry.
Of course girls fancy him.
So do you like him?
Do you want to marry him?
You could tell me the truth.
And if you like him, I'll let him marry you and we'll be mother and daughter-in-law.
Mrs. Miller, I'm Mr. Miller's assistant and our past only crossed out of workplace.
I don't have anything for him that I'm not supposed to have.
What do you mean something you're not supposed to have?
Love is the most wonderful thing in the world and the most uncontrollable emotion.
How is it something you're not going to have?
Mrs. Miller, I'm married and I love my husband so very much.
So much. Really?
Do you believe yourself when you say that?
Last Friday night, after you signed the divorce papers, you ran off to Alice's place and stayed for the night.
Love your husband.
You're stalking me?
More than stalking you.
I've got to the bottom, including how you seduced your neighbor in your sophomore year.