Mrs. Miller you can just stop beating around the bush. What exactly is your point? Leave your job right now and leave Alice
Leave New York City and never said put in this town again. I'm sorry, but I'm going to let you down
I'll never leave my job much less New York City
You two look fairly cute, but there are many girls prettier than you
Are you sure you can have Alice wrapped around your finger?
My job is not having him wrapped around my finger. I'm giving you two choices right now
One is to leave New York City right now. The other is to leave after you fall from grace
Ginny, you're smart. You know what to choose
My butt off day and night only to make money so I can have a place of my own in New York City
I've never been so delusional about this man. I did nothing wrong
You shouldn't have forgotten how you left MC City in the Inglorious manner back there
Said I'm not leaving my job, and I'm not leaving New York City
Mrs. Miller if you want to play dirty and go ahead. I'll play along