What?
Ginny is the woman we've been trying to turn off but in vain.
Then an old lady was worried about me going after her and protected her well.
For more than a year, I wasn't able to find out who Alice was married to, however I tried.
So Ginny is Mr. Miller's wife?
Then why didn't she reveal herself?
That's what's so spooky about this woman.
She goes to great length to get close to Alice, first to make Alice fall in love with her over time
and reveal who she is when the time is right so that she can secure her position if the new Mrs. Miller.
Mr. Miller is kept in the dark about it?
Alice has always been obedient to the old lady and was serious about forming a family with that woman.
It was only after he misidentified someone else as Ginny
and thought that his wife was cheating on him that he wanted a divorce.
So what do we do now?
They have signed the divorce agreement.
In a month they will inevitably meet as they go to court to walk through the procedures.
Ginny presumably is waiting for this day.
So we have one month to either seal the divorce without letting them meet each other or come up with the smoking gun.
Proving Ginny was cheating on him.
Okay, I'll take care of that madam.
Mr. Miller!
How much has Alice heard?