Bruce, send this woman to Africa.
No, please Mr. Miller, forgive me, I won't dare to do something.
Let's go.
Please, honey, wish us you a happy birthday.
And get rid of that filthy woman who cheated on you.
Did he really hear it?
For all of these years, I've done so many things for your benefit.
How dare you say something today about Chining?
This is the very last time.
Otherwise, you'll be soon seeing some of my tricks.
You came all this way today to warn me not to touch your young assistant.
Are you serious?
It seems he hasn't found out who Jenny is yet.
But he knows that she's on our radar.
This has to be done discreetly and our names must not get involved.
Yes, ma'am.
Just do it now!
Let's get her out of New York City today in the most glorious way possible.
Thank you.