Sofia, where are we going to get the wedding invitations for you and Mr. Miller?
Look at her.
It's clear around the corner the new Miss Miller is right on the way.
I know right.
Geez, stop making fun of me.
We're not.
Assistant Jenny, my feet hurt.
Go get me a glass of juice.
Little bitch, are you deaf?
Why would you order me around?
You're just an assistant serving tea around.
How come we a pride?
Believe it or not, I can get you kicked out of New York City.
Another one wanting me to get the hell out of New York City.
I am Mr. Miller's assistant and the only orders I take are from Mr. Miller.
Try to become Mrs. Miller first, then you can bark orders at me and I'll be happy to lick
her boot.
Go off me!