Alice, please don't blame Jenny. She didn't mean to hit me.
Her tells she is the junior, spoils the fuck.
Of course I won't blame her.
Be glad your fist didn't hit her just now, otherwise.
Hey, you good?
We're going to play murder mystery, Alice.
Jenny, you guys wanna join us?
You guys have fun, I'm not in.
Not interested either.
Alright then, let's go. Let's go have fun.
Olivia, come on.
Mr. Miller, thank you.
Why don't you go play the game?
Is there anything you want to tell me?
Yes, but I don't dare to say it.
Miss White, if you tell Mr. Miller about the ladies' visit today, your grandmother and MCC will be in danger.
You have so much to attach you.
Your grandma doesn't.