Mr. Miller, I'm going to see if the guests are having a good time.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry about what happened today, but I've taken care of it.
And she won't dare to bother you again. You can concentrate on your work, okay?
With a few words, Mr. Miller had the fear and the sense of how the loss hit within me smashed to pieces.
If I were her husband, I would have held her tightly in my arm.
You're sharing that with me by her side. There's nothing to fear.
I'm just a boss. The man who's entitled to hug her can never be me.
Thank you.
I'll let the driver take you back if you're not in the mood.
Well, have you ever played murder mystery before?
I'm never played, but it sounds fun.
Hey! I thought you guys were incoming. I got upset about it for a while. Come and join us.
Have a seat.
We are a team, Olivia. Let's go over there.
You're my wife. There's no rush.
We got plenty of time later back in the room.
It's my date. I've got such a gorgeous wife.
Want to play husband and wife with Ginny?