Afro-dizi?
Jenny. Jenny.
Mr. Miller, who drugged us? Why did he set us up?
There's a strange scent in the room.
I smelled it as soon as I entered the house. I thought I was perfume.
So, Mr. Miller, the drug was put in the room first.
It's possible that it wasn't aimed at you and me?
Oh no. This room was originally arranged for me and Ken.
If I had been honored to influence of drugs and sex with Ken,
I would have been ashamed and forced to leave New York City in the most possible and glorious manner.
It's not random. Everyone thinks Ken is a playboy and will ace fingers on every woman.
You think it's me?
No. Your mother. I think she's coming from me.
And Ken is nothing more than a randomly picked tool.
But no one expected you and him to switch rules before the game started.
Jenny, don't worry. Nobody's gonna walk away from this.