Wrap them up with transparent material, and deliver it to purchase his office when he gets back.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Miller, I'll leave you to it then.
Felix, you ask Bruce to send her off.
You better get back now, and I'll put you back on the trip.
The second you heard that the assistant Jenny has woken up, you pulled the trip and came over, and you ignored her.
What's on your mind?
Miss White, Mrs. Miller has already flown abroad, and those minions under her have been taken care of.
No one will be looking to trouble you again.
I appreciate it.
Miss White, what a coincidence.
Mr. Purchase?
You remember me.
Are you dining alone with your friends?
With my boyfriend, got a problem with that?
Oh, looks like the cheating is real.
Alice, if a man is betrayed, how would you comfort him?
What are you trying to say?
I just saw your wife, and her lover, dining at this restaurant.
Would you like to go over and say hello?