Timoth, Alice, wait, you were a husband and wife after all, and you're not the only man
in the world who's been betrayed and form her about the divorce proceedings tomorrow, understand?
Consider it done, don't worry, as long as she's in New York City she can't get away with it
to come to New York City Courthouse tomorrow and the proceedings, okay?
What is it? One of the three great things in life.
Oh, let's see, promotion? Is it salary raise or husband dead?
You're close. The lawyer notified me to go to the divorce proceedings tomorrow.
I'm going to be a single woman again soon, although my previous life was not much different
than being single. The marital status does complicate things, and I did not
to have any fancy ideas towards other students.
Join your day, huh? We must celebrate tonight.
Cheers! Cheers! To a single life!
Grandma, I'm out having me all with Jason and Mick.
It's Jenny, right? It's MC Central Hospital.