It was all just hearsay, and nobody saw what happened back then, and we all must have our own judgment about what's wrong and what's right.
Here's say, the video clip of her cotton bed is still here, I'll offer it to anyone interested, for free.
I'm not interested. I'm busy here.
You've been defending this little bitch.
I'm not interested in that.
Does she teach you how to seduce men?
You filthy slanderer. Go away!
Oh, what are you doing? What are you doing?
I'm not interested in stirring up trouble in the hospital and slandering. We are now taking you back for questions.
When did I slander anyone? This is arbitrary arrest. I'm suing you for slandering.
Come on, officer. This phone contains video clips, showing how this couple acted up in the hospital, as well as their verbal abuse and defamation behaviors.
Oh, rest them. I did swear. So what? I was swearing at my own family. Does that have anything to do with others?
I'm not the same genie anymore.
But you guys are still the same, as nasty as ever.
You guys are not worth the time of day.
You watch your little bitch.
Miss White, you foretell a thing like a prophet.
I'm not a prophet, but it will have its eye heart for that couple.
Now they're both going to be in custody for a while.
A few days' detention is too lenient on them. Take the evidence I gave you earlier and submit them.
I'm going to make everyone who has sent me a back then pay the price.
Don't worry. I'm on it.
Grandma.
Genie. My grandson-in-law didn't come with you?
Grandma, he is not available to see you. Why don't you come with me to New York City for him?
This way I can trip Grandma to go to New York City for better health care.
What? My condition!
Grandma, do you want to see him or not?
Grandma has so much to tell him. I'm only afraid he won't want to listen to.
An old woman nagging.
You're a senior. If he didn't listen to you, I'd make him regret.
How am I going to come and feast and play along by then?
Sounds like my granddaughter has a big say in the new family.
Okay. I'll go to New York City as you said.
Okay. I'll make the arrangement then.
No hurry. I have something for you.
Genie. Your father's compensation for the car accident
and the money I left you are all in this card.
The passcode is your birthday.
Grandma, I am making money. I don't want your money. I just want you to be healthy.
Full girl. I know you are making money.
Some of the money is the compensation for your father's death and some is saved by me.
I hope you will be good to yourself. You've got to take it.
Grandma, I'll take it then.
That's my girl.
I'll figure out a way to return the money to Grandma.
Genie. It's been a year and a half since you and Caston got married.
But I don't see your belly getting round.
Grandma, we're still young. There's no rational babies.
Caston is 28 and you'll be 24 in a few days.
Isn't it about the time?
Although, baked in the character of the child brought up by my longtime bestie.
Oh, men are playful creatures in nature.
It's more settled.
Be a miracle to my belly round up.
Caston and I haven't even had the chance to get laid.
Grandma is getting late. He should get the rest.
Do you think your grandma is nosy? Or are you hiding things from me?
No, Grandma, you know that I haven't even promoted for six months and I traveled a lot for work.
It's not the time to have babies.
Cast, you're right.
To have a stay in the family.
Totally. The inside of a veteran teacher is indeed something else.
Yeah, Grandma, you should rest.
Miss White, what the hell do you want?
Mr. Lin, please tell Keith that I can't divorce him for the time being.
Miss White, we can't go back on our words.
You signed the divorce agreement.
Today's the day to wrap this up. Why are you backing out now?
I just want to postpone it and not cancel it all together.
Why so?
Because my grandma is sick and is bringing up her grandson in the hall day long.
If I tell her I'm divorcing, it will only make her conditions worse.
So I thought of waiting for her before going through the divorce thing.
Can we have some decency here?
If your grandma's all, just take your boyfriend.
Why must you hold up the thing with Caston?
My boyfriend?
Right. I told him I had a boyfriend before.
Whatever I got myself into.
This woman is obviously stalling because she has found out about Caston's true identity.
She wants more money.
Name your price.
What price?
What? You don't know how much you want yourself?
I just want my grandmother to get well.
Do you even believe yourself? You don't love him.
So what clicked her?
How much money it will take for you to divorce him?
Who cares about his money?
I'm not accused and is truly a scumbag.
It's not like I can't make money. What the hell wants his money?
What?
It's just unbelievable.
Cheating on you with that straight face.
For the divorce proceedings.
And then lying about your grandmother.
Grandma, they're getting sick.
It's haunted.
But don't worry. This time, I will make it.
What? Her grandmother's sick?
That's what she said.
Well, send her some money.
So that she will take care of her grandma.
And then you can wait until her grandma gets better.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Sir, my mom says she doesn't want to hear your voice.
Place.
You tell grandma that the woman's grandmother seems to be sick.
What?
Jenny's grandmother is sick.
What is it earlier? You little brat?
Grandma Jane?
Miss Merler, this morning.
Where is Jenny?
Jenny is on her annual leave 10 days.
It's our busiest time toward the end of the year and she takes her annual leave at this time?
If I remember correctly, the president is going to be important.
The coffee is cold. We'll get another one.
Yes, sir.
The president is like a ticking time bomb.
Jenny, come back to rescue me.
Jenny, I want to have a few words with you.
What is it, grandma?
This kid isn't just a looker.
Those eyes are pure innocence. Hard not to like her.
If you need help, give me a shout.
We're family.
As for my grandson.
Until you two officially split.
Your husband and wife.
And it's his duty to lend a hand.
Okay, I won't bother him. I don't owe him a favor.
Jenny.
Is Kestin done with his work? Can I see him tomorrow?
I'll talk to him tomorrow.
Kestin, I'm really sorry.
My grandma is seriously ill and she keeps asking to see her grandson in law every day.
I can't break the news to her, so I am not going to divorce you for now.
If you are available, could you please come to the hospital to visit her?
Just act like a loving couple for a while.
And once her conditions have improved, I promise I'll...
Jenny, why don't you just call Kestin?
Grandma, he's busy at work and it's not convenient for him to answer calls sometimes.
Is that right?
Kestin, could you reply to my message if you see it?
Sure.
Thank you for agreeing to see my grandmother.
May I ask when you are coming so I can make the arrangements?
Fine. I'll meet your grandma, but I don't want to see you.
Let's schedule a time. I'll make sure to avoid you.
Tomorrow afternoon.
When the hell is Jenny coming back?
I don't know, Mr. Mother. Get lost.
I've sent you the address. Please don't tell Grandma that we are good and good divorce. Thank you very much.
Grandma, Kestin has agreed to come and see you tomorrow.
Oh, oh, oh, good, good. Jenny should grab a tidy up a bit.
It's the first time meeting your husband. I gotta leave a good impression on him.
Grandma, he's your grandson-in-law and not some big shot.
Oh, he's more important than any big shot in my heart.
Oh, Kestin will speak?
Come in. Come in. You must be Kestin.
Grandma, how are you?
What a candy on the eyes. Sit down. Let me have a good look at you.
You heard from Jenny that you're busy with work.
How are you getting along with Jenny then?
Anna, I want to have a private chat with my grandson-in-law. Would you excuse us?
Yeah, sure. That guy is just smoking hot.
Thank you. I'm so happy that you took time amid your busy schedule to come see me.
It's the least I can do.
And Jenny, I hadn't spent any time together before you married.
But because there's no spark between you two.
It's so important to take time and cultivate the relationship so you can't sacrifice family for work.
Yes, sure.
Jenny has a strong personality. She doesn't show her weaknesses in front of others.
She just keeps it to herself, so please take care of her.
Sure.
Kestin, did you and Jenny have a spat or something else?
Don't worry, Grandma. We are fine. As you just said, we didn't have any chemistry between us before marriage
and have been apart for most of the time after, so we are still in the bonding stage.
After more than a year of marriage and they're still just bonding, they definitely have a problem.
You know this time, Jenny has been putting on a happy face, coaxing me along the way.
Kestin, just be honest with me.
Are you two not doing well in your relationship?
Come in. You must be Kestin.
What a candy on the eyes. Sit down. Let me have a good look at you.
How are you?
From Jenny, that you're busy with work. How are you getting along with Jenny then?
To have a private chat with my grandson-in-law. Would you excuse us?
Yes, sure. That guy is just smoking hot.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm so happy that you took time amid your busy schedule to come see me.
It's the least I can do.
You and Jenny, I hadn't spent any time together before you married, but because there's no spark between you two.
It's so important to take time and cultivate the relationship so you can't sacrifice family for work.
Yes, sure.
Jenny has a strong personality. She doesn't show her weaknesses in front of others. She just keeps it to herself, so please take care of her.
Sure.
Kestin, did you and Jenny have a spat or something else?
Don't worry, grandma. We are fine.
As you just said, we didn't have any chemistry between us before marriage and have been apart for most of the time after it.
So we are still in the bonding stage.
After more than a year of marriage and they're still just bonding, they definitely have a problem.
At all this time, Jenny has been putting on a happy face, coaxing me along the way.
Kestin, just be honest with me.
Are you two not doing well in your relationship?
Can you handle it if I tell you that your granddaughter has been sleeping around?
Take care of yourself, grandma. I'll come to visit again.
Are you two divorced?
Not officially yet, but we're heading back.
Why? No love or...
Other reasons?
Any chance of patching things up?
Thank you for telling me the truth.
Don't tell Jenny yet until I figure out how to break it to her.
Sure. Take care.
Now, it seems that the marriage I tried hard to set up has a secret, mom.
Come to see me.
Look, he's also considerate.
A single room arranged for two caregivers to take turns looking after me.
You don't have to come to the hospital today.
Take a good rest.
Okay then, remember to eat on time. I'll come and see you after work tomorrow.
Me and Kestin are both good kids.
Could it be that fate hasn't dealt the card?
Kestin, thanks for visiting my grandma. She's walking on air now.
She sure knows how to put on a show.
Just remember to not back out at the divorce this time.
You have my word.
Grandma, why switch to the regular word and let go of the caregiver Kestin's grandma arranged for you?
I don't want to waste the money.
What should you talk about with Kestin yesterday?
Jenny, if you decide to get divorced, go ahead. I'm backing you up.
Look, Kestin is just tied up with work. We're fine.
When I asked you to marry Kestin, I thought he was someone you could entrust your whole life to.
I want you to have a complete and happy family and someone who loves and protects you on behalf of me.
Grandma, I understand.
No, no, you don't, you don't. You marry because of me and try to sustain this broken marriage for my sake.
That isn't what I wanted. I have only one wish and that's for you to be happy.
If this marriage brings you nothing but pains and stress, why hold on to it?
Grandma, you really think so?
I'll Kestin now.
Set a time to go through the divorce proceedings.
Kestin, I can proceed with the divorce now. When do you think we should do it?
Miss White, do all the documents and I hope you'll be on time this time.
Grandma, take a rest. Come even need anything. I'm going to get back to get the marriage license.
Madam, your grandson-in-law looks like a one-in-a-million man. Is it in a shame to just let him go like that?
However true that is, Ginny's happiness is what matters most.
Ginny?
Grandma agreed to my divorce. I can now get at the divorce. Help me find the marriage license.
Absolutely. We're going to turn over every rock that we have to.
Kestin Miller. Kestin Miller.
Same last name as my flawless boss, Alice Miller, but the two are worlds apart.
When will you go for the proceedings?
We'll come along with you and play a festive song then.
It's a divorce. Let's keep it low key, but I'll treat you guys to a feast in advance to celebrate my divorce.
Thank you.
Ginny, what are you so excited about?
Isn't it obvious?
It's got a big carried away and ain't too much.
You're not pregnant, are you?
It's one of three best things in life.
Mr. Miller, I have something to attend to this afternoon and I need to ask for a half day off.
Look at that happy face. She really pregnant?
Both of you can take the afternoon off.
Mr. Miller, extra leave for us again?
Any objections?
No, not at all.
Alice, your wife seems to be really excited this time.
Why is Ginny here?
Your wife is really out of this world.
Even that stereotypical outfit is not going to hide her beauty.
It's a pity that the man who owns her is not you, but another guy.
What are you saying?
Is it that woman in the business to her at the entrance is my wife?
You're not going to tell me you don't even recognize your own wife.
Are you?
Ginny White? It's her.
I can't believe that I never had any doubts.
Doesn't she know that I am Keston and Alice?
We've been wrong all this time along.
What if this call goes out and it's not Ginny answers?
What are you waiting for? Make the call.
Pick up the phone.
Pick up the phone, please.
Ginny.
Keston, I'm here. Where are you guys?
It's really her.
Oh my god, so Ginny White is my lawful spouse.
And who can rightfully claim her, no matter who she has in her heart,
or whose child she cares, it can't change the fact that she is my wife.
Alice, what's wrong with you? Get out of the car!
No, I'm not getting a divorce anymore.
Are you guys kidding me?
She backed out of it last time and it's your turn now.
Tell her my decision.
I just go.
Mr. Burgess, where's Keston?
Sorry, Miss White. Keston said he doesn't want to go through with this divorce.
Are you guys kidding me?
Miss White, you both had your turns. It evens out now.
Is this some kind of game to you? Is the voice a joke?
Why don't you go back first? I'll let you know when he changes his mind.
It was my fault that I missed the appointment the other day.
And you guys canceled it today, so let's call it even.
Why don't we schedule another date, tomorrow or the day after tomorrow?
It depends on Keston's mood.
He's the one who asked for the divorce, and now he's backing out of it.
What's wrong with him?
You're right, there is something wrong with him.
Miss White, why don't you leave him alone?
Your marriage has always been a castle in the air.
Why don't you just start over with another guy?
Why the long face? You know she has a boyfriend.
Let me ask you this.
What are the three best things in a woman's life?
Promotions, salary increase, and the demise of her husband.
Oh, Jenny was so happy this morning because she was divorcing me.
Keston's really sick.
He's the one who cried for divorce, and now he's going to go back for it.
Does he think marriage is a game?
You know how to drive, don't drive.
Mr. Miller.
Just passing by. Happy at work.
And pissed off on your break.
Mr. Miller, excuse me if there's nothing else.
I'll give you a ride.
Thank you, Mr. Miller. I'll head home now unless there's anything else you need.
Is it possible that she hasn't found out where marriage is like me?
Or maybe she knows everything or refused to accept me because she found another guy?
Mr. Miller, please stop acting like this.
Who the hell am I to?
Mr. Miller, you're on my boss.
And?
Nothing.
See you then.
Prom was Mr. Miller today, something's not right.
Mr. Miller, here's everything you asked about Jenny.
Ms. White had a tough time over the years.
Her father passed away when she was five, and she was almost raped by her neighbor who covered her during her sophomore year.
The guy then planted the blame on Ms. White for introducing him in the first place.
What about her uncle and aunt who had been bullying her?
Ms. White has sent them both to prison. They'll be stuck in there for a whole week, the most.
Find a way to have these bastards detained there for the rest of her lives. You understand?
I got it, Mr. Miller.
What about the man who almost raped her in the past?
He's from a small family of M.C. City. Mr. Miller, do you want?
This man doesn't need to exist.
Got it. Consider it done.
Because of these things you don't believe in love anymore, right?
That's why you married me following our grandmother's advice.
Find me the best doctors from all over the world.
Now, I need to find the best treatment for Ginny's grandma.
Okay?
Hi, grandma.
What are you doing here?
Have you come to see me hit the roof over your divorce?
Huh? Is that what it is?
I'm not getting a divorce. Ginny can only be my wife.
What did you say? You are not lying to me.
You're right. Ginny is a nice girl, and I had some misunderstanding about her before.
Now, I want to protect her and live the rest of my life with her.
Alice, is this all true?
But she doesn't want to be with me.
What do you want me to do? I've got to make this straight up front.
There's nothing much I can help you with.
It's your wife, and you've got to win her over yourself.
Grandma, what? Ginny, the divorce thing didn't go well?
He's been walking back on it.
But don't worry, Grandma. Whether he divorces or not, it won't affect our lives.
Did he say why he's not divorcing? Something must have happened.
No, he didn't say any reason.
Oh, Ginny, even though we're not locals of New York City, and you don't have your parents to back you up.
As long as I'm still breathing, I won't let Kristen take advantage of you.
Ah, no. I'm going to ask for an exclamation from Kristen's grandma.
She don't on her grandson, and you are also the apple in my eye.
Moses, you're right. I am going to give you and Ginny an explanation.
What Kesta did was just out of line.
He was the one who wanted the divorce in the first place, and now he's backing out.
What does he think Ginny is?
If he dares to show up in front of me again,
I'll break his legs. I'm fed up with it.
I just can't take this anymore.
Jane, take it easy. You want some water? Easy, don't do it.
Moses, I know you're soft-hearted. You're so soft-hearted.
But I can't take advantage of your kindness and just let this go.
It's not possible. I mean, with what he's done.
Pack up and come with me to South Mountain Manor.
You can rest off there and let's blow that brass money.
Let's blow that brass money.
Grandma, Jane, I can't afford my grandma's medicine bills.
We can spare keys since money.
No. Ginny, you need to wrap your head around this.
As long as that little rascal hasn't divorced you, your grandma is his grandma.
And he's entitled to spend his money.
He must pay the price for his unruly behavior.
Grandma, what do you think?
Ginny, I think Jane has a point.
I'm going to go with her to South Mountain Manor.
No, Grandma, calm down. This is huge.
We have a serious- Calm down.
Calm down.
How on earth am I supposed to calm down when Keston is getting on my nurse?
Actually, Keston is a nice boy.
It's just that you can't force things like marriage.
He's nice. What's so nice about him?
He's 28 years old, and he's never been in love, nor does he play around.
Then finally, he listened to me to get married.
Then he messed the whole thing up.
That sounds like a compliment.
No. It's not as bad as you make it out to be.
Come Ginny, we're going to South Mountain.
Grandma, Keston has hired us caregivers who are better at taking care of people than you.
Hurry back to your work.
Then you two take care of yourself, helping by when I have time.
You're a young girl. Go date or something. Don't dwell on us.
Leave us alone. You deserve to have a life.
Come on. How does a married woman go on dating?
I don't want to take the blame for cheating.
Hey Ginny, my shoes got dirty.
Come wipe them for me.
Olivia, why would I do that?
I'm not a major client of your company.
Even if you are a big shot customer, it's not my job to wipe your shoes.
Alice should be divorced by now.
So, I'll be the wife of your boss down the road.
It's your opportunity to wipe my shoes.
Don't make me fire you.
Big news.
Miss Miller said he wasn't getting divorced and bought a giant diamond ring for his wife,
which is worth at least $30 million.
Wow, $30 million?
The president surely loves his wife dearly.
Who was dreaming of Mary and the president?
Why is Alice still dragging about the divorce?
There's shameless bitches of slop from the slums.
What trick did she use on Alice?
She's squaring off with me now.
I miss with Alice's wife, but for sure I can make you suffer, bitch.
We've got a problem.
What's going on?
The ring I put in the safe for the Mrs. is missing.
Someone must have stolen it.
Why me is my privacy?
Did you press out? I need a surgeon.
How could it be my purse?
How could it?
Because I couldn't do it myself.
I found it!
You bitchin' daze?
Come with me to the police station right now.
What are you doing?
This little bitch stole the ring you bought for your wife.
What are you talking about? I wouldn't do that.
It's something you can't afford in your lifetime, so of course you've covered it.
She didn't need to steal it. The ring was bought for her.
How so? Isn't this meant to be given to your wife?
Yes. Jenny White is my wife.
What?
On the contrary, you are the person who set her up.
I've asked security to pull up the surveillance.
You're going to jail. Security!
Mr. Miller, did you make a mistake?
No. Jenny. I'm Jane's grandson.
Kestin Miller. The one who married you.
How is it you? Our marriage was arranged by our grandmothers.
Mr. Miller, you don't have to accept it, and if you back out now, I'll agree.
I'm only afraid that you'll back out.
I love you not because you're my wife, but because you are who you are.
I still owe you the proposal. So, Jenny, will you marry me?
I do. You scare me again.
Seems you were tired last night. Why didn't you continue?
Come on, we have a meeting in the morning, honey. Go over.
Where's the diamond ring I gave you? Why aren't you wearing it?
It's $3 million. What if I drop it? Can I buy a super expensive safe and lock it inside?
You're happy I'll buy you another one if you drop it.
Give me another ten if I lose it.
Grandma's what are you doing?
It's one year into your marriage, and you're still not pregnant.
We're concerned.
You're not shooting blanks, are you, grandson?
I was shopping for medication online for you last night.
What are you talking about, Grandma?
This family is welcoming a new member!
Oh, this is wonderful news.
Oh, finally have a grandchild.