How can I help you?
Heather, sir, from Creative, I'm here to get your son off on the new camping puzzle.
And as for you, I don't need employees to pull stunts like that, so...
You're fired.
When do they call you Declan Ice?
So, Heather, what do you think about this proposal?
I think it's good.
But it could be better.
For instance, the targeted demographic could be expanded.
And here, maybe adding some interactive elements.
Don't press it.
My money on you, Heather.
So don't let me down.
Hey, dude.
Waitressing out Wayne's party tonight?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm in.
No, I don't mind serving those rich snobs.
As long as the money's right.
Okay.
You see ya.
Get me on the guest list to the Wayne's party tonight.
Be nice to the customers.
Good smile.