Jesus Christ, Michael, I'm getting changed in here.
Be at this location in an hour.
The client doesn't appreciate tardiness.
No.
Mass dancers don't engage in those kind of transactions.
We signed a contract.
Don't forget, Betty.
There's a special clause in our contract.
If someone's willing to spend $100,000...
And I don't have the right to...
Refuse.
That's right.
This guy's willing to spend $100,000 and some girl he doesn't know.
Must be a cuckoo.
The Empire Hotel?
This is where my regular job is.
If they see me, they're like, this, I'm going to get fired.
I'm sorry, Betty.
Believe me when I say that the client is someone you do not want to cross.
Think about your mom in her medical bills?
I mean, you don't want to disappoint her.
Do you?