Hey, Nike.
What's crackin'?
You okay?
God, Anthony, you scared me.
We're closed.
Mr. Wade, I'm afraid this is not our business hour yet.
A girl from last night, Michael, where is she?
She didn't show up last night?
No, she did.
She did, but, uh, listen, Michael,
I don't have any time for your fucking games.
You're gonna find her for me,
or you and your club here are gonna be, uh, in hell.
I'm sorry if my girl didn't live up to your standards,
Marcus, how about I send you two more?
That's compensation.
You know what?
Like, I'm gonna make this a little bit fucking easier for you.
Why don't you just tell me everything you know about her?
And I mean everything.
That's all.
Now.