I want you to fire Betty in that idiot Anthony.
One sec?
Did I save my game?
Okay, I did it. Okay.
So, fire Betty and Anthony.
Right.
I'm sorry, I'm afraid I can't do that.
Why?
Because he's not qualified.
Sir.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Anthony Senny, the eldest son of the Senny family.
Senny?
Senny.
My father had me experience all the entry-level positions at the hotel
so I could learn how to manage and operate everything
with a little more efficiency.
Kelly.
I'm gonna have to ask you to stop your unreasonable behavior
and leave immediately.
Please get off my property.
You're actually kicking me out over that bitch?
Is Senny preparing to sort of work against the Gambino?
No, this is just between me and you.
I'm gonna have to ask you to stop harassing Betty.
And if you don't,
I will be forced to show you no mercy.
How could she make both you and Mark so devoted to her?
Well, for one thing, she's a better person than you.
So, for the sake of your Betty,
perhaps we can work together this time.
I'll help you snatch Betty from Marcus.
And Marcus will be mine.
Deal?
No. Please leave.
Listen to me very carefully.
No one is to know about my identity, especially Betty.
Yes, sir.
Okay.