I knew it. That bitch.
The Gambino family is gonna showcase these beauties
at the Global Jewelry Convention next week.
Each piece is extremely valuable,
and they believe we can protect them better
than a security company.
You're right, Han. Where did you get that ring from?
Don't lie to me. I'll be able to tell.
So, wonderful John's guys.
We hired to escort a batch of jewels to the docks
and I swiped the jewel from the stash.
Take that ring off. Let me see it.
Who are you supposed to deliver that stash to?
I don't know. All right?
Trust me. I'm just a nobody.
I don't know anything.
All right. You feel free to tell Kelly
the truth about Betty's situation
and let her know that I'm gonna get even
with her sooner or later.
As far as the ring goes, keep it amongst yourselves.
I understood.
Now, get out of my sight. Go!
Don't you have something you want to say to me?
Thank you. And I'm sorry.
I need you to understand that from here on out,
your mind, and that my words are absolute.
Don't disobey me.
Match for you.
You've just seen me as a toy, don't you?