Harrison, it is not what it looks like.
Oh, it's exactly what it looks like.
She's carrying my baby.
Enough!
What are you doing just leave?
No, not without my baby.
What are you planning on doing?
Marrying him and pretending it's his?
That's disgusting.
This is absurd security!
Get him out of here.
No need for that.
I'll leave.
Lisa, you'll regret this.
Harrison, this is an embarrassment.
I warned you not just anybody
is fit to be in this family.
We're figuring it out, right?
We're laughing.
Figuring it out?
A scandal like this as an engagement party?
The press is going to tear us apart.
Oh, and you can forget about handing you
the Happy Holiday Village Project.
There's no way in hell I'm giving it to you now.
My God.
Do you think you've earned it?
I got rid of your problem, didn't I?
I'm getting cute with me.