Thought I was on off duty
You didn't answer your phone. I had no idea where you were
Everything okay
Okay, my sister out of the hospital
I'm already big for everything
Apparently
The lives of rich people like you actually
Okay, I can I can help just hold on
Hi, yeah, dr. Fang. This is uh, this is Harrison Winkler. I have a friend
Alice Black her sister Emma is at your hospital, and I was just I was wondering if she could be moved to a
Different room
Okay, is that is that doable? Thank you. You fixed all of my problems
No wonder you want to marry and do your family
Stay in a chance
Drunk Alice. I'm sorry. I'm sorry if I offended you. I I will what if I told you you did have a chance