I'm sure he's just a few minutes away.
It's one second.
What is going on with him?
Why isn't he answering?
It's late to his own engagement.
This is how the Winthler family treats us with disrespect.
I deeply apologize.
This is not like him.
Dad, I'm sure something must have happened.
He wouldn't do this on purpose, right?
Right.
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
Badge, what the hell happened?
Car accident.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Do you have to go to the hospital?
Come on, he's fine.
Probably some brake failure or something.
Total accident.
I never mentioned brake failure.
How did you know?
Just a lucky guess.
Well, I didn't do it.
What the hell?
He's nothing but a bastard like a dog.
Why do you keep protecting him?
Well, even if he is a dog, he's my dog.
And you don't get to insult him.
You heard that?
You're nothing but a fucking dog.
You're a little pet.