Ms. Black, you're seven weeks pregnant.
Are you sure you want to terminate this pregnancy?
Positive.
Well, we can schedule a procedure for next week.
Does a father know?
He doesn't need to.
Is he the machine?
A father who can't be loved.
A child who isn't wanted.
Alice, Alice, I think I should be okay.
Harrison, what are you doing here?
Well, you disappeared without a word.
Again.
If I found your phone in the woods last night.
Yeah.
I didn't feel well, so I left early.
I'm sorry, I should have told you.
Yeah, I was worried.
I mean, I checked every hospital in LA before I found you here.
You didn't have to do that, Harrison.
Yeah, I know.
Obviously I didn't have to do that, but I care about you.
Alice, are you pregnant?