I SAVE the Clark family business from you.
YOU.
YOU'VE DISGUSTING, SPOILED, INFECTED, RAT.
DING EVEN BUDDING.
IT TELL ME BEFORE THE WEDDING.
You did it.
How many more excuses can you make?
Did you ever love me?
I love how salty.
How could I love someone who is such a nightmare everyday of my life?
How could I love someone who can make me sick?
Here at the end, all you care about is frecky love to you.
What you should really be wondering about is how a drug-free virgin like you ended up
like, since you're dying, I figured I'd let you in on a little sick.
Someone was hired to inject you with this disease.
It's a surprise you didn't figure it out for yourself.
However, jump off of the building to save the world from your disgrace.
You didn't do that, she couldn't wait.
It was frecky.
The love of your wife didn't want you.
Twenty bucks to a drugie, he was free, and you're the dirty slut.
He'd be even drinking it?
Oh, that was my act.
I wanted to watch you sit and do what you want.