Hey, you're gonna be a doctor, okay? Let me call 911.
Do you want to eat? Do you want to eat? Is that true for you?
I just want to eat.
Oh, no. It's too late.
I don't. Don't say that.
I'm so sorry. I should have been there. I thought all these news that you were happy.
It would have happened in a minute, but if I had a moment, it was really like this.
I would have done something. I would have stopped the wedding.
Shannon, I would have taken you for Ricky Trax.
I'm so sorry. I should have done more, Shannon. I should have done more.
I could never imagine someone other than me. I bothered to be so kind to me.
I'm such a fool. Let our heartless burn in my life. I'm a fool. I'm a fool.
In my next life, I will choose to forgive my next life.
I will be sure you are the happiest woman in the world.
Shannon, Shannon, Shannon, Shannon!