I told you to buy lunch for Karen and you ate it, mind to God, you are just such a...
Hey, aren't you?
I spent this with my own money, two meals or twenty meals, what's it to do with you?
Your money?
Even if you spend it, it still tracks as money, dumb.
Who is that so?
Who's money?
I think getting lunch when you're told to, from your boss,
is a simple task, and you came up with me with something so simple, that you just be fucking stupid.
You want to use my boss first?
A completely able-body woman too lazy to get her lunch?
I think she deserves the tummy ache.
You?
You are a tracks family maid.
Taking care of his girlfriend is literally your job.
Is that so hard to comprehend?
When he tracks, am I a maid?
Alright, she had me.
I don't know what game you're playing, but I'm not doing it.
Don't cause any trouble, otherwise I will not forgive you no matter how hard you bite.
Buddy?
Why would I, what did I do?
You're so tough, don't you?
It's crazy how quickly you just lost a seat in the car.
I can care less if you welcome.
Your car?
It was never yours, and it's time you learned your place.