What the hell are you doing?
You'd expect a free ride in my car to insult me?
That's Ricky tracks his family's car.
Why is he letting that bitch do that to him?
That's what you get for letting the maid drive in the car.
If you give a mouse a cookie, come on, Ricky!
Pull her out!
Why do you have to act like this?
Look, I'll forgive you about lunch.
I don't want your forgiveness.
You can walk over all I can.
Stop following me.
I have to get in the car, or I'll be exposed.
If anyone knows I'm the son of the driver,
it'll be helpful.
Ricky helped him drag me out of my own car.
It's job Ricky dealing with that ungrateful low life.
That's exactly what she deserved.
Ricky is so cool.
Dad, our driver forgot what we worked for.
Calling Ricky, asking for forgiveness.
It's too late.
The only one bad game for forgiveness is him.
Watch.
My car's about to pull back.
Get out.
Shannon, please get in the car.
I'll take you wherever you want.