Oh, there is a line to cross. I had no idea, but this is just the beginning, Ricky tracks, Karen.
Bye.
Driver, drive.
Where's your bag?
No one. Where's your friend, Ricky?
Oh, Aunt Jo. From now on, I don't have any friends named Ricky.
Yes, you'll finally come to your senses.
Aunt Jo was the kindness of all servants in the house.
In my past life, she always warned me about Ricky, but I was so blindly in love that I pushed her away.
In this life, I won't fail her again.
Miss, I'm so sorry. I spoke out of turn.
Oh, no, Aunt Jo. It's okay. You're absolutely right.
I think I'm gonna lay down, though. It's been a long day.
All right.
Johnny Wonder came by for a visit. I can send him away if you're too tired.
Johnny? Where is he?