Alright, Ancho, I think it's time to start dinner.
We're not waiting for Ricky.
Why?
Say, goodness, Ms. Shannon won't be a suck-up anymore.
I'll have everything ready right away.
Thank you.
Yes.
Johnny, your grades have been good in school, right?
Well, yeah, I mean, I studied my part, so, yeah.
Well, mine are terrible.
Man.
Would you want to be my tutor?
I mean, you could just come here every day and help me study.
Well, I thought the Ricky tracks isn't you.
And you love him so much that you push me away.
Oh, well, he's about to get fired, so...
Well, well, well, hey, I mean, I'm available.
And if you won't, you're going to be such a marvel.
Yeah, tomorrow then.
Yeah, tomorrow?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Ancho, I'm really sorry, but I have to run.
Something came up.
But thank you for having me here.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
My...
Shannon?
Why did you think he was a good idea to tell my father a new one today?
Huh?
They found out everybody.
What is wrong with you?
Go out there and apologize to him, right now.
Hey, I disciplined my driver.
I paid his salary and he left me on the side of the road, and yet you weren't able to apologize?
He is my father, and he had nothing to do with any of this.
Anything he did, but I told him to.
He went out of this.
If you ever come, you can take it off of me.
I see how it is.
Daddy only listens to you, in that case.
You can both pack your bags and go.
Ricky?
I can't have you here anymore.
Ever since you started tutoring me, my grades have only gotten worse.
Why am I paying you anything at all?
Because you're fucking...
Oh, that's fucking why.
I explained the same shit to Karen.
What does I explain to you to pick up the information?
No problem.
You're dumb.
As rocks.
Search for anything.
I don't.
But do not keep falling back on me when the grades are looking worse than they already are.
Fine.
You will.
But I want you and you're good for nothing, father.
I live here.
You know what?
You're right.
It's not because you're fucking stupid.
It's because you're obsessed with it.
You want to go out with it.
You can't focus.
And that's why your grades are so good.
I think you're talking about...
This little fuss that you're creating.
It's because you're jealous of me and Karen's relationship, right?
You think I want to be with you?
Oh my God.
It's obvious.
Oh.
Ricky tracks.
In this life, I would never want to be with you.
Sorry.
Well, you can say whatever.
But if you disrespect me like that, ever again in public, whatever happens to you next is completely your fault.
Did you be able to drop Karen off first?
All right.
My boy.
I'm a driver.
You did not ask for my...
From now on, no unnecessary people in my car, including him.
Miss Shannon.
You have a good relationship with Ricky, right?
I would want to let something small like this get in the way of your feelings for him.
This time I checked, your job description was a driver.
Do you want to pursue therapy?
That's probably why you didn't do...
Oh.
You probably want to do well in med school.
Is that why you're behind the wheel?
Don't talk to my fuck.
My driver like that.
Get out.
What?
Oh dear, you think you're worthy enough to sit with me.
Drive!
Shannon, you've really crossed the line this time.
You've officially pissed me the fuck off.
Ricky, what is going on with you?
She's the daughter of your driver and you're letting her push you around like this?
Everyone says you're the rich one and she's the fake.
Maybe they're wrong.
So, I heard you were talking to Johnny Wonder.
Why do you care?
No.
Bringing him around and trying to make me jealous is never going to get him to forgive you if that's what you think.
I want to think that.
I mean, I don't even like thinking about you.
You know what I can't stand?
Women who can't make up there.
I've made up my mind about you.
Actually, I can't believe I've tolerated you for so long.
But the way you treat me and spend my money on me.
Aaron?
Money?
I've heard of that mind to fix your dumb ass brain.
Well, then maybe I should demand a refund and my grades would go up.
Well, it's not my fault. It's your mind.
Ricky, you're fired.
What?
You do find someone else?
Don't worry, I already found a new tutor.
You know,
you're playing hard to get.
It's just not a thing to fix on me.
And if you keep it up, you're just going to lose me as a tutor.
And, well, are you with that lead or shame?
I'm the dumb one.
Ricky, you're fired.
You?
Ricky, what's really going on between you and Shannon?
Who knows you? I don't give a shit.
Well, it's your birthday tomorrow.
Are we still celebrating with your family about it?
Are you going to help me write a dress?
Ricky?
No, you...
I'll write a dress.
You don't even know.
Me?
That's what's going on.
Shannon always plays my birthday celebrations.
She's just acting dramatic behind the surprise.
Oh, she's taking it too far.
Shannon, do you want me to birthday party to get my drinking this?
Ricky, why aren't you saying anything?
What's the note, everyone?
Tomorrow night is my 20th birthday.
It will be held at the Royal Court Hotel.
There will be food.
There will be drinks.
There will be music.
And, well, it will be a night to remember.
Oh, my God, the Royal Court Hotel?
That is, like, higher than five stars.
The track's family owns the Royal Court.
The staff literally found...
...to Ricky.
Holy shit.
Yes, you do have to get me a ticket.
Get yourself a ticket?
No, no, no, no.
You see, you're personally invited.
Actually, as a matter of fact, everybody here is invited.
Ricky, should we invite Shannon?
Do you think she'll come?
Shannon?
No.
Even without invitation, she'll still come around.
Shannon, you think you're so clever.
You think this party will save you?
No.
You're in for a rude awakening.
Nobody disrespects me.
Yeah, she can't seem to stay away from you.
I'll have to teach her and listen.
God, Johnny is nothing like Ricky.
Johnny has patience.
He speaks well.
He never complains.
And, oh, my God, he's handsome.
How could I have been so blind in my previous life?
How could I waste all my time on someone like Ricky tracks,
especially when Johnny was right there all along?
Is there something you don't understand?
Oh, no, I'm just too dumb.
Shannon, you are not dumb.
Just, you have a bad study, Matt.
I'll tell you what, let me help you build a better foundation,
and then if your grades still don't improve,
you can kick me to the curb,
and look, I won't even keep the money that you pay.
Are you sure?
I mean, do you really mean all that?
Of course.
Here.
What you want to do is you want to find the most powerful denominator you can.
Shannon, seriously?
What's your deal?
Ricky, what do you want?
You do my shit in the basement.
Well, yeah, because this afternoon I told you you're fired.
So why would you stay at my house,
especially in a nice room,
and especially after I fired your father?
If you're willing to stay, the basement is yours.
You must think it's so fun fucking humiliating me.
You really hate me?
You must have been so dramatic.
I don't think I don't know what you're up to.
Tomorrow at the birthday party,
I'll make sure you regret this.
I'll make your meal in front of everyone in apologies.
Well, we're in the middle of a session,
so can you stop interrupting?
Well, just wait.
Three, two, one.
What the hell is she doing?
Why is she acting so tough?
She's trying to make me angry.
All right, I'll teach you a hard lesson for that.
Hey, I'm really sorry you had to see that, Johnny.
Maybe I should just go.
I mean, you're not seeing like you're in the best mood, so.
No, no, no.
Hey, I am in a good mood.
Are you sure?
By the way, what are you doing tomorrow night?
I don't know why.
Do you want to go to the Royal Court Hotel for dinner?
Yeah.
I haven't been in years and I miss the food.
Years.
Didn't you go with Ricky last night?
I mean, you guys seem to go there a lot, so.
Hey, now, how do you know that?
The Royal Court Hotel is my...
I was there too, I saw you guys.
Should I start avoiding you like before?
Do you want me to be with you?
No, of course not.
Okay, well then I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay, I'll see you then.
Shannon, dare you show up here.
Excuse me, what are you even talking about?
After everything, you have the nerve to come to Ricky's birthday party?
Oh, oh, it's his birthday?
You know what?
Totally forgot.
Now I remember.
Last time I spent a hundred K on that asshole's birthday party,
and when I was about to confess my feelings for him,
he shoved his tongue down Karen's throat.
Ugh, well, this time I'll get Ricky tracks an unforgettable birthday.
Oh, quit pretending.
Ricky didn't invite you, but you decided to show up anyway.
You're so... unclassy.
Who do you think you are anyway?
Are you, uh, Ricky's little bitch or Karen's?
Oh, and I'm so sorry.
I forgot your name, but only yours.
Yap, yap, yap, yap.
Yancy, yap, yap.
God, you're so annoying.
Shannon, I'm surprised you showed.
You know, throwing a little party like this is going to make me forgive you, Rick.
Oh, Ricky, tracks.
You are something, thinking that everything is about you.
You're telling me this isn't my birthday party?
Ew, no, why would I throw a party for you?
Unless Narcissists just waiting on the cake.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Shannon, it's Ricky's birthday, okay?
Let's not make a scene.
He's always been so nice to you.
Even his family's treated you like a friend, not a servant, okay?
Let's not make him angry.
Hey, don't get violent with Karen.
Alright, if you have a problem, you can take it up with me.
Shannon, you will apologize to Karen right now.
Ricky, it's my, just forget it.
It's your birthday.
I don't want to make a scene, and I...
Shannon did it a purpose.
Are you going to apologize or not?
I didn't push her, so why the fuck should I apologize?
How dare you talk back to Ricky like that.
You're such a monster.
You hate yourself so much that you make fun of Karen because she's pretty and kind.
And that makes her an easy target for someone like you.
If Ricky won't beat you, I will.
You are Ricky's goddamn mate!
Someone needs to put you in your place.
Stop!
You must have some kind of death, Rich.
What's wrong with you?
Donnie, you saved me again.
Again?
What do you mean again?
Shannon, get over here right now.
Don't touch her.
You didn't come here for a birthday party.
No, you came here for him.
I told you, I didn't like seeing you around him.
Ricky, what is wrong with you?
When you're lacking, you tried to kill me.
You didn't do anything, but now you get mad when someone tries to help me?
Don't ask your head.
My lacking?
Yancy would never hurt a fly.
You hit Karen first!
Pretty great.
But, you know, kind of embarrassing yourself here.
And you really don't want that, right?
You're putting me through all this shit because you want me to throw you a fucking birthday party?
If being Karen bothers you, it's just too much for you to handle.
Well, I could just easily step aside and then you could find the chill out.
You're so pathetic.
Can't let you a rich boy and let you get tarnished in front of everyone.
I'll play along and you'll see how it turns out.
You know what?
I understand.
And I don't want to ruin anyone's fun, so I rented out the platinum lounge for your party.
I hope that's okay.
In the end, Shannon is still throwing me the party.
She really is my obedient little bitch.
And she will be forever.
You know what that does just fine?
Thank you so much, that means a lot to me.
Of course.
Everyone, there is nothing to see here.
Let's get this party wrong.
Come on.
Let's party.
Enjoy the rest of your night, Johnny.
Did you really hire out the platinum?
God no.
But it's Ricky's birthday party, so he might as well have some fun until he can't pay the bill.
You know, I heard the owner of this hotel is a complete jackass.
I wonder what he's going to do when he can't pay the bill.
My money?
He's going to break his legs.
Actually, I've heard that the owner of the Royal Court Hotel is not such a bad guy.
Oh, man.
What a shame.
You know, I guess I could settle for him kneeling and begging for forgiveness.
You're right.
Thanks for saving me.
I owe you dinner.
Let's go.
Too high.
Tabio, I saw straight from New Zealand.
Mr. Trax, the card's been declined.
What do you mean my card's been declined?
I mean, it's been declined.
However, if you have another one, go about it that way.
Somebody else didn't pay for this already?
Shannon?
Oh, okay.
You look mad at this.
Is there something wrong?
I know.
You did this on purpose.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to expose you yet.
But just know your embarrassment is just the beginning.
This is for our spread?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Mateo, I'd like to have George organize everything as usual.
And tonight, please take a hundred out of Tilpiers.
Well, since Ricky can't ask me nicely, I guess I'm just going to have to tell everyone the truth.
Okay.
All right, Shannon.
All right.
Can you please stay for the bill?
Thank you, Mr. Trax.
I've never been humiliated like this before.
Everyone is laughing at me.
I'll make a big double for this.
Is Shannon paying for Ricky's party?
Can he not afford it?
Of course he can afford it.
He gave his credit card to his maid this morning for food, and look where she went.
The most expensive restaurant.
She is so shameless.
Anytime.
Well, I was supposed to treat you to dinner, but this whole scene with Mateo, I mean...
Johnny, I just hope you had a good night.
You've spent enough money on that asshole already.
Okay?
I'll make sure that Mateo refunds all of it straight back.
Johnny, do you own the hotel?
Yes.
There is no need to repay me, and there's no need to spend money on Ricky...
...of this food.
It's to die for.
Thank you.
I'm very proud of our menu.
I think Luigi has done a wonderful job in the kitchen.
And actually, I want you to feel comfortable here.
Shannon, I want you to feel free to come whenever you like.
Are you suggesting that I eat for free?
Well, do you pay for your food at your own home?
No.
In my past life, my father tried to arrange a marriage between Johnny and me,
but I resisted and refused to get to know him.
What a terrible mistake.
He's wonderful.
It's late.
Can you drive me home?
Yes.
Well, finally you're home.
I bought Ricky to apologize to you.
Mr. Trax, your son didn't offend me, so he doesn't have to apologize.
But you fired him?
Yeah, I did.
But I also fired you.
One was a tutor who made my grades worse.
And the other was a driver who left me on the side of the road.
But so funny is they still had the nerve to live on my property.
Miss Clark, Shannon, it was my fault.
I need this job.
Your father was my classmate.
Get let in down.
Well, you should have thought about that before leaving me on the side of the road.
I'll talk to Ricky.
I'll make sure he's the best teacher you've ever, ever had.
Mr. Trax, he's talking about your son, but he's just sitting there.
Not apologizing and moping.
Do you really want me to find your soul?
I owe a lot of money.
I need this job to pay it off.
Or comes out of you to wish it.
Get on her good side.
The entire family fortune could be yours.
Hours in the future.
Have you heard me clearly?
Get your shit together and apologize.
You know, I'm getting tired.
I should probably get a bed.
I told you.
Apologized to Miss Clark.
Now!
Shannon, you have gone way too far this time.
Ricky Trax, in my past life, I not only supported you, but your gambling addict of a father as well.
Let's see how you pay off his debt without the protection of the Clark family.
Shannon, did you really pay for Ricky's birthday party?
Because we thought he was the rich one.
So this means, look, if you want to know more, just ask your master himself.
Sure, he'll tell you everything.
We just find it really strange.
If you spend so much money on him, why isn't he with you?
Why is he with Karen?
Because, it doesn't matter how much of my own money she decides to go back at me.
It'll never change her poor grades, her two timing heart, and her soul full of lies.
And there is not a single thing that you can pay your calls close.
That's right.
She's at the bottom of the class because of her grades.
She throws money at Ricky to impress him, but then goes out with someone else.
Even if you're rich, she's a bad person.
Exactly! Bad brain, bad heart.
And I wonder why Ricky doesn't like her?
Yes, this party.
She insisted on throwing this event and followed my credit card.
She's doing all this to humiliate, embarrass all of you.
And before you can even say that it's your money, it's the money that's owed to me for trying to fix your brain.
Your money doesn't mean shit.
What are you laughing at?
I think you are the worst tutor in the entire world.
You know, it's incredible that you do great in class.
Because I am great. My grades are great.
It's your fault that yours isn't.
Is it because I'm dumb?
Or is it because of the way you teach?
Whatever.
Didn't you get a new tutor? How's that been working out for you?
Actually, we have another test coming up.
Let's see how that works out.
You want a bed?
Sure. If you move up 100 spots on the rig, which I'm asking a lot, I won't admit that I was wrong.
Deal!
Cool. Actually, I'm so confident in this bet that if I do wind up losing, I'll even run 10 miles on the track.
Ricky, what does that even have to do with me?
If I win, I want you to kneel down and poke you until I forgive you.
Are you insane?
You think it's okay to even ask that of Ricky?
Sure. He'll do it.
As long as you promise to do the same exact thing.
But you have to bend like a puppy every day for a week.
Unless you scared and wanna bow out.
Insane!
She actually agreed?
She's completely out of her mind.
I'm insane!
I haven't seen you as far away in here!
I missed you so I came back.
Love you all.
Oh my god.
Is this Shannon's new target?
Ricky, is this the guy you said she's been hanging out with?
Yeah, that's him.
She's been going for him for a while now.
She wants him.
Why is she all over a guy in his 50s?
I knew she wasn't rich.
She got herself a sugar daddy.
I wonder why Ricky hates her.
She's disgusting.
Shannon, I know it's your father.
But if you think I'll tell anyone, not Shannon.
Enjoy your sugar daddy.
Ricky, do you think she's getting all of her money from that old heart?
You think she's that lucky?
She's relying on someone, whether it's you or her sugar daddy.
Shannon, this is only the beginning.
What's going on?
You're not usually this happy to see me.
What happened?
Nothing.
I just, I feel like I haven't seen you in a lifetime.
I just really missed you.
In my past life, Dad was killed in an accident on a business trip.
The whole Clark Corporation was thrown into chaos.
Somehow, because I was a fool, Ricky Trax and his good-for-nothing father took the company from me.
In this life, I'm not only going to protect Clark Corporation, but I'm going to protect my father as well.
Shannon, love.
Is that Ricky Trax still causing you trouble?
Please, listen to me. He's bad news.
Don't spend your time there. He's not worth your time or attention.
I'd like to introduce you to a friend's son, Johnny Wonder.
Listen, I know, I know. It's a ridiculous name.
But he is a terrific young man.
From a wealthy family that's well respected.
Would you give him a chance for me?
For you, anything.
Did help just freeze over?
Whenever I criticize Ricky, she loses her mind.
Shannon, love. Are you sure everything's okay?
Well, I did fire Ricky Trax and his father.
But if I do see Johnny Wonder, will you promise me one thing?
No more business trips. You will stay home.
Very well. I promise. In fact, tonight, I'm seeing the Wonder family.
Would you like to join me?
Well, I would, but I'm going to see my new tutor, Johnny Wonder.
So, well, please, young lady. The chip off field block.
I'm the armabella. Go on.
Hey, uh, I got to tell you something.
Yeah.
I made a bet with Ricky that if I don't move up a hundred places on the next exam,
I have to kneel down and beg.
A hundred places? What if you win?
Oh, well, if I win, he has to run 10 miles, bow down and beg.