Look, I guess I'll help you win, then.
Wait, really?
Yeah, I mean, look, you're working hard, you're clearly improving, so...
Well, I know.
I know I'm doing a little better, but a hundred places?
I know, but we've got the time.
Plus, as far as I can see, I mean, Ricky Trax was a terrible tutor.
Look, I'm pretty sure that he was the reason that you're so far behind.
You knew it.
What a freaking able!
Oh!
Mr. Wonder, my grades are near your hands.
Here.
Attention class, the monthly exams have come back and, as expected,
the top of the class are Ricky and Cameron.
I guess Shannon will be running all afternoon.
But I would like to draw attention to someone else.
Ms. Shannon Clark.
Professor, did Shannon go from dead last to second to last?