Yesi, I expect you to be respectful and shut your mouth.
Shannon has moved up 253 places. That is amazing.
What? 200 places? A professor found us in a mistake because
your grades are so poor, there's no way she could...
I made no mistake. Shannon, you have done a great job. Keep up the good work.
Thanks professor.
Oh, where it was?
Did you forget about a little bloke?
You got lucky this time.
So what?
Locker no luck. You lost the bet.
So you better start running and then kneel down and beg.
Unless you want to beg now.
Shannon, I'm acting all high in writing. Moving up to magic places is not that impressive.
Ricky is right first and Karen is second.
You don't see them acting all high in writing.
Girl, why are you even yapping?
Ricky placed a bet that I couldn't move up 100 places.
And guess what? I moved up 200. So it's time to pay up Ricky Trucks.
Karen's a lap dog and you're the ring of Nancy's heart.