Fine. I'll run. But if you think I'm getting my knees and begging you, you are so wrong.
So you are a backing out on your word?
Got it.
Shannon, we're all friends here.
Asking Ricky to kneel down and beg is a bit much, don't you think?
A bit much?
Karen, you didn't say a word when your pet of a friend told me to kneel down for a week.
You know what? You can kneel and break the slot.
You're taking us too far, Shannon.
Don't push your book, Shannon.
Now I'm starting to think that maybe you cheated on the exam in order to make Ricky look better.
How else would you explain your grades and proving so much?
Even though Ricky's been tutoring you every day and you are still failing.
Where's your proof, bitch?
Oh, your house grades are the proof, bitch.
Anyway, we hope you have time to study after tempting to your sugar daddy's knees.
Hey, fuck your mouth.
Just you wait, Shannon, just you wait.
Everyone's gonna know that you're a cheater and a whore.