Shannon, stand up.
Does something wrong, Professor?
Someone has reported that you have cheated on this exam.
Is this true?
Does this person have any evidence?
Well, the grades have taken a tremendous leap,
so it's understandable that some students are very suspicious.
Let them suspect. I don't care. I didn't cheat.
Okay, well, for your reputation and for being fair,
I'm excited that you can take the test again. Do you want to do it?
No, of course not.
If she didn't cheat, what would she be so afraid of?
If someone makes an accusation, they should have proof.
Otherwise, it's slander.
Let's say they accuse me tomorrow, and then the day after that,
how many times do I have to redo work in order for them to shut up?
I might as well drop out since I'm performing for them.
Why did she get so smart?