You're being unreasonable.
The teacher told you to retake the exam, so stop arguing.
This retake is a chance to clear your name.
You don't want people doubting you behind your back, do you again?
Professor, I'm sorry. The reasoning behind this is absolutely absurd, but...
For you, I will retake the exam.
Shannon, it's no big deal. There's no need to feel guilty.
Who doesn't feel guilty?
Still making excuses.
Stunning zombies.
You have to shut up.
You're always trying to find something to bitch about because you're so boring for Karen's approval.
Professor, since she accused me without any evidence, should there be consequences?
What did you say?
Professor, Yancy has accused me of cheating without any proof and that has targeted me repeatedly for weeks.
If I retake the exam and prove that I didn't cheat, I think she should drop out.
You want her to drop out? Seriously? How could she be like this?