If you don't drop out, I'll sue you
for spreading rumors and false accusations.
And if that's not enough,
our teacher knows that you're a dishonest, untrustworthy liar.
I can only imagine the letter of recommendation
he'll write about you.
Shannon, we're all friends.
She was just worried about you going down the wrong path.
Morally, she was trying to wake you up.
Don't ruin her future.
Right, isn't forcing her to drop out too much?
No, Karen, if you care about Yancey so much,
you can drop out in your place.
I mean, Ricky would take care of you.
Shane, you care about this.
Yeah, Karen defended you.
She treats everyone equally.
Treats everyone equally.
Why does she want you to know me to drop out, huh?
Of course.
I would defend you, Yancey.
Dropping out is a little too much.
Shut up.
You are always acting like a saint,
but I never forgot.
So you deserve what's coming to you.
As for you, Yancey.
If you really, really don't want to drop out,
I guess we can make an arrangement.
Please.