Oh, we're not gonna die, dummy.
You don't have the whole hospital backing you up.
I mean, if you can't run one more mile,
you can always drop out.
Why are you so mean?
Me?
Do you even know what you said to me today?
The things you did?
Nancy, it's either you run or you drop out, okay?
I'll run.
Good luck.
Karen, it's changed so much.
I can't keep doing this.
Nancy, don't worry.
She's just being unreasonable.
I mean, can you imagine how disgusting
she must feel having to please her sugar daddy all the time?
I mean, can't even imagine.
Robin, if everyone found out, you know,
that would set her on the right path.
You're too kind, Karen.
She's so cruel to you,
and you just want her to be a better person.
She's a disgrace to our school
and deserves her body to help!
I had pictures of her with a disgusting old man.
You could post them only.
Oh, no, Nancy, that's that's too punch.
What would the principal do if long doubt,
especially with the outstanding student awards coming up?
I could do it at the ceremony.