You're here. Did you come to cheer for Rudy?
No, I have zero interest in cheering for him.
I'm not sure their joke on a tennis ball didn't cheer for you.
Shannon, you are such a horrible liar.
You come cheer for me all the time.
Oh, well, I hate to break it to you, but I'm not here for you. I'm over it.
Look, just because you got your grades up and all that, doesn't mean you're special.
And that doesn't mean that you're better than me and Karen either.
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you talking?
I wasn't listening.
Shannon, enough. We were just trying to be polite.
You know, we were all friends once.
Oh, thank God I have standards.
I don't listen. Nobody wants to be friends with her anyone.
Shannon, you're getting too full of yourself.
What's it because she has a rich sugar daddy to support her?
Oh, what? What did you say?
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
Uh, and Shannon.
Um, it's time for me to shine.
Who are you playing?
Some boy, some rundown score.
He hasn't got shit on me though.
Oh, Ricky, you're amazing.
Shannon, so who do you think will win today?
Oh, my God.
Is that this guy that's playing against Ricky?