Isn't that Shannon's new boy toy?
She is really something.
She has a sugar daddy and a boy toy as simple as Ricky wants to do her.
He is quite handsome.
He is really handsome.
Is it this presence about him?
He might not be hotter than Ricky, don't you think?
Everyone around Shannon is rich at the standing or exceptional.
Well, I took Ricky from you. I'll take this guy too.
Such Shannon's trying to seduce this guy.
I wonder if he knows she has a sugar daddy.
Once he does find out.
Just take her to the curb. Just like Ricky did.
Don't worry.
You're well the real Shannon's.
You're not here to watch him.
Are you?
That's none of your business.
Now, why don't you go warm up?
Shannon, laugh while you can.
You won't be laughing for long.