Do it, huh? I've arranged your marriage with Eric to help save my company.
You can't just sit around, alright? Go get the money, go get it!
Are you okay? Did you show that new candle to your hubby? Did he like it?
Yes, but Riley showed up. So, I left.
Riley is always hanging all over your husband. You're sure you're okay with that?
I'm fine, really.
It's been two years, Kat. Do you still want to keep going with this contract marriage thing?
It's not healthy.
If only Eric is happy.
What about you? I'm fine.
You're too nice, sort of.
Alright, enough of that. Let's go shopping.
Good, good, great. Want it? Send me your email. I'll give it to you.
Yeah, sure. Great. Here you go.
You just can't leave us alone, can you? Now you're stalking us?