No. I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going to repeat myself.
You promised me to leave Andrew alone.
And you promised me you wouldn't see him again.
Now, not just Andrew, but the whole but family will pay for his mistakes.
Please, just stop.
I'll come back with you.
And I'll never have to see him again.
I'll listen to you.
Do whatever you want, but please, bear him.
Please.
Now you're begging me.
How do I know you mean it?
Go home away from me.
Got it.
What did Eric say to you?
I warned you.
Stay away from my boyfriend.
That's my husband you're talking about.
Does he treat you like a husband?
He was forced into this marriage.
People like you bring troubles with those around him.
I mean, Andrew's already in jail because of you.