You've caused quite a mess, haven't you?
We took you in, we raised you, and this is how you thank us?
What's next?
Are you gonna give me a new successor?
The doctor said it's not genetic.
There's a good chance the baby will be healthy.
There's always a chance, but we can't take that risk.
The sooner you and Eric divorce, the better it will be for both of you.
Who said I'm getting a divorce?
You know, mother, you really should keep me in the loop on this sort of thing.
I mean, after all, it's not like Catherine.
We were just chatting. Nothing to worry about.
Oh, why would there be anything to worry about?
Well, we're all here.
Let's eat, shall we?
Catherine, I heard from security that you went to the hospital.
My stomach was feeling a bit off.
Are you okay? Why didn't you tell me about this?
I know you're busy with work. I didn't want to bother you. It wasn't a big deal.
If it's not better by tomorrow, let me know. I'll thank you straight to the hospital.
Catherine, are you sure this is just a stomach issue?
What if you're pregnant?
No, it's not.
Well, that's a relief.
Pregnancy would be troublesome to deal with.
Nobody wants this baby.
I will protect you, and no one will know about you.