Are you sure you're not pregnant?
No
You know, I've been taking pills to not get pregnant
They're very effective
You better not be lying to me. You understand?
All right, I'm spreading a sex or size. No sexual activity
If there's anything heavy bleeding again, that could lead to a miscarriage. I
Want to stay here for a few days
Why the change of scenery might be nice, you know
It's more lively here with so many people
If anything comes up, you call me right away. All right. I'll be back to pick you up in a few days
Eric waiting for someone is too painful. I don't want to wait anymore
You can partner for over 20 years
You and your brother are crazy. I appreciate you meeting lawyers for Andrew. I do
Even though we're struggling right now
We don't need Catherine bending over backwards for us anymore. We've been good to her
Mostly because we've seen what she's gone through with you and how you treated her. You are the crazy one. Not her
Is it true? Is it true what they're saying?
Just tell me did you set up Andrew's accent to get back in her eye on?
What do you think? But first I never would have believed it was you
But no, I guess it doesn't matter anymore does