Is that true? Did you marry me just for the sake of your grandmother?
That's not for you to worry about.
You never really loved me, did you?
Catherine, can you just drop this? Why do you listen to what other people say?
What Andrew and William say?
You and I are happy together, aren't we? At least sometimes.
Eric, what am I to you? Answer me for real this time. Please.
You are very special to me. We'll always be together, just like we always have been.
No, I'm not. And no, we're not. Let me go, please.
After all these years, after everything that I've done for you, you're this unhappy with me.
I want a divorce. Please, I am so tired. Let me go.
You. I see.
After all these years of letting you live with my family, you still pick him over me.