Good, I'm glad you're done pretending mother because I'm done pretending to
You need to make Eric fall in love with you and then marry him
The entire inheritance you got it. I'm depending on you really you don't come from a good family to work with me
Be good, and I promise you I'm completely changed your life. Yes, ma'am. I always want to talk sons are
I'm not done yet don't you think that I don't know about your hostile take over the but family share and how you staged
Andrews car accident have alerted the police to open an investigation
No
I just sorry
Catherine's fault without her
Everything will go back to normal. I'm back
You