Riley, I will give you whatever you want.
Okay, great Catherine is innocent.
Let her go.
Anything.
Now you would have given me whatever I want.
I want your love and I want your shares.
Fine.
Don, the shares are yours.
But please let her go.
What about the other part?
Hmm?
That was never on the table, was it?
Fine.
Go to me, but you'll give me the shares.
Have Leo, then the paper's over.
Now.
Okay.
Leo, it's me.
I need you to bring the share transfer template over the abandoned warehouse on Fifth Street.
Okay.
No.
Don't ask me any questions right now.
Okay.
Just do it.
Riley, calm down.
Leo will be here in 10 minutes.
Just let Catherine go.
Since you just proposed to me that you actually care about this pathetic little me?
Sadly.
You still have to get rid of her.
No.