If only there had been any other way to get my son married, our texture is such a workaholic.
Texture is the perfect man for my Lillian.
My grandma must be so happy in heaven now.
We shall leave.
God bless us with grandchildren soon.
It was set up by our mothers.
But we did sleep together.
I guess she's my wife now.
We got the French headquarters in three hours for the opening ceremony.
Your private jet is ready.
We need a leak now.
I'll be right there.
Take care of my wife for me.
Hey kid.
What are you doing here all by yourself?
Take the police station.
Want to tag me along?
A little smart ass, huh?
Whoa, look what I got here.
Why don't we hang out?
I'll have plenty more in my car.
I only eat chocolate covered strawberries.
Or a little brat.