What's going on here? Sorry about that. My son likes to run around while I'm not
watching. No, it's been a day. Should I pull shit? Terry, give this man to the police.
Oh, come on. They're very good looking. Oh, thank you. Kid, you can't just ask
random strangers to be your dad. Boss, we need to go. We're gonna be late. Mr.
Good looking. Is Daddy yes? Have you seen this little boy? He's about this tall
brown hair. I'm already married. Stay here and tell your mom he's here. My
buddy I will keep you safe till she arrives. Just too bad. I thought I was
getting Mr. Good looking as my daddy. You had me so scared. Mom. People can't
be your daddy just because you ask. What does my daddy look like? Does he look
like me? I've only spent one night with him. I never even saw his face. Daddy's been
gone so long. Mommy doesn't remember what he looks like. Lillian, you're late. Sorry,
I had to wait for the nanny. The CEO is back from France. Everyone is meeting
him in the lobby now. Let's go. I see.