Mr. Good-looking.
Kid, what are you doing here?
I live here.
How are you, kid?
One, two, three, four, four.
Four? I've been away for six years.
I can't have a four-year-old son.
My wife had a bastard child.
Why'd he leave?
I was gonna introduce him to Mommy.
Hasn't your mom ever told you never to open the door for a stranger?
My mom only said, don't give away personal info.
I'm five-year-old, but I told him I was four.
Yeah, big difference.
One day you're gonna get yourself Kid Math, kid.
Terry, are you sure you have the right address?
Of course.
Denny, was someone at the door?
Terry, my wife's been cheating on me.
What? How do you know?
She's a four-year-old son.
I've been gone for six years.
Do I need to show you the math?