Denny, was someone at the door?
Mommy, it's their good looking this year.
You opened the door to a stranger?
Oh, he left something too.
You don't open the door to strangers?
He's very good looking, like me.
So, a random guy saves you from another random guy,
and now he knows where you live?
Tell Mommy what do you do the next time he comes here?
Call the police.
Add a boy.
Mommy, when is Daddy coming back?
Denny, did you open the door because you thought it might be Daddy?
Daddy's not coming back.
Mommy can take care of Danny alone.
Daddy is such a playboy.
Maybe.
Where did you learn that word?
Don't worry, Mommy.
I can pay Mommy's bills with Granny's card.
Denny, stop showing off.
You're only supposed to buy juice with this card.
I'll take it from you if you use it too much.
Well, I best go see what he left at the door.