Your word has five letters.
It starts with D and ends with a Y.
Daddy.
No, my turn.
Okay.
Hit me.
It's a color.
Orange?
Yeah!
What?
My turn.
Three of the five letters.
Sorry, we were playing a game.
Her boyfriend moved in.
I can't believe I was dumb enough to dig her side.
You hit me in psycho?
You'll pay for this.
What happened to your face?
I opened the door for some psycho and he punched me.
Look in my face.
Denny, you said that a man was here earlier.
What did he look like?
Who's your guy good looking to?
Guys, you are way off track.
You've got a psycho creeping on doors,
punching people like a jack in the box.
Call the cops!
Okay, let's eat.
This looked like the flowers I got for Mr. Windsor's wife.
How did it go?
Lillian cheated on me.
Lillian's a good girl.
She would never.
I saw her with a kid.
You dummy?
That is your child.
He called another man daddy.
We were only together for one night.
Now she has a four-year-old son.
Does that make any sense to you?
Nevertheless, our family owes Lillian big time.
You left without a word.
She was all by herself for six lonely years.
Are you taking her side?
She cheated.
You want a divorce.
I still want him.
She do that.
And Danny looks exactly like you.
Promise me you will give her a benefit of the doubt.
I'll handle it myself.
I've seen it enough.
Terry, get a lawyer to prepare the divorce papers ASAP.
You just got back.
Just get it done.
Let's meet him.
I need a drink.
Strong as a skunk.
Get him at Ryu Kawak love house.
What happened?
It's my boss.
I have to go.
It is.
I doubt Charles is awake right now,
and I can't leave you on your own.
I'll go.
I'll protect you.
All right.
Get dressed.
Stay here.
Mommy has to go find the drunk boss.
No worries.
Mommy, I'll be good.
This place.
I mean, his mommy's new.
Help her find your boss.
This is a billionaire-exclusive clubhouse.
How did a little street bat like you get in a place like this?
I'm not.
Is that kid?
It has $8.8 billion.
Yeah, right.
Monopoly money?
Come on.
Even though his mom is unfaithful,
the kid is innocent.
Stop.
Is that how you treat a child?
You're fired.
Who are you to fire me?
This is a DM-owned high-end club.
Not some soup kitschy for brokeasses like you.
Don't worry.
I can take care of this with my money.
Stop messing around.
Yeah, little punk.
Watch your mouth.
Beat it.
I've seen a lot of rich folk around here,
and that ain't you.
You're never going to get there,
even if you work your ass off.
Security!
Throw them out.
That's your boss.
Our... our boss.
You... you're...
Terry.
EA of... the boss.
So he really is our...
Please, please, Mr. Windsor, don't fire me.
I'll apologize to your kid.
Please, please forgive me.
I'm following his own name.
Beat it.
Good looking.
You're actually a really nice person.
I wish I could say the same thing about your dad.
My dad is really not...
Of course not.
Or everybody will know she's been cheating on me.
Are you a CEO, too?
There's some good bossing people around.
Kiddo, do you know what a CEO is?
Of course.
Be CEO one day.
Look, kid, this isn't the park.
We'll call your mom and get her down here.
Where is Mr. Windsor?
Room 306.
Wait here.
Here you go.
Oh, Kiddo.
Mr. Windsor, I've been looking all over for you.
I just bumped into my wife's kid.
He's resting in this room.
Your wife's kid.
You mean your kid?
Is it because I'm not wearing a T-shirt that says
my wife cheated on me on the back?
I guess we'll never know.
It's like we're still buying into the cheating wife theory.
So is your wife in there, too?
No, the kid somehow found his way in without his mom knowing.
Yep, kids will do that.
You know kids well.
Of course.
I raised one myself.
The father isn't in the picture?
Oh, him.
It's the same with her without.
Sounds like Lillian also is a complicated marriage.
So, how old is your kid?
Four.
Mine's five.
He's here somewhere.
Maybe they could be friends.
What's the cheater's kid we're talking about?
I could stay out of it.
I don't say why not.
His mom won't be here for a while.
Wow.
He is so kind.
He won't take it out on an innocent child.
And I've been looking everywhere for you.
Come on, you guys.
Holy shit.
I've been waiting for you guys forever.
Let's get blackout drunk.
Mr. Winsworth, this is...
Oh, friend, I used to grow up with.
Lily, you look absolutely ravish.
I bet your decks are here treat you nice and easy at work, doesn't it?
Sir, please, I take my job very seriously.
I'm sure you do.
Why don't you come work for me?
I'll double your salary.
Really, Jamison?
Boaching my assistant in front of me?
Come on, decks.
I've never seen you this worked up about an assistant before.
You're just a little curious.
They better not get into a fight.
I'm thrilled that you think so highly of me.
I'll drink to the hat.
I knew I liked you.
Your kid is still here.
She has to drive me home later.
I'll drink with you.
All right.
Well, then one won't cut it.
Decks first pass down here, poor bastard.
Why don't you take him upstairs?
He's got a presidential suite.
Professional my ass.
I'll go get you some water.
Wait, stay here.
He's not going to do anything to me, right?
He's married.
Mr. Windsor, sir, are you?
It's me, Lillian.
Lillian?
My wife?
Why did you betray me?
Because I was gone for so long.
You got tired of waiting?
What are you talking about?
It's everyone close to me.
You bound to leave me.
Is he talking about his wife?
Lillian?
What are you doing here?
He must have thought I was his wife.
Sir, you had a lot to drink.
And I...
He is so devoted to his wife.
Being so respectful, even when he's drunk.
Come on, Lillian.
Snap out of it.
She shouldn't have cheated on him.
This man is your boss.
That must be his wife.
Danny, how did you get here?
Mr. Mancher told me you're here.
This is a bad time.
He is just my boss.
Mr. Good-looking is your boss?
I approve.
Mr. Good-looking.
Do you know him?
I want him to be my dad.
No, Danny.
He's my boss and I'm his assistant.
And that's that.
Just quit.
He missed my whack card.
Danny, are you spending your dad's money to get back at him?
Besides, Dexter has more money than can fit on your black card.
Mom, he's making my daddy.
No, he's married.
End of discussion.
Fine.
Who's over there?
Um, nobody's served.
Just me.
Who's over there?
Nobody's served.
Just me.
Where are you hiding me?
He's kind enough to let me take you to work.
But sneaking into his room is a big no-no.
I'll find someone to come take you home.
Good morning, sir.
Would you like some water?
Work keeps dying at me.
How did I get here?
You were drunk.
You have no recollection?
No.
Good.
He didn't know Danny was here.
Did you stay here all night to take care of me?
Where's your kid?
He's fine.
I had a friend come pick him up.
Where's your husband?
He's busy.
You still love him?
I can't bore my boss with my personal matters.
He's got a lot on his plate as it is.
Of course I love my husband.
Thank you for asking.
Why does that bother me so much?
And get Terry.
Time for work.
Good morning, everyone.
Regina, here is your coffee.
Double cream, no sugar.
I don't want your coffee.
Okay, what's going on?
Drop the act.
Everyone knows you slept with the boss.
That's not true.
Who told you that?
He's wearing the same clothes from yesterday.
And you guys arrived to work in the same car.
He was drunk.
I wanted to make sure he was okay.
And I'm sure you made a move on him.
Must be nice.
You've got yourself a man at home.
And a man at work.
That's not me.
That's my friend.
You know, you must be really good at making those time sheets
because you have so much time in your schedules
and all these men.
You have no proof.
I just really don't like cheating, bitches.
Sorry.
Oh, and you're going viral and it's now a company scandal.
Our share prices took ahead.
Our boss worked so hard to build up his reputation
and you destroyed it unless it's not.
You really think he'll still want you around.
Mr. Windsor, I have to quit.
Is this about the rumors?
You heard?
I know everything that happens in this company.
He's not really into me, right?
Sir, if people see us like this,
the rumors will spiral out of control.
So what?
You can't control what we're going to say about you.
I never wanted this.
You should have cleared things up.
Look, I have to quit.
I won't let you.
Why not?
You worked so hard to get where you're at.
And now you're quitting because it's some stupid gossip.
Nobody will believe me.
So that's it?
You let them walk over you like this?
I'll give you half an hour.
Tell you what help.
Find out who started these rumors and get back to work.
Sir, are you trying to help me?
I don't have time for assistance.
Sir, do you trust me?
Of course.
Make sure Lillian gets all the help she needs from the deck department.
You're all right.
It's supposed to be that special.
Regina?
This is for slandering a coworker.
How dare you hit me?
This is for disregarding rules and spreading chaos in the company.
You?
And this is for women everywhere.
Do you know how much damage you can do with lies?
You're lucky I'm not taking you to court.
Kitty's got a clause.
I wouldn't mess with that.
Where's your proof?
You're crazy.
The tech department traced these photoshopped photos back to your company.
The tech department traced these photoshopped photos back to your computer.
How dare you spread rumors about your coworker and boss.
Apologize or quit?
So what?
You can't fire me.
I can fire you on Mr. Windsor's behalf because I know he doesn't tolerate dishonesty.
He wants all of his employees to be treated with fairness and respect.
Well said.
Lillian is right.
I want to allow any of my staff to be defamed.
He heard me, but he's not mad that I spoke on his behalf.
Have any of you are so curious about what's going on between Lillian and I?
That would be a good time to speak on.
No.
Then I better not have to hear another word about it.
But Mr. Windsor, she has a complicated relationship with men.
Lillian has always been professional.
And I can't say something about you.
You're fired.
What?
And anyone involved will take a pay cut.
No, please.
No, I swear I won't do it again.
Please, I need this job.
I need it.
Lillian?
What do you think?
I'm not a saint.
This is just overdue karma.
That's more like it.
That's not my trust that assistance should be.
Terry, get out of my face.
Mr. Windsor, please.
No, please.
I do your price, everyone.
He is such a gentleman.
I really owe him a big one.
Alex, make sure my wife signs the divorce papers by tomorrow.
Why don't you ask her yourself?
It's not like you don't have her number.
She's shamelessly living with her lover amid our marriage.
They even have a child together.
I don't want anything to do with her.
Yes, who is this?
This is Alex for divorce.
We ought to talk.
I don't hear from him for six years, and the first thing he wants is a divorce.
Lillian is the messenger.
Let's proceed with dignity.
Clearly not.
Where should I meet you?
Sitting over the location right now.
I'll have the papers ready.
See you there tomorrow.
Danny, will you be sad if your mommy and daddy get a divorce?
No, I want my mommy to be happy.
Mary, Mr. Good-looking.
He's a CEO, too.
Dexter is a good man, but too bad he's not for me.
That's not going to happen.
Mr. CEO's wife broke his heart.
I'm sure there's a way.
I'm coming with you tomorrow.
Yeah?
What are you going to do?
I'll beat up that playboy for you.
All right.
You can come, but only if you stay in the lobby and don't run around.
Alex, it's nine o'clock.
Where is he?
You should be here soon.
It's probably just traffic.
I'll be sure to brief the next wife.
Not sure how much she'll like waking up to an empty bed.
Lillian, I've practiced law, not marriage counseling.
Look, there's no need to wait.
I'll just sign it.
Are you sure?
What if he changes his mind?
He can have everything, except for our apartment.
And in exchange, I get full custody of my son.
All right, then.
Just sign right there.
You know, most people would kill for half of his fortune.
I'm talking about billions.
We don't need his money.
Great.
Notarization isn't a month.
We'll be in contact.
See you soon.