Stop.
Be my dad for a second, please.
Me?
Your dad?
Thank you.
You're the best.
Well, my dad is right here.
He's not your dad.
You're a liar.
Even though things got ugly between me and his mother,
it had nothing to do with him.
He's just a kid.
He's not a liar.
I am his dad.
Well, your kid's a bastard and you're a punk.
Unlike my boy here, he's going to be head of Z Corporation one day.
Best believe I can bankrupt it right now.
You're smart.
You'd be on your knees right now.
You moron.
Then maybe I'd make you a janitor.
Bankrupt is Z Corporation in three seconds.
You're just full of jokes.
The only company that's a match for us is DM Group.
Three.
Two.
One.
Market Crash.
Corporation went bankrupt in three seconds.
Their loss has exceeded $10 billion.