Dexter was drugged. He's not himself right now.
Keep your cool woman. Be professional.
Sir, you have a rash. I'll get the door.
Um, you're gonna have to apply the women on his chest.
I don't think that's...
I just cut my finger. You're gonna have to do it.
Hurry.
Okay. Okay.
I've never seen a woman get this close to him before.
I should give you a medal.
Let's just focus, Terry.
Dexter, what are you gonna do to them?
I'm gonna make them pay.
That's what you should do.
Let them know they messed with the wrong guy.
You got a real player on your team, boss.
Where do you live? Terry can give you a ride.
Oh, thanks, but someone's actually coming to pick me up.
Is it her husband?
What's wrong?
I think her husband's coming to pick her up.
Let's leave them alone.
Dexter sounds sour.
Is Lillian going to be the new Mrs. Windsor?
Huh? Christian?
Mom!