My name is Hermione daughter of the richest man in the southern region. I go by tea and hold a PhD in computer science
Three years ago. I fell in love with Chris at a party since then I've hidden my identity and become his executive assistant
Secretly dating him so you have a board meeting at 10 meeting with that Middle Eastern oil tycoon at 11 and an online conference
The international business division from two to six then eight eight what eight you?
Have a date the executive assistant
sounds good
Plus we've got a problem. There's a massive group of hackers attacking our service the entire tech team is under water
Okay
New plan cancel all of my meetings for the rest of the day
Except for the last one if possible that man
Still as irresistible as the day and met him
LM is under attack
Now I need answers so who's causing it and how are we going to fix it?
The main issue is that LM dominated the southeast market last year
So as a result we accumulate many enemies and we just cannot identify it. Okay. I need answers
All we know is that over 300 hackers are attacking our firewall simultaneously
They are about to bridge our firewall. If that firewall is British, Ellen is finished. No
No, no, what is happening?
Our computers are hijacked. Why isn't responding either? Same here. Nothing's working
Boss we are out of options
You all are LM's top talent
You have graduated from the most elite universities. Is this how you're gonna handle conflict?
Only we were as good as dr. Quinton dr. Quinton
Didn't you study under him only tea dr. Quinton's favorite ever matches level, but tea has been missing for three years
Ellen is facing a huge crisis
aren't they just for sure ruin if I don't reveal that I'm tea, but
Will it change everything between us?