A girl from the slums claiming to be Dr. T.
Chris, get this liar out of here now!
I'm ready, please, don't speak like that in the office.
You don't believe me?
Seriously?
Without evidence, it can be interpreted as slender.
Fine.
I'll prove it.
Now that the crisis is over, I'm withdrawing my authorization from the Browns.
I won't let Lucy impersonate me anymore.
So she's the real T.
If Chris finds out, he'll back out of the engagement.
Anyone in my way has got to go.
Lucy, where are you?
Oh, I know you're there.
Miss...
Keep your voice down.
Why are you following me?
The big boss then has to protect the little boss.
What? Little...
He doesn't need your protection either.
Stop sending people to follow me, or I'm just never going to come home again.
How about that?
Yes, sir.
Copy that, sir.
Much better.
I said...