I didn't. It wasn't...
If Lucy's legs sat with any long-term damage,
I would make sure you paid for this.
She kidnapped me. She tried to maybe confess
that I wasn't a little dog to tea. I was terrified.
It's okay, I'm here now.
Chris, take her to the place.
I want her locked up.
No, this is not what it looks like.
Lucy kidnapped me.
There's got to be surveillance footage or something somewhere.
Well, the surveillance footage near the office
was conveniently broken.
So what do you want me to do?
I can fix it.
Really?
Chris, let's not waste any more time on this vicious woman.
Can't Lucy the hospital now?
She's pregnant?
Is it yours?
You know, that's not really any of your concern.
You should take some time today because I'm gonna have to get to the bottom.
What actually happened?
Not my concern.
Yeah.
Do I matter at all, do you?
Chris, don't do this.
Hermione!
Chris, are you okay?
I'm so sorry I was late.
I'm here right on time.
Just take me home, Danny.
What's where you're fucking going?