Who are you?
Should I tell her who I really am?
No, I can't reveal my true identity.
Home I ring the system.
For however long I've known I ring, she's always spoken about you very highly.
I ring and I've been through a lot over the years and I know that it would mean a lot to her for you to be there when she wakes up.
I can't let those who hurt her get away with this and take the company that she's worked so hard for.
What are you gonna do?
Look at me. I look just like my sister, don't I?
Pretty untrained are you? Yes.
I'm gonna pretend to be her.
I'm gonna take back her company.
Look at those assholes.
What like her are you?
She's pretty classy. She grew up in London.
I grew up poor on the Upper East Side.
But uh...
You can teach me how to be like her, right?
Yes.
I can teach you.
One more condition.
Don't want me to just be my assistant.
I need you to be my knight, my puppy, great lover.
Irene, my dearest wife.
You were taken far too soon.
Rest in peace, bestie.
You'll always change.
I should place my car.
Ladies and gentlemen, Irene is gone.
And as you can see, I'm more grace-trick than anyone.
But Admiral Group can't be left unhandled.
So I've decided to take over.
I've decided to rename the company.
From Admiral to the Lion Group.
But Miss Irene isn't dead.
She's at the office.
That's impossible.