There. And then what I'll tell you about being British.
Yeah, yeah, I've got it. Got it.
A bottle of water and a cup of tea, please.
Be careful.
It's Miss Irene. She's been missing for almost a month.
We thought she was dead.
Mr. Gwen will be so happy.
He loved her so much.
Gwen loved my sister?
Yeah.
Since Wendy's pushing someone off a balcony count as a love.
Gwen is good at pretending.
To the public, he's a prominent business member.
A loving husband.
He's more evil than I thought.
We have to be careful, Mary.
Is it he gets the chance he could expose us?
Trust me. I'll make sure that Gwen and Jane are paid for their sins.
If you're afraid, just don't calm Mary, okay?
The Irene, I'm always going to break into the CEO's office.
If they do, I'll just say I have some assistance who seduced me.