You.
You're not having me.
Who are you?
My dear bestie, Jada.
Irene has been missing for a month,
vanished without a trace.
You're just a fake.
Brought him by him.
She's a fake?
This woman has plotted with Irene's assistant.
He had her undergo surgery.
She make her look like Irene.
Despicable?
Maybe they even killed her.
Jada's Irene's best friend.
She must be telling you truth.
But how did she know that she was killed?
Only someone as smart as me could see through this woman's disguise.
Speechless, are we?
Throw them out.
I don't want them tarnishing Ireland's company.
Don't you dare.
Into a lap-dong.
Please, to be perfectly cling to Irene.
Is your master gone?
What day you step foot in here?
What proof do you have?
Poor, doggies.
You're quite handsome, closer.
When it's served me instead,
I'll make you a good little boy.
My head.
On my head it hurts.
I think I've done something about a rooftop.
Go to hell, you foolish woman!
No!
Yes, it was very cold and windy.
What was your fault?
What are you talking about?
What windy rooftops?