What windy rooftops?
You were with me, remember?
It was very cold.
And you bought me a birthday shawl.
You were quite broke.
So I looked like you my card.
Anything for my bestie, remember?
My gifts for your best friend with her card.
What a leech.
Don't shut it, you losers!
What's wrong with you spending a tiny bit of our money?
She was rich enough.
You lived in her house rent free.
She financed your movie career.
She bought your magazine covers.
You're only famous because of Irene.
And you fucked her husband.
She's so ungrateful.
Jada really is living off Irene.
She practically begged me to take the house in money.
What I brought to her life is worth much more than that.
There's a de-list celebrity.
What do you actually bring to the table?
What does she bring to the table?
I mean...
Lithna, the Duke of Wood Street,
plans to invest in Admiral.
For me.
Wrong.
The Duke of Wood Street's investment is actually named for me.
Specifically, isn't that right, Danny?