One password, access denied.
I told her she wasn't tiring.
Now get this impostor out of here!
You want me ready for a trip to hell with me, my Cerberus?
You really like comparing these dogs, don't you?
It's because you're my puppy.
And I'm joking. Do you really think you can put the correct password in?
My finger slipped.
Press the wrong key accidentally, but it's fine.
There's one chance before you count marks.
What if she gets it right this time?
Don't give her a second chance.
Dad's trying hard your job.
The impostor just assaulted me.
I was trying to catch you, but it's very hard to grab such a slippery bitch.
Darling, you still have shares in the company, don't you?
And you?
You got very used to using me for my money.
So what?
Well, I shouldn't let our shareholders be the ones risking everything, should we?