I really want my bestie to make her splash.
Considering I'm no longer Miss Irene's assistant,
she can't tell me what to do.
Don't anger him.
Even the cutest puppy bites.
You're crazy! Just like her!
I thought that was a compliment.
I said, ah! I know you two are fucking.
I'm unworthy of Miss Irene's indulgence.
I'm merely the assistant.
Sister Gwen, maybe you just can't seem to satisfy Miss Irene in that, er... area.
Darling, don't bring up my husband's sore spot.
You know, he finishes quickly.
Thetic.
Not like you.
Keeping me happy all night.
Let's keep it down.
It's a spare, Mr. Gwen, to pry.
Shut up!
How about that?
That's if I'm still fine.
This captain's from ruling you.