Darling, why are you, why are you getting so worked up, don't you love me, don't you trust me anymore?
Shut up! Get off of me, you weasel.
Everyone knows that our marriage was just a show anyway.
You've lost me. You've fast given me all your assets.
Never.
Oh, a normal thing actually.
Slip with me.
Maybe. Just maybe.
Consider buying you a divorce gift. What do you want?
I gave you a chance, but you're a little lover boy here.
It just keeps taking all the decisions for you.
What are you going to do? I expose you to the media, of course.
Why would you do that?
Well, then you make you look like a bigger idiot.
If you can't control your wife or your marriage, you can't be CEO.
Shut up!
Don't you lay a hand on her. Get off me!
Who do you think you are? Duke of Woodspoon.
And even if he was, for some reason on your side.
You think that the Jew is going to be on your side?
Look like I say, what's this get out? He's not going to be on yours, is he?
Illusional boy!
Here's on our side.
Because I am.
When I'll do it.
Throw a little party in the hall. See you in the bedroom.
Oh.
I know you idiot.
I mean, I'll give you animal entertainment.