I mean, I'll give you Admiral Entertainment.
Yes! Brilliant!
I'll publicly announce it in three days' time.
What are you doing?
The company will be yours.
Until then, don't bother me and Daniel anymore.
I hope you enjoy your time together.
Irene didn't expect it, did you?
In the end, the company will belong to me.
What are you doing here? Foolish woman?
I brought you a little surprise.
Are we having a threesome?
A ring?
Well, unless you've got magical powers, I've said I'm disappointed.
Well, the magic effect it does.
This is the Duke of Woodspree's ring.
It's allowed to control all the resources in the city.
Fuck me sideways, darling.
How did you get it?
Don't worry about that.
With this ring, I must powerful as the Duke of Woodspree.
Darling, aren't you clever?
Fuck Irene.
It depends on my precious jader.
Oh, but this ring.
I'm the most powerful woman in the city.
I'll crush Irene like an ant.
Oh, Jader, you are my true love.
Oh, at this time, make it up to you tonight.
I'll make sure we get rid of Irene.
This time for good.