Oh, he looked familiar. I'm sure I've seen him somewhere.
Oh, I remember. A coffee shop.
Down the street. He's a barista, right?
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah. The barista.
If my plan fails, I won't be able to protect my sister's company.
We'll lose everything.
Gwen and Jada will be brought to justice. Trust me.
For my sister's sake, this has to work.
I'll do everything in my path to stop Gwen.
Yeah, he deserves everything he gets.
Harry, if I lied to you, would you leave me?
It depends what you lied about.
If you broke my heart, I'd have to break something else.
When the time is right, I'll tell you my identity, but not now.
Jada.
Irene, I have the photos.
If you don't want your fair to be exposed, meet me, alone.
Fine. Let's see what Jada wants.