Great, now she has what?
Daniel, why aren't you here yet?
We'll see if that little dog wants you once you have nothing left.
How could I be the party?
I'm doing it.
I have an announcement. Gwen is going to be a father.
Well, I'm not quite yet.
Yes, that's right.
Gwen and I sell mates, but we can finally be together forever.
Okay, darling, can we discuss the meta later?
I mean, get news, obviously.
No, no, no, no. We've waited long enough.
Besides, getting married soon.
Did you really just divorce me to marry my best friend?
Jada and I assault.
Irene forced me to marry her and threatened to kill Jada if I did.
Irene was a side chick, and she cheated.
She deserves this.
I won.
Irene, I'm about to become the richest man in this city.
And I'll become the richest man's wife in the city.
Don't be too jealous now.
Oh, darling.
What are you going to spend our money on?
No.
Well, like Irene's money.
It's a shame she works so hard and can get spend a penny.
Bye, whatever you want, my beloved beauty.
Enough.
It's time for the charade to end.
I'm not Irene.