I'm not Irene.
What did you just say?
I'm Irene's twin sister.
Mary.
That's impossible.
I've known Irene all my life, and she's never mentioned anything about twin sister.
I told you to lost the plot since I divorced you.
You belong everybody mental.
Back in your hospital.
I moved with my mom when I was young.
It's a family secret.
Of course you wouldn't know.
You didn't wear the company's mind.
Oh, is that so?
This contract needed Irene's signature, but uh...
Oh no.
I'm Mary.
What are you trying to say?
I'm trying to say this agreement is invalid.
Bullshit!
This agreement was with Adderall, and you don't even own the company, so that means...
You're in breach of contract.
The penalty for breach of contract is astronomical.
What do you...
You might have to sell Jayda to pay for it.
I don't think you're gonna get very much for her though.
She can't tell you the truth, can she?
The truth and nothing but the truth.
If you can't pay the penalty, you're gonna go to jail.
You and Jayda.
Oh, maybe you can get married there.
You're framing me!
What a vicious woman treating your brother-in-law like this.
Oh, my brother-in-law?
You're a fair led to my sister being pushed off a balcony!