I mean fell off about me was an accident. Very sad but these things happen. I'll suit you for smart. Oh, I'll tell everyone
They were behind her
Yeah, she discovered their affair and so to keep their secret. They push her off a balcony
Well and Jada can burn in hell if what she says is true, but she hasn't provided the evidence yet
You have no truth she wouldn't challenge me
In front of all these people
Damn right I do
I want everyone to see you for your true colors fucking parasite
You've leeched on my sister for her whole life for everything she had
And you're gonna spend your whole lives in prison where you belong
You think you are judging us like that a present like you darling get the uh
Jukes me the Duke of Woodspree has arrived who wants to fuck with me now
This is an ancestral ring the ring is real
Maybe it's not the Duke of Woodspree. It's the duchess of Woodspree
That's right. I've seen it somewhere. Let me have another. No, no, no. Someone like you. It's not long to come near this game over Mary
Wake up and face reality beg me. Maybe just maybe I'll throw a dog a bone and I'll give you a slither of yes
About your massive death
My darling here is that that is a Woodspree. I can't have managed to drop in the bucket
That's right in the name of the duchess. I plan to invest 300 million
Gwen's name the duchess really is crazy rich
300 million, you know, that's not even half the penalty duchess jade is that all you've got
Here's your chance come on stage in the wispy family guarantees your right future
Here doesn't look like you have any trust with them and I'll just considering and thinking over get a whole stage now
Sign the papers otherwise
I'm with your bankrupt
See see a bright future don't you?
Oh, yes, my duchess. I love you
Irene's fake sister little kid. Oh shut up Gwen bad enough for your shit
You want evidence of them killing Irene? I've got it
Time for you to be exposed to the world
Not just me darling. Your dear husband when he also helped
So and that's not it. There's a voice note
Go to hell you foolish woman. Oh my god. They are murderous the evidence that you wanted
Satisfied you know you know anymore you idiot. Why did you run your mouth job? Let me fix this. I'm the duchess now
I run this city
So what if I murder somebody no different than kidding and being a duchess gives you the right to kill people?
Oh my god. I despise rich fucks like you
You just look all noble and fancy and pretty on the outside
You're filthy and rotten on the inside the Duchess of Woodscrew. You're really quite evil
I can't believe we believed
Didn't stop the Duchess when I have the ring
Publicly impersonate the Duke of Woodscrew
What are you doing here old man? Who's telling the truth?
You're still acting. Let's not get carried away. Shall we? Stop creating a scene with your man
I don't know your garbage. I wouldn't want to get physical
Would I I think twice about doing that Gwen attacking Royston here is like slapping the face of the woods
A fake just like her
You know very well, Jamie was in the duchess. You just get out of the way
You're an important little sin. You're an imbecile. You just need to keep his mouth shut. Get off me. Royston
It's not me. It's there before
You're grace. Give the order. I have the wrongs proof. Do you have? I am the witness witness
I'll see all this they believe you. Do you think the ring means everything? The whisper ring is in my hand
The girl's needs to be said you don't need sus possessions to prove himself
People with no status that need a little ring to prove themselves. It is only an accessory
everyone please
I'd like you to take one of these rings as a gift from the Duke of Woodsprew to prove that they mean
And one more thing Mary Brown my fiance
She orchestrated this whole plan
To expose you to the justice on her sister
Irene called me just before she died
It's a little higher idea. Please family look off Gwen. Oh, you know the pursuit. Yes, he's a stain
You would force me to bed with you, but you could confess your love and then decide if you
Record these two and expose them to the city
Tomorrow's headlines ready. Make sure to capture every detail to please. I'm pretty obsessed with you
I'll do anything sweet sweet Jane
It's dog already has no no and one more thing. I'd like to make an announcement to miss Mary Brown. Miss Mary Brown
Will you marry? Crazy? I'm not a noble woman. I can't just marry a Duke. You say yes
You lied to me. Does it give you thrill?
Mary I keep me in the dark like this
Mary only lied to you because I was trying to protect you Jada Gwen and Jada have been arrested
Tell the prison self to keep them safe from my behalf the guards are signed to protect Miss Mary have returned
And Miss Mary need to keep this safe. You're grace
You've been waiting all day
You could just go up and see
Just doesn't want to see me wasting. Why did my identity made it quite mad to be the Duke?
Why do you have to be one of those rich ass holes I despise and my sister?
Oh, you're grace. Miss Mary has opened the curtains. Mary
You still have feelings for me, don't you? Mary's talk to me. Please. I miss you
I'll talk to strangers. I don't even know. I'm Daniel Vanderwood
Everything ended when you hid your identity. You know you promised me no secrets
I only hid my identity because I was trying to protect you trying to protect me
Stop treating me like a child Daniel. I'm trying to say is it not that matters. I don't care about you
You know, I'm not I read anymore. So you just stop this believe me
Please in honor of the woods refamily in honor of the family
You don't get it. Do you? I'm just a normal girl, okay, and I love my normal life
And you're the elite and you know what we don't make a good match
Mary, I love you all the cars gowns estates
Castles even the stars doesn't mean anything. I'll throw it all away
I don't care about any of that. You know my dad promised my mom the world and then he's still abandoned her
I'll step down as the Duke. I don't care. It means nothing to me. You only mean something to me
Mary, please. You've got to listen to me
It's not fresh clean slate. Let's get to know each other as anyone Mary. Mary. I love you
I'm Mary Brown
Bartender living in London
Favorite colors yellow
Favorite fruit was a melon like
So that's how you won my sister back. It's pretty cliché pretty much anyway
You're awake and Gwen and Jader in jail. I couldn't be happier. Thank you so much
For getting back everything I worked so hard for so grateful
So when am I planning the wedding? Am I bridesmaid?