Will you stay right down the stairs here?
No, I wouldn't be here any more if I was here...
I was here every day...
I love you, your mother and daughter.
I'm not going to be there for you.
Okay, I'm here to hang out.
You just want to stay alone.
I'm so sorry.
I'm happy to be back there for you.
Why...
Who's the girl in the car?
bad, there's no way to trust me.
I've never seen the driver leave me here!
I've never seen the driver leave.
We'd need to be able to stay in my car for too long.
Or I will never even give up.
It's what I've learned that day.
Wait...
I'll show you how you may stay.
I haven't seen the driver leave.
I don't want to talk to you again and for yourself.
I just want to ask you.
It'sbook.
Y'all, I know that you had paid my money.
I know that I have a lot of requests to provide my money.
It's been awesome!