Oh, wait for you, Olga.
That happened.
Nothing to worry about. Just some issues with the film crew.
Why are you being so nice to me?
No reason.
Here. Take this card.
It's unlimited. Spend it however you want.
Why are you doing this? I don't want your money.
Well, if you need money, just let me know, and you can stop looking for odd jobs.
Odd jobs? Acting is my dream.
I danced in strip clubs for a living, but people like you born from a silver spoon wouldn't understand that.
Then stop doing it.
We're in a contract marriage, right?
I won't interfere with your life, and you can't meddle in mine.
Acting is something that I've always wanted.
And besides, I'm not going to take your money besides the number that we agreed on.
You need to rest now.
Do you mind?