Why did you bring me here then?
Well, it was actually his idea.
Hello.
Hi, is this Jean?
Who is this?
This is Edward Arduin.
I recently invested in a film project
that I want you to take your friend, Thelma.
I think she'll be great for a lead role.
Wait, wait, you're Edward Arduin?
I wired the payment to your account.
Thank you.
Oh, wait, wait!
Oh, I still can't believe I spoke to a legendary Edward Arduin.
I can't believe you knew all this time and you didn't tell me.
Don't look at me.
I'm just the middle man doing somebody else a favor, okay?
And you still have to believe.
You know, a lot of people say that Edward's not very nice.
He's like a stone cold man.
Why is he being so good to you?
Yeah, I don't get it either.
I mean, women must be throwing themselves at him.
Why?
What do you help?