Well, you won't take my money, and I can't allow the wife of Edward Artoan to just work
a regular job.
Oh, okay, so that's why.
Our all-rich people listen to what they're saying.
What was it?
Nothing.
This is great.
You know, you can be real sweet sometimes.
This is delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
Sweet pea.
Good morning, man.
And what is left already?
Thank you.
I saw you were cooking last night.
I watched through your tinsel.
Uh, yeah.
It was Edward.
It is the cook.
It's Horton.
Gotta go.
I'm good.
What is going on?
What are we waiting for?
Let's get started.
One of our lead roles is not here yet.
Ugh, no one thing.
I ask everyone here.
Is it should be?
Sorry, guys.
Traffic was nightmare.
All right.
I'm ready to start.
Wait.
I thought that she didn't get the part.
Well, how about that?
Looks like I'm gonna be playing here.
It's deep.
We'll see about that.
42 delta take two.
Ready.
You have to leave now.
Not without the love of my life.
I'll wait for him no matter what.