But Thelma is the lead.
Yeah, that wouldn't make any sense.
We can't make more changes to the script,
and we're already behind.
Better get right to it then.
You don't have to do this for me.
I'm not doing it for you.
Doing it for my own investment.
All right, we have added a line to the script.
So now, Thelma, Carla's new line will be your Cufus.
Slap. Got it?
All right, and... action.
You have to leave now.
Not without the love of my life.
Oh, wait for him no matter what!
But what if he's dead?
What if he finds somebody else?
He's just gonna spend the rest of your life
waiting for someone who will never come?
Then I'll be sure to leave no room for regret.
Pot!
Oh, Bravo!
That was perfect, Thelma!
You handled that perfectly.
Alma, where are you next to the love of Carla after that line?
Uh, no need for that.
I think that my character is above that kind of pettiness.
We'll expose you, Thelma.
Sooner or later.