Could you maybe explain this you know how to better mature if I get it?
I mean, it is pretty straightforward. Just do what it says without improvising.
Well, not you. Oh, great yesterday.
I want to go over this one part. Now, when you say this line, I'm about.
See who wins?
What am I doing this afternoon?
Well, it's kind of a very important meaning. Did you forget?
Castle, some of my apologies.
What?
So, what do you normally do when you're not working?
Uh, I do scriptees.
Oh, I was thinking more along the lines of going to the movies.
There's actually a good one out right now.
I mean, maybe if you're interested, we could try to catch it together.
I'm sorry, but I really need to focus on this job right now.
Oh, yeah, sure, sure.
You're a really interesting person to talk to, you know that?
Edward, are you here to see me?
Are you part of that?
Edward?
It's not for you. I'm sorry.
Why is she still talking about you?
Go put the steps in the lounge.
Got it, boss.
Edward?
What's your name again?
Actually, it doesn't matter.
What were you talking to my wife about?