What are you doing?
Carla and I aren't together.
I'm here for you.
You really expect me to believe that.
Don't worry.
Yeah, girl?
What?
Gene, are you absolutely sure?
Yes.
Positive.
I used to know this guy from the streets,
and he and Elgar drifted around for months.
So where is he?
Well, they later got separated, so he has no idea after that.
But that's gotta mean that Elgar's still alive, right?
Oh my goodness.
Thank you so much.
You have no idea how much this means to me.
It's been 10 years.
Don't forget, you are married too.
What are you going to do?
Oh, to force him.
Once our contract is up, I needed the money.
Elgar will understand.
I know.
Edward seemed really into you.
Actually, Gene, I think I should keep my distance from him.
You OK?
Yeah.
Want to tell me what happened?
I just want to be alone for a bit, OK?
Is this about Carla?
I told you I went to see you, not her.
Edward, I don't care who you're seeing.
We're only married on paper, right?
Is this because we're moving too fast?