I thought this was my personal changing room, like it's always been.
Carla, this room is for the lead role.
He wears his outside.
Well, actually, I'm all done here.
Carla loves taking things that aren't hers.
Be my guest.
Use it.
Aren't you quite generous then?
Mm-hmm.
Edward's not here, so you can drop the act.
We actually need to get back to work, if there's nothing else.
Actually, I can finish my makeup myself.
Go on.
What do you want to talk about?
Let's make a deal.
A deal?
Hahaha.
What the fuck do you think you are?
Well, as far as I know, I'm Edward's wife.
Kind of deal.
Stop picking fights with me.
Stop giving me a hard time on set, and I won't take anything away from you.
I'll actually help you with whatever you and Edward have going on.
Alright, deal.
I'm done with this room, by the way.
It's yours if you still want it.
I don't need your pity.
Don't you have, like, business to run?
What are you doing here all day?