Boss, you've been here for a while. Is everything okay?
You're the one she's looking for.
Do you remember what I did to return to the Arduan family?
About Algar.
Are you telling me that Mr. Arduan knows his illegitimate son is Algar?
Yes, and now the old man wants him back.
Mmm, another brat to show their inheritance.
If I could only get rid of his mother,
getting rid of him shouldn't be a problem.
Madam, it's our fault.
Please don't withdraw your donation to the orphanage.
If we work together on this.
Take care of it.
But make sure you're new to yourself.
Yes, please.
Have to see it, sir.
I got rid of the woman who killed my mother.
Sent me to an orphanage.
Everyone associated with her over the years.