I did whatever it took to gain my father's approval, to secure my inheritance, my methods were ruthless, my conscience, and Calus.
You did what you had to do.
I'm a different man, a monster, she doesn't even recognize.
If she finds out this is the man she's been looking for all these years, it'll drive her away.
I can't lose her again.
So it was true?
Arcon and I, we roamed the city for a winter, and a lot of people say he made some enemies.
One night, under the bridge where we slept, he got stabbed, and he died.
No, you're mistaken.
He always had a ring with him.
It was a nice ring.
I think he had the letters A and H on it.
I told him he could pawn it for a few bucks, but he just kept it with him.
He can't just be gone. He can't just be gone.
It's okay.