Edward, what are you saying?
I told you to stop pulling these tricks behind my back.
I didn't do anything!
Don't listen to her, she's making it all up!
Carla had someone on the prop team switch the fake knife with a real one.
She almost killed Delma and myself.
Edward, I'm sorry, I messed up.
Please, please give me another chance.
I've given you plenty of chances.
Really, Edward, tears.
Please stop, please stop yourself.
He ate!
Doing all of this for a man, I hope it's worth it.
Edward, you know everything we did, it's because I love you.
If you try her to hear again, you will be sorry.
The hand rub is in place.
Well, now that that's over, we should talk about what you said to me earlier.
Which is what?
That you were attracted to me.
We're not gonna talk about that.
That's not fair, you tricked me!