You said something about money and assets, and then after that, not a thing.
Okay, back to work, come on.
Can we talk?
I heard you've been looking for someone.
Yes.
I believe this could be helpful.
This place is reopening soon.
I'd like for you to come.
What does this have to do with the man that I'm looking for?
You'll see.
Okay, I'll go.
I don't want to spoil the place.
What does this have to do with Edward?
Yes, I trusted you.
Guys, we're blowing up.
What do you mean?
After we posted the behind the scenes, we went viral.
Selma became a sensation.
She's now trending number one, big star.
Trending, does this mean more money?
Of course it does, and that is just the easy part.
I was thinking about my next movie, and I want you.
Wow, this is a dream come true.
And we are having a rap party at the hottest bar tonight.
All right.
You'll wonder who's so generous.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.