Boss, I bought this new contract.
Do you think that I won't be surprised by the party I'm throwing for?
Oh, definitely.
So, should I pick her up or do I had a shot with the party?
You don't do this often, do you?
Great party, Edward.
You'd only be fitting, right?
Not entirely bad.
Thank you.
How would you like to thank me?
Sorry, everybody, attention, attention.
Thank you, thank you.
First off, this has been an amazing three months.
I'd like to thank everybody in here.
Here is two.
It's huge success.
Cheers!
Mm-hmm.
And now a few words from Edward, the man, the big boss, without him, none of this would be possible.
Thank you all so much.
I just want to say how grateful I am for the opportunity.
Jay is an exceptional director.
He's casting remarkable.
Thelma's performance, in particular, out of this world.
And I'd like to take this moment to tell her that I'll always be there to support her.
Cheers.
Stop it.
By the way, do you think Algar will watch my new show?
Do you think it will recognize me?
This is really hard to hear, but you've got to let him go.
Algar's gone.
I'm not giving up until I know for sure.