Mr. Arnold, you got a seven?
I don't.
So, Mr. Arnold, what brings you here, thinking of joining the entertainment industry?
You don't want to be here.
Sorry, I can't help you with that.
So, this new film is a romantic drama with some comedy.
When you're in J's and you're in J's.
You ever want any meat?
Let's go!
No.
Not yet.
Ladies, I would love to thank our amazing director, J, for all of his amazing visions
and everyone else who's helped me on this incredible journey.
What?
I lost specifically.
And I'm so excited to get started because I know that this is going to be another hit.
Alright, ready to check out the set for the new movie?
I want you.
Actually, do you want to check it out together?
Sure.
Della.
Della, Della.
How do you win back a woman?
Two hours?
Who wins?
Gifts are always a good movie.
How would you?
Let's get back to the other side.