Oh God, your car. Look at you. You're just like a total whore. How could this be your car?
Hand over your phone. Please.
That's enough. Mr. Hart, what are you doing here?
Mr. Hart, the youngest billionaire in the States, it's one of the top ten hottest bachelors.
Do you have a problem with my car? I'm with my woman.
But she was stopping... No, of course not.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Come on.
Mr. Hart, thank you so much seriously.
I... Oh!
Who the hell were that?
Oh, it's just my client's... wait, client confidentiality.
I can't let him know what I'm doing here.
Your client? Do you work at the bar?
Yes. Yes. I work at the bar.
I use a couple, huh? I mean, it happens.
Wait, she's working here, and that woman is pissed at her. She? An escort.