You want a divorce.
Grandma, I told you.
I don't even know her.
We have no connection.
I'm gonna hire a divorce lawyer.
Five years ago, if it wasn't for Olivia, you'd be dead.
Olivia? Isn't that?
She has the same name as my wife.
She can have whatever she wants.
Money, the house, the company, everything.
But love and marriage are off the table.
And as for the killers from five years ago,
I know who they are now, and they won't get away with it.
I'm not worried about that.
You know what you're doing, but Olivia is a good girl.
Why don't you try to get to know her, at least.
Maybe you will actually like her.
But I have invited Olivia for dinner tonight,
so you better be on your best behavior and make a good impression.
Don't be the same jerk you've been for the past five years.
That must be Olivia.
Good, dear. Come here.