Oh, Olivia, dear, come in.
There he goes again.
I can't believe it.
I am so sorry, Olivia.
Will had a sudden work emergency.
Please forgive him.
How about you, stay for dinner.
I cooked a prime rib and chicken.
You know, it's okay, Miss Foster.
I actually have a lot of work to do, so let's just reschedule, okay?
I am a disaster.
Oh, hello, sweetheart.
Bring your head to this place.
My.
Let's have some fun.
Stop.
Don't shut up.
Shut up.
Stop.
Wait, is that?
Don't get up.
Give it up.
Oh!
Stop.
Get lost, you old Greta.
Mr. Hurt?
Olivia, what are you doing out here?
What are you doing out here?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm a...
Yeah, I'm good.
I can't let him know my own marriage is a mess.
I'm a divorce lawyer.
Yeah, I was just...
I was meeting with client.
I didn't expect to run into that mess.
Client?
You do, uh, post calls?
Yeah.
Occasionally, I just try to be flexible.
Let me drive you home.
It's not safe out here.
Thank you.
Mr. Hart...
or the ride...
and saving me.
Why do you do it?
I mean, the...
the job.
What's wrong with being a lawyer?
Well, it's challenging, but...
my family really needs money.
My grandma, she just got out of the hospital recently, and...
the bills are...
a lot.
She must be really tough...
struggling so much for her family.
Anyway, um, thank you again.
Wait, I need you.
My company's hiring for an executive assistant.
The pay and perks are pretty good,
and I think you'd be great.
Would you be interested?
You...
want me to be your assistant?
Yeah.
Then you won't have to deal with situations like...
earlier at the war.
I really appreciate the offer.
Mr. Hart, but, um, I can handle my job.
Seriously, that is so kind of you.
Yeah, well, you change your mind just...
let me know later.
I will, I promise.
Thanks again.
Hey.
He's not as cold and distant as I thought.
Ben drove you home.
I saw him at the front door.
What?
In a fancy car.
Dropped you off, didn't he?
Thought he was your husband.
Oh, he is.
So you got yourself a rich boyfriend now.
The field, huh?
What are you talking about?
You know he married.
He's just...
someone I know.
Oh, yeah.
He married five years and you've never seen your husband.
What kind of a marriage is that?
Where are you going?
Is that job interview you talked about?
You know.
You're so stuck and you're boring little job.
I'm heading to a nightclub downtown.
Once I snag a rich guy, I'll never have to work like you.
Maybe someone in finance, trust fund,
six, five, and blue eyes.
You don't get it, do you?
What?
What kind of client coming sure you're prepared?
Yes.
Yeah, absolutely, Mr. Wilson.
I will be ready.
Well, the client's already in the conference room.
Mr. Wilson's in there with him.
He is a total potty.
Looks a little picky though.
Good luck.
Mr. Hart, I have the best way of shrieking town.
All I show your wife doesn't get a penny.
Well, he's actually not my concern.
Next, Mr. Hart.
I'm Dominic Vanderbilt.
I'm sure you've heard of my family.
Trust me, I can help you.
First off, no, I've never heard of your family.
And second, how exactly would that help me in my divorce?
I know how greedy a woman can be in that fact.
I want a solution, not a battle.
This is the best you can offer.
Seems like your firm isn't interested in representing.
Wait, Mr. Hart, please.
Mr. Hart.
You know each other?
No.
Mr. Hart, this is Olivia.
She's one of our top divorce lawyers.
You're a lawyer.
Is that news to you?
I introduced her to you.
Don't you remember?
And you rejected her.
Sorry.
Mr. Hart arrived early, so we started to appreciate it.
It's fine.
He won't choose me anyway.
I already tried.
Anyway, Mr. Hart, it is a pleasure to see you again.
And, uh, good luck with your divorce.
Wait.
I want you to be my divorce lawyer.
Me?
I thought you didn't want me.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
You turned her down when I first recommended her.
That's why we're here.
Now you've changed your mind again?
It was a mistake.
So?
Will you represent me?
Of course.
Of course she will.
It's our pleasure.
Right, Olivia?
Let's start with the basics.
How long have you been married and do you have any children?
God, I can't believe I mistook her for an escort.
She's nothing like that.
Mr. Hart?
Oh, uh, five years.
No children.
Why do you want to get a divorce?
Will you have married because she saved my life?
There's no real connection between us.
Wow, that's, uh, quite a story.
How did she save your life?
Uh, it's a long story.
Maybe for another time.
But anyway, I figured I owed her as much.
So, if I can afford it, she can take whatever she wants.
Wow.
He's willing to give her anything she wants.
How nice.
If only my jerk husband was half as considerate.
Olivia, I'm not trying to hide anything from you.
It's too complicated.
Uh, no, no, no, sorry.
I was just thinking.
Um, okay.
I think I have a great grasp at the situation.
Now it's the important part.
Telling your wife about the divorce.
Would you like me to handle that or do you want to talk to her yourself?
I'll call her.
Hello?
Mrs. Foster?
I've heard William's been talking to lawyers.
That's nonsense.
If he tries to use a lawyer to intimidate you.
Let me know.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you, Mrs. Foster, but I'm a lawyer, too.
He can intimidate me, but I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Is this Olivia?
This is your husband.
What?
So this is Olivia's mysterious husband.
I'm not...
What a divorce.
It's time we discuss a settlement.
Settlement?
What are you offering?
Cash, stocks, or bonds, whatever you prefer.
If that's not what you want, you can't be villain Miami or the estate Beverly Hills.
Olivia's husband is eluded.
I can't let this opportunity go to waste.
I need to think about it.
Okay.
Let's meet on Friday to finalize everything.
It's your fault you left your phone at home.
Now the jackpot is all mine.
Make this count.
What was that?
Oh, uh, it was just some personal stuff.
I just talked to my wife.
We've been on Friday to finalize everything.
Can you come with me?
Of course.
That's what you pay for.
Uh, what kind of woman is lucky enough to marry a man like him?
No.
Oh, I got a really big client today.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm.
Congrats.
Anyway, when was the last time you saw your husband?
Uh, like five years ago, but we only met once.
Why?
I'm just curious.
Do you think he'd even recognize you now?
Probably not.
He wasn't really in the best shape back then, so I would say no.
Oh, that sucks.
Hey, have you seen my other phone?
I, uh, think I left it at home today and I haven't been able to find it.
There it is.
Oh, no!
This is mine.
Sorry.
It just looks really similar.
Have you seen mine?
No.
It brought us somewhere else.
So, about this meeting with your wife.
Do you have any thoughts on how you'd like it to go?
I want it to be over quickly.
No drama.
No fights.
Okay, sure.
I will try and make sure it goes really smooth.
Buddy, he's such a hottie.
Wait, isn't that Olivia?
What's she doing here?
How is Olivia here?
Does she know about the meeting with her husband?
He doesn't know Olivia is his wife?
Are you alone?
With my lawyer.
She's trying to make sure everything goes smoothly.
Is there a problem?
So he's the big client Olivia mentioned.
She's both his wife and his lawyer and she has no clue.
If you want to talk, tell your lawyer to leave.
Otherwise, there's no deal.
My wife wants to talk alone.
I'm sorry about your whole life step out for a bit.
It's okay.
A lot of people get nervous about lawyers.
I'll just wait outside.
Long time no see.
It's cut to the chase.
We only got married because you saved my life.
There's no actual connection between us.
This marriage is a burden to us both.
Olivia saved his life.
She's never mentioned that.
It's good a divorce.
Name returns and I'll compensate you fairly.
He's loaded and hot.
Cashing in seems like such a waste.
I need some time to think about it.
Don't try this out.
I'm not going to wait forever.
You have one week.
After that, the offer's off the table.
Uh, did your wife agree to the divorce?
She won't say what she wants.
She'll probably go big or she cares about his money.
I feel like she's so different now.
Different now?
Well, it's hard to say.
When she saved my life, she expected nothing.
And now she's a total gold digger.
We found the one behind the attack five years ago.
It's Sebastian Crowley.
His company company.
And he wants to take us down by going after you.
He thought he could come after me and get away with it.
He'll pay for this.
I want his company gone in a week.
He'll have nothing after messing with me.
Wow, that's pretty cool.
You're afraid of me.
Actually, I admire your sense of justice.
Sit for 10.
It's not supposed to be.
You know, they come to crawl?
Sometimes when you're kind to your enemies, you're being cruel to yourself.
That's why I choose to be strong.
She has the same name as my wife, but they're so different.
Tomorrow is your birth for dinner.
It'll be there too.
You two can celebrate together.
It's time to have a proper talk with that jerk.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Oh, and I have a little surprise for you.
I'll find out tomorrow.
Thanks.
Hello, day tomorrow.
No, it's just a small family dinner.
It's my birthday.
Wait.
Her birthday is tomorrow?
Lydia, you did all of this?
You actually remembered it was my birthday.
Oh, of course.
I wanted to do something special for you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
This is so good.
So I heard you got married because you saved your husband's life.
Mm.
Bit.
That.
Well, he got into some trouble these guys were after him.
And I helped him hide from them.
Actually, I stole a scar from that night.
From now on, both your husband and your scar belong to me.
These flowers are gorgeous.
They must have cost a fortune.
I heard Olivia's husband sent them.
So romantic.
Oh.
Can I help you, sir?
I'm here to see Olivia better.
Oh, are you her husband?
What?
She's married?
Of course.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Her husband's at this beautiful bouquet earlier and we thought you were him.
Oh, I'm in here.
She is now.
Hi.
The delivery guy said that he delivered me something do you have to know where it is?
From your husband.
Isn't that sweet?
Oh, this must be the surprise Mrs. Foster mentioned.
She sent it in my husband's name.
Oh, and this gentleman is here to see.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't see you.
Did you want to talk to me about something?
So?
Yeah.
For the past five years now.
So the family dinner you mentioned yesterday.
That was with your husband.
Yes, and his family.
The flowers are forward.
Oh, for a friend who just moved.
I should get going.
Do you happen to know why Mr. Hart was here?
She's married.
Who's the lucky guy that got to marry her?
Grandma?
Olivia, I know it's been tough for you these past few years.
Will has been so caught up with his work, he's neglected you.
But tonight, you two will finally talk it.
He should be here any minute.
Thank you, Mrs. Foster.
I appreciate it.
Mrs. Foster, I'm sorry.
The boss had a last minute emergency and won't be able to make it.
He sends his apologies.
Oh, dear.
Olivia, don't worry.
I'll get him here tonight, no matter what.
This is unacceptable.
It's really okay, Mrs. Foster.
He's probably busy and we'll get another chance to be.
Actually, you know what, I totally forgot.
I've got this report due in the morning, so I should really get going.
What an unforgettable birthday.
My husband doesn't want to see me.
I don't even know what he looks like.
I'm a divorce lawyer who can't even handle her own marriage.
Screw it.
I need a drink.
She's married?
How's that even possible?
She didn't even mention a husband.
She's probably celebrating her birthday with him right now.