What?
What was that?
Oh, that's just... just my cousin.
Anyways, sorry for being like really drunk last night.
Thank you for taking me home.
My pleasure.
Call me next time you need a drinking buddy.
Can we talk about this, Mr. Hart's gone.
I swear nothing happened.
Hello?
Our foundation is hope that this Wednesday at Magnet Palace.
We'll be sure to be there this time.
I promise.
We'd love for you to join us.
Wednesday?
Mrs. Foster, I'd love to go, but I'm not quite sure if I'm free.
How about I check my schedule and I'll go back to you?
Oh, of course, dear. Let me know.
Okay.
Magnet Palace.
That place costs a fortune.
Who are you talking to?
Oh, it was just my husband's family.
They're hosting like this charity event.
Wednesday?
Are you going?
Uh, yeah, I don't know.
Probably not. I've been really busy.
So, do you like when I talk about...
Oh, no. No, I'm fine.