Do you decide what you want?
I heard the Hark family is having an event Wednesday.
We can talk there.
How do you know about the event?
Your grandma invited me.
Okay, Wednesday it is.
Keep your word this time.
And don't bring your lawyer.
That's my condition.
I'll be meeting my wife on Wednesday.
She still has issues with the lawyer, so I'll be going alone.
Just wanted to let you know.
Okay, stay cool.
Come down Olivia.
Okay, plans on Wednesday too.
Just keep me updated.
This is Foster.
Hi.
Yeah.
About the charity event you mentioned?
I can make it.
I'll see you Wednesday.
I'm going to confront that jerk.
Her marriage keeps going in the instruction and there's no reason to stay in it.