Do you have an invitation?
Oh. No, I was actually invited over the phone.
Well, I'm afraid you can't come in. This is an exclusive event.
Well, why don't they need an invitation?
Oh. Because I say so.
They don't smell like some gold digger trying to crash the party.
Mrs. Foster actually invited me.
So please let her or Gary Hoffman or Butler know. They're expecting me.
Oh, did your homework and everything?
Looked up the family member's names?
Real ambitious, aren't you?
You know what? This is ridiculous. Please let them know or let me in.
I've seen plenty of women like you. I think wearing a fancy dress will get you an in with high society.
Making up pathetic lies to mingle with the rich.
Newsflash chick, you don't belong here.
Next time you want to get in, apply for a janitor job.
You know what? This is bullshit.
Security, get her out of here.
Hey, no, I did not.