Mr. Hart, this woman doesn't have an invitation, she's trying to sneak in, just another gold digger trying to crush the party.
Is that so?
Mr. Hart, what a coincidence.
What a climber. Are you flirting with Mr. Hart? You're parking up the wrong tree.
Mr. Hart isn't someone you could just cozy up to.
If you don't want to be the next slapping stock, you'll better leave before he kicks you off with himself.
I think it's you, we should leave.
What?
She's my lawyer, and she's here with me.
Or do I need an invitation too?
No, no, of course not. I didn't know if she was with you.
Oh, and that's why you chose to insult her?
You're fired. And for the record, no company or the Hart name will ever hire you again.
No, no please!
Oh, right, that's impressive.
He's even hotter when he's all serious.
I thought you had plans tonight.
Well, brings her hair.