I'm going to go get myself another drink.
Oh, Mr. Hoffman.
Olivia.
Um, Mrs. Foster said that Bill was here.
Do you happen to know where he is?
Uh, I think he just stepped out.
Left.
Again.
You could always wait.
I have waited five years for him.
I'm not going to waste another second.
Ugh.
Why are they just talking?
Did they have a fight?
I need to tell Ms. Foster.
Name your price.
What do you want?
You brought your lawyer.
Why is Olivia Bennett here?
I said no lawyers.
She's not here as my lawyer.
It's just a coincidence.
How do you know her name?
Your wife?
Of course I should know your divorce lawyer's name.
And the scar remembers too.
After all these years, it's still here.
It will be forever.
You have no idea how bad it hurt when I was hit by those thugs.
Isn't that a bite mark I left on her shoulder?
What does that have to do with the thugs?
Who are you, really?