Oh, I am so sorry, I thought you were someone else.
She looks exactly like Lydia.
Put this on!
Put your mouth shut.
Having fun pretending to be Hart's wife?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know you're not really Mrs. Hart.
But don't worry, I can make it happen.
As long as you give me something in return.
So I saw you talking with your wife.
She's a lovely girl, isn't she?
Are you sure she's my wife?
There's just, I don't know, something a lot.
Of course she's your wife, what's gotten into you?
Alright, but I was talking to her and she seems like nothing more than I'm going with her.
Since she's nothing like that.
She had no idea who you were when she saved you.
She didn't have to hear my- Oh, she's back!