I'm sorry. I shouldn't have recognized you, sorry.
William, no, please, please!
Miss Bennett! Police! Don't move!
Are you okay? Go on ambulance!
You'll pull through, dear.
Miss Bennett, we check the surveillance. She's the one who helped Crowley break into your house.
How could you? Why would you lie to me?
You want to know why?
Why do you always get everything?
Why are you always so lucky?
Why is your husband one of the richest men in the world and I have to date on nobody?
You're insane. Why doesn't he want me?
I'm younger and prettier than you.
You know what? I should have never let you stay with me, you traitor!
You know what to do.
Do you hear his family?
Oh, how is he?