James didn't tell you where he got the necklace today.
Marcus in the entire weed family is after that right now.
If you keep it on, you're wearing a target on your back.
It literally looks like a target.
I'm not part of this, but I'm afraid she's right.
Thanks, buddy.
I'm assuming you don't want Marcus to think you had anything to do with this.
Fine. Let me make a couple calls.
Lisa, do you think you could show me who James is?
It looks like the devil's coming to us.
Hey, buddy. They didn't have a wine, so I got one.
Betty? status report on Betty.
Sir, we've located Betty.
Where is she?
His trip up and down now.
Okay, is Marcus there?
No, he's still nowhere to be found.
Well, then find him.
Send more men out and find him.
We have to find him before Betty does.
I'm sorry, sir, but your father has forbidden the families involved in any gang-related matters.
I don't give a shit. Okay, can we just have to find Betty?
I promised I swore to her that I would protect her.
Just get my gun ready.
Jules, what are you talking about?
Are the Jules.
Okay.
Those Jules, my father has him.
My dad, he's working with little John.
He paid us a fortune for those Jules.
What's his intention?
They don't want to take over the Wade family.
That's everything I know are.
They swear, please.
You should have thought about that before you hurt Betty.
You can't kill me.
You don't even worry between her and me.
Where is she?
Where's Betty?
Oh, you're again, huh?
How the fuck did you get in here? Are you even old enough?
Alright, so you're looking for Betty.
Let me tell you something about her.
You got no fucking clue who she is.
No fucking clue.
Shut up.
Shut up, Marcus.
One move from me and you'll never see her again.
What are you going to do?
Blow my fucking brains out, Anthony.
What's Betty going to think about that?
Where did you get the gun?
Your parents?
Put it down.
I was trying to protect you.
You're not even 21.
You can't even be in here.
Go home.
I didn't ask you to protect me.
Come on, stay out of here.
Betty.
Betty, Marcus is dangerous.
Okay, he can't protect you.
I can save you.
Please, Betty.
No.
I'm going with Marcus.
No, it's never going to hurt you.
Yeah.
I'm going to have to stop over by that body.
He'll never be happy.
I swear.
It's okay.
The Gambino family and old John.
They betrayed my father.
I think that he's in a lot of danger.
I'm going to go.
I need you to stay here.
Wait in backstage.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay, Betty?
No.
I'm going with you.
It's too dangerous.
It's too dangerous, Marcus.
Mr. Gambino.
Marcus.
I think you should understand it.
You're not welcome here anymore.
I can say the same thing to you, John.
So am Mr. Gambino.
Since your son's here, you might as well tell us.
Where are the jewels?
Fred, there's a misunderstanding.
The Gambino family is and always will be an ally to the Wade family.
Is that so?
Is that why you had your son James here team up with John?
Is it commit treason?
Shut up!
What are the missing jewels?
Exactly.
James gave it to Betty's friend as a present.
And here's another piece.
We got it off a man that James hired.
What else James stole me, Mr. Gambino, is that you know where the rest of the jewels are.
It's a horrible misunderstanding.
You see, I'm a decent man.
And I would never, never have any hidden agendas to betray my friends and allies.
This is unacceptable.
All I can say is, it's a shame to have someone like James in my family.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wade, and I'll do my best to make sure that he learns his lesson.
How about this, Mr. Gambino?
We'll settle things down within the family, with Uncle John.
As for the jewels, the Wade family will take them as compensation for their losses.
They'll take an insurance buyout.
It's a win-win for everybody.
What do you say?
Of course.
Understood.
Okay.
It's done.
Old John's been taken care of.
Thank God.
It's all over.
Betty, thanks to you, I was able to attract down the jewels.
You're stuck by my side.
The whole time through all these life threatening events are amazing.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Yes, Marcus, I'll marry you.
Everything looks great, Ms. Wade.
The baby's in good health.
Hey, Doc.
I'll walk you out.
So, I guess your condition returned back to normal, sir?
Would you mind telling me?
How'd you find your cure?
It could be helpful for my research in a related field.
I don't know if it's applicable to your research, but I guess it only works with Betty.
Interesting.
Do you plan to continue this treatment then?
No.
Everything's great.
I did it for my wife, Amy.