Kevin, you're here. How wonderful. The fundraiser will start soon.
Would you mind? Could you please keep your distance from us?
For nonsense, but since we are here, of course, we will donate something for our dear Port Leo.
Dad, they're donating. How kind of fun.
Kevin's real estate business is really flourish, leaving his family quite wealthy.
That could significantly boost the donation.
There's a quarter with that vegetable, Leo.
Kevin, they actually think we were here to donate for them.
Quite so, isn't it? Poor fools. But nobody came here except for us.
Kevin, you're not here to donate.
For that pathetic vegetable in a wheelchair? No.
Only fools like you could think I'll stand one day and be your hero.
You don't have to donate, but please don't insult Leo.
Dabina, dear. You shouldn't waste your time with that rotting vegetable.
Here's a handsome young man waiting for you.
If you were clever, you would get rid of that wheelchair nightmare.
And run after the wealthy tree. How can you even think like that?