My god, Leo, you're awake!
I must be saying things!
I can't believe this.
I mean, Divina's the useless boyfriend actually woke up.
Oh, Leo?
Divina!
You're awake?
Uh...
You're a big jerk.
What took you so long?
I know, Divina.
I had something to wake out and stream these past three years.
I tried to wake up with all my strength.
No idea how much I missed you.
That much I loved you.
Thanks.
The tears are all my fault.
Each one is pierced straight through my heart.
Gosh, everything can do well for you.
The most precious thing for you in the whole world.
It's not your fault.
Leo, I have never regretted waiting for you.
You never regretted anything for you.
I've missed you so much.