How dare you act this way in front of Mr. Brandor.
You fool.
You still think your useless ass father could come save you?
This is Mr. Brandor.
Anybody come around here going to get killed.
It's really a shame, Drew.
Because in fact,
Mr. Brandor is here for me.
But you were right about the last day you said, yeah.
Because you might as well take your own gun and put it to your head.
You're going to be the one that dies today.
You scum.
This is Mr. Brandor headed a Brandor group.
Your poor ass couldn't touch this man's shoes.
How dare you insult me?
Understand that Drew is vital to the Brandor group.
Mr. Brandor is here to see Commander Drew.
And today you're going to realize why crossing us is a big mistake.
Get down and apologize.
Sir, that's not really a means. It's a mistake.
Mr. Brandor, sir.
You shouldn't be here, sir. This place is too dirty.
You shouldn't be with this girl.
Let me take care of this fool right now.
Then we can go get the young Mr. Brandor.
What's your plan?
My plan.
I'm going to put bullet through this man's head right now.
No! No! Stop! Please!
You know the wrong thing.
That's a professional mercenary.
You should always ask for the name of the target before pulling the trigger.
I know, isn't it? That's Leo Thorton.
You're wrong.
It's Leo Brandor.
You fucking idiot!