Mr. Brandor, we really didn't know who you are, that's why we offended you.
If we had known, we never would have dared.
Who I am is that important, you understand?
And as for Divina, she is not just some prize that can be traded.
How dare you force for a ponjoseph?
It's not only kidnapping, it's rape.
F' meow.
You're worthless idiot.
You really like dangling your wealth over other people's heads?
Well, as of today, I am taking all of your wealth from you.
I am bankrupting your company and making sure that all of your future projects go south.
As long as I'm alive, I'll make sure all ghosts are fine.
Take this quarter.
Now it's the only thing that you have left to your name.
Enjoy the slums.
No!
My money!
What, Mr. Leo, please?
It's just, it's Ferris.
We cannot live without money.
Get him out of here!
No!
He would have thought that Leo had such noble background.
Nina, I think you should leave.
What, what do you mean?
Are you trying to...
Your behavior has been ridiculous today.
I don't think this engagement is going to work.
Are you asshole?
What were you trying to say?