Mr. Bailey, what are you thinking, Leo?
I was thinking that maybe I should send out the invitations for the party with a brand
or name on it.
Maybe it'll be more convenient that way.
Of course, everyone's going to answer an invitation for the brand or a man.
Yes, and that way we don't have to make any calls.
All right, Leo.
I know you don't want to leave Davina, but you need to return your family first.
Your uncles are extremely worried about you.
They spend a lot of money trying to find you.
Of course, Dad.
I'll see you at the party.
Send an invitation to Davina's uncle's family, but do not mention my relationship with her.
Sir, do as I say, my reasons.
As you say, sir, I'll handle it.