What a lovely place. Oh, Barton. This is my first time in a place like this. Do you think
Bob and the others will come? Well, they would have to, right? It's an invitation from the
brand rules. There's really no reason for them not to. Guys, it's okay. Leo knows our
situation and besides, even if no one comes, it's not gonna affect our loved ones.
Yeah, our luck is finally changed. Brando's invited us to young Brando's welcoming party.
This is a chance to meet some big names. My boyfriend Billy's father is a hotel
manager here. We can accuse us around. Absolutely. Maybe. We can even meet the
family members of the Brando family. You know it. My dear, I knew you meet the
perfect boyfriend. You're a thousand times better than that. Silly Divina in her
terrible Bailey family. You know what? She can bring herself to leave that
losing boyfriend of hers. She's not even qualified enough to be compared to me. You
made it. Barton, what the hell you doing here? How did you even get an
invitation to the Brando party in the first place?