Bob, even though it's been a while, I knew you'd still come.
Yes, Uncle Bob, I really appreciate that you're still willing to reach out to us.
No, no, no, no. This has the reasons we are here have nothing to do with you at all.
Bob, I tried to call you yesterday.
Young Mr. Brandore will be announcing his engagement to Divina.
I tried to tell you, but you hung up, or would you just shut up?
Do you even know what you're saying?
This is unbelievable. You're disgusting poor people.
How serious do you think of such delusions?
Leo, did you tell Jack not to mention your relationship with Divina in the reception invitation?
That's correct. We will spoil Divina's family and friends with a typical Brandore family hospitality.
But until then, I want to conduct a little test.
To see where Divina's family and friends loyalty lies.
Oh, I see.
I'll be heading down to the party.
Governor Colbert's and father should be finishing their conversation soon.
I suggest you get me down here soon.