Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, you threw out the thief's voice out!
Idiot.
Billy's father is the owner of the hotel.
If he wants to teach you a lesson,
he just has to say the word!
It's right.
Me, isn't as stupid as you are wasted on your time and money
when you're pathetic boyfriend.
And now you're breaking into this noble party
pretending to Mr. Brandar is gonna marry you?
Okay, Daddy can you be!
Your stupidity is a cloy.
I think the most ridiculous person in the world.
Bob, watch your mouth!
The Vita is not stupid. We never lied. Everything we said was the truth.
Oh, Barney.
Being promised to ride in your brain.
I actually feel sorry for you.
I really don't know.
I'm pathetic.
It seems that we should have attended that ridiculous fundraiser that you threw.
Maybe if we donated some money, you wouldn't be so dramatic.
Don't you dare speak to my father like that.
We are family.
How can you be so cruel?
I feel like girls.
Oh, he made cruel.
There's some other slums on you all the way from here.
You're polluting the air of this party.
You make me sick.
Get the hell out of here, you favorite.
Just because you're wealthy does not mean you shouldn't insult others.
Aubrey lies in your soul.
Meow.
Mr. and Mrs. Bailey, why don't you two go relax in the VIP room?
My end of this.
I'll stay with Devina.
Daniel, you must protect Devina.
So, you're Leo.
This is the one you've been talking about all these years.
You really shouldn't talk about yourself like that.
What?
Shut up, you piece of shit.
You're just a vegetable in a suit.
Do you really think that you're a billionaire?
Billy's my boyfriend.
And his father's a hotel manager.
Show some damn respect.
Aah, arrogant fool.
You just now call the tea room and the VIP room.
Everyone knows that the VIP room is for the friend or only.
You have no right to be here.
Me neither.
Is Devina really still your girlfriend?
She was just fantasizing about marrying a thing on Mr. Brandor.
What a foolish girl.
She's nothing but a peasant.
You can't talk to Devina like that.
Jay!
Idiots.
What I said earlier, wasn't direct enough.
Let's try again and I'll be more clear this time.
Your sister Devina is nothing but a filthy disease written for.
Shit.
You're the disease written for no more.
Oh, David, you're talking about Devina.
You're not even worthy of touching one single strand.
I'm gonna insult Devina like that and you have to be ready for my revenge.
You piece of shit!
If either of you keep insulting Devina like that, your family won't even be able to recognize their own family's corpse acceptable.
I appreciate it, Leo, but please stop fighting your bodies.
I'm not doing for you.
You hear that?
I'm letting you go because she asked me too and you're lucky.
I'm crazy, though.
Your piece of shit.
You and that bitch girlfriend of yours.
My father gets here.
I want you to kneel down with fucking boots.
Kyle, today's Mr. Leo's welcome party.
Furthermore, he will be announcing his engagement to a wonderful young woman.
It is a great honor the Brandois have chosen your hotel for this event.
Do not.
I repeat, do not mess this up.
Oh, I will assure you the party will go up extremely well.
I hope to earn considerable favors from the Brandoir family.
It would be my greatest honor.
Keep Devina's name out of your filthy rat mouth.
Billy, I want to make sure I heard this correctly.
Did you say that your father is the hotel manager?
Yeah, that's right.
Are you afraid?
Because it's too fucking late now.
Because the hotel manager is nothing but a ward on my pinky.
You scum.
Piece of shit.
How dare you insult my father like that?
You and that bitch girlfriend of yours.
You scum.
Watch your mouth.
What are you going to do about it?
Your sister's a whore.
Disgusting, brainless idiot.
Say another word about Devina.
And you're going to find out what hell looks like.
Loser.
You loser.
See, in this world, the rich can teach the poor a lesson.
In this world, the rich beat the poor.
You welfare peasants have no voice.
You're done.
Your words are pure ignorance.
All men are created equal.
Devina's right.
Wealth isn't everything.
You insult women with your filthy words and you place money above everything else.
The world looks down on you.
Even if you wore a gold card and carried them.
The world's most expensive cane, everyone would still look down on you in disrespect.
That's cute.
Daniel?
Don't you stand there.
He's been disrespecting your sister.
I think it's time that you teach him a lesson.
Come on.
Let's go.
Asshole.
Stop it.
Dad.
The buoy.
Mr. Leo.
He did this.
That scum in his bitch girlfriend of his.
And they crashed this event and had this peasant beat me up.
Him.
You did this?
But I feel like that's the whole tell man.
You should find out who's responsible and handle the situation.
Oh my God.
You stupid pauper.
Don't you tell me what to do.
Leo, are you okay?
Devina, don't worry about mine.
This is honestly kind of fun.
The more they break about their wealth, the more arrogance they have.
The louder they'll beg for mercy later.
But.
Daniel.
They slapped you twice and me once.
That's thrice.
It's time to give it back to them.
What a joke.
Look at your perilous pathetic boyfriend.
Nothing but a clown.
Where is she?
Leo is not a joke or a clown.
I've said multiple times that money and wealth isn't everything does not make a good person.
Besides, even if you were rich, the Bailey's have a gold mine worth five billion dollars.
I doubt you have anything that compares to that.
Oh blah blah blah.
Bullshit.
And I have a gold mine worth ten million dollars.
And I'm going to go play golf with Governor Colbert next week too.
Great new loser.
Governor Colbert will be joining us later today.
But he's here to see me.
Not you.
He's actually here to congratulate me.
Alright.
Whatever.
You bragging little jerk.
Alright?
I'm going to that bitch girlfriend here.
You know what?
Your mother must have been a whore to raise someone like you.
Shut up.
Daniel, what are you waiting for?
It's time.
What are you going to do?
Yeah.
You don't have enough courage to do anything if you...
Dead.
Hey.
Good job, Daniel.
Today we're teaching this comma lesson for degrading women and using a little bit of power.
Well, I'm going to call security and you're all being jammed.
I hope you all die.
Jack.
Listen, Dyson, what are you doing?
Shut the fuck up, Kyle.
From the moment you slapped Mr. Video, your hotel no longer exists.
Mr. Dyson, no.
Why are you listening to this guy?
He's just a troublemaker.
Why are you treating him with such respect?
Dyson, what are you doing?
Why are you hurting my dad?
This is a mistake.
Leo.
Bastard.
You're a worthless piece of garbage.
Nothing but a rat.
Doc.
Doc, what are you doing?
We have nothing to offend you.
But you've offended Mr. Leo and that is far more important than offending me.
What?
He's nothing but a beggar.
Then we're not his girlfriend.
Why would you show him so much respect?
No, it's quite the opposite.
Mr. Dyson, why did you hit us?
I mean, who is this noble scum?
Who is he, really?
What's the rush?
You'll soon find out who I am.
And then you'll beg for mercy.
He's there.
I think I just saw the chairman of the thorn group.
Oh my God.
That's Mr. Brandor.
He's the head of the Brandor group.
Mr. Brandor.
He is here.
Oh my God.
We're actually giving him.
He's such a celebrity person.
Mr. Brandor.
We offer our sincere greetings, Mr. Brandor.
Yes.
Your presence in this grand hotel brings even more light to such a grand place.
Your sincerity touches me.
Mr. Cloud.
Miss Cynthia.
I'm glad you're here.
So tell me.
How did the conversation with Governor Colbert go?
You scum.
How dare you face the chairman of the thorn group.
This is Miss Cynthia and the esteemed Mr. Brandor.
How dare you speak with them.
Yes.
Sure loser.
How dare you disrespect Mr. Brandor like that.
He's looking at gravestones.
Where to put it right now?
That's right.
We're going to die today, kid.
Enough.
Everybody.
Do you even know the theme of this party?
We do, Mr. Brandor.
This is a welcome party for the young Mr. Brandor.
We've got gifts and everything.
Just young Mr. Brandor hasn't arrived yet.
Nonsense.
What do you think is standing in front of you?
What?
Mr. Brandor?
What do you mean?
You mean, could it be?
The young Mr. Brandor?
But that's impossible.
Silly girl.
The truth is right in front of you yet.
You still say it's impossible.
You've been ruined.
Leo wasn't trying to cause you any trouble.
He just wanted to find out who your true family and friends are.
You know that he is what we need to do with any.
Thank you for telling me, Miss Cynthia.
I completely understand.
Today is Leo Brandor's homecoming party.
Leo is Cynthia, my son.
He didn't use my surname only because of the Thorne family's family tradition.
My son is an outstanding young man who will inherit everything that belongs to the Thorne family and the Brandor group.
That news wasn't great enough.
We have another big announcement.
Divina Bailey.
Kind.
And loving young lady.
During the three years that Leo was in the home,
Divina dropped out of school and used all of her savings.
To treat and care for our son.
The love between Divina and Leo is strong and tender.
And as expected, Leo is going to marry Divina.
This loser?
He kept me the young Mr. Brandor.
And then Divina is going to marry him?
That can't be true.
Mr. Brandor and Mrs. Thorne, Governor Colbert has arrived.
Please, invite them in.
To meet you Mr. and the young Mr. Brandor.
And of course, the beautiful Mrs. Cynthia and Mr. Vintra.
A pleasure.
Thank you for joining us on such a short notice. I totally appreciate it.
A pleasure indeed. We have more gifts to bless your marriage.
You are made for each other.
Your story is the most touching story we have ever heard.
These are two pure world couplings.
Handcar by Master Robert.
The pair for the gentlemen is elegant and solid.
While the pair for the lady is delicate and exquisite.
These are for the young Mr. Brandor and Mrs. Divina.
Wishing them a beautiful happiness in the future.
The tradition worldwide in a husband's auction?
Please, old friend, it's sounding ten million dollars.
What?
This is a silver tea set.
Handcrafted by a royal artisan.
I worked very hard to acquire it from a Danish collector.
With the fine exquisite.
Therefore the couple to bring them joy and a happiness full of love.
I know that. I've seen that.
That's a family heirloom from the royal Dutch family.
Someone just tried to buy that for thirty million dollars.
I can't believe it's here. I never thought I'd see that.
It's my year.
I almost feel as though I don't deserve them.
You looked after our Leo when he was lost to us and no one else would.
You deserve more than you can imagine.
Governor, these gifts are unbelievably precious and elegant.
Thank you.
We will cherish your blessings, Governor.
Oh, I'm Billy.
I almost forgot.
Didn't you say earlier that you were going to dinner with Governor Colbert
and you were going to play golf with him?
He's right here. Why don't you ask him?
Mr. Brando, please, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you.
Forgive me. Please.
Forgive me. I'm begging you.
Look, I'm sorry. We didn't know who you were.
We made a great mistake.
We were being very foolish before.
Please.
Can forgive us.
While you were all Divina's family, and I do want to go easy on you,
you have completely let wealth and power get to your heads.
You do not deserve to be Divina's family or friends.
It's oblivious when you were Divina's friends.
You didn't mean her, Divina.
Do I need to remind you how you've treated her?
And you even slapped her brother.
Divina, what do you think?
When they needed help, my parents stepped in and gave them a hand.
But when the roles were reversed, they beat us.
And even insulted us.
We don't need family like that.
Divina, how could you be so heartless?
We're family.
Divina, please, stand up.
What, you're still planning, Divina?
Sir, you are beyond saving. Take them away!
We can't do this.
We have to be his uncle!
The family!
How could you do it?
If our obstacles are out of our way, we can get married.
We have a beautiful life together.
Leo, this feels like a dream.
Leo, reset the engagement ring you prepare.
Divina, Leo spent a long time picking up that ring just to make you happy.
Leo Brandor, don't you want to know why you had that car accident years ago?