I can't believe the nerve to walk out on me.
Just cancel the room.
Chloe, I can't. It's past cancellation time.
Just say it's a player player.
I can't. They're cracking down on things.
And with the hotel getting acquired, I can get fired.
Eva, you know I can't wait for the room.
Maybe you should have thought of that before you booked a $5,000 night suite to loan some rich guy.
He's stiffed me.
In more ways than one.
Please, I'll pay him back.
I can't.
It's under my name. I can't pay for it.
Our management will fire me.
I need this job for my mom.
I don't have that kind of money.
What kind of money?
Chloe, what are you doing here?
I have to get back to work.
Chloe!
I can't wait for this place sells and they don't have to deal with idiots.
Eva, I see we have a guest in the Presidential Suite.
Good. I'll be keeping track of it.
Wow.
Your best friend just cost you $5,000.
What am I supposed to do with a $5,000 night suite?
I mean, if you have to pay for it, you might as well enjoy it.
I guess I'm just drinking my way into debt at this point.