Speak of the devil.
Your highness, um, can I call you your highness, um, Duke?
Can I, can I, can I please take a selfie with you?
Of course.
She's fired.
Security.
No, please, please.
Like, I worked really hard.
Please don't.
I love you.
He fired someone over a selfie.
He definitely can't find out we slept together.
Your grace is an honor to have you here.
I am Christine Bernard.
Yes, I know.
You are?
Your reputation precedes you.
You've been the GM for the last five years and helped in the acquisition of this hotel.
Well done.
Since you're new here, I would like to offer you my secretary caped to assist you.
Mr. Sinclair, great to be working with you.
Yes, I will need a new secretary, but I prefer to choose my own.
By the way, I am calling off the acquisition.
We're no longer silent.
You can't call it off.
I've already signed a deal memo with Mr. Arrington.