I want her.
Excuse me?
You ought to be my new secretary.
Did you accept?
No.
No, sir.
I am just not capable.
Are you the grant?
Why her?
She's just a stupid death girl.
She's the only one who didn't throw herself that Mr. Sinclair.
Thank you so much for the offer, but I can't accept the job.
Whatever.
Someone else would be glad to take it at $20,000 per month.
Well, $20,000?
That's more than I make in six months.
Yes, for sure.
I'd be honored to be Mr. Sinclair's secretary.
How the hell am I supposed to hide who I am from my boss when he's my actual boss?
Did you find her?
Miss Archer was just fired for having an affair with the guest.
Apparently it took place on the premises and it followed booking the suite to hotel.
Or guest?
I think it's user.
The room you accidentally walked into last night was booked in her name.
She was fired because of me.