Are you going on a trip?
What's he talking about?
Oh, he thought I was leaving.
Well, without a job, I can no longer pay the rent on my own, and I can't move home because
my parents are dead, so I have to find a cheaper place by tomorrow.
Listen, I appreciate you coming, but last night was a mistake.
Let's just pretend it never happened, besides it's not like someone can magically give
me my job back.
Actually, I can.
It's my hotel.
Your hotel?
Interesting Claire is the owner and new CEO.
Oh my gosh, that's so embarrassing.
I have no idea.
I'd be happy to have you real high.
I can't work with Ava.
She'll blow my cover.
Thank you, but I think I could stand the gossip going back.
I'd rather be homeless with my dick, maybe.
I just need to get back on my feet.
Well, would you like to live with me, just until you get in your job?
That ain't good.
Oscar worthy.
You need to get that.