I'm sorry, Ms. Grown, so I'm not familiar with the American term jack-off, if you could explain it to me.
Um, never mind.
Good morning, Mr. Sinclair.
I just got word from her that she's decided to move in.
What should I introduce her to all the staff has?
Friend?
He called the girl who's gonna move into his house a friend?
What a jerk.
Richmond really are something.
He slept with me and he had a girlfriend.
Mr. Sinclair needs you to help his friend move.
Asshole, of course.
Perfect chance to see what kind of woman this future duchess is.
I'll confirm with her and send you her address.
Ms. Archer, Mr. Sinclair is secretary.
We'll come to help you move.
What time is convenient for you?
His secretary?
He means Ava.
No need.
I don't have much, so I can do it.
Thanks, then I'll see you soon.
Oh my god, this is the last time I've ever done this myself.