Oh, I'm sorry.
This, his shirt is worth more than you.
Stupid idiots.
My apologies, are you burned?
We need to call it empty.
I'm fine.
It's not her fault.
Kristin, speak to my secretary that way again, before that.
She answers to me, not you.
You're clear.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Sorry about your coffee.
I'm Clifford Harrington, and you are?
Eva Grant, I apologize again about your shirt, please.
Let me get it dry cleaned.
Is there something wrong, Mr. Harrington?
No, you just remind me of someone.
Eva Grant, is it?
Yes, Mr. Harrington.
I don't mean to speak out of turn,
but when I was listening to the meeting something dawned on me.
Go ahead?
Even though JPG chains may not acquire M Hotel,
we could still be close partners.
There may be something to salvage here.
What the hell do you know about corporate partnerships?
I apologize.
She is not qualified to even be in here.
She should be a janitor.
Watch it, Kristin.
And we're willing to come back to the table,
but only to hear Ms. Grant's proposal.