Fuck, no, no, Mr. Harrington. There is nothing to discuss. We have signed a deal memo. It is too late to back out of the acquisition.
Things change.
You'll need to tell me you're willing to walk away from the hotel acquisition.
If I see a collaboration plan, I can't refuse. Yes.
In that case, we'll do our very best to provide you with a plan that satisfies you.
But we, is grand.
Of course, Mr. Harrington.
Amazing job, David.
Why did Clifford change his mind because of my secretary?
We'll see you soon.
You little bitch.
You just killed promotion.
I swear.
I'm gonna make your life a living hell.
You will be scrubbing toilets when I'm done with you.
Mr. Green, one of our shareholders, is during a party at 8 p.m. tonight.
It was unclear whether you'd go with him.
As his driver?
His guest.
His guest?