Mr. Green, allow me to introduce Ms. Ava Gromt.
Edmond, nice to meet you.
I didn't know you were bringing your girlfriend.
No, no, I'm not his.
Ms. Gromt is my secretary.
Oh, lucky for me.
Well, I know this is a work event, so I can still have a good time.
Oh, trust me, you don't want to see me drink.
Oh, no, I do.
Since we're going to be working together, I think we should get a chance to know each other.
Now, if you can now drink me, Ms. Grant,
I'll agree to work exclusively with Emo Tails.
If that best stands, then I'll do all the drinking tonight for Ms. Grant.
Now, if you'll excuse me, Ms. Grant, we would like to discuss the Oasis Project in Vegas.
Mr. Sinclair, are you okay?
Look, I know you were trying to protect me and the Brits can drink,
but if you can't handle your liquor, you should really stop.
You were at least functional last time.
You lost time.