Not if Edmond has my back.
You're calling him Edmond?
How?
Really fallen for him, haven't you?
I mean, royal title doesn't make him a good guy.
Just be careful, Ava.
He's just my boss.
That's all.
Besides, he has a girlfriend.
So...
I just got this new dress that would go perfectly with those blue earrings your mom got you for Christmas.
Could I borrow them?
You're living the high life now.
Why do you want my earrings?
And I only have one left, unfortunately.
Oh, that's fine. That's the new trend.
Please, make sure to give it back to me. It means a lot.
Yeah, of course.
Well, I've got to go.
You use that limb?
I'll take this off your hands.
It reminds me of you.
Okay.
Sure.