Is this some sort of revenge thing for firing you? I'm calling security.
No need. My boyfriend owns the place.
Boyfriend.
Yeah? I'm Edmond Sinclair's a live-in girlfriend.
I told you. I'm Edmond Sinclair's live-in girlfriend.
So what brings you here, Miss Archer?
I thought that would change the tenor of this conversation.
I heard you want to get rid of Ava Grant.
And I heard the two of your best friends.
Not anymore. She seduced Edmond last night in our living room.
I knew there was something up with her.
What can I do? Edmond will never let me fire her.
Well, he can't protect her if she keeps messing up her job.
I have a feeling that today's important meeting may be a little more dramatic than expect.