Of course. From now on, it will be in charge of the entire collaboration project.
Young lady, you have a bright future ahead of you.
I really appreciate it, Mr. Harrington.
Sir, I don't mean to speak out of turn, but I don't have much experience.
I do want me to take this on.
Because I see the potential in you.
And you remind me of my daughter.
Does she work at the company?
No, I haven't seen her in years.
I thought after my son's accident she would resurface.
I've tried to find her, but I think she stays away from me because she hates me.
I doubt that.
I think if you're meant to find each other, you will.
I hope so.
Would I be fortunate enough to invite you to dinner sometime, Miss Ava?
Of course. It would be my honor.
Stop thinking about it. I'm taking you out to eat to celebrate the deal with Clifford.
Pick anything you want.
Of course.
I'll drive so you don't change your mind.