No. No, I don't know what you mean.
I'm the Presidential Suite.
I leave work every day.
I'm not going to be renting Presidential suites.
I guess I was wrong with that.
This is the necklace I had custom made for Vic's 12th birthday.
How does Ava have it?
Find out who she really is.
I made you shots. Try one. Tell me what you like.
What's that?
Oh, the earring?
I was so out of it when you asked me about it last night.
I totally forgot what you were talking about.
Do you remember it, don't you?
I was wearing them the night we met.
I lost the other one, but I figured it symbolized our meeting,
so I thought I'd wear it anyway.
You like?
It was you.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Wait here.
Now you have no reason to doubt me.