Okay, what was so urgent that I needed to get here right away?
Povered Harrington from JPG, has invited Ava to a private dinner at his house tonight.
What? Why?
Why would a stubborn asshole who's been hell-bent on acquiring Enlottel suddenly changes attitude
for that bitch? Because what's between her legs? That's why.
I can't believe she knew that love.
Clinging on to Edmund now seducing Clifford, he's old enough to be your grand father.
As soon the whole world will know she's a whore. Kate's already falling.
I think I've fallen through someone I shouldn't.
When I was young, I fell in love with a man no one wanted me to be with.
Dad? But he was the perfect guy. He was. And he was our family's driver.
Hey, why didn't you have a driver? I never told you this.
I was born into a wealthy family. When I ran away with your father, I gave up everything.
But I never regretted it for a second. So, Ava, if you love someone, be brave.
And if you need help being brave, just look at that lock.
I'll always be with you. Don't say that. You're with me now.
Mr. Harrington? What are you doing here? Mr. Harrington? What are you doing here?
I shouldn't have kicked you off. I'm sorry we lost so much time.
What's going on? I am on each other to rely on.
You're gonna be your best. No more Mr. Harrington.
Actually true. He's meeting her mother. I've been here for a while. It's really comfortable.
That house up there is beautiful. Yeah, it is. Fountain over here.
It's still surreal how I found you two. You know Ava, I'd like you to inherit JPG.
And we should make our relationship public. I appreciate it. But I'm not ready for everyone
to know. And besides, I'm not ready to leave. I'm a hotel just yet.
You mean you're not ready to leave, Edmund. I understand. Just let me know when you're ready.
Look, two flights to Seattle. We have a visit with a pondering hotel.
Were you? You were going with me. You were going with me.
You accidentally slept with your boss twice in a month? What is wrong with you?
Whatever happened last night? Just forget about it.
You don't remember what happened last night. What was that? Give you a key.
Ava, what are you doing? After all.
If we really feel... It looks like my night just got better.
What do you say? Come on! I like to kill them. So we didn't...
We didn't know. We did the other time though.
What? I'm not sure what you're talking about. It looks like my night just got better.
It looks like my night just got better. Do you like tequila? Do you like tequila?
You weren't the mysterious woman that night.
That Mr. Sinclair. I think you had to meet him these with someone else. I think I'd remember if we...
You know. Honestly, a bit disappointed. I've been trying to ignore my feelings, but I care about you, Ava.
Why shouldn't we? You know why. I just want to be talked to you to dream beside you and to explore
your life to shield you from the sorrows of this world.
What am I supposed to do? Be your mistress? What about your girlfriend? What about your girlfriend?
She's... I'm pregnant. It's complicated. So then this isn't happening, and the only relationship
between us is a professional. Excuse me. I meant... I'll have you shirt dry cleanser.
I didn't even kiss him in the house for two days. Do you know where he is?
You should probably ask your best friend. She's traveling with him.
What the hell? They're together all the time now.
Probably sharing a hotel room this very moment.
Wernie Slett, it's none of your school room cliffer. Now you have to end in two...
Um, ma'am. That vase was acquired by Mr. Sinclair at an auction for two million dollars.
Make it so hot.
Me.
What have you done? What have you done? You lost your mind.
Oh my god, and I'm so sorry, are you okay? I... pregnancy hormones, you know. I just get so sad
when you're not home. Where have you been? On a business trip. With that little bitch.
You know, I think it's time that we talk about our future.
I think we should get married as soon as possible for the baby.
For the long day of traveling, I need some rest.
I really will. Where's my balls?
I'm afraid. I'm afraid madam knocked it over.
It wasn't intentional. I was just holding it in my basement.
Smirk all you want, dumbass maid. I'll fire you when I'm with Duchess.
The reason she became host of her annual prince is because bitch was death.
She's ruthless. Doesn't she care that he has girlfriend? No.
She even seduced him, or right in front of her.
And there's something else about her.
Something else about her.
She hooked up JPG's chairman.
No fucking way. Gross. At least I think there's a heart.
Mr. Sinclair, you wanted to see me?
Yes. It's for you.
What's this for?
Well, today's a big day. We're leaving the press conference.
So you should look upon.
Wow. This is gorgeous. I've never worn anything this beautiful.
Good. Wear it.
Nail the press conference.
I will, sir.
This just came from Mr. Harrington.
Or Eva.
Apparently, Mr. Harrington also thinks that it was too clean.
Go get ready. We saw in a now on.
Sir, why is Harrington sending your secretary gifts?
To a little strange. I don't pay you to go subject.
Photographic evidence is much more impactful.
All of the shareholders will be at the press conference this afternoon.
We will make sure Eva is destroyed.
Once this gets out, Clifford Harrington will have no choice but to distance himself
from Eva to protect his reputation, and Edmund will be done with her.
Well, in that case, there is no need for the disguise, Duchess.
Your competition is about to lose, and your position is secure.
Chloe, I'm doing here.
Eyes just here for lunch.
At our office building?
Why didn't you tell me? We could catch up.
How do you have both of my earrings?
You only let you one.
I lost the other one that night at the hotel of Edmund.
I'll take this off your hands.
I paid for your little hotel room and cleaned up your mess with your special guest.
There was a millionaire?
A trillionaire, actually.
I didn't want you to feel bad because he's everything you ever wanted.
It was you.
You're the girl who moved in with Edmund.
That's what Edmund said.
That he was still someone else for me.
You've been pretending to be me since that night.
I have to tell him.
Wait, wait, wait.
It was an accident.
I was trying to help you, and we fell for each other.
I wish I could give you everything back, but it's complicated now.
It's not just about you.
I'm done taking care of you.
I'm having this baby.
You're pregnant?
If you do, he's gonna leave me and the baby, and I can't be a single mom.
I don't know how to do that.
Chloe, you're such a fool.
This is the only thing I've ever wanted.
Please, please take care of him.
I like you always do.
Please let me have a promise I won't tell him.
I'll quit after the press conference, and I'll never see him again.
So, I'm so sorry about everything that I've done to you.
You'll always be my best friend.
Is that the same secretary?
My skirt looks absolutely incredible today.
Okay, she's wearing the dress sent by Mr. Harrington.
First off, I want to thank you all for attending our press conference.
I am thrilled to announce the strategy collaboration
between M Hotel and JPG.
As you all know, this has been a huge undertaking.
I didn't know that cow could clean up that well.
And we are glad to have finally reached an agreement with JPG
and welcome Mr. Harrington and his company into our family.
What's happening?
Is your Clifford Harrington's mistress and you've been spying on M Hotel's?
What?
How much Clifford pay you to steal?
Nothing.
Are you crazy?
This woman is trying to set me up.
She's a liar.
I'm a liar.
Why would the chairman of JPG go to such great lengths for mere secretary unless he was screwing?
Is this true?
M Hotel could not allow behavior like this.
These photos don't prove anything.
And Mr. Harrington has absolutely nothing to do with our meeting today.
Friendship.
Clifford has been paying for all of her mother's medical bills.
That's more than a friend.
Mr. Harrington and I's relationship isn't unusual.
So you finally admit it.
Miss Grant, you are fired.
We will investigate the corporate espionage
and our lawyers will be in touch.
We will do no such thing.
She is doing the only thing.
Hey look at them.
I wasn't lying.
She's a whore.
How dare you talk about my granddaughter like that.
Granddaughter?
What the fuck?
This shit just got pretty.
I wanted to respect Ava's wishes and keep her true identity private.
But I couldn't let her reputation get ruined like this.
May I introduce Ava Harrington.
My granddaughter and Eris and future president of JPG Hotel Group.
Granddaughter?
Oh my god, that's why you gave all that money to me, Mom.
I was getting the wrong information.
How dare you frame Mrs. Grant, you wicked bitch.
You blamed her for stealing a job that you wanted.
And then you set her up and you used me in the process.
I never should have listened to you.
Get out.
I never want to see your disgusting face again.
But, boss, I did exactly as you told me to.
Don't fire me.
Ava, I have always admired your talent.
This whole situation is just a big misunderstanding.
Let's find out.
I think we should.
And you should leave.
But don't we need to finish the meeting?
Yes, we'll continue.
But without you present, you're no longer the GM.
No, no, Terrace.
You're fired.
Well, let's just say, Claire, I think everything I've done has been for
in the best interest of this company.
You can't just kick me out of here.
Security.
There's one more.
Her.
I started investigating the moment I heard these outrageous rumors.
This morning, I learned that this woman and Christine
had been working together to destroy my granddaughter.
After everything I gave up for you, you do this to me?
You know me, and you lied to me like this?
You're my best friend.
I don't even recognize you anymore.
Best friend?
I was manipulated by Christine.
I really thought you and Clifford were involved.
The first time at presentation you got deleted.
It was you, wasn't it?
You had Edmund.
But that wasn't enough.
You had to ruin my career too.
You were the only one with access to my computer before the meeting.
Ava, I would never do anything to her.
You have to believe me.
No, I don't.
You lie again and again.
I don't know who you are.
I don't understand.
You didn't know each other.
She's my roommate.
You told me you lived alone.
Edmund, I didn't say anything because I didn't want to make things weird.
I think you'd like me being your secretary's best friend.
Besides, we weren't close, but we rarely know each other now.
This woman knows nothing about me.
Nothing?
Chloe, I'm done being manipulated by you.
I don't care that you have a baby.
Edmund, it was me that night.
Not her.
It was you though.
Okay, maybe it was her the first night,
but it's been me ever since.
We have a connection-
Science!
That way?
I want you to leave.
And I don't want to see it ever again.
Her child.
There is no child.
We never slept together.
Wait!
There's something I need back.
I don't want you having any.
You win.
I'm going to announce my retirement
so that I can spend more time with your mom the amount.
Will you take over JPG?
What do you say?
If you ever mistreat my granddaughter again,
I'll ruin you.
You have my word.
I won't let it down.
Ever ignore it, was you?
Excuse me, sir.
Madam, a special delivery.
It's a handwritten letter.
Is attending our wedding?
Sorry, I didn't say anything.
I send him an invitation.
Technically, he is family.
But I'm poor.
I mean...
I know I'm a duke, but first and foremost.
So, I have all the hotels.
This is the high mode suite.
Exactly.