Oh, and this? This is just the tip of the iceberg.
I have a whole collection.
I think you're all just talk.
How do we know that these aren't things?
Well, if you think they're fake,
why don't you have your uncle examine them?
These pearls are exquisite.
The texture is silky,
the translucence is divine.
These pearls are priceless.
The cut of this diamond,
is impeccable.
It's top quality, and this cream.
I've heard of it, but I've never used it.
Three years ago, the doctor I hired to treat Breanne was the only one who manufactured this facial cream.
How come she has this? Maybe she's really...
So what if it's real? Maybe it's Jamie's money.
Stannis, she didn't use my money to buy this.
And even if she did, she's my wife.
She can use my money, however she wants to.
I can't control how she spends money.
But random weird products, she's giving us gifts.
What if it kills grandma?
Grandma, how can a selfish bitch like Breanne be a good?
She's right.
Even if the diamonds and the pearls are real,
she's still just a sly, trailer trash woman.
And if you insist upon staying married,
then you must hand over your cigarette ring.
Mother, what do you mean?
Well, pre-end can't be the head of our family's wife if they don't get a divorce,
then someone else must step up to be in charge of the family.
And I wonder who you think would be worthy enough to be my wife.