Where the hell are we?
I'm sorry, I get like this every once in a while.
Plas to change to a you fucking loke.
What do you mean?
I mean, look how fucking fed you are.
You won't be alone like this.
Well, since I'm not gonna be here forever,
do you wanna fuck me right now?
You know this mysterious actor yours is
really making me a lot hornier.
For fuck's sake, I'm sorry, I have to take this.
What the fuck do you want?
Now I'm out with friends.
I told you to not.
Fuck you, I'm not losing another fucking second on your fat ass.
Now if you saw my fucking day tonight, you'd kill yourself, yeah.
Sorry, just some idiot.
What is that?
What are you some kind of freak?
I need to go now.
I'm not the fucking doors, I need to get the fuck out.
I need to get out.
I'm just going to throw some of your-
Let me go!