Did you get all the boxes I told you?
I did.
So if you're going to reach out of stuff now?
Because what the hell you scared me?
What are these? I've never seen them before.
It's none of your fucking business, Myra.
I really hate this questioning attitude.
Enough. Like I'm trying to hide something from you.
Yeah, I do feel like you're trying to hide something from me all the time.
Enough of this shit, Myra.
No, you haven't heard enough.
I still don't know why we moved to this shitty place.
I won't be stupid for taking the backseat of your stupid life.
Fuck are you seeing? Do you even hear yourself?
Why just let me go?
Myra.
Why just let go of me?
Don't make me do things I don't want to.
If you step out of that door, you know what's going to happen.
Don't come here.
I can't even go for a fucking run, can I?