Give me back my watch!
I swear I didn't see anything now yet!
I know you!
Yeah, Daddy's an alcoholic and a genuine gay environment.
Mommy's slaving away for the Boltons.
No, I'm not the debtor!
Yeah, down there.
But mommy be able to keep her job when her boss finds out her son's a fucking thief!
Stop it!
Don't hurt him!
What are you doing?
Oh, well, well, well.
You're a little thing.
Don't touch me!
You care to join us for some fun?
I'm the Boltons' daughter, but my dad will have you arrested!
Hey, I'm a princess.
Should I have some?
Don't touch me!
Mmm, she's warming up to us both.
Get up!
Whoa!
Come on!
Let's go! Get in!
I think we're safe now.
Thank you so much.
Here, you'll end a son, right?
Yeah.
Here, let me.
You have some more.
Thank you, Miss Bolton.
I hate being called mess.
Hey, how was the city?
It's all right.
Honey, I have been seeing all this stuff in the news lately about crime rising in the city
and I'm worried about your safety.
So, I brought over someone who could be your personal, well, I guess you could call them your bodyguard.
Aaron!