So, you're your lambda son.
I remember you and Charlotte shared the same birthday, isn't that right?
Yes, sir.
This has been so unsafe lately.
I don't want our precious daughter in any danger.
Mom, I'm perfectly fine on my own.
Charlotte, you're almost 21 now.
Don't make your mother and I worry about you.
I don't even know why we send you to college.
You've shown interest in nothing other than partying.
Mr. Bolton, please don't be so hard under it.
I've actually heard that Ms. Bolton is doing quite well in school.
Maybe just give her an opportunity to prove herself, sir.
Mm-hmm.
Come in.
Did you call for me, Miss?
I hate being called Miss.
Hey, thanks for what you said at dinner.
I really appreciate that.
My dad just doesn't get it.
You know, the things that are important to me, he doesn't care about.
Sorry that you had to see that.
I understand, Charlotte.
I mean, my mom talks about you all the time.
She says your father is very strict and your mother is very busy.
But you just want to be yourself.
There's nothing wrong with that.
I didn't realize Yolanda was so attentive.
She really cares about you.
Hey, why don't we just, why don't we be friends?
Call me Charlotte.
Don't call me Miss ever again.
If you do, I'll fire you.
As you wish, Charlotte.