How's she doing, doctor?
Well, it seems like Ms. Bolton's allergic to seafood.
She had anaphylactic shock.
Her airway collapsed, her blood pressure dropped.
She's in the coma.
You weren't known until she wakes up with me brain damage.
It's a very rare condition, about 2% of people,
and likely genetic, as I have to ask,
which one used allergic to seafood?
This is impossible.
None of us is allergic to seafood.
Neither one of us is allergic,
so how could your other be?
Camille, did you and she don't mean that?
Oh, stop blaming me.
I have done nothing wrong.
Hold on, Ms. Subalton, it doesn't have to be genetic.
Okay?
But if you're like, we could run a paternity test.
Yes, I would like.
Let's do a paternity test.
If she's not my daughter, Camille.
She's my daughter.
What?
Oh, she's my daughter.
I'm allergic to seafood.
No!
She got it from me.
Oh, what?
I switched the babies.
I switched my daughter for your son.
Where is she?
How is she?
She's stable, son, but it looks like
they have some news for you.
What news?
I'm not your real mom.
The Boltons are biological parents with their son.