What are you doing?
You look incredible.
Not now, Aaron.
Ever since you stood up for me all those years ago,
what is this?
Charlotte.
At the Welsh community ball, I'm going to disappoint everyone.
They're going to have to cancel the engagements.
No, no.
You belong to me, and I can only be with you.
Aaron, no.
I'm serious.
Hey, listen to me.
Charlotte.
Stop.
I don't want to marry Caroline.
It's always been you.
Stop.
I've already made the decision,
and I'm saving up money.
And as soon as you marry Caroline,
I'm taking me and my law I'm out of here.
Please don't do this, isn't Charlotte.
I've spent years bettering myself for you.
Who are you kidding?
I could never marry a hick like you.