I can never marry a hick like you.
I can never expect this from you.
You know, even if I do marry Caroline,
it won't matter.
You can't leave the Bolton family.
I make that decision now. Yes, I do.
Now, meet me in the ballroom in five minutes,
and you don't want to know what will happen if you don't.
If your dad finds out, he'll never let us go.
Any moment now.
We got intel this Bolton kid's gonna be passing through here at 9 p.m.
Remember, I'll distract him. You tase him.
Yeah? I got it.
Hey there, coders.
What are you doing?
Wanna come have some fun with us?
Hey? Where are you running off to?
That's off.
Oh!
A live one.
Just so you know, I'm a Bolton heir.
If you lay a finger on me,
that'll be the last time you see that finger.
Go on, you're a Bolton.
It's true.
You're bullshitting.
I'm the daughter of the Bolton's.