Why are you not picking up your phone?
Hey, God, you're okay.
Hey, what's going on?
We just got a call from someone who claimed that they've kidnapped a Bolton kid and demanded $10 million.
Mr. Bolton?
Where's Charlotte?
Didn't she come back with you?
No, Charlotte should be here already. She left earlier.
What?
Those guys could have kidnapped her.
Oh, my God!
Hey, we need to get her to the hospital right now.
She's so breathing.
But hurry.
Be here for five minutes.
Aaron, your lawn has been like a mom to you for years.
Same goes for me and Charlotte.
She's my little girl through and through.
And even though your dad won't say it, he feels the same way.
Hey, Mom, I know she'll be okay, but Charlotte.
Mom, hey, I promise I will protect Charlotte, okay?
I'm gonna go find her right now.
Stop!
Which one of you is heading?
It's me.
Where's my son?
Where's Aaron?
Hey!
Oh, she dies.
She?
Charlotte, I thought it was Aaron.
Dad, you have to help me.
Charlotte, what are you?
Buddy, is this your fake daughter?
I heard that she's close to Aaron.
And frankly, I don't want anything to potentially hurt my daughter's marriage.
Yeah, hate him.
Charlotte, I raised her as a little kid.
Dad, please.
I can't.
I have to save her.
You play hero and try to save her.
The wedding is off.
And you know me, I don't let things goes enough.
Bolton's family will be toast.
For what?
A girl who's not even really your kid?
It's your call.
Dad, please.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
Dad, please.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Dad.
Sorry.
Hey!
Get back here!
Get back!