I'm supposed to marry Erin.
I know you don't even want to marry him.
Think about how he's treated you all these years.
Give me the ring.
And you can take Yolanda whatever you...
Yolanda?
No. I've made up my mind.
Yes, the sooner the better.
We're pushing the reception back by an epinar.
I'm getting you that dress.
Oh my God, what are you doing?
Let's go.
Charlotte, you were truly amazing.
I'm not stupid, Caroline.
Erin is mine.
You can go take your seat.
Hey everyone, before we begin, thank you for gathering here.
We're not only here to celebrate the wedding of my long lost daughter,
I have a very important announcement to make.
I have decided to leave the majority of the Welch family fortune
to my eldest daughter, Charlotte.
Dot this right now.