Stop this right now, Mom.
Samantha, what are you doing?
Aiden, I am still your wife.
Don't I have the right to be here?
And besides, Erin is supposed to be marrying my daughter.
That's not your decision to make.
Listen, it's not your wedding to crash.
Carolina's still young.
And she will have other opportunities to find a man.
You little slut.
You're just like your mom, that snake, Yolanda.
She wrecked my marriage, and now you
have the nerve to do the same to Caroline.
Samantha, you sabotaged my relationship with Aiden.
You almost ruined our lives.
But no.
Enough.
Aiden, the Welch family owes its prominence to my family.
And now you just decide to abandon me and Caroline
for her little slut.
Samantha, this has nothing to do with Yolanda or Charlotte.
Just tell me what you want.
Name your price, OK?
Just do not mess up Charlotte and Erin's special day,
any more than you already have.
All right, then.
I want you to turn over the Welch family fortune
to Caroline.
Absolutely not.