Caroline is not fit to inherit the welter state.
And this illegitimate girl who is once Aaron Servant is?
Enough's amount of it.
Caroline is also your daughter, and she deserves the Welch family estate.
Why don't we settle this fair and square?
We'll each control the Welch family business for a month, and whoever does a better job, get the inheritance.
Alright, a fair competition it is.
We'll do what you say.
Now, let the ceremony continue.
It looks like another storm is coming.
When will I finally be able to escape this cage?
Don't be afraid, Troy. I will always get here.
What's wrong?
Yeah, I think I had too much to drink.
Here, I'll get you a towel.
What's going on? I've been taking birth control pills.
Could it be you?