I'm her lover.
Oh, wow.
I underestimated you.
Answer, put it on speakerphone.
Don't tell her anything.
She's, uh, she's Clueless.
She'll be over very soon.
Good job, baby.
So, yeah.
Where are you meeting her?
Um, room T-2-5.
It's in Emperor Hotel.
You just betrayed her.
How do I know you won't betray me?
I don't know.
Sharp, you don't understand.
She threatened me with my sister's medical bills.
Okay, I'd never have done anything that would hurt the company by you.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Um, listen.
If you're loyal to me, I'll help you.
And your sister.
Just go about your plan.
And don't tell Samantha anything.
Oh my gosh, Sharp.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I swear to you, from now on,
I'm loyal only to you.
Caroline, what are you doing?