Caroline, what are you doing in here?
Erin.
No.
Don't tell me you don't like it.
Get out.
Sure.
What's going on here?
Don't let me interrupt.
No, listen, this is not what it looks like.
Shh.
I'm not mad.
Charlotte, you're so generous.
Ben, I guess I'll continue.
I've been.
Why not all three of us?
Really?
It's the three of us?
Sure.
Why not?
But you should know.
Erin has some fetishes.
What fetishes?
Well, Caroline, I grew up in the countryside.
We used to do it in the farm.
We'd be rolling around in the hay and listening to all the animals.
Mm-hmm.
Especially the cows.
The cows?
Yeah.
How's knowing?
It really turns me on.
Like this?
Moo.
Is this how?
Kind of.
Maybe a little bit more.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Keep going.
Just like that.
Mm-hmm.
Just go to the St. Emperor hotel.
What?
Mm.
She's planning something.
I have to stop her.
Coming with you.