Come in.
Here are the documents you requested.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Hey, you mentioned that your sister is coming home from the countryside for medical treatment.
How's she doing?
Well, you know, she was supposed to be going home, but her horse acting up.
You know, she needs round-of-clock care.
I'm stuck at work, so I'll place it a little bit far.
She's crashing out of the hotel in the office.
You see, wouldn't it be okay if I dropped off some stuff to her?
I just got a couple things figured, you know, brighten her moon.
Really?
I mean, that'd be wonderful.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
Hey.
I won't be home for dinner tonight.
Who are you having dinner with?
Colleagues.
Do I know them?
Male or female?
Why so many questions?
Just a loving husband concerned about his wife.
I'll see you later tonight.
Charlotte is having dinner with some Colleagues.
Why don't you keep an eye on her?
And with Adrian?
It could be.
Oh, Charlotte, you are so naive.
I've reclaimed what's rightfully mine.