I'm sorry to disappoint you Madam, but this really is all just a coincidence.
I was concerned about Charlotte's safety, so I had her followed by security.
It turns out it was Adrienne and his sister Lisa staying at the hotel.
Charlotte was only there for a few minutes.
You had me followed?
I just had to be sure.
Honestly Samantha, if Adrienne had only lasted five minutes, you wouldn't still be his lover.
Now would you?
You're the one manipulating everyone and you have the nerve to pin it on Charlotte?
We don't need your drama.
Get lost.
Just you wait and see Charlotte.
I'm sorry I didn't trust him.
I love him.
If Aaron doesn't trust me, can I trust him to be our baby's father?