I know that's where everything is right now. There's still a lot of the ropes that I need to learn about the business
Yeah, I'm trying about the same result. It's just why I mean I like that
We're gonna expand that portfolio
What's wrong with her? Are you too? Okay?
And we're fine. Mom
If I were likely to say anything about that, that's good. Sorry
Charlotte Charlotte are you pregnant?
Of course she is and Aaron do you want kids?
I think maybe
Someday, but now isn't the right time
Right. Yeah
No, I'm not pregnant. I just went to the doctor and they prescribed me some new medication
And I'm just feeling a little nauseous. That's fine then. You better go rest
Thanks
Aaron, why don't you just say it's not the right time to have children?
Because it isn't and Charlotte has to focus on getting the welcome here since
Kids want to help that