I'd like it if you just signed the contract.
Okay, I'll sign.
Great.
If you kiss me.
What are you doing?
Stop pretending.
Stop it!
I gotta go.
What's up?
What's going on here?
You touching my assistant?
Robert, no.
Come on.
She came on to me.
I tried to stop her.
Bullshit!
He tried to kiss me.
Is that true?
Robert.
Deals off.
If you go in here again, you're dead.
You understand me?
I'm fine.
See you tomorrow at the office.
Lady, I'm sharp.
Don't be late.
Rosie, what's going on?
What?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, my dear.
Mmm.
I'm so glad you came.
Of course.
Tell me what's going on.
I'm losing weight fast and the doctors don't know why.
So I read on the internet that it's a symptom of cancer.
Cancer?
What can I do?
Oh, tell me what I can do anything.
Before I die, I have one request.
Meet my son.
Oh, you rest.
Thank you, my dear.
All right, I'll be back soon.
Mom, you sit on the phone.
You were sick.
Why are you drinking?
I didn't hear you come in, dear.
The doctor said one glass of white wine can actually easily discomfort.
Okay, so what happened?
I just feel so bad.
You haven't met your wife yet.
Well, I'm busy.
I told you that.
Please do it for me.
I promised your father that we would take care of his daughter.
The family got the money, right?
Do they want more?
Is that what this is about?
We can give them more.
Money is just a cold, hard number, Robert.
Yeah, you give her the warmth of family.
Just meet her at the Boulevard Hotel tonight.
And if you don't like her, you can divorce her.
Deal?
69.
Be kidding me.
It's done.
Fucking relief.
Hello, dear.
Um, he's about here.
I'm so sorry, my dear.
I really, really thought.
It's okay.
Just, uh, just wasn't meant to be.
So he didn't show up.
Again.
Men, you see this is why I don't date.
Okay, how long until your father's debts are paid off?
Oh, I don't know.
Rosie handles all that stuff.
Okay.
I know I've said this before, but I think it's strange that she set you up with her son,
who you've never met.
And she's also handling these debts, which you've also never seen in their full detail.
You know she's like a mother to me, okay?
I trust her with my life.
I know.
He better be rich and tall, okay?
If so, you better find out if he swings both ways.
Oh.
He is so angry today.
I think he found his wife cheating on him last night.
Wait, but he's married?
Look at these nails.
Do you see them?
He said that these are not workplace blue.
What kind of common is that?
Blue?
What is wrong with him?
Do I pay you two to chitchat?
No, sir.
We were just talking about paper work.
Yes.
Very angry.
Now, I love my job.
I love my job.
Hi, Sophie.
This is Kevin Todd, your husband's divorce attorney.
Divorce lawyer.
Why does he want a divorce?
Why don't we talk when we meet?
How's Pine Tree Cafe 4pm?
Okay, yeah, yeah.
I'll be there.
Sophie.
I guess we should get right into it.
Sure.
Hear the divorce papers?
Read them carefully and we can discuss.
See, out of his mind, he wants me to pay 30 million in moral damages?
Keep reading.
On the grounds of deception, I've never even seen him.
He should pay me for walking out of the wedding.
Hey, inside voices, let's keep it polite.
I'll talk to him and have him take that part out, but how soon can you agree to the divorce?
In an instant.
Okay.
I'll let him know.
Hey, she won't agree to the moral damages, but she will agree to the divorce immediately.
Okay?
He agrees.
Sophie, where the hell are you?
I need you here.
I can't find Nick anywhere.
Hurry up.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm coming back right now.
Look, I really have to go, but I will talk to you soon.
We have an issue.
Sir, you were looking for me?
Yeah, I need my lunch.
Looks like Nick went to the fucking nail salon.
I'll go get that right now.
Sophie.
Hi.
I never congratulated you on your new position.
Welcome to the family.
Thanks.
I'm happy to be here.
I'm just going to get Robert's lunch.
Oh, actually, it's just one.
He gets the same thing every day.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm going to go play this then.
Oh, yeah.
Have a nice day.
Hey, YouTube.
Here's your lunch, Mr. Kensington.
Sorry.
Would you like a water soda or something?
This tastes different.
This isn't Popeyes, is it?
Oh, no.
It's day of sale.
Hmm.
What?
Is everything okay?
Mr. Kensington?
Mr. Kensington.
Hey, somebody help.
Mr. Kensington, wake up.
Good news is we pumped his stomach just in time and got it all out of his system.
He's going to be okay.
Do we know what happened?
He just passed out.
Well, Robert has a very severe peanut allergy.
Oh.
I didn't know that he didn't tell me.
I've been his doctor for years, so he must not have known what was in his food or what
he was eating because he would have never eaten it.
But he has the same thing for lunch every day, so I don't know how possible.
I need to have an investigation.
Hey, sleepyhead.
Mr. President, you're awake.
When can he be discharged?
I need at least 24 to 48 hours, Robert.
Doc, you know me, I'm fine.
Uh-uh.
You heard her.
I don't strain yourself.
I have to take this, but I'll be right back.
Hey, Kevin, what's up?
Sophie, when can you come sign these papers?
You're rushed out of the cafe.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I will.
I just need 48 hours.
I'm dealing with an emergency.
48 hours?
She wants 48 hours.
Yeah.
Okay.
Fine.
48 hours?
No more.
Who are you talking to?
My friend.
What kind of trouble?
Maybe I can help.
His mom forced him to marry someone.
An arranged marriage.
Totally get it.
Totally understand his pain.
It's terrible.
You do?
Yeah.
Complicated, but I do.
My friend thinks the same thing.
So what's he going to do about it?
He wants a divorce.
They were going to make a deal, but got her cheating.
What's her side of the story?
Like on her cheating.
Who cares?
So it is you.
Well, to be fair, Nick told me, but...
Of course.
Only tell Nick when you want the whole world to know.
Oh.
We love him for it.
But I completely understand.
Really?
Yeah.
My friend is also in an arranged marriage.
Except they've never even met because he didn't shop to the wedding.
Wow.
That guy is a worthless piece of shit.
Your friend should be able to divorce him piece.
Thank you for listening.
No, thank you.
It actually helped to talk about him.
Let me get you some water.
Sophie, why don't you stay with me until I'm discharged?
I'll pay you three times your hourly rate.
Absolutely not.
Why?
Do you not want to be around me?
Oh, no, no.
It's not that.
I'm objecting to the rays in my rate.
I'm just here doing my job.
I do have a favorite asking you.
Anything for you, sir?
Yes.
Right there.
Oh, yeah.
I feel so good.
Oh, my God.
Should we close the door so that nobody sees?
It's okay.
It's just lotion.
Yeah, the allergic reaction gave him a rash.
That you decided to scratch.
Why?
What happened?
Nothing.
I wanted to make sure that you were okay.
And, sir?
Okay.
He is so weird.
One more signature and you are divorced.
He wasn't happy that you needed this extra time.
Well, I'm not his toy.
He should have been a man and come to deal with it himself.
Okay.
I'll pass this along to him and get his signatures.
It'll be official.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I told you to separate them.
Not kill him.
I didn't know he'd be that allergic.
Do you realize this brought them closer together?
You.
Idiot.
Rosie, are you home?
Yes, dear.
Come on in.
Hey.
It's just you.
I thought I heard voices.
Must be the cat outside.
Always screaming.
I can't stay long.
But I wanted to let you know that I signed the divorce papers.
Oh.
I'm so sorry, my dear.
It's okay.
Once your son signs them, it's over.
I just promised me our relationship won't change.
Of course not, dear.
Come here.
Give me a hug.
I have to go, but I love you.
I love you too.
What the fuck do you say?
Can I believe my ears?
Ugh.
That was some quick handiwork.
All you need to do now is get her fired.
Nick, who do you think is the best person to take over the Dragon Group deal?
Uh, well, Marcus and Hannah did a very good job on the presentation.
I prefer Sophie.
Of course you do.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
You wanted to see me?
Sophie, are you familiar with the Dragon Group deal?
Yeah.
I was told that it's potentially the biggest deal of the year.
That's right.
And I want you to take it over.
Me?
Oh.
Thank you.
Thank you for trusting me with it.
No.
Thank you.
Hello.
Do you need anything else?
I'm sure you'll do a great job.
Sophie.
What do you want, Hannah?
Dragon Group deal, huh?
You really did get into his pants.
Oh, please.
I earned it through my work.
Yeah.
Through your work, we'll see how good you really are.
You're here.
You're bold to come here.
I'm surprised they haven't fired you yet.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You didn't notice the three extra zeros in the Dragon Group contract?
Who do you group lost $10 billion because of it?
No.
No, I reviewed that contract over and over.
Where is it?
Well, I heard what you did with the Dragon Group.
Ooh.
Ouch.
I didn't do anything.
Okay?
It's a big misunderstanding.
I'm going to figure it out.
Oh, you didn't do anything except cost this company billions?
What exactly do you have against me?
What have I ever done to you?
I just don't think unqualified people should be promoted.
Especially not whores who sleep with the boss.
I beg your pardon?
How dare you?
Sophie.
Sophie, Sophie, Sophie.
Now, to this day, I still don't understand why my cousin hired you for this position.
But as the vice president, I am going to have to fire you.
Well, that's interesting.
Because as the vice president, you have no authority to fire people.
Only the president does.
And that's me.
Now, everyone can stop gossiping and get back to work.
Robert, I think you're looking at this the wrong way.
These losses are making us suffer greatly, and it's all her fault.
Mr. Kensington, I have nothing to do with this.
And being framed, I know it.
You were the last one to see the contracts.
How would you know that?
Well, Sophie, I will be taking this very seriously.
But I won't need answers by tomorrow.
I really didn't do this.
I believe you.
But I operate off evidence.
Not words.
Go!
I'd like to request the security footage from the office, husband.
What?
What do you mean by erased?
Couldn't that be?
I don't think we've been officially introduced.
My name is Nick Foster, the president's secretary.
Tara.
I have just been told that some of the surveillance footage from last night has gone missing.
That's true.
Well, who else has access to the footage?
Just me.
So no one else could have erased it.
I'm going to need you to tell me exactly what happened.
It was Hannah.
Well, that was easier than I expected.
She made you delete it?
Well, you can't necessarily delete it.
She has the footage.
Oh, really?
I'm sorry.
She was really aggressive, and you're not going to fire me, are you?
It's okay.
She's a bitch.
Let me take care of it.
Tara, what can you do for me?
Your time, baby?
You did great.
He has no reason not to hire you for the position.
Well, let's save our celebration for after she gets fired.
Wait a minute.
Why do you always have to tease me like that?
Huh?
Sorry to interrupt.
Hannah, is there something that you'd like to tell us?
Um, no.
Nothing about what happened last night?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You set me up.
Set you up?
I couldn't even pretend to be as dumb as you are.
Can't fuck your way out of this one, Sophie.
You?
You're just really jealous of me.
What's your obsession with my relationship with the president, huh?
Do you have a crush on?
What?
Do you?
No.
Just hand over the video.
You can't make me.
Uh-huh.
Bust it.
And now we take you to the president.
Whoa.