I grew up in a foster home, just outside the city, and then this woman who I now realizes
your mom took me in when I was 12.
She raised me, and the last year she told me that my father actually owes her a lot of
money.
And the only way to pay his debts was to marry her son, who I had never even seen.
I guess that's because you're in Italy at the time, like you said.
Yeah, I mean, I knew she had taken some money, but obviously I didn't know that was you.
That's so weird, though.
She would keep us apart our whole lives and then wanted us to get married.
Yeah, that is strange.
What about your father?
I never knew.
He was obviously the one who gave me the Fuji group, and I had the condition that I had
to be married to receive the $100 billion inheritance.
He'd never shut up.