If Adam really is Emma and Owen's child, then Emma must have been with Owen the six years
she was missing.
Why did she agree to marry Dan when she came back?
I was so confusing.
Look at how Owen misses Emma.
There must have been feeling, feeling much and well, I was really handsome.
He's Emma's man, my brother-in-law.
I can't like him.
Why does he keep appearing in my dreams?
When I was sorry, Srinny, I was lost in my thought.
How on her bite?
I'm sure I don't want to eat.
What's up, dad?
Can't you eat sweet tea tree?
Of course you can.
Can we have some juice?
Stop asking so much.
Did I say something wrong?
Well, definitely not.
Wait for me, sweetie.
I'll get you some juice.
I feel like I've been here before.
Remember.
So you're the bitch, Owen Bortbeck.
Watch me how I handle you.