My birthday is this weekend.
What do you want for your birthday?
The cake from the cafe last time was so delicious.
You can have more of that cake.
I'll go buy some later.
Let's go now.
You can go together by a big one.
Big cake tastes the best.
What am I going to do with you?
Sir, you're a special guest.
When should I order the cakes for you?
Give me a pen.
Russell Menard?
Well, my last name is Russell.
Sir, you are a special guest.
Please take this cake as a gift.
Eric, is it really you?
Your father just came to beg me to marry you.
And here you are, hooking up with another man.
You really ought to be ashamed of yourself.
Damn, what are you doing here?
You pretend to be so naive and innocent with me.
But now, you're so good at producing that.
You and your sister, one is infertile
and the one who gave birth to the kid is begging to marry me.
You two are fucking sluts.
That's this big one.
Shut up!