Why didn't you tell me you were Emma?
Because you heartlessly abandoned me!
I never abandoned you! I look for you!
And you disappear!
I lost my memory for six years!
How? What happened? Tell me.
You know what? I'm worse off now than I was before.
I'm not good enough for you. So just let me know.
No. Erica, I will never let you go.
Sorry. Emma, Erica, why didn't you tell me who you really are?
I was right in front of you and you didn't recognize me!
I'm sorry. What exactly happened? Where were you taking?
Isn't that a question I should be asking you?
That day you went for a checkup.
My family told me that they found suitable corneas and had to operate immediately.
I asked Freya to tell Reed to look after you and I promise them that I will be back right after the surgery.
You asked Reed to look after me? You trusted Reed?