You trusted Reed?
Yeah, he's been like a father to me since I was a boy.
Okay, instead of letting him take care of me, why didn't you take me with you?
You were in such a hurry, you didn't have one second to wait for me!
There was no time to book the jet and the only available flight was 20 minutes later.
I rushed back as soon as I could to be with you, I swear to God.
Because of that, my recovery was difficult and now I get headaches every time I stay up late.
Reed has been taking care of me.
Reed, give me a breakup letter that said you didn't want me anymore.
He locked me in a basement.
He bit and abused me.
He fed me medications and wanted to abort our child.
What better?
How was that possible?
And he's daughter Freya.
He's been accusing me over and over again.
The necklace, now the kidnapping.
These people are a family to you.
I'm just some girl who bore your child after you dancing fancy!
Get out!
That's not true, listen to me.
Stop talking.
I'm the only one who understands the abuse I've suffered.
If you don't believe me, go do some digging.
Otherwise, I'm taking Adam away from this dangerous place.