So this is the surveillance footage from that night.
But neither are we not afraid of how enough time to come into crime.
Wait a minute.
See that?
It's been tampered with.
I'll get right on it.
What happened to that information that asked you to get about Emma Wood?
Oh, uh, why haven't I read anything back?
It's submitted information two weeks ago or so, but
Ms. Freya took it.
But the diamond, well, she told me she would personally hand it to you.
Idiot.
Who do you work for?
Why would you give it to someone else?
It's just Ms. Freya who's a childhood friend, and to be honest,
everyone in the mantra thought she would be the next musus.
Tell everyone that my only wife is Erica.
And if anyone else thinks differently,
I'll throw them in the Pacific and feed them to the sharks.
Got it?
Yes, boss.
No wonder Erica misunderstood my relationship with Freya.
I need to drop clear line with Freya as soon as possible to reassure Erica.
Down's involvement in Emma's death would be related.
This is what Erica was most worried about.
If I can find out the truth,
I should be a lot happier.
Get to the bottom of this.
Especially what Erica said about being abused and imprisoned six years ago,
I need to know the truth, the whole truth, all right?
And stay away from Freya and her father.
And if you mess up again, I know I throw myself into the Pacific.
If I do, just get out of here.
You will not be harmed anymore, Erica.
But now I need to figure out how to win her back.