What? You call me out just to let me watch you drink tea?
I just wanted to give you another chance to work for me.
Why? Because you couldn't handle them by yourself.
And how far have you got with your planning?
I bet you haven't even stepped foot inside their door, have you?
What is in it for me if I work with you?
No, direct benefits. But I can help mitigate some of the losses.
I would have thought that a man like you on the surface...
A wealthy young man from an upper-class family
would be involved in such scandalous affairs.
Living together and taking lewd photographs.
Mine, mine, mine.
What do you want?
Well, that depends if you're willing to work for me.
Otherwise, I'm not sure where these photographs will end up.
Go to hell.
I've prepared a surprise for you.
The next time you meet, you'll be begging me to help.