Court him down, you bastard!
Let go of my son!
Your son, he does not even recognize you.
You're pathetic, covered.
Dad, you're hurting me.
Let me go.
Shut up.
Have you forgot how I thought you?
No crying.
No talk back.
He's an innocent child.
If you want, come at me, but let him go.
Alright, that's enough.
Listen, I'll give you whatever you want.
Just put him down.
Let him go.
What I want?
You took away my woman, my child.
They belong to me.
You even had the boss to hit me in the car for less time.
I want you to kneel before me.
What are you crazy?
Do you understand what you're talking to?
Aren't you afraid to get hit by a car when you get outside?
Down on your knees.
Three, two...