Is that your fake sympathy?
I hate that. Stop it. Spit it out. Why are you here?
I've got good news for you.
Your days of suffering are over.
Dan's father, Henry Morrison, the head of the Morrison family,
sent someone to tell us that Dan is willing to marry you.
You and I just have to go back and we'll get back to our bougie lifestyle.
So celebrate your little victory.
It's not about me going back to some bougie lifestyle.
It's about you getting as much money as you want.
Look, I raised you to marry a wealthy and powerful man
to help support the family, right?
Now this is what you should do.
You should be grateful that I'm helping you marry into such a noble family.
chosen gratitude.
Sweetheart, I need to talk to Grandpa about something.
Why don't you go to the study and find your dad?
Is that your kid with a new boyfriend?
Well, he got big.
Does this house belong to him too?
If it truly does, then you need to get busy.
Anybody who can afford land here is either wealthy or powerful.
Maybe even more powerful than the Morrison's.
But you need to decide.
Him or Dan, or maybe you could serve them both.
I don't care.
Either way, our family will truly prosper.
Enough, Bert Wood.
You are disgusting.
Listen to yourself.
Are your daughters some goods for you to trade?
If that's the case, I don't have a father.
You, Bert.
How dare you speak to me like that?
Time to teach you a lesson.