I know you are the heir and ruler of the largest
conglomerate in North America.
I'm just a girl from an ordinary family.
Listen, Erica, look at me.
To me, you're the most exceptional and beautiful woman I know.
And that's all that matters to me.
You know what?
Even if you were a beggar, I would still love you.
Say that again?
Say what?
I love you.
Come here.
Why is this a DNA report?
After our laboratories repeated tests,
the first genetic test was found to have been tampered with.
On the second test, the genetic match between Adam's sample
and Owen's is 0.1%,
indicating no blood relation between the two.
Beautiful weather today.
Perfect for doing something meaningful.
Really?
I'm going to play a new game?
Maybe later.
Would you like to know how your sister died?
I think today we're going to finally find out what really happened.
What do you mean?
I want you to bear witness to this.
Son, would you like to watch your daddy punch some bad guys?
Oh, dare you treat me like this.
I'm going to get my attorneys, and I'm going to sue every one of you.
Let me go!
Relax.
You're just here to enjoy the show.
But if you keep yelling, I'm going to have him tape your mouth shut.
You play your trick to sell your daughter to a family.
You'd be so lucky.
Who are you?
We'll get to that.
In the meantime, I want to introduce you to someone.
Say to me.
So sorry.
I don't dare you.
I hurt my son.
I'm in prison.
How dare you?
I assure you there's nothing illegal going on here.
See for yourself, not a scratch.
The tithes are turning.
Your family's going down.
You're a man.
Go to arrogance.
I advise you to apologize now.
I'm not proof of my family.
Or I make sure you can't survive in this city.
I will you.
The last person who said that is in the grave.
Yeah.
The company's stopped.
The price has hit the limit down.
The family's going bankrupt.
What, baby?
Seems like you got the short straw.
What have you done?
Just having a little fun.
It's impossible.
You couldn't have done this all by yourself.
It has to be a trick.
Sir.
This is our family crest.
It represents everything we stand for.
Truth and honor.
Russell family.
Remember Russell family.
Oh my God.
Oh and Russell.
Just with the heir and the current leader of Russell family.
Are you still going to force Erika to marry your worthless son?
Miss Owen.
No, it's all fault.
It's all fault.
We shouldn't have your sweet Miss Erika.
I'll do anything you ask.
Just please spare us.
Anything?
Anything.
Get down on your knees.
And beg my forgiveness.
And I'll consider pardoning your family.
Miss Owen.
Please spare us.
Spare our family.
Do you really think I was being serious?
Get up.
You tricked us, huh?
What?
You tricked us?
Fuck.
Do you think a simple apology is going to make up for everything that you did?
Your time's over.
Now you're going to pay.
Dad!
Dad, more reason you're under arrest on the suspicion of murdering Emma Uud.
Father!
Please help me!
Did you really think you'd get away with it?
Emma was always one step out of you.
Justice will prevail in the end.
Owen, what's going on?
I think it's time that you know the whole truth about what happened.
Erika, my sister.
Perhaps by now I'm no longer in this world, but I still want to apologize to you sincerely.
I'm sorry.
It was my selfishness to be with Dan that led me to see your boy Adam.
I never expected you to call your break down a memory loss.
I also never expected that that once, Dan found out Adam wasn't his biological son.
He would immediately start abusing us and even send people to kill us.
So, I love this message in advance.
If you're reading this letter, then he has killed me at this point.
I'm sorry I can't apologize to you in person.
I tried to take back your status for you.
So, when I found out Owen was looking for you everywhere, I sent him information about Adam
and secretly arranged for Adam to meet you.
I once loved the wrong person.
But I hope you can't reunite with your family.
I sincerely wish you happiness.
Be happy for me.
You're a responsible sister, Emma.
Love you always.
Atlas, I've sacrificed everything for you.
How could you?
Your sister are liars, liars.
And let me tell you one thing.
Do you think this is the truth?
Even if you think that Adam isn't my child, are you sure that he's yours?
Prison is a place that's going to chew you up and spit you out.
If I were you, I'd use your remaining assets instead of a good funeral plan for him.
Thank you, sir, also.
I'm not invited to know the family.
Adam is our child.
Who could be behind this fake DNA report?
If I recall, you previously were...
No, no, no, no.
I will comply with all of your arrangements.
All right.
Given the recent happenings and your age, you're no longer capable of being in charge of wood family.
And that title should rightfully pass to Erica.
Here's the contract for your transfer.
Just on here, and you can quickly step into your retirement.
That's great.
Mr. Russell is very considerate.
But I will not take any more of your precious time.
Mr. Russell has prepared a nursing home for you, and we will leave immediately.
Fucking Erica.
Leave Dan.
Bert and Harry couldn't deal with you.
Time to unleash my beast.
Now that I've got you here, why don't we clear up all the misunderstandings once and for all?
Okay, you go.
I'm listening.
First, that day by the pier, I'm sorry I didn't listen to you.
I recovered the footage, and yes, you were taken.
Let's leave that in the past.
I did think about leaving then.
What?
What is the second thing?
The second thing is when you were taken back then.
I want to know everything that happened.
First hand.
Reed locked me in the basement, gave me abortion pills.
He also told me that, that whole thing was orchestrated by you.
Because you were afraid that me and my child would leave a stain on your family.
Nonsense!
Reed told me that you were taken away by the family.
And that he tried to intervene, but he was injured in the process.
I've known him since I was a boy.
Maybe he had his reasons.
I mean, he did let me go at the end.
Why don't you have a talk with him?
Leave no regrets.
Dan and Bert were brought in by Freya, probably to so discord between us.
She even switched to Adam's DNA report.
Didn't many other crazy things.
Yeah, she's just crazy.
If he provokes me again, I will beat her up.
Tomorrow I have some things to take care of at the south matter.
It may take a day or two.
In the meantime, stay away from her.
Be careful.
When I get back, we'll deal with them together.
Good.
So now, we'll let it weave.
Clear it up.
All the misunderstandings.
How about we do something productive?
What?
Hmm.
My poor daughter.
It's time to back up for everything, so that we can live on.
I will plead with Owen.
I believe in his character.
Three generations of our families serve them.
So I'm sure you will show us mercy.
Look at you.
There's no turning back.
Ever since we hurt, there's no turning back.
Do you really think that a man like Owen would actually forgive somebody for hurting his child?
Don't be afraid, Dan.
Trust me.
I will make Owen fall in love with me.
I'll make him see that I am the right partner for him.
As long as that bitch in that bastard is dead.
You will take him out.
Tomorrow as planned.
Leave the rest to me.
I'm going to deal with it personally.
Adam, sweetie.
Stop playing.
Time to go to bed.
You, my roses.
Even when they're crushed, they can still hurt people.
Dad, you're done.
I'm sure that he already knows everything.
I'm sure that he probably wants to kill me.
But right now, my father has been completely distracted.
And you, I'm going to thoroughly enjoy torturing you.
I failed six years ago to kill you in this bastard.
I won't hesitate anymore.
And I will not allow you to come between me and Owen's marriage.
You are insane.
Nonsense.
If you want to save your son, get on your knees and crawl through the roses.
Do it.
Now, I'm going to whip him high.
No.
Then get on your knees.
Crawl through the roses.
Now, I will do what you say.
Just don't hurt him.
Mm-hmm.
Get over here now.
That's okay.
Mom will risk you.
Don't risk her.
Stupid bitch.
You are nothing but a low-life bitch from a shit hole.
How dare you look at me like that.
Look at you.
You're kneeling on the floor.
So act like a maggot that you are.
Stop looking at me like some tough dog.
I'm a dog.
Look at yourself.
You are drowning in your jealousy because of your insecurities.
Do you have a few words of anyone's love?
Mine and Owen's love has nothing to do with status or background or our families.
We just love each other.
And you are committing unforgivable things for a man who never showed you a sex.
I'm going to destroy my entire family and since I can't get rid of it again,
I'm going to take away the person who loves the most, which is you.
Of wrong things, I will take all the blame.
You'll take all the blame?
She hurt the ones I love the most.
She's going to pay.
And you.
I know what you did.
I know whoever I trusted you more than anyone.
Sorry, sir.
I know I betrayed your trust.
I'll fray-eye as my only daughter.
She got totally obsessed by you.
Her love for you, I've driven her mad.
It's my fault.
As her father will not stop being her.
Even for helping her.
Is Erica.
I'm sorry for all the harm.
I will.
All the darkness.
I promise.
But please.
Please.
Spare.
Free us life.
I'm sorry for you.
Fail.
To protect you forever.
Or give me for not fulfilling your wish.
If there's another chance I would do better.
I love you, Freya.
Oh, well.
You always treated me like family.
I owe you a lot.
If there's another life.
Letting Freya go, truly gone mad.
Sending her to the mental hospital was the best option.
She meant that I can see that you're upset.
Harry's gone to prison.
Dan's verdict's out.
Evidence is sentence to death.
We're in a nursing home and finally have you back here with me.
We could finally start a new life together.
An angel sent from heaven.
I'm sorry I didn't keep my promise.
I shouldn't have left you alone.
You needed me most.
Well, let's start making up for a very present.
That's not sweet.
What's wrong with you?
I think this bed is too small.
I want to hear the violin.
What are you doing?
Are you flying?
I'm in that ER.
Dad was exercising.
Really hot in there.
Exerciding in the bathroom?
I'm enjoying.
Get down on the floor and give me 20%.
I don't want to find this here.
I'm actually taken from all.
Hmm.
He's always like that.
He's having his shoes.
I don't blame him.
But more siblings to play with.
You're paying.
Yes, yes.
The best accommodations, the best teachers.
An absolutely no room for error.
Problems?
Of course.
Starting next week, Adam will attend.
The best ways of crowding summer can't be in the world.
For a whole month.
The boss' mind is becoming harder and harder to read.
I really need a vacation.
What do I have to go through some accounts?
Well, because Adam, it's time that you brought me a real man.
You can protect your mom.
Because you're too energetic, taking up too much of your mom's time.
Then what do I have to go for a whole month?
Well, there's a lot to learn.
And that's what you're going to grow up a lot faster.
Don't worry.
We'll come up with you up soon.
Okay.
Because your presence is preventing them from having another child.
Uncle Ben, Dad said true.
Oh no.
There goes my month-long vacation.
I told you don't have to do anything.
Let me take care of you.
That's it.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
Would you like a donut?
Oh my God.
Is that like I can do anything anymore?
Well, I'm just trying to make up for all those last years of being a good dad.
Taste it.
Would you like it?
Yeah.
Hey, Emma.
Sorry we couldn't have eaten to you for so long.
Dan got what he deserved.
Sometimes I wonder if you can see us from up there.
Guess what?
We're going to have another baby.
Doctor says it's a girl.
I want to name her after you.
Is that okay?
When the time comes, I'll bring her to see you.
Emma's a beautiful man.
Our daughter will love it too.
You're still like me when I'm a sister.
I'll be a good big brother.
Of course!
No matter how many children we have,
Daddy's always going to have time to play soccer with you.
Goodbye, Emma.
Just like you hoped.
I found my happiness.