I'm sorry, are we out?
Oh, I'm Allison Miller. I am a handmade jewelry designer.
So you sell my hat online for contract marriage?
Oh, is that for me?
Me, thanks.
I like mine with a bit more sugar.
I'm Robert Johnson's.
Yeah, I know your name, Robert Johnson.
I just don't know how you'd be so hot.
Anyway, so are you down for this?
I mean, I know it's crazy.
I mean, I won't really cause you any trouble.
It's just a formality, really.
Would you be willing to marry me today?
Well, that's a bold proposal, but not interesting.
This might also be a way for me to push back against the pressure from my family.
Well, Allison, it's definitely a first, but I accept your proposal.
Really?
It's good marriage.
Let's get married.
Sarah, a woman named Allison looking for Bob Johnson.