You CEO of MJ Group got married just like that.
What about June?
Some pine tree for years.
June and I are ancient history.
It's a note of her business.
Jason, I need you to purchase a small place for me.
Something that downplaying my CEO status.
Don't you think you should tell Allison the truth about who you are?
No, yeah.
Any news on Kevin Rodriguez's recent move?
It's required actively.
It's meant to be playing something.
Kevin Rodriguez is no match for me.
Allison, you actually married someone to adopt Sarah?
Yeah.
Hi.
I'm Robert.
Allison's husband.
Sorry the house isn't that big.
Oh, no, don't worry about it. I'm just thankful you were willing to marry me.
Wait, how did you get such a nice place in the hills?
Oh, I've been renting it for years.
Well, I'll have to move in because the adoption agency is going to be stopping by for a home visit in a few days.
So we'll have to play the happy couple until they come and then that we can get a divorce.
Tell them I'll be a good wife.
Yep.
Your arrangements are really thorough.
So, you seem to be pretty well off.
You're quite cancer if you don't mind me saying.
Why would you even agree to a contract marriage?
Is this like a scam?