I need you to figure out everything you can about Allison Miller and her connection to Robert Johnson's.
Immediately! Listen! Hey! Oh my gosh! It's good to see you! Ava, we work together at the Crown Hotel.
Hi! Ava, I'm so sorry. I kind of had some memory issues in college and it's all kind of fuzzy,
I don't. I don't actually remember working at the Crown Hotel. Uh, yeah, it was a long time ago,
I guess. Hi. Hi. So, I ran into somebody today who said that we worked at the Crown Hotel together,
but I don't remember working there at all. What happened in college? Well, your mom got sick
and you had to pay her medical bills, so you took a job at the Crown Hotel for a while.
I just wish I could remember. I just feel like there's this big chunk of my life that's just
missing. Don't worry. What's important is that you made it through and you're here now.
You have to make it through this! I can't lose you! What's good?
Give the adoption officer. Over the home visit in the interview for Sarah's potential adopt.
Thank you so much for coming. Appreciate it. And you must be Allison. Nice to meet you.
So nice to meet you. Shall we? Yeah. So why is it important that you adopt Sarah?
Well, I feel like we have a lot of love to give. If you want to provide a safe and nurturing home
for a child in need. And how long have you two been married? A whole month. Best decision of my life.
It's quite a short time. What made you guys get married so quick? Uh, well... I'll be honest.
This is really suspicious. Are you sure you're not just an inter-raging girl?
Allison is my soulmate. I couldn't win another day to make up my life.
Well, I could tell that the love you guys share is very real. And I have a great feeling about all of
this. So expect good news very soon. Thank you. Thank you so much. Oh my gosh. You were amazing.
Have you ever thought about us being more than just a contract? Sorry, I don't know.
No, it's okay. Take all the time you need to think about it. I actually made a reservation
for us. Don't wait for you at the restroom. Listen, I call for eight o'clock, all right?
So why don't you check your little book and find my table, please. Check it. Oh, you don't know how to read?
Allison. Adam, wow, it's been a really long time. That has been a long time. Too long. You look
amazing, just like always. You know, I was thinking this is gonna sound completely out of nowhere,
but I just bought this no big mansion down the street. It's like the one that we always used to
talk about. What do you say we give another shot, huh? You know what I mean? What do you say we give
another shot, huh? You know what I mean? Seriously? Yeah. You abandoned me five years ago. Oh my god.
And I'm married now. So you know what? You can get lost, Adam. Oh, you're married now, huh? Yeah.
Really? Mm-hmm. Who wouldn't marry you now in your past, huh? Jason. That's a serious question.
And you need to find out everything about Allison's past. Tell me. I would. Jesus Christ.
Let's go. Hey, hey, not so fast. You know, I own part of this restaurant, all right?
And I say that you too. Oh, and welcome to India. So take a hike. Very sorry, sir, but I'm afraid I
have to ask you to leave. Let's just go. It's Robert Johnson's. I need to speak to the manager.
No. Wow, tough guy. What's up his phone, huh? What was that? You call your mom?
Mr. Johnson's. I'm so sorry. Please, right this way. Thank you.
Are you kidding me? You're going to let them in it. Well, then fine. Give me the table next.
Sorry, sir. We can't let you in. So Robert, I heard you got married. When am I going to meet
my daughter-in-law? Soon, mom. I promise. It's just all happened really fast. Well, that's all right,
dear. Take your time, but don't keep me waiting too long. I gotta run. I'll talk to you later, right?
Yes, sir. I'm all out of the seats. You're very welcome. You don't like mushrooms? Not really,
but... Oh my god, Robert. Oh my god, Robert. We got the job. My gosh, congratulations. I'm so proud of
you. How about I take you out tomorrow night after your medical screening to celebrate? That would be
great. Hey, what are you doing here? I had the day off, so I thought why not spend it with my best
friend? I can accompany you to your medical exam if you want. That's fine. I'll just catch up with you
later. Okay. Alison Miller? Um, it's okay. I got it. You're the results of your medical exam.
Here you go, Alison. Everything's perfect. Alison, I know you and Robert are getting close,
but I think that you should not tell him about the memory loss. At least not yet. I really don't
want to lie to him. I just don't want you getting hurt. You know, people can be so judgmental about
these things, so I just want you to be careful, right? Okay. Seven and eight. What a pleasure to have
you down with us tonight. We prepared a special dish just for you, and of course we preserve the
presidential speech for you tonight. I've arranged a lot of company events here. That's why they're
being so accommodating. Try it. And it's good. The trouble. I'm going to take a quick shower,
make yourself up. I'm afraid I might do something inappropriate. Good night. You know,
pretty good. This is John Sinner. You have an impure thoughts about you. Well, aren't you
going to introduce me? Nice to meet you. Call me Hila. Or better yet. Call me Aunt Hila.
I have something for you. It's a family heirloom. Possibly accepted.
Nonsense. It's a tradition for the women in our family to pass it down. I want you to have it.
Why don't you keep it safe for me? I would hate for something to happen to such a precious heirloom.
It's so nice to meet you, Hila. Nice to meet you too. She's not like the other, is she? Not interested
in material things. She's special. When are you going to tell her who you really are, Rob?
When are you going to tell her who you really are, Rob? I'll tell her the truth.
When I know for sure that she loves me for who I am, not for my welfare status. I need you to make
50 copies and have them stapled and collared within the hour. Sure. Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Do you believe the incompetence? I don't know why they had his entry level nobodies.
You were so right, June. You should be running this place. I'm your best, but nothing seems to be
good enough for her. Listen, I know it's tough, but you just have to bear it. Rumor has it June is the
CEO's fiance. They've been together for six years. Rumor has it June is the CEO's fiance. They've
been together for six years. The CEO? I wonder if everyone's sucking up to her.
I can't wait work without my permission. No, I didn't. I was just doing my job. I don't care.
You took too long. I'm writing you up for an unauthorized absence. June, that's not fair.
I've just completed every task that you do. I want to hear your excuses. Pack up your things.
No. I can do this. Give me a chance, okay? All you given these menial tasks.
Done. Do you think you're so capable? Prove it. Land the big client we've been pursuing,
and I'll consider letting you keep this job. That's my disadvantage.
Allison, how are you making progress with the client?
Remember, you can't seal the deal. Don't bother coming back. I'm going to close this deal, June.
You can count on it. I'm going to show you. How am I supposed to face him after everything that's
happening between us? What if he refuses to set a contract? She is 22 back and three parking
grades. You were at their wishes. Can we talk about the business proposal?
Look who it is. Yeah, we can talk business if you move on. What do you mean? I was thinking
if you win, I'll sign your little contract. But if I win, we're going to have to be a little more
private for me to explain that. Fine. What's the game? Adam, that's not part of the deal.
You know, maybe I don't care what the deal is. Stop Adam, get off of me. Get off of me.
Get your hands off before you bastard. Get your hands off before you bastard.
That gorgeous guy I've never seen him before. Is that Robert Johnson's? What is he doing here?
And what's his connection with Allison? Are they together? This is my bar.
Why don't you just get the fuck out? Oh, Mr. Big, tough businessman.
Do you want to do it, huh? You got to hit me? This ain't fucking over. Fuck you guys.
Are you okay? Sorry to give you, sir. Oh, thank you. What if he tries to retaliate?
What if he tries to get you fired or something? What matters is in your safe.
Jim, the deal with MJ Group is off. I don't give it so much you have to do, right?
Just make sure that bitch house. What the hell happened to your face?
Is that fucking Lisa Johnson's? Hey, you mean the C-O-E-M-J group?
Listen, he's gonna regret it, all right? I swear he got it. He must do the bitch with his.
What happened? Your face, it hurts, all right?
The moment the stock market opened, Rodriguez's assets took a pretty huge hit. They lost over $4
billion. I suppose they'll be paying us a visit soon. Mr. Rodriguez, the reason your assets took such a
hit is because of your son, Adam. Adam? What's he got to do with that Davis?
Last night he attempted to assault my wife and he's been harassing her at work.
You're serious? Is this true? You assaulted his wife? We would just fucking hate it, all right?
No one will threaten or harm my wife without consequence. How could you do this? Look, look,
look at the mess you cost. You know, you will apologize to Mrs. Johnson's and ask for forgiveness
immediately. Let the Servers are a reminder to you, Mr. Rodriguez. The Johnson's protect the wrong.
I'll handle this right now. You have my word. Dancing with her?
$4 billion worth of dancing. Can I sleep in your room tonight? Of course. It's not that I don't want to.
I just didn't want to press you anywhere. I'm ready. That was incredible. I love you so much.
Robert, some information about Allison's past. It's not in records. She gave birth during college.
Her boyfriend at the time was Adam Rodriguez into her. She suffered from near depression.
I got a college. I heard you failed to secure the deal with Mr. Rodriguez.
You're fired, effective immediately. May we speak with Miss Allison Miller?
May we speak with Miss Allison Miller? Miss Miller. I want to extend my most
seropology from my son's inappropriate behavior. What he did to you was totally unacceptable.
I want to assure you that it would never happen again. Please accept this gift as a token of our
regret. Mr. Rodriguez, I... You don't have to say anything, Miss Miller. Just know that you're
the full support of the Rodriguez family. Look at you, brother. I had overheals in love.
That's a far cry from your Playboy days. Those days are a long time, Peter.
Allison's the only woman I want. Hey, did you ever think about that one-night stand you
had five years ago? At the Crown Hotel? Sub-drunk that night?
Burn him. Are you curious? What if she was so important? You know what? Curious.