You know, Allison, believe it or not, I was taller than Robert at one point.
Oh.
Really?
Uh, what are they all saying?
Robert, what are they all saying?
What a surprise to see her here.
She knew we were here and it's just not coming.
Allison, dear, did you know that Robert and I used to date?
We were quite the couple back in the day.
June, that was a long time ago. Things have changed.
Of course. I just thought Allison, did you know about our history?
June, maybe we should get out of here.
Robert and Allison are trying to enjoy their evening.
What the hell was that?
Are you trying to ruin Robert and Allison's marriage?
Oh, please.
She deserves another truth but her little husband.
The truth?
You mean like how you don't rob her because he wasn't good enough for you?
You had no idea he was CEO of the company, did you?
No.
You were too busy chasing some rich exec, trying to find something better.
But Robert was the exec the whole time.
You don't deserve Robert, June.