What do you want, Jim?
Some information may be of interest to you, Mr. Johnson's.
What kind of information do you got?
The kind you could ruin else in Miller's perfect little life.
You may be gave you the leverage you need to get back at Robert.
I'm listening.
Listen up, Archer. I got some information that you might be interested in.
And it's got to do with you and your wife.
Don't worry, I'll make it easy for you, all right?
You give me $50 million.
And I'll make sure that having a secret stays safe with me.
What secret?
Have a look for yourself, but it looks like she might add a kid in college.
I got copies of that too, so you need more.
Think about it, buddy.
Jason, I need you to transfer $50 million into Adam Rodriguez's account.
Immediately.