Robert, why did you lie to me and tell me that you rented this place when you actually own it?
Look, I'm really sorry I haven't been completely honest with you.
I originally bought the house for myself, but with you it's become a home.
A home that I want to share with you forever.
I know what to say.
I know. We've been through a lot.
And I'm sorry there are parts in my past that I've kept from you.
Trust me, when I say that I love you,
then I only love what's best for you.
I'm sorry.
What? I thought it was all settled.
No, I'll handle.
What is it?
That was Jason. There's a problem with Sarah's adoption.
Her faster mom doesn't want to give the approval.
What do you mean I thought everything was settled?
What are we gonna do?