Allison, there's something that I should have told you.
You did give birth, Allison, five years ago, to a baby girl.
Read a little girl?
Where is she?
What happened to her?
We put her up for adoption.
Your mom thought that it would be for the best.
You guys gave her away without telling me?
I'm going to find her.
I'm going to bring her home.
Allison, I think that you should consider how this might affect Robert and your marriage.
I should Robert have to bury the burden of my past.
No, it's not fair to him.
I think we should get a divorce.
Robert, there's something I need to tell you and it's going to change everything.
Okay, whatever it is, we'll face it together.
I love you.
The better what?
I have a daughter.
Robert, a little girl.
But I gave birth to five years ago.