Have you been waiting for me?
I've missed you so much.
I brought you something back.
Did my parents invite you?
Where are they?
Here it is.
Shameless.
You've been abroad for four years,
and the first thing you do is try to steal my man.
You're mature, other and long.
You're a man?
Yes.
Your sister and Connor are engaged.
Since when?
Last month.
And you were not invited
because we know what you were doing behind our backs.
Connor told us everything.
Your name has been removed from the family trust.
You've lost your rights to inherit Johnson architect.
You may leave.
Now.
Dad, I'm Connor.
I was coming to propose to you, and now this?
Is this true?
Yep, it is.
Let's go.
Hands off.
I can see myself out.
What is this?
Cheap shit.
That Connor jerk is full of shit.
I knew it.
I thought we were meant to be.
I can't believe I was going to propose to him.
I am beyond stupid.
Do you know what exactly he said to your parents?
No.
And anybody who knows what actually happened
isn't talking to me.
Well, you're welcome to stay at my place tonight.
And that will be a lining up to marry you when you're ready.
Till then, maybe you can make the most of your single life.
And make Connor pay for what he did to you
by getting with his super hot uncle.