You're here already.
I've been here for an hour.
Aw, you already missed me.
Let me be clear with you.
I'm only getting married to you,
because I'm trying to be a ranged marriage to my father.
Is that clear?
Get divorced after two months.
Plus, you're young. I don't want to waste your time.
I can decide what to do with my time.
What a good-looking couple.
Congrats on your marriage.
You're going to have the most beautiful kids.
And we won't have kids.
Would you guys mind getting a little bit closer
and maybe looking a little bit sweeter?
And, sir, if you could smile, that would be amazing.
Oh, he has facial paralysis, so he can't really smile.
Congratulations to the both of you.
You are now officially married.
Why does he have a different last name than Connor's mom?
Your last name is Mancini.