Hi Mr. Grouchy face.
When I said you could move in, I didn't mean to move everything in my house.
Isn't this place so nice? It was so weary before.
Now it feels like a home.
Come on, I have something to do.
Ta-da, come sit.
I call it Sunday morning.
You named the balcony?
Imagine you've overslept in its Sunday.
You wake up from me as snoring.
You come out here, lounge on the couch, sip a cup of coffee, read the newspaper,
and then you stare up at the clouds, pushing that Sunday morning would never end.
Well, I think you should call it the corner where you waste your time.
How do you call it Monday morning? So you work a little harder.
Come on, have a little time.
I mean, what is this couch you made of? This couch is horrible.
This is a bad idea.
This man stubborn as a mule.