Hey! That's my design! I've been working on those ideas for over a month!
How did you get your hands on that?
Excuse me, would you mind be quiet, please? We want to see this.
This is the fourth dimensional world that I designed.
It's a mysterious and undiscovered world.
This is an undesiner from Johnson, pretty impressive.
She certainly has a bright future ahead of her.
Bullshit! She's a thief!
This is my cosmic eye.
Are you going to mention the academic research areas
or the artistic spaces built using new technologies,
such as photoelectric current walls and new LED lights systems?
And how do you know all the details about my concepts?