Uncle Paul, planning on doing some renovations to your villa soon?
When are you gonna have time to do all that with your busy schedule?
Johnson Architects, they should take care of that for you.
Jennifer is a great designer.
You should give her a chance.
I know a thing or two about the Johnson designers.
All right, their style, it is luxurious, but their taste.
It's just, it's too traditional and reserved for my taste.
That's where there's room for communication.
You can express your desires to Jennifer.
Their reputation has taken a bit of a hit.
Could you please help them out?
Would you do this for me?
I've met with Jennifer before, and honestly, she lacks the experience.
And you know what?
She knows nothing of today's technology.
Latest materials, high-tech appliances, it's...
I'm outside the car. You come out now.
Oh, it's a matter.
Your lips feel lonely without me around.
I already regret being a part of this conversation.
Oh, my gosh.
Want a speaker phone?
Yep.