You need to go make amends.
I'm sorry?
Don't you play coy with me?
I'm busy building my own career.
I don't have time for your petty little show.
What? Having regrets?
You know, if you were still the way you used to be,
maybe I could have helped you out too.
Your words don't mean anything to me.
Your manners are horrific.
Why don't you ask your father to make you the heir
and see how he responds?
How of your mind?
No wonder your parents disowned you.
You deserve it.
Connor, do you ever listen to yourself?
Your presence is nothing but a constant nuisance
to the Johnson family.
Do you even realize that because of your accusations,
Johnson's reputation has been tarnished overnight.
The company's market value has dropped two billion dollars.
It is all your fault.
It'd be my fault if I didn't tell the truth.
You stole Jennifer's work and her reputation.
What kind of person could be so mean
to her own family?
You told my father that I was talking shit
about my family to reporters.
What kind of person tears apart another's family?