When did I ever say I want to marry you?
The Baratheon Group invested into the series company and there were tons of money the dollars
Look at you. You're just a broke ugly. It's sneaky.
I can't even believe that you ever dreamed you were gonna marry my son. Oh, I see where this is going
You know success get to your head
You want to hang out with social butterflies and you forgot how I supported you as a girlfriend since when were you my girlfriend?
I never said I liked you and I definitely never asked you to be falling over yourself for me
So everything I did for you meant nothing. Yeah
When your landlord kicked you out, I found a new place for you and you got fired from the start group
I funded your startup company. I got new clients for you. Whoa. Okay, stop it right there. All right
She was the one who invested in my fun
You're just a delivery girl, and here you are taking credit for everything all over again
What a total scumbag. She's got poor taste in men
Miss Nichols
Targaryen even
Tyrion Baratheon is a better butler to me. You think you want to become CEO without me asking me to help you the past three years?
Come on listen to you the Targaryen mystery
The largest house in the world largest bank owner second in the world also, you know the last hundred years the greatest
Collectors of collectibles as well. Don't you try to fool me? No Targaryen heiress would ever be like you
That's right. Why does mr. Baratheon even know about you? Oh, did you send him yummy photos too?
She's not dare you sneak those photos of me
Leak are you serious? She sent me those pictures trying to convince me
seduce you
It's and she'll get you soon enough and if she doesn't I don't know about that
But what I do know is that I've linked all of your feuds online
Oh looks like they've gone viral
Anyone ever marry you you're bastard. I'll marry you