I'll marry you.
I can't stand a kind girl like that being bully bottles of assholes plus if I marry her
I won't have to deal with nagging to get married again. He actually stands up for me when I meet it at the most
Okay, let's get married
Yeah, that's the couple straight out of heaven
That's only for now
Soon enough, I'll make him the richest man in the morning
Lord, I'm already the richest man in the south. What's the point making a hub of richer than the Mr. Baratheon?
Getting dumped definitely drove you insane
But yeah
As soon as I get that $2 billion from the Baratheon project
I'll free some money. We use it for therapy
So I'm sure once we come back to sanity
You're gonna realize how tragic it is that you married a hobo to get back
Why are you still offering me pity money?
You know, I set up that bid to get you the project. You can say goodbye to that now
You should really be careful. I lie like that could snowball into a disaster
I wasn't burning. She's still trying to take credit. It was me who pulled the strings from a series
The bid is only for show strings, huh?
I bet they're not strong enough to overpower my company the stark group
You mean the stark family who owns most of the real estate in the south?
That's the one breathing in the real world more like king of cuckoo land
Your lives are gonna snowball into disaster. It's not a lie. I really do own the star group
Okay, you a delivery girl and you a hobo do low-life stage reading out loud over there
Let's go series
Insanity tea my lady. Oh what the series have the project. Why did he betray you?
Don't worry. There are plenty fish in the sea. We'll make sure that you have your pick