If you're the organizer, then I'm the owner of this hotel.
Brian, the Stark family owns this hotel.
Stop embarrassing yourself, or you'll be a disgrace in both the North and the South.
If you want to come in, at least dress nicer.
Did you dive into a dumpster for that dress?
Look at you. You've got nothing on Marjorie.
It's a good thing that this race dumped you.
Otherwise, I would be embarrassed if you had this meeting.
Get you in for all time's sake, but your clothes are pretty trashy.
I can let you in if you take them off.
Oh, dear. I'm so considerate. What are you waiting for?
Hurry. Take this bitch's clothes off.
The spark is about to be here. It was one of them.
What are you afraid of? This is the North.
Mr. Vissery is favored by the most powerful family.
And I think Mr. Baratheon, he would he would back this up.
And besides Mr. Baratheon and Mr. Stark are both men.
What man doesn't like a nice homey strip show?
No. Not on my watch.