That's bullshit!
How dare you accuse me of something so horrible!
What's going on?
Grandma, that is why I presented you with the cream,
because the powder you're wearing right now is poison.
How can I be?
That was a prestigious royal product that Melanie bought from me.
No, I'm sorry, but that is a carcinogenic talcum powder.
That's BS!
They are from exclusive salons.
Trailer trash like you wouldn't know if it would be different.
Exclusive salons?
No!
Stannis rented out the warehouse at Shif's house.
Stannis, is that true?
Grandma, I have no idea what this bitch is talking about.
How do you know that?
You don't have to make things up just to defend me.
Don't worry, it's 100% true.
Oh, what the hell do you know you tramp delivery girl?
Stop spreading this shit!
So this, is Stannis' order for talcum powder.
And this is Melanie's order for an empty powder tin.
How did you get that?
I have colleagues that are more than happy to do me a favor.
Her connections are scary.
Never rub couriers the wrong way.
Grandma, don't believe her!
This is fake!
Stannis, this is your handwriting!
Grandma, even if I got an empty box,
who's to say it's filled with talcum powder?
You'd have to test it.
I know how to test it.