Varys, you're basically begging me to banish you to the rainforest.
Captain, Varys, Miss Brienne is our captain's perfect match.
She's kind, beautiful, and honorable.
Stay out of this.
Even if that's all true, she's just a deliberate girl.
She's a what-the-of the captain.
Whether she's worthy or not is not up for you to decide.
Please, everyone, sir, Captain!
Please, divorce her, Captain.
Varys, are you trying to make my decisions for me?
Captain, but this woman...
Stupid!
You're so stupid.
With your recklessness and your responsibility, sooner or later, the Targaryens will bankrupt
you.
Why do you care about this wedding anyway?
Who are you, the state government?
Listen, not only are we not going to get divorced, we're going to have the most grand
wedding.
Captain.
Oh, no, don't worry.
You'll definitely be on the guest list.
Because I want to prove to you whether I'm worthy of Jamie or not.