This is not my dorm.
Please, Mrs. Miller, please keep your hat still.
Mrs. Miller, I've just been harper.
What's going on?
This may come as a shock, but you have amnesia.
Amnesia?
Yes, you damage your hippocampus in a car accident.
Resulting in partial memory loss.
You probably think you're 21, but you're actually 25.
And you're married to Patrick Miller.
Is Patrick?
Yes.
And me.
Wow.
You doesn't know I've lost my memory.
Don't tell him.
No, why will we?
I finally got the minor point dreams.
One complicated thing.
I'm just going to enjoy being Mrs. Miller.
Patrick, I've loved you for so many years.
I know you're Patrick Miller.
The big stern campus.
Everyone in this college knows how much I love him.
I'm ready to give him all my heart.
The five-year-old me has a hot hobby and tons of money.
Patrick will have to seem a dress like this.
This is him.
My husband.
You're awake.