What? You've got to tell me everything that's happened, because I don't remember anything after that goddamn wedding.
What? What are you talking about?
Trust me. I feel like I'm still 21. I have no clue what happened during those past few years.
Oh, I'm genuinely sorry if I did your wrong. You'll always be my best friend.
Wait, wait. So you just lost your memory, huh?
Your mind has raised all the unhappy moments about your past.
But Patrick, should I be happy? I'm having my passion.
You should be. If you hadn't been happy, I would have been happy for you too.
But I've been hurt so many times because of Patrick and Vivian.
And I bet your amnesia has something to do with them.
So you know, Vivian too.
Who's she?
Patrick's childhood friend, always by his side.
It treats her like a sister, but who knows what their relationship is really like.
How much? My life is frustrating.
Girl, just forget about it.
You know, there are plenty of guys out there waiting to be picked.
Maybe it's time for you to get back into the dating pool.
From the gentleman over there.
Fine. I don't even like this kind of...
We're in old places.
Hey, I don't need to hear your critique of my taste, okay?
Fine, I'll just stick with you.
The usual is. Thank you.
Oh, it's fun, me.