Is she wearing hot couture? Her dress is stunning.
Shut up, I know that why the dress looks completely handcrafted.
I really need to know the designer.
Me too.
Sorry, honey.
I'm late.
Oh my God.
Is this supposed to be Patric's ugly wife?
But she's so pretty.
Seems like whole rumors about her were completely fake.
She and Patric is perfect for each other.
Just mean, I'll make sure you embarrass yourself today.
Hello there.
At this year's wife, I'm sure you have excellent taste.
So may I ask you, what do you think of our restaurant design concept?
Well, I guess being pretty is her only trait.
She must be dumb.
I can't believe she can't even answer a simple question.
Oh, and the hind work environment is clearly not for a house by like you.
Maybe you should go home and cook.
I was just thinking, oh, really?
You mentioned your design was inspired by the Bauhaus.
But to me, it looks like a total ripoff of Euler's famous architectural work.
He didn't touch rice.
I've never even seen Euler's work.
Really?
Yes.
But his work is a must study for every interior designer.
And if you're not familiar with it, that means you don't even know the basics.
Well, well, well.
Patric.
Nice, Jasmine. He's an interrogator like that.
It seems like she's enjoying humiliating me.
Both of us.
Maybe there's some research next time.
If you decide to show off.
Oh, come.
I didn't even know you knew about this stuff.
You know nothing, Patrick Miller.
Mrs. Miller, I didn't realize you were smart as you're beautiful.
I would be delighted to invite you to my art studio sometime soon.
Cheers.
A minute.
Mrs. Miller pregnant.
Oh!
Michael is relation.
When was your last period?
I don't remember.
What kind of question is that?
So, you're not pregnant, are you?
Pregnant?
How can I be pregnant?
I can't be screaming.
Did you lose all interest in me?
That car accident really turned everything upside down.
I really need to find out what's gotten into her tonight.
Patrick, what are you doing here?
I thought you didn't even like me.
I remember what you said last night.
When we made love.
Last time?
The only thing I remember is being mentally in love with him.
But how do my feelings before it turned 21?
You said you wanted something wild.
You said you wanted being my slave until your legs hurt.
I... I did.
I know we shouldn't say yes to this jerk.
But damn, I lied to him for so long.
Yes.
I'll be your slave.
Be honest.
Have you lost your memory or something?
What's in his dad?
You know, I said this worst to me.
I was tricking you.
His celebrity's suspicious looks like I have to play alone.
Yeah.
What is sad sounds so nice, since you want to make it happen?
I thought you were always prepared.
I mean, you were in charge of supply after all.
What?
Be prepared, can't you?
So you do want to have my baby?
Talking about and why the hell did you plummet to my back in the middle of the night?
Don't you know what consent means?
But we were scheduled for today.
Have you really forgotten?
It's how you arranged.
Scaredled sex?
Why would it come up with something so ridiculous?
Listen, if you don't want to slip with me,
why?
But don't accuse me of breaking the rules we made when we got married.
So he only slept with me because it was his dinner.
I was so pathetic.
I get it now.
Just leave me alone.
You don't have to make any fantasies come true anymore.
We'll be strangers in this house for now on.
Why do I feel sad and lost?
Isn't this what I always wanted?
Finally, some free time to sit the exhibition.
I stuck her in real daylight.
What is this world coming to?
This is Miller.
It was a detective here.
You're hot.
I did my job pretty well.
Didn't I?
I can't believe I actually hired a detective to stack my husband like some privilege room.
Now it's time to pay.
To $100,000.
To $100,000?
Where am I going to get that much money?
Try this one.
What a great business deal.
Making money from Boss, Jasmine and Vivian.
Jasmine brought a lot of negative publicity to the restaurant.
And fixing this will cost money.
You wouldn't hesitate to spend whatever it takes, right?
It's not about the money.
I promised you our parents I'd take care of you.
But are you really taking that project seriously?
Patrick, I swear on my grave.
This is the last time going to cost you money.
Please, believe me.
I'll do better, please.
Jasmine just spent $100,000 on your card.
She's fucking crazy.
She's never used that card before.
Well, I think she's trying to get table with me.
So, you're going to let her spend $200,000 for no reason but won't help me with my problem?
Don't mix things up.
I'll help you for the one last time.
Catch restaurant in order and stop embarrassing me in public.
As the real Mrs. Miller, I need to hurry up and get the studio worst.
A bad Jasmine will go crazy again when she sees my photos with Patrick.
I want it to work.
No way. No way.
Why not?
Wouldn't it be better for you and your child who speak hard, Vivian?
These photos are not what they've seen like.
None of the admirers anymore.
I want it to work.
Again, I refuse.
Converse.
He's all yours.
Isn't that what you always wanted?
No, you're business.
Don't come into my office again.
Unless you have a valid reason.
You can't believe here if you used to do worse here.
I'm going to find another way to handle this.
Are you alright, sir?
I haven't seen you this upset since you've handled the company's financial crisis.
Tell me.
Why do you think Jasmine suddenly wants a divorce?
She knows that Vivian and I are just partners.
I used to hate her irrational cleanliness but...
I was just a completely different person.
I feel divided.
Sir, Mrs. Miller is her own person, makes it possible to read her mind.
Perhaps you should just talk to her to find out the reason.
I did.
It's probably because we didn't get intimate last time.
And so feels that I've been distant from her.
But haven't you always wanted to divorce her, sir?
Not anymore.
But now I'm going to plan a date for us.
She'll definitely fall in love with me all over again.
Why isn't Jasmine back here?
Should I give her a call?
We've invited a Michelin star chef to prepare steak tonight just for her.
No, no. I don't want to sing to eager.
I'm not eating.
Wait. I invited her Michelin star chef to make a steak tonight.
What's it got to do with me? Don't you know that I don't even like steak?
She doesn't like steak.
So you are telling me that the fried chicken is better than the steak?
Yeah, this could be a dessert.
Maybe I'm a taster.
Use me this time.
You saved that trick.
I want to let you get away with this.
Sir, Mrs. John seems to be in serious pain.
You might want to take a look.
I'm not a doctor.
Tell her to just go to the hospital if that's serious.
Alright.
Not anymore.
What do you mean not anymore?
You were ready to make love just a couple seconds ago.
I was in the mood.
But now I'm not.
Got a problem with that?
Now if you'll excuse me, Mr. Miller.
I'm going to leave you alone so you can enjoy a swim.
It was too close.
I almost let you get what you wanted.
I really need to get the divorce done as soon as possible.
You're still working as reports, right?
I've got some scoop for you.
No need to thank me.
Sir.
Is it now?
Who did this?
How did they get these photos?
Just one can say this.
Get it taken down immediately.
I said immediately.
Don't you hear me?
Sir.
I've already checked.
These pictures were sold to the press by Mrs. Miller herself.
Does she want?
Sir, maybe Mrs. Miller really wants a divorce this time.
I didn't get it.
She was now like this.
It was only me and her world that now people changed, sir.
I suggest you talk to her to clear things up.
Could you be in love with someone else?
Follow her every move and find out what she's up to.
It's the project I did in the college.
The hell didn't stop here.
Mine claim tricks on me.
That name sounds so familiar.
Jasmine?
Sorry.
Looks like Phoebe was right.
She really doesn't remember anything.
I know.
Phoebe's brother.
Is you don't remember me?
I've heard you already was in Patrick.
Isn't it right?
Well, I realized this marriage isn't right for me.
If I make her my wife, it would definitely boost the profits on my gallery.
Good for you.
You shouldn't settle for being just a housewife with all your talent.
If you're interested, you can come and work at my gallery.
Um, seriously?
I don't really have enough experience.
Don't worry about that.
I've known you since you were 22.
And they're exactly what you can do.
You'd make it great.
Art curator.
And it's awesome.
Art is my thing.
And maybe you can catch me up on what's been happening in the art world over the past few years or so.
I spent too much time at home.
Let's go to my office.
We can talk more there.
Sir, we've got the problem.
She wants to work.
It's some shitty gallery.
I've never held a position at the company before.
Maybe she's becoming more and more unbearable.
I think you could try.
So I assume she'll be going to work tomorrow.
Let's see about that.
To work?
We're getting to work soon.
So I gotta start looking out for myself.
You already have a great job.
Don't you remember?
Shit.
Do I really have a job?
I remember nothing about it.
I just don't want that job anymore.
I want to fresh start.
Guess I'll have Vivian to cover your old job.
Are you real?
There is no way she can handle the same job as me.
You'd be a friendly idiot if you gave her my position.
Bring me back before she screws everything up.
Hey, finally back.
Did the boss reinstate you?
Yes, everybody looking at me so weirdly.
You don't remember?
Wait.
You didn't hit your head during this car accident, did you?
Who is not?
I'm just curious, you know.
After all, I'm this your wife.
So it shouldn't come with the surprise that I'm here.
Oh, yeah.
People are saying that you reported Vivian's restaurant out of your jealousy.
That it was all Losey set up and you were just a liar.
What?
Me, a liar?
No, I shouldn't be saying this.
But it's so Mr. Miller's fault for not knowing all of this.
After all, Vivian's restaurant clearly has issues.
Um, let me test you.
What's my role at the company?
You're the art director.
You're mainly responsible for promoting the hotel and organizing high-end exhibitions.
And how's that related to Vivian's restaurant exactly?
After her restaurant was renovated,
the CEO sent you to inspect it.
And you discovered that it didn't meet the safest standards.
And when I told Patrick, he accused me of intentional defaming Vivian.
Let me just sign the complaint.
Let's go.
We are going to get to the bottom of this now.
Well, let's walk.
Apologize to me.
Now.
What are you talking about?
The restaurant.
I never slander Vivian.
Both of you owe me an apology.
Oh, she's just me.
So you came back to work just to throw a tantrum?
Let me turn right now.
Whatever it is, we'll talk about later.
No.
Leave.
I'm so...
Let's just...
So weak.
This is all the evidence.
I had it that time.
I suggested it can all the look.
Why did you give them all the art to me?
Are you saying I didn't give you any of this before?
Yes.
Why wouldn't I have believed you otherwise?
Then you can check it now.
And if you still believe Vivian, after seeing these,
I have nothing to say.
Just me.
I know you want to see the test me.
But this restaurant was my parent's dream.
I will never, never let you take it away from me.
Vivian, are you out of your mind?
Patrick!
You promised.
You take care of me.
I've done enough for you over these years.
I'm sure they wouldn't blame you for anything.
I'll definitely get to the bottom of this.
I apologize.
What if I told you I can help you secure an exquisite collaboration with Isaac?
Isaac?
Does she mean this genius artist who's been off the radar for ages?
If she can really make that collaboration happen,
then the talent's going to hit the next level.
The collaboration of the restaurant are two separate issues.
I'm still getting to the bottom of this.
So, he's not a violent defendant, Vivian, after all.
I can secure the Isaac collaboration too.
Isaac is anonymous and highly acclaimed artist.
Not some dumb housewife you'd know.
Let's make a bet then.
If I can secure this collab, you'll hold a press conference
admitting your restaurant issues.
And apologize to me.
As you wish.
But if you fail, you're out of this company immediately.
Do destroy you, Jessica.
Why would you make that stupid bad with Vivian?
Isaac rose to fame four years ago and then simply vanished.
No one knew you since then.
How would you even start to find that artist?
Well, I've got a plan.
Of course I do.
I have my own plan.
This is between me and Vivian.
It's none of your business.
Would you be none of my business?
You're my wife.
Is he really concerned about me from once?
You're made bad with her in front of everyone.
How can I protect you if you lose?
So you think I'm guaranteed to lose?
You've been under my wing all these years.
How else can you ask for help?
Maybe I could ask no of her help.
Well, that's nothing you need to worry about.
Find the artist Isaac for me as soon as possible.
You lose chance.
Is everything alright?
I need your help with something.
And you're the only person who can help me.
No problem.
Just tell me what it is.
Thanks sweet fans.
I just wanted to ask you.
Could you get in contact with Isaac?
Well, it seems like you still hasn't remembered anything.
It's urgent.
And authorization for collaboration.
Since your galleries showcases their work, you must know each other, right?
Yeah?
I know, Isaac.
I can help you.
But I needed to agree to one thing in return.
And what would that be?
Will you marry me?
Jasmine, I've had feelings for you since college.
But Patrick was always into me.
Now that you're finally getting a divorce,
let me be the one to treat you right.
Liz, this is too sudden.
I've always seen you as a friend.
Looks like she's not as gullible as she seems.
It's fine.
I just wanted to express my feelings to you.
We can take it slow.
After all, I've been waiting for you for so many years.
How about if you're willing to rock in my gallery?
I will help you with this.
Isaac, is that okay?
Why am I thinking about Patrick even now?
Could I still have feelings for him?
I'm here.
I'm sorry, but I need some time to think about it.
I can gather authorization for Isaac alone.
Of course we will.
We are allies of this one.