Look right here. This is my restaurant's gifts report.
Proving that you falsely using me of everything.
You must apologize to me. Right now.
You know, damn well, how you got this gifts report.
Do you want me to tell everyone?
He just jealous of me. She bought...
Bibi! Enough.
Are you defending her?
I won fair and square.
Not only did I get the authorization, but Isaac also allowed me to exhibit the most famous painting.
What? Is this Isaac's painting?
Why are we still standing here?
Hurry up and find some way to contact Isaac.
I'm sorry, but I really couldn't find any way to reach the artist.
This is what Mrs. Miller painted for you and your first anniversary.
So beautiful. Why could I not remember this?
You were too overwhelmed by the company crisis at that time to focus on anything else.
Mrs. Miller was really sad for a long time because of this.
It's urgent. Find out if Jasmine and Isaac have any connection. Why didn't you ever tell me?