He must be sick of his little, uh, little caterpillar, right?
Mine's way more rather than his.
And I can give you anything you want.
Never in a million years.
Bitch.
Stop it! Let's go on me!
Go!
Finally, someone made you a dickwerk, huh?
Get out.
For a skin you would feed you to the dogs.
You always think of me as the bastard.
This bastard's gonna get coronated one day, mate.
Mm.
Yes.
Is that how you do housekeeping?
Groveling under another man's face.
What the hell do you want?
I want you to pay for everything you did so well.
I know what he told you.
I'm not the one who killed your sister.
Fire!
My gosh, don't move.
Just let me go.
I promise.
I'll never show up again.
But you die slowly, my voice.
Is that really what you want?
Your brother said you've been impotent for the last three years.
You don't seem to have a problem getting hard for me.
Wake up!
Wherever I am, if I'm in hell, you'll come looking for me.
Who do you think you'll be free?
You don't.
Skipped with me.
That explains why you're in such a horrible state.
What do you mean?
Max is not the gentleman we used to know.
He's a monster now.
I saw him execute a traitor.
He was so bloody.
So horrible.
I'm your best friend.
I will help you.
Yes.
Where is he?
Where are we going?
I know a place.
Max will never find you there.
Trust me.
Where are we?
I'll come to dark with.
You are going to like it.
She's all yours.
Take good care of her.
Rest assured, once inside my dungeon, nobody gets out alive.
What if Mr. Luther finds out she's not in the right place?
Trust me.
That will never happen.
Remember this place?
I know you miss it.
Welcome home, sweetie.
You're the one who brought me here?
You think I would do this without Max's consent?
Scarlett, why are you doing this?
I thought we were friends.
Who am I to be your best friend?
For crying out loud, you've got good looks and a decent upbringing.
You don't deserve the Luther family.
I do.
I was wrong to think that locking you up would make Max forget about you.
But now, it looks like I'll just have to kill you.
Do your job.
DTX.
Remember?
I'll kill you if you dare touch me.
Well, I remember.
You said the same thing the first time I gave it.
But as soon as it answers your body, you ask for more.
No.
The little girl that drives me crazy.
Nina.
I'm sorry.
No.
Look, it's me.
Max.
Why don't you touch me?
Because you make me sick.
You have to calm down.
Why don't you touch me?
Because you make me sick.
You need to calm down.
Max, what have you done?
Get out.
Stop torturing her.
Who are you?
Max, I don't even know you anymore.
You're still weak.
You want now.
Drug me and sell me like a slave again?
But you get from this.
Are you happy now?
I've become a whore to everyone.
Shut up!
You deserve wars for what you did to my sister.
You want me to be a little slut?
It's just a tip of the ice.
You want to see more?
Want to see more?
Mustful and unsatisfied.
I said stop.
My life is ruined.
All I want is to get away from you.
Max.
Take her to the secret chain.
Don't let her out.
I was Nina.
She's been on a hunger strike for days.
Make her steak and mushrooms.
It'll cheer her up.
You'll have to eat.
One can not squeeze me.
It depends on my master's mood.
You're not as cool as it is.
You better eat.
You can't fight against him without strength.
Nina has never been to the state penitentiary.
What did you find out about Nina?
Ms. Morgan was imprisoned this whole time.
And she got addicted to drugster.
You killed Mr. Black.
You was my best deal and my best cash cow.
How could you do that?
DTX?
That's what that is, right?
Our family doesn't do drugs.
According to Father Swell, I'm in control of the underground business.
Just stay off my turf.
It's a mercy that I even let you be part of the family business.
It's Nina Morgan, isn't it?
You do everything for now.
She's a nobody.
I don't have to do anything for her.
And why'd you luck away in your house?
She means nothing.
I told you I don't give a shit about that.
I can see right through you.
So much I can do to her.
To you.
She'll be.
Stop drinking.
Stop hurting yourself for that selfish woman.
I'm not doing it for her.
I keep her around so I can torture her.
Max, I'm the only one who truly cares for you.
I know I can't have a child, but I'll figure it out.
I'll do anything I can.
A child?
Yes.
Our child.
A forever bond.
A testament for our love.
What's going on?
Jesus.
I can't stand it anymore.
You've come clean once.
You can do it again.
Guys are double flea-
It's all right.
I'm here.
You can get over this.
What is going on?
It's an author.
Hey, stop.
You betray me.
Again.
How long has this been going on here?
My nose.
It's not like that.
He was just trying to help me get off the drug.
Please.
By hugging you?
It's on my phone.
You can go.
I'll do anything.
No, you're still weak, Mr. Luther.
Please.
Don't blame Ms. Morgan.
I will take any punishment.
Touch you.
Let's see what you do for your love when you know.
I wouldn't marry you before because you couldn't see.
Now I've solved our problem.
She can have our baby.
And you can become Mrs. Luther.
No.
I'm not doing that.
You can't do that to me.
You are in no position to bargain.
Have my baby.
Or I'll kill Lance.
I care about him but I'm not having your child.
Just so you know.
I have your father too.
What did you do to him?
Nothing good.
But I can't promise that last.
If I have this child,
will you finally set me free and my father?
If you have this child,
you and your father will be free of the Luther family.
What about Lance?
Sure.
Him too.
I'll do it.
But once that child is born,
you will never see me again.
You have my word.
Did Mrs. Luther hurt you again?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry to have dragged you into the water with me.
It's okay.
I can take this.
Cinderella without her glass slippers.
Anciously waiting for her prince.
Hmm?
I still remember the first time I met you.
Dressed like Cinderella.
Lighting up the whole school dance ball.
I could tell.
It's as ugly as fun.
Stop!
Nina.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
I shouldn't have helped you that night.
Now I'm Cinderella.
You're the maid.
Clean up the mess.
What are you doing?
I can explain.
Why didn't you fight back?
How?
This is the Luther household.
Who am I to defy Mrs. Luther?
Mrs. Luther, huh?
How long has this been going on?
Almost a week.
Are you pregnant?
Oh, I can't have his child.
Let me help you.
You need to get a test to see if you really are pregnant.
I don't need your help, okay?
You know what happens when you do?
I don't care.
I'm going to catch you out of this hellhole.
But before I do, you must not let Mr. Luther know anything about this.
Why can't you get hard?
Am I not hot enough?
Did I do something wrong, Maxie?
I promise I can do better.
The only problem is you're not her.
But what is wrong with you?
You need to go to the doctor.
Like you care.
You look like you're pregnant.
Do something.
I'll get you a towel.
What is this?
This is an heirloom that has been handed down in the Luther family.
It's beautiful.
One day, we're belonging to our child.
What's in your hand?
You better be able to conceive in your condition.
I can't.
Every second I spend with you in Scarlet is disgusting.
What do you want?
First of all, I can't be confined to this house.
I need fresh air.
You can go for a walk in the yard once a day for one hour.
Second, I gotta have my own room.
I need good rest.
Lance will see to it that you are not disturbed while you're resting.
Last but not least, I want Scarlet to be my servant.
And take care of me.
What makes you think I would agree to?
I name my requests.
You make the decision.
I see what you're playing at.
Pregnant.
Maxie's child.
Are you gonna keep it?
Sure, it's my baby, but you can't know about it.
I need to get out of here.
He's dangerous.
Come with me.
We can go to Texas.
I have a house there.
I love your baby like it's my only.
I don't like this.
Get me something else.
How dare you?
Do what she says.
Clean this mess up.
No way.
I've done everything you've asked.
When can we start to plan out the surrogacy?
I need to see my dad first.
Don't push it.
I need to make sure he's safe.
Fine.
I'll take you to my cocktail party tonight.
Your dad will be there.
You like this, don't you?
Do you really like this shit?
Yeah.
You can be happy now.
But don't get carried away.
Once this baby is born, you'll be ditched.
Put this on for me.
Made.
Excuse me?
You always did look stunning in the way.
Do that again.
Never see your father again.
What am I?
You're Barbie doll?
It's perfect.
Let's go.
It's party time.
You're staying here.
But I'm Mrs. Luther.
Not yet, you're not.
Cinderella goes to the ball.
Gus Gus stays home.