The Luther family has long time been invested in Mr. Morgan's company.
As of recently, we found out he has a drinking problem.
He has greatly affected the performance of the company.
After careful deliberation, we've decided to withdraw our investment.
Please, don't take the money back.
It can mean that.
However, out of humanitarian concerns, even after Morgan Corporation was bankrupt,
we provided Mr. Morgan with a monthly allowance of $100,000.
Get out.
Sadly, Mr. Morgan has squandered away all of his money,
and now he intends to blackmail Mr. Morgan.
Nonsense!
I will not let you slander her.
My lawyers will take over.
Mr. Luther, you seem to be very protective of Ms. Morgan.
I was gonna make a formal announcement, but since you're so curious,
Mrs. Morgan is my fiance.