Nina. You okay?
I'm fine.
Get this off.
Stop!
Bringing fake money to a kidnapper.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
What do you do to my dad?
Why do you still care about that jerk?
After everything he's done to you.
Stop being such a saint.
Stop pretending that you care.
Okay?
Just leave us alone.
Would you regret it?
We're part of the Luther family.
How dare you lock us up like this?
Don't worry.
I just want to have a discussion.
What's better to discuss?
You make all the decisions.
I turn a blind eye to all your underdoings with Donnie.
That doesn't mean I'm somebody to be mess with.
You have no right to tell us what to do.
Now.
Does anybody else have anything to say?
Now is the time.