Sir, our stock is being sorted aggressively. We're about to hit the limit down.
What the hell is going on here?
Half of you came from major investment banks. Our stock is about to crash and you're telling
me there's nothing we can do.
Sir, this is a coordinated attack from multiple investment funds. They're shorting us simultaneously.
There is nothing we can do.
Sir, what are our next steps?
Well, looks like Shepherd View might be a backdrop by lunchtime.
Hey, this is a privacy lesson.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Could you hold on cleaning for just a couple minutes?
Mr. Shepherd, building a public company and they're just by the years? That's impressive.
But losing your cool over a little market turbulence? That seems out of character for you.
Do I know you?
Wait, what are you doing?