Mr. Yates.
What? Only two bodyguards this time?
You're not going soft on me, are you?
No, ma'am, I just thought you might like the screen today.
Now listen, everyone is waiting in New York for you to claim your inheritance to see you have the lowest ground.
Mr. Yates, you know that my investigations here aren't finished.
Ma'am, I still don't understand why you've kept your identity a secret.
Why are you married this Ben Harrison fellow?
Look, today is Ben's birthday.
Anything we need to discuss, we can do it some other time.
Ma'am, it really is time for you to set your inheritance.
Because what I want is a simple life with Ben.
Ma'am, at least do me a favor and let Terry walk you up to the house, for my sake.
Divorce papers, sign in.