Why?
You were not worthy of my son getting more.
The Harrison group is practically a local celebrity now,
especially since it's landed a $100 million contract.
The Shepherd Group.
And you.
You're just a cleaner.
The truth is, Laura, I've wanted a divorce for a very long time.
I need a wife who reflects my status.
I secured that $100 million contract.
You!
A cleaning woman!
You're putting up million dollar deals.
Don't make me laugh.
I did!
It was my present to Betty for his birthday.
I was the one who got right here and seemed to give Ben that deal.
What are you doing here?
Clearly, Ben has found himself a woman more suitable for the Harrison family.
Amber's family.
He's practically the local royalty.
Local royalty.
A small-town rich person is royalty.
And what qualifications do you have to judge, Miss Cleaner?
Your resume boasts supermarket cashier and dinner waitress alongside janitor.
Doesn't it?
Ben, what's going on?
Is this what you want a divorce?
Because of her?
Oh, please.
I've spent years building Harrison group.
You're still a cleaner.
You just grew apart, that's all you've got.
A part?
No.
No, I won't sign any agreement with this.