Laura, I want to say thank you properly for saving Shepherd Group.
It's, it's really no, no worries, Mr. Shepherd, but um, I'm just going through a divorce.
You see, it's, who are you, Laura's new squeeze?
Excuse me, do you know who I am?
Is this true?
You hooked up with this man, while you were married to my son?
Shame on you!
Mr. Shepherd, I'm...
For your information, my name is Brian Shepherd.
I'm CEO of the Shepherd Group.
Oh please, a big shout like Brian Shepherd wouldn't be called dead for the cleaner.
You really don't recognize him, do you, Amber?
That's really interesting considering I thought you were the one that secured that contract
for Ben.
That's ridiculous.
He doesn't look like that.
My ring.
Jason, give it back to the sleeves.
What are you doing?
Laura, let's get you out of here.
Now.
Hold on a minute, Laura.
Who the heck is this man?
Have you been sneaking around?
That's all right, man.
This is none of your business.
Oh, Brad said bodies.
You're not going anywhere until that's what you tell us what's going on.
We are the Harrison's.
You can't just waltz in here and take her.
Harrison, compared to the Shepherd Group, you're nobody.
I'll go back.
What?
Are you saying that is Brian Shepherd?
That's a lie.
Don't you dare walk away from me, Laura.
You come back here and explain yourself.
Don't you take another step towards my son, Laura?