Laura, does Ben even know you were the one who secured the 100 million deal?
Let's just say that Ben underestimated me.
I don't feel good about going through the signing event.
After how they treated you, maybe we should cancel it.
No, no, the event will proceed. Besides, I'll be there.
There's a lot that I don't know about you, Laura. Who are you, truly?
You'll find out, Mr. Shepherd.
Um, can you pull up over here, please?
Mr. Gates, I want you to call all of the Lewis Group's business partners,
and we're going to have a meeting, an investment meeting, one week from today.
Make sure everyone is there.
Because after that meeting, I'm going to reclaim my place as the CEO of Lewis Group.
Oh, excellent, Miss Lewis. I'll stop making arrangements tomorrow.
Ben Harrison, you're going to know exactly what it feels like to lose everything.