Sorry, that, that brand is not for sale.
You see? If we can't have it, neither can you.
Mr. Yates, yes, this is Laura Lewis.
I'm calling to discuss the sale of our high-end clothing brand, too.
To Shepherd Group.
Oh, come on.
Calling the Lewis family, but we won't get in anywhere, sweetie.
Exactly.
Come on, this is pathetic. You really think this is going to work? It's sad.
Excellent.
Thank you, Mr. Yates, that's all.
Yes?
What?
Are you willing to sum it to brand?
Awesome.
Thank you.
Hello?
Yes.
Wow, yes, of course.
Absolutely.
Mm-hmm, thank you.
The store, along with the entire brand, has been sold to Mr. Shepherd.
The Shepherd Group is the new owner.
How may I be upstairs today?
Well, Laura, I don't know much about fishing.
So, I would like to give you this brand to you.
You can't be serious.
You don't have the kind of money to buy this store.
Don't listen to her, Brian.
You, too, just go do whatever you do somewhere else.
You're not welcome here.
I want the two of these out of my store.