Well, well, well, look, I decided to join the party, playing dress up again Laura.
One more, there's a respectful remark towards Laura, Ms. Smith, and you understand the meaning
of rude.
You've threatened my girlfriend in front of everyone?
For this, Ms. Goldigger.
You know Ben, I really cared about you, even after all the horrible things you said to
me after our divorce.
I knew the name of a great psychologist in New York.
Maybe the shrinks and maple wood aren't equipped to deal with your issues.
Enough!
I've had enough of this drama.
Yeah, me too.
So I did again, and you regret it.
I'll get the hell out of my face.
Let's see if you two even make it past the door.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Ms. Smith, but your name's not only guest list.
What?
That's impossible.
I was invited by the CEO himself.