You okay Miss Duke?
And you are?
Amber Smith.
I'm the Maplewood branch manager of Lewis Group.
What branch? I've never heard of it.
What do you want from me?
That Laura!
She tore up my invitation.
Do you think you can get me inside?
What? Your little manager title couldn't get you past the front door?
Please don't waste my time.
If I can't have Brian, neither can you.
The Duke family has more influence than you think.
Chloe, good to see you. I've been expecting you.
Uncle Jones, how are you?
I need your help with something.
What is it?
Anything for my little Chloe?
It's Brian.
Who's that woman? I thought you were.
She's a con woman.
She actually used to be a cleaner in his company.
What?
Are you saying Brian left you for a cleaner?
She's pretending to be a Lewis to get close to him.
What are you planning?
I want to destroy Shepherd Group.