Seriously? Can't you even get this little thing done?
Sorry Vivian, I'm just tired from washing dishes a little bit.
Remember who got you this jaw, Frevisa? You'd be nothing without it.
Vivian, remember it was my mom who paid for both our tuition.
She wanted us to study together, and have you helped me find my dad and brother.
Please, your dad ditched you and your mom because of some foreign flanging.
Get over it! How could you say that we're family?
No, no, no. Who are Lawrence? We are not family.
Your birth mom is dead. It's my aunt who adopted you.
What? Right! You hit your head and can't even remember anything.
You don't even know your dad's name. You tried to find him with some necklace?
Idiot! God, whatever. Now get out. You're fired.