When's the old man come?
It's my take a while.
Where's our waiter?
Hey, can we get some drinks, please?
Thank you.
Cheers.
How long am I supposed to wait?
He texted he said he'd be here in just a little while.
Are you sure you don't want to let go get some rest first?
What was in that drink?
I'm... I'm burning up.
It's just something to help you relax, all right?
Look, you've not seen Miss Lauren in, like, ten years.
You were having any errors.
I'm moving, thought maybe it'd be a good idea for you to try a few other options, you know?
Like, another word, and you'll never speak again.
You're fucking hands off me.
I'm not waiting any longer.
I did no hookers.
I'm not a hooker.
You don't matter.