Ryan, stay focused.
I got a question to ask you.
Have you been intimate with any other women at this club?
Of course not.
Then just wait.
First time in investigation.
Liar.
You really think you've won over?
Don't Ryan prove it.
Strip her down.
Let's see how irresistible she really is.
Vivian, no, you'll pay for this.
No, stop.
Let me go.
What is this?
Babe, why don't you go take a walk?
As for her, this has to sickle from the red light district.
You're in my dark web.
I love a thing for pregnant women.
I'll handle this.
Oh, Vivian, we're family.
No, I'm not.
Maybe you should ask your missing dad and brother.
Or your mom up in heaven.
It's not Ryan.
I've just checked in with Miss Wilson.
She has not been with any other men.
See?
I told you she was a good kid.
Fine.
I will accept the child.
But this woman, there's no way in hell.
Ryan, don't be a fucking asshole.
You want our rightful heir to be a bastard child?
See?
I told you.
She just found out she's pregnant,
and she's already trying to cash in on the wish that I grant her.
Not Ryan.
She only withdrew two grand from your account.
What?