I need to find it.
Wait a minute.
Was it like special?
My mom, she gave it to me, said it was important, said that it would help me find another family.
Hey, hey.
I'll find it.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Look, at least you have a mom.
The Lord's in mind is, let's try and get some rest, okay?
I'll look into the necklace.
Welcome to the estate.
Oh my god.
This place is insane.
It's absolutely unreal.
The room is right here to the left.
This bedroom is bigger than my whole apartment.
All this has been prepared, especially for you, by Don Ryan.
This could last me the whole pregnancy.
Well, it's just a month.
He's also gotten you your personal nurse and a nutritionist.
They're going to customize your maternity plan.
You know, he's never brought home a woman before.
I'll show you to your room.
What's this?
I thought you might be hungry after work, made it myself, all natural ingredients.
Do the staff all quit or something?
Let me make something clear.
This estate has rules, whatever you're used to.
Things work differently here.
That's what we have kitchen staff for.
Are you serious?
Whatever.
This tastes exactly how low I used to make it.
She even used to put them in leave, just like that.
Electricity bill is too high.
It's high.
Why is it so hot in here, that the staff forget to turn on the AC?
This room is so big, it takes forever just to get to the bathroom.
What are you doing here?
This is my room.
You enjoying yourself?
I...not bad.
Are you done?
I know we've already umm...but...
Cut the crap.
This whole thing you planned this, didn't you?
What?
Plan this?
That's rich.
Look who's enjoying it now.
You can even see it through your towel.
Don't press your luck.
This relationship is purely financial for the baby's sake.
Nothing more.
You think I planned this pregnancy?
Who knows?
I want a DNA test.
You're doubting me.
I have no idea you were such an arrogant, self-righteous jerk.
If you have nothing to hide them, what's the problem?
You're the mother.
Yes.
I understand that.
How am I supposed to know that I'm the father?
You cost me my career.
And for what?
I'll just pretend that that night was a bad dream.
I don't expect anything else for me.
What do you think you're going?
I'm moving out.
I can raise this child on my own.
Stop right there.
Let go of me.
Why are you being so damn difficult?
Anyone would feel hurt because of some wild guess.
You're telling me you wouldn't feel angry if someone doubted your mother.
I'm sorry.
I was out of line.
The truth is, my mother and I went through the same exact thing.
I almost lost my adopted father because of those same doubts.
My sister, Laura, she was the one who convinced him to keep me.
Laura?
Sounds familiar.
I had hurts.
I'll stay at the lakeside apartment tonight.
You get some sleep here.
I had the staff turn the AC on.
You don't have to worry about utility bills anymore.
Not while you're with me.
And if you want to work, you can try our family jewelry studio.
I hear they're hiring.
Stop.
I found her.
Laura?
You were right.
Okay, where is she?
She's at the flea market right now, and she's selling the necklace.
Okay, that means that she's probably struggling.
Okay, take me to her now.
I hope that for the rest of my life, all I see is her smile.
Let's go now.
Your name is Vivian.
I used to go by Laura, originally from Lillira.
It was a gift from your father, wasn't it?
Who is she?
The necklace?
Damn it.
Did the witch read me out?
Yes, so what?
I'm Don Ryan.
Do you remember me?
Don't Ryan?
Ryan.
See, don't Ryan?
Yes, yes.
You remember me.
I'm your stepbrother.
Oh my goodness.
The most loaded mob boss in the city.
How did Lauren get mixed up with him?
Don't be afraid.
Your father and I have been looking for you forever.
Father?
Your birthfathered.
Don't you remember him?
Yes.
Of course, I just lost some memories after everything that
happened.
I understand.
That night, 10 years ago, when you saved my life,
you must have been through hell since then.
Come back to the estate with me.
Let me take care of you.
Or if you prefer your independence,
there's $5 million for a fresh start.
Oh, million?
Oh, this is amazing.
Oh, my God.
No.
Why don't you come back to the apartment and think it over
for a few days?
Yes.
I would love that.
I can't believe I found him.
So keep this going forever.
She seems different from how you described.
Maybe we should do a DNA test.
It's enough.
She's been through hell these past 10 years.
Can you imagine?
And also people can change.
Anyone would feel hurt because of some wild guess.
Just give her some time.
We'll figure out the past slowly.
Hello?
Fail cultural re-Italian, right?
Yeah.
It's all set.
They're expecting.
Got it done.
I'm right by the door.
Oh, willing.
Sure, Mrs. Don receives our finest services.
Mm-hmm.
With Mrs. Don on board, we're going to be the talk of the
town.
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm...
Please move.
This isn't some window shopping territory.
Mrs. Don is coming.
But I'm actually...
Oh, my God.
You must be this Don.
That design evive is unmistakable.
Please.
This way.
That's right.
I am Mrs. Don.
Whoa.
That's unfortunate.
This place is way out of your league.
I'm a jewelry designer, remember?
If it weren't for you, I would still have a job.
Back off, don't stung Mrs. Don's way.
Can I show you one of our latest pieces?
Seriously?
You have the wrong person.
I'm the one you should be meeting.
Please.
Mrs. Don knows quality.
Look at her with her limited edition.
Everything.
She's the real Mrs. Don.
Look at you.
Where'd you even get the money for all of this?
Like I need to explain myself to you.
How dare you speak to Mrs. Don that way?
Security?
Get this checked out of here.
If you're the real Mrs. Don, then prove it.
See this piece right here?
Let's see which one of us can actually drop the cash on it.
I can make the transfer right now.
Will that actually get me some service around here?
This one?
Please.
Give me some clearance merchandise.
Exactly.
Expecting VIP services for bargain bin prices dream on.
Every customer deserves a respect.
We don't judge by price tag here.
Is this how you treat our guests?
And who might you be?
Another one of her boy toys?
Still playing your little games with man, I see.
I tell you what.
My role is simple.
The highs better, gets the best service.
This is Tom Abbott, the jury tycoon and our boss.
So what?
Well, lady, this is a one of peace, expensive, yes, but unique.
You would suit perfectly your elegance.
I'll take it.
Will that finally get me some service?
I'll pay double.
You'll never get the upper hand, bitch.
This one is our showpiece, one of a kind.
This one's nice, too.
I'll take them all.
Double price.
You know what's final sale on all luxury items once they leave the counter?
Did you actually swipe your card for any of these?
And the total comes out to 2.8 million.
What?
You know what?
Hmm.
Nothing really catches my eye here, but congrats on your haul, though none of it really suits
you.
Well, bring the card reader for VIP guests.
You?
You haven't paid yet.
Back off, Miss Vivian.
May I have a word?
Wait, you know me?
No, it's been a while.
College was great that you didn't have forgotten me.
From college.
Tom Abbott.
Oh my god.
Hi.
I'll be looking for you.
Looking for me?
Why?
I just wanted to know how you were doing.
You know, he saw the show in there.
That's my cousin Vivian.
She'll do pretty much anything to ruin my life.
Although she is good for business.
You're right.
Well, we hit quite a sell because of you today.
According to the rules, you're up for 700k bonus.
Oh, you can keep it.
Give it to Vivian.
She's the one who made it happen anyways.
You played me.
Here.
That's more gifts.
What?
This is stunning.
The design is incredible.
I designed it myself.
I didn't even love it.
Wait, Tom.
I can't accept this.
Oh, come on.
You won't accept the bonus nowadays.
It's not even pressing.
It's just, I had a necklace that I lost recently.
An important one.
Then wear this until you find it.
Come on.
They'll tell me you don't like my design.
Let me help you.
What's going on?
I thought we were meeting Lauren.
I said drive.
No, I can do it myself.
Was that Ryan's car?
I wanted to ask him about the missing necklace.
I found what's going on.
I centered there to work.
I'll flirt with the owner.
Look, maybe there's just some kind of like missing
or standing or something like that.
All right.
I'm very busy.
There is a private jewelry salon tomorrow.
Top designers from all around the world.
It's exclusive, but I can make an exception for you.
Really?
This is a huge opportunity.
Let's see you tomorrow then.
You bitch.
You pushed me to this.
I won't let you win.
Come here.
I've been working on something for your family.
You enjoy yourself today?
It was fine.
Just a small hiccup.
I'd like to work there if they
replace that store manager.
It's a nice piece.
Is that the one you've been looking for?
Oh, this?
No, of course not.
The owner is actually my college classmate.
He designed it.
By the way, any news about my necklace?
Seems like you're enjoying that one plenty.
You sure you need another one?
What do you mean?
Small gift, big implications.
Seems like the manager isn't the only one
you're trying to replace.
He's just a college classmate.
And besides, his design inspired me.
Look, I just created this new crust for your family.
That's your business, not mine.
Just don't tarnish my family name.
Are you doubting me?
I've been faithful to this marriage.
I thought you'd trust me that much.
Trust comes with proof.
I trust what I see.
Fine.
Even if you don't trust me, trust the mother's heart.
For my baby, I'll be a good mother and wife.
Damn.
Is she saying this for the child?
Good.
And I'll do my part as a husband and a father.
But don't expect anything else.
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry about being a good father.
What?
Don, Miss Vivian is injured.
Call the family doctor.
I'll be there.
I'll be there right now.
Wait.
You said you'd look for my necklace.
I drew it here.
Can you just look on the way?
Some other time.
That hurts.
Oh, come on.
There are just scratches.
Nothing major.
I got shoved at a jewelry store.
She tried to grab everything I wanted.
Who did this?
Give me a name.
I forget it.
Can't exactly start a war with my cousin, can I?
Why would she do something like that?
Classical hurry, you know?
Hooks up with random guys.
Try to steal my necklace.
Maybe I should just stay away from her.
Maybe you should stick around and get me safe.
Come on.
You're free.
You're stressed like that.
I mean, I just feel like I'm losing my mind.
You know, I know Lord might be trouble,
but I just, I can't bring myself to do anything about it.
I even had the instinct that maybe Vivian
was already sold a necklace in the first place.
You're not losing your mind.
I was thinking the exact same thing.
And it has to help Vivian.
Once we know that she is my sister, for sure,
then I'll deal with Lord.
In the meantime, just keep an eye on my place
for advancing your jewelry salon tomorrow.
You would take Miss Vivian's mind out, thanks.
My mother's birthday is coming soon.
Can you help me find the perfect gift?
Women's perspective must be better than mine, I guess.
Of course.
This one is perfect.
It's classic, but still stylish.
And it's a beautiful mix of vintage and modern touches.
Exactly her style.
Wow.
After all these years, we still think I like.
I'll take it.
Mr. Tom Abbott, what an honor to have you here.
And you are?
An old college friend of mine.
Excellent jewelry designer, actually.
She will be joining my team very soon.
This is Cecile, the owner and the host of this whole designer
in the business.
You're the famous Cecile.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Well, just wait.
We have an even bigger surprise guest coming.
Go check if Don Ryan has arrived.
What are you doing here?
I see the two of you know each other.
Well, that's less work for me then.
I'll leave you to it.
Excuse me.
With him?
Seriously.
You know, I knew there was someone else, but Vivian?
Really?
No, she's not.
She's just mine.
You OK?
Yes, just dizzy.
Ryan, I left my nausea pills in the car.
Could you please grab them from me?
So really in there.
Here, let me help me clean up.
Don't touch me.
I can do it myself.
Bitch, I'll ruin you completely.
It's all for the baby.
Remember, who he's in love with isn't your business.
All right, are you OK?
Ryan, what are you doing?
She's my fiance.
You care to explain what your college friend is doing here
with you?
Is that all you want to talk about?
What night do you have to even question me?
What's that supposed to mean?
You have someone, and then you still come after me,
and then you want to question me, too.
You mean Vivian?
Lauren, she's my...
Miss Lauren, is this your purse?
Yes.
We found the stolen items inside.
You'll need to come with us.
What?
No, stop.
That's impossible.
Wait, wait, hold on.
No.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
Ryan, Ryan.
Vivian, Lauren's in trouble.
I need to go and save her.
Don't.
Trust me on this one.
No, my cousin, better than anyone else.
She's always had sticky fingers.
It's impossible.
She's been with me the entire time.
She couldn't have done this.
Let me handle this, okay?
Trust me.
Stay here.
I know how to fix this.
So I'm trying to listen to you, Vivian,
so you can just take her.
Mr. Abbott, this event is invitation only
for our most esteemed guests.
We never expected, look,
we have to take her to the police.
Don't make this any more difficult.
I didn't do any of that.
I didn't steal anything.
I haven't even seen whatever it is.
Look, I know her.
She wouldn't do this.
That must be a mistake.
Mine going easy on this one for my sake.
Lauren, you've been stealing since we were kids.
But here?
Really?
What are you talking about?
Ms. Vivian, you're really close with Don Ryan.
Do you have any suggestions?
Where is that DNA report?
Any minute and I'm done.
Five minutes.
I need those results.
Well, since you found the item,
let's handle this quietly.
I'll compensate for my dear cousin's mistake.
No police.
Better for anyone, isn't it?
Compensation?
Really?
You're making it seem like I actually stole it.
I didn't steal anything.
And I don't need your help.
Don't you self-lucky or things get much worse.
I'd rather face the police than accept your help.
Fine.
But that's your choice.
Remember, once in there, good luck getting out.
The four minutes gone.
Where is it?
I'll call them.
Hey, I need to know which one.
Which one is really my sister?
Take your hands on my fiancé now.
Look, I just got the DNA test results back.
This Vivian is Don Logan's flesh of blood.
Your stepsister.
That doesn't make any sense.
Vivian, what are you hiding?
Keep your nose out of it.
This is family business.
It's enough, Vivian.
This isn't the time or the place.
Who's that?
He stole it.
Find him now.
What?
I'd love to be with our baby.
They will.
Wild?
That she'd get everything.
Can you take care of her?
Back off.
Unless you want this getting ugly between our families.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I spoke with your doctor.
He said you're fine.
And the babies are as well.
But you need to rest, OK?
It can handle on me.
Doctor's orders.
This position, my body heat up against yours,
is the best way for you to relax.
Trust me, if it weren't for the babies,
you wouldn't be getting this special treatment.
Funny, come without a DNA test, you trust me.
Yeah, well, even you wouldn't lie to God
in a moment like that.
Who do you?
Vivian is my sister.
If you don't like her, that's fine.
But I need you to avoid her.
And quit picking fights with her.
You think I'm the one who started this?
I know that she hurt you.
And I know that she is a temper.
But she saved my life.
I owe her.
You'll see.
I'll prove to you the kind of person she will lose.
Champion rosewater.
How could you?
Great job by the jewelry show and the DNA swap.
Ryan trusts me completely now.
But we can't keep that bitch anymore.
If I can't get to Ryan, this little princess will have to do.
The real Dawn heiress, huh?
She's carrying his baby.
As long as she's around, we're at risk of exposure.
All right, so Dawn, it's Mrs. Abbott's birthday tomorrow evening.
You gonna be attending?
Of course.
She's got poor in politics.
I can't ignore that.
Besides, it's time for Vivian to start making the rounds anyway.
What about Mrs. Lauren?
Have something even bigger planned for her debut.