Mrs. Abbott, I had this blue diamond custom made for you.
It's one of a kind.
Only a woman of your refinement deserves such a piece.
You must be the Don Eris.
It's exquisite.
Thank you.
I love it.
And this lovely lady is your...
Mrs. Abbott, may I present you my fiancé?
Happy birthday, Mrs. Abbott.
I heard you have an appreciation for Eastern culture,
so I got you something special.
Wait.
Scrap is that.
How can you bring such a thing to Mrs. Abbott?
Vivian, mind your manners.
Yes.
Who even knows what this is?
A piece of paper?
Where's the penny?
Is this how you'd tip a beggar?
What could I even expect from you, Vivian?
You don't read any books, nor do you have any taste.
Now, let go.
You better let go.
Get your grabby hands away from me.
I mean, work.
The cultural arts master.
It's no money can buy such a piece.
Truly thankful.
I couldn't ask for a better gift.