Vivian, we need to talk.
What is it?
You care to explain what happened the other day?
What do you want to hear?
I don't understand.
Why frame Lawrence?
And who is the guy?
You know why?
I love you.
And I know you love me too.
Jesus Christ, Vivian, for God's sakes,
you're like a sister to me, nothing more.
Yes, I am grateful that you saved my life all those years ago.
I will forever be grateful for that.
But you've got to stop this, okay?
You have to.
It is because of her, isn't it?
No, this has nothing to do with Lawrence.
This has everything to do with your attitude.
And I'm sorry, but you just can't stay here.
It is her.
I will never forgive that bitch.
Enough!
Damn it!
What?
Don't.
The man with Vivian was Jacob.
But he's gone underground.
You're kidding me.
Okay, well don't say anything to Vivian.
Bring him to me.
I want answers personally.