Come on, come on, stop it!
You're not welcome here.
Will I hate you too hard?
Don't forget, I will stay here too.
Fine, I'm pulling out.
My family is done with you.
Lauren, I have another student near my place.
If you want to work there or leave there, just say the word and you have the job.
You don't get to make decisions for my fiance.
She's carrying my child.
And the dawns is in some company that needs saving.
So now is your child, huh?
I thought you had some doubts about that.
You know what?
I don't care.
As long as it's Lauren's child.
No DNA test, no questioning.
Ryan, please.
You know there's nothing left between us.
Just let me go.
Okay?
Don't push me.
I won't push you.
But don't forget, Lauren.
You're the one who promised to stick around for the baby's sake.
I won't be there for my child.
But I'm done.
Being your trophy wife.
I meant what I said in there.
Let me take care of both of you.
I'm not like him.
Let me help.