No, Tom. I can't.
I'm sorry. You've been so good to me.
It's all right. I get it. It's hard I didn't go.
What is it?
We've got a situation at the studio.
Okay, what happened?
Client files that Mrs. Dom was in charge with have been leaked. They're lawyering up.
Okay, where is Laura? Is she okay?
She went down there to handle herself and they were just there.
Why would she go down there by herself?
Okay. I'll wait to bring the car around.
I'm all in her faces on her own.
You know the Don name used to mean something.
And now look, all my private information's all over the market.
What are you gonna do to fix this, huh?
I swear I kept everything locked up.
I don't know how it got swapped out.
I promise.
However you want to handle this, I'll cooperate.
I'm filing a lawsuit.
Now what the entire Don Brand blacklisted.
You understand?
Please, just, it's my fault. I'll take responsibility.
No, this is my family's business. I'll take full responsibility.