getting knocked up out of footlock, and you don't even know who the father is, do you?
I...
I don't know.
Really, you don't know?
No, the Walton family will not allow tramps like you to undermine our family.
You pack up your things and leave.
Wait.
Before you go, I need to make sure you haven't taken anything that's not yours.
After all, you were never Walton in the first place.
I knew you still had feelings for Alex.
Bitch, stay away from my fiance!
If I want to raise this child, there's no way I can stay in school.
Maybe it's time to get a job and prepare for my new life.
This is definitely the school.
Have you checked all the records?
Yes, but we don't have enough information to narrow it down.
She's gotta be here somewhere.