My dear boy, are you still working?
Oh my, this girl is lovely.
What's your name?
Hello, madam, my name is Emily Wilson.
Oh, Wilson?
That's had a good friend who was a Wilson.
How long have you been with my Henry?
Oh, uh, Mr. Anderson and I aren't together.
Nana, why didn't you come here today?
Of course, I came to check if you're having lunch on time.
Samuel told Mayor often too busy to eat.
That's why I keep telling you to hurry up and find a wife
who can help take care of you.
Samuel is resistant after all.
You can't bother him with everything.
Unless Henry
tells me to like Samuel.
You into men?
Nana, it is not like that.
Well, no matter what I think,
you should be the best.
Emily and I are actually seeing each other.
Really?
Help me with this and I will help you out with your job.
Yes, Mr. Anderson and I are actually dating.
Perfect.
Weren't you always looking for that mystery girl all these years?
Be able to let her go.
That is different.
If I find her, I will make things right and take care of it.
Make up for what happened.
At least what I think happened.
All right, all right.
You're made up your mind.
We'll bother you too.
Emily, next time come to my home.
So about my job?
You know, I think I have a different job.
I mind for you.
I'm gonna drop a contract.
Bontract girlfriend?