and I'm nervous why you've met my grandmother before she loves you it's it's
gonna be okay oh grandma I brought him only family you look so beautiful today
thank you come sit with me how about we cut the cake first yeah okay
happy birthday what you tell me cut the cake okay this is Anderson why don't you
have the first slice right but I can't eat too much and I need to go to bed
early you young folks enjoy yourself now me have you two settled down yet yeah
good to hear you know when you are a little one my best friend used to tease
me about you hitching up with her granddaughter I figured if you hadn't met
Emily yet it might be a good opportunity to arrange a meeting between the two of
you and who is she grandma