Alex, darling. You've been working so hard. Why don't you just take a drink?
You don't need to do this anymore.
What?
This whole housewife routine. I don't need you bringing me drinks anymore.
How about one more for all time sakes?
This tastes funny. Do you do to me?
You brought this upon yourself, Alex.
If I can't have you, I will destroy you.
You are mine. Always have been, always will be.
Henry. You've gathered all the information on Sophia.
Go on.
Sophia was originally born into the Walton family, but she was switched at birth and they did not discover the error until she was 16.
She went by the name Wilson.
The original Wilson daughter, the one that Sophia was switched with, was named Emily.
The Waltons adopted Emily and intended to raise the two girls together, but eventually for some reason she was kicked out of the house.
If Emily was originally a Walton then, was there a chance she was that woman from seven years ago?
She was expelled from the family house around the same time, but it's unlikely that she would have been at the event.
Understood. I need you to keep investigating the Waltons and her old school.
We have to find this woman from seven years ago.
Sure.