Thank you for helping me out back there.
I meant every word that I said.
You become a member of the Anderson family.
They won't dare mess with you again.
Henry, there's something I haven't told you yet.
Seven years ago, there was an accident and I got pregnant.
When Jack was three, he developed leukemia
and there's a chance of a relapse now.
I need to find his father for treatment.
I think Sophia might have something to do with it
and that's why I went to her wedding.
I'm still looking for Jack's father.
So, Sophia is behind all of this?
Not entirely sure.
Thank you. I'm sharing that.
I'm still going to help you find Jack's father.
I hope.
Yes, they know.
Henry, we found the girl from seven years ago.
I'll be right there.
Sorry.