Samuel where is she in a small town outside of Santa Barbara? Okay, a range of meeting
I'll meet with her and I will make sure she's properly compensated. Mr. Anderson
I'm afraid things might not be how you imagine. What do you mean?
After that night she was kicked out of her house and
when we went to the school she had just dropped out
Later on she tried to commit suicide. Is she even alive? Yes, but as a single mother
with no qualifications she's very limited on what she can do. What do you want to do?
Why are there no photos? Her identity had to have been intentionally hidden.
It's just going to take a bit more time. All right, work on this quickly. Thank you.
I have to talk to Emily. Hey, how was work? It was fine. Emily, I love you.
What's going on? We have to break up. What?