What?
I'm sorry, but we have to break up.
I don't understand.
What?
Is there something you're not telling me?
A long time ago, I hurt a very good girl.
She was forced to become a single mother because of me.
You say that so carelessly.
Do you understand how hard it is to be a single mom?
I know.
And I have been searching for her to try and make amends and I just recently found out
that she's been living a very difficult life.
So I need to go to her and take responsibility for her and my child.
You should have done that a long time ago, Henry.
I know.
I'm still going to compensate you for everything that you've done far beyond what the contract
says.
Don't bother.
We'll just break up.
Jack and I will move out tomorrow morning.
No wait, Emily.
I still want to help you find Jack's father.
Why couldn't it have been you seven years ago?