Who gave you this ring?
Someone who hurt me, a long time ago.
Who was that person, Jack's father?
Yes. Why do you care?
You must really hate him, don't you?
Shouldn't I hate someone that changed my life forever?
Yeah. You should.
What do you want, Henry?
I have an idea. You can clear your name with the press.
And maybe find Jack's father, too.
Henry, I'm nervous.
It's okay. I'm here for you in every way.
You trust me?
Mr. Anderson, everyone's here. It's almost time.
You got this.
Good afternoon, everyone.
I would like to address the rumors about me and give a formal explanation.
Do we really have to do this?
She's being brave by stepping up and explaining.
Plus, I can't let her do this alone.
First of all, the photos that were taken were digitally manipulated.
As you can see, here and here, they're fakes.
As for the child, yes, I do have a son.
And I love him very much.
And the father, the father, I don't know, back then, I...
Who do you think you are, you shameless hag, dreaming of Mr. Anderson? You...
Henry!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Anderson. I...
Are you kidding?
As for the child, I would like to offer an explanation.
Seven years ago, Emily became pregnant.
And she was alone, and had to deal with that darkness herself.
And now today, she's still dealing with baseless accusations from you all.
Once I realized my mistake, I wanted to make a mess.
So seven years ago, I was the one...
I was the one that left you to be alone.
And I want to make up for that.
Emily, apologize, and can you ever forgive me?
Henry, don't have to lie for me.
Emily Wilson, will you marry me?
What's going on here?
Alex is done with you?
These are your things.
He doesn't want to see you around anymore.
I'm pregnant with this child.
Can I just tell them to deal with the Anderson's?
How would he treat me like this?
Where is he?
Miss Walton, please. He doesn't want to see you.
He did.
She went to go find Emily, didn't he?
Doesn't he know she's about to get married?
Look, she won't get away with this.
Emily!
Emily, you're here.
So, would you want to tell me?
Isn't it you who asked me to come here?
Sophia said you wanted to see me.
She did.
Sophia, what are you doing?
Just clearing the obstacles between us.
Emily, come here to wake up.
What is this about? Are you insane?
You think you two can create something new together?
What did you do?
I added a little something to your drink again.
Alex, you know you're so naive.
Henry's going to kill you.
You're going down.
Samuel, we've got to go.
Oh, it's me.
Oh, I can't move.
Emily.
No, it's fine.
Henry, you have to believe me. I didn't.
Samuel, get the paparazzi out of here.
I don't want to hear a word about this in the press.
Come on, Emily.
Say that one.
Say that.
Henry, I'm okay.
Does anywhere else hurt?
I think we should go to the hospital.
No, it's nothing, really.
That's not nothing. We should get that looked at.
Will this incident affect you and your business?
Don't worry about that. Let me handle everything.
Okay. We got you.
Do I know you?
I'm Patricia Anderson.
I'm also the main shareholder of Anderson Imperial Hotel
in case the name didn't make it clear for you.
So spit it out.
How much money do you want to leave Henry?
No, Auntie, it's not like that.
Don't call me Auntie.
You're not married into the Anderson family yet.
Do you even realize how much Henry has lost because of you?
You can't even imagine.
So, you don't want money?
Didn't make this perfectly clear for you.
Get out of LA with your illegitimate child as soon as possible.
I'm not leaving unless Henry tells me to.
I made a promise to stay by his side and I intend to keep it.
Do you know how pathetic Henry looked at today's board meeting?
He almost passed out at our stock top 20%.
Is he okay?
No. What help can you offer him?
Except to bring him down.
Bitch. Stay away from Anderson's.
Let's go.
There's our Uber. Ready?
Samuel, I need you to keep an eye on Sophia.
Copy.
Make sure that Emily and Jack are safe.
Got it.
Henry, you need to take care of yourself too.
You look like you were about to pass out this morning in the meeting.
Henry, what?
It's Emily and Jack.
Something happened.
They didn't make it.
Mmm.
Oh, that feels so good, honey.
You know how I like it.
Mmm.
Patricia, I need to talk to you.
What did you do to Emily?
She decided to leave on her own.
I didn't pressure her.
And if you use your dividends from the Anderson group,
what's going to happen to you and your little boyfriend?
I didn't do anything.
It was that girl from the Waltons who told me.
I just wanted Emily to leave you for the family's sake.
Everything else is not my concern.
Come, Sven.
Samuel, it's time to release all the information we have on Sophia.
Get it done.
Forgive me for not saying goodbye,
but I've been thinking a lot and I feel this might be for the best.
In the time we've spent together,
I've seen how much pressure you bear from everyone in your life.
I feel helpless when I see you face all that pressure alone.
And it hurts me even more when I realize I'm just a burden to you.
I'm deeply grateful for all that you've done for me and Jack.
But I just can't stand watching you suffer because of someone you owe nothing to.
I'm going to look for a new life in a different city.
I must have been crazy thinking I could track down Jack's real father in the first place.
So farewell for now.
And hopefully when you see me again,
I'll be the real brave Emily, just like you said.
What?
Still alive?
You piece of crap.
Fine.
Figure it out yourselves.
Sophia, your next gig just got cancelled.
This is up for me.
I'm Sophia Walton.
How dare they cancel.
Mr. Anderson arranged a public smear campaign against you.
None of the studios will take you now.
Look, here are some of the recent comments about you online.
Accusing you of bullying other actors on set and even tax evasion.
About two thirds of your fans have unfollowed you.
For David!
Sophia, the baby!
Yes.
Yes, I'm pregnant.
No, Alex, he won't abandon me.
Alex, darling, they're spreading all these lies about me online.
Did you kill Emily?
Don't be silly.
Okay.
And now that Emily's gone, we can have a family and be together.
Okay?
Just forget about her.
I will investigate Emily's disappearance.
If I find out you did it, I will ruin you.
Remember that one night?
We were so happy.
Sick.
What did you do to the baby?
You made me do it.
Guess what?
Emily is not actually dead.
Where is she?
I will never tell you.
You will never see her again.
At least not in this life.
You're our hero, Bill.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome, Emily.
I still remember how generous you were to me all those years ago.
I wouldn't do I am today without you.
So, everything set in Miami.
Just relax and have a good trip.
Thank you.
Be careful.
The car you're back to get into has been following you for a while.
You're probably trying to kidnap the boy.
Bill?
Is that you?
Yes, Miss Emily.
It's me.
If Sophia doesn't succeed, she's not going to stop.
Get in.
Don't worry about Sophia.
I'll take care of her while you're safe and get away.
Please.
Take care of yourself and try.
We will.
Be mommy.
Be a stranger.
Will we ever see Uncle Henry again?
We will.
Not for a while.
And we've got everyone looking, so have a new soon.
Okay.
Oh.
One more thing.
Sophia's outside, demanding to come in.
Get her out of here.
Hey, get out.
I know where Emily is.
I'm listening.
I want $5 million.
Okay, let's go.
I can make her come willingly.
Hold it.
But you can't know where she is.
Henry, we can't trust her.
I can't afford to lose Emily and Jack.
Then pay me.
And you'll be able to see them both.
And how can I trust you?
Unless you got any other ideas, I think I'm your best choice.
Fine.
$5 million when you bring her here.
No way.
And how else are you going to get that kind of money?
Three days from now, at my house.
I'll let you know what time.
I need you to show up.
This time, I will pay you ten times I did.
Seven years ago.
You're finally here.
Been waiting a long time.
Where is he?
Emily, I can't figure out how Henry treats you so well.
Why are you still hung up on some mystery guy?
It's none of your business, Sophia.
You grew up in this huge house.
My house.
Do you have any idea how jealous I am of you?
And Alex still can't get you out of his head.
Do you understand how hard I worked for him?
I learned music, fashion, how to be gentle.
Then finally he came to me.
Do you really love Alex?
Or is this all just a game to you, Sophia?
I love him.
Then why do you keep bringing me into it?
Well, I still hate you.
I hate that you stole my life.
I hate that you took Alex from me.
So, seven years ago, I decided to win your life.
That night, did you enjoy yourself?
So was you.
All those years ago, it was you behind that night.
Either way, I'm not letting you go again.
Come on out.
Well, well, look who it is, the man from seven years ago.
What are you up to, Sophia?
Oh, I know you've been dying to see him.
Isn't this what you wanted?
Do we live that one night?
You're insane.
Either way, I'm not letting you go.
Not again this time.
You really don't remember me, do you think?
Let me go.
Trying to escape, huh?
I'm doing this for you.
This is who you've been looking for for the past seven years.
What's this?
Aren't you afraid of what I think when he finds out about this?
Alex doesn't care about you.
Alex never liked you.
He wouldn't marry you, Woody.
You will never be me.
I don't see her, Henry.
She must be inside already.
Okay, notify everybody immediately.
Keep it on the exits.
Here's Emily.
She's inside.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
We can be together.
Seven years ago.
Wasn't you the one from seven years ago?
Seven years ago?
She told me to go to that party.
She told me to find you and drug you and bring you up to the attic.
She wanted me to rape you.
I brought you up to the attic, but I couldn't fall through with her commands.
Because you resisted.
And then Prince Charming here, he showed up.
And he saw what happened.
And he saved the day.
And he actually did for me.
Because once I kicked his ass, then I drove him and brought him up to the attic.
And once the love drug took its effect, I knew that his confused mind would do the rest of the job for me.
So, if it wasn't even...
It was...
Yes.
Just a scratch.
No, it's not.
We should go to the hospital.
Emily, I'm so glad that you're finally here.
And they were back to dinner.
Here is Sophia's statement.
Emily went to Sophia because of the man from seven years ago.
Yes.
And it's all my fault.
And I failed the protector.
Henry, I suggest that you tell her the truth.
Brought you an apple.
Thanks.
So, what's going on with Sophia's case?
Sophia's been arrested.
Court date's been set.
What about the man that was with her?
He was injured.
He was in the hospital.
Which hospital?
This one.
Do you know the room number?
503.
What do you care?
I just...
I need to ask him something.
I just need a lock of hair.
A surprise.
You scared me.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing here?
I'm the person you're looking for.
What do you mean?
Only from seven years ago.
The man you spent that night with.
Asshole!
Do you know how hard that seven years has been for me?
For Jack?
Look, it was all my fault.
You and Jack have had to endure so much, and I apologize for all of it.
You could hit me if it helps, okay?
Are you okay?
It's just hit the wind.
How long have you known that it's me?
I've been searching for a while, but once I found the ring at your place, I knew it was you.
Is that why you asked me to stay?
No.
I did that because I'd love it here.
I only asked you to stay because of who you are.
I am so lucky to have found you after all of these years.
And I will work every day to make up for you.
In the night week, please.
No, Henry.
This is... this is a lot.
I understand.
I need someone who's going to be there for me, Henry.
For Jack.
And not leave us.
There's no one I'd rather have.
Than you.
Will you spend the rest of your life with me?
Henry Anderson.