Mary? You want me to get married? I did not come back to America for this.
Selena, this isn't just anybody that you would be marrying. It's Nick Branson. He's a billionaire.
So are you? Isn't that enough? I am not some piece of property that you can just sell, dad. Absolutely not.
Well, that's too late. Too late?
He's your fiancé. My what? Indeed, I've already arranged it.
I feel like in America I have never even seen. Dad, I just graduated. I need the free to pursue my dreams of becoming a fashion designer.
You can do that. What do you mean? I've given this much thought.
It's a contract. Nick Branson owns JS Jewelry. Under the contract, you will work there as an intern designer, remaining as his fiancé.
And after three months, you're free to do as you wish. JS Jewelry, the high-end fashion brand, doesn't get much better than JS Jewelry.
And if I wish to not marry him? As long as you complete the three months. Deal.
But under one condition, I need to develop my career base on my talent, not my name.
So, I want to keep my identity a secret. I don't want anyone knowing that I'm Selena Murphy.
Instead, I will go by. Selena Collins.