Are you serious?
George Murphy's daughter will be our new intern?
Okay, goodbye.
Did I hear that right?
The billionaire George Murphy?
Yes.
God damn it.
Oh, the Murphy era is working for us.
That's crazy.
I don't get it.
What would a billionaire's daughter intern here?
That's why we're so upset.
Isn't that a good thing?
You dumb bimbo.
She's the CEO's fiance.
Oh shit.
That means our CEO is going to know everything
about what's happening in our department.
What are we going to do?
Treat her like a queen, you fool.
I wouldn't be surprised if the CEO is sending her here
to spy on us.
You know it could be a good thing.
You make a good impression on her.
She could promote you.
At least one of you is thinking.
Quick, get me her name.
Now, HR didn't specify any names.
It just says that we have two new interns here today,
meaning one of them must be Ms. Murphy.
So too, HR.
What are you two still sitting there for?
We have to go pick her up.
Oh, he's that hurt.
Are you stupid, Emma?
What kind of billionaire daughter
would be driving a shitty car like that?
That's funny.