Actually, not really.
I have one.
You what?
What did you steal this, you little thief?
I guess I'll see you there.
Whatever.
They probably won't let you in anyways.
Girls?
Invitation time?
Wait.
That doesn't make sense.
What doesn't make sense?
If you're really a billionaire's daughter,
why would you need an invitation?
Shouldn't you be drowning in invites like that?
You should be swimming in invites like these, right?
Actually, that's a good point.
Would you mind if I keep this one?
I have a friend who might want to go.
Sure.
I actually can't even make it.
I have another amount of time.
Are you sure?
Or is that because you actually don't have an invite?