Hello, I'm here, sweetie. Yeah, well, are you gonna get me an invite or not?
Well, those are a little hard to come by and you know, they don't give us security guards to take us to the events
It's not a ticket. It's an invite and I don't care how you get it, but you will get me one
Oh, and make sure it's a VIP
invite
Sweetie. Hello
We have exactly two hours to get ready for the gala
Wait, who took my invitation?
Wow, is she really doing this? Mm-hmm girls. I think she's accusing us of stealing. Oh
Does that mean that our pro and turn won't be able to join us at the gala sure? Absolutely now. We'll make sure to send you photos
Let's go
Miss Murphy. Here you go this week's event invitations. Thank you. Here we go