These two are with me.
Oh man.
I can't let you enter through here.
This is the VIP entrance only.
And I'm VIP.
Invitation is not a VIP invite.
What?
Oh.
How could you do this to me dad?
I told you VIP.
Sorry.
You can exit right here and you'll see it.
It's a very long line.
You can't miss it.
So you and your friends can enter over there.
I'm Grace Murphy.
Do you know who I am?
I don't care who you are.
You can't come through.
How does territory just daughter?
Does nobody have papers?
I don't remember something.
It's not a hat or a hat.
What's this chicken head doing in the VIP line?
Step aside ladies.
Step aside.
Welcome in.
Right this way.
I wonder who should sleep with to get that invite.
Excuse me sir.
Her invitation is a fake.
I need you guys to move along.
Okay.
I already told you your entrance is over there.