What's this? This is dad's life savings. All of it. He told me that if you can't
let him go, then we have to help you, your family. Are you serious? Very serious.
I'm a dad who's hosting a fundraiser for Leo. Come home. We miss you. That's amazing.
I'll come home right away and let you down. I appreciate you. You're still doing this for me.
I love you. I've got to make this so guilty. My sweet Athena. How are you? Don't feel guilty.
You've already worked too hard to challenge a deep love and commitment to Leo. How can we possibly ignore you?
Oh my precious angel. Don't say that. We're a family.
They're actually came back. She's nothing but a beggar.
Nina. She's a member of our family and she's going through a tough time. But we should be there for her.
Oh, dang yo, stop it. We're about to get married. You don't have the money to waste on others. Save the pity.
Don't cry my daughter. Kevin and the others will be here soon. We'll be able to eat crazy before money.
Jesus, what is this? Like some kind of homeless shelter? Ugh. Smells as bad as old Mrs. Brown's famous liver recipe.