Yeah, this is a lovely young lady I saw at the coffee shop the other day. I haven't stopped thinking about you since
Joseph, is it?
Thank you for the compliment, but as you can see I have a boyfriend.
Devina, my new manners, Joseph's father, is the deputy manager for the storm group of Memphis.
Why, Joseph himself is ahead of an apartment. You show him some damn respect.
That's right. Having Joseph's attention is an honor.
Wisely, I have no one's plaything, and I'm not just gonna go off with the highest bidder. What an idiot!
What? It means the truth. What she said is both funny and immature?
Devina, you are dumber than you look. Did I hear you apply for the Thorne Medical Charity Program?
Let me be the first to say here. You're not gonna get the result you want. Yeah?
What do you want? I want you to come with me, and I'll help you with your little application.
Otherwise, say goodbye to this veggie on wheels.
What gives you the right to mess with matters of life and death?
Because I get what I want, and what I want is for you to come with me.
Now, no!