Do you have any idea what you're saying?
We're going to kill you.
Kill me.
Are you off your meds?
You really think working for the thorn group is that impressive.
My background is way more impressive than that.
Yeah.
You piece of shit.
Like the thorn group would have anything to do with trash like you.
I'm going to count to three if you don't get your little ass over here and kneel in
front of me and Divina and apologize.
I'll send you to hell.
Three.
So you can't talk to me.
You can't talk to me like that.
You piece of shit.
Guys, gifts are ready.
Good.
Mr. Leo is back.
He met an angelic girl who took care of him all these years.
Let's go welcome them back.
Ma'am, Jack Dyson has already gone to welcome Leo.
It'll take about an hour to get to his address.
I'll tell the driver to take the thorn express highway.
I need to be there in 30 minutes.
Jack Ma'am.
Homie, you still got some fight left, huh?
Fuck it.
I got no use for you.
Wait!
Look, we're such an idiot.
It's an honor to be with Mr. Josa.
Why do you have to bring everyone down for your useless boyfriend?
Go with Mr. Josa.
No.
It's like going to be him.
Is it me?
I'm going to excuse him.
Is his dead dog over me?
I'm going to take your girl right in front of you.
What?
No, he won't touch me.
Listen up, shitface.
Touch her again and you'll regret everything.
What the fuck do you think you are?
My father is the manager at the thorn group.
You're going to wish you were still in that coma.
I'm your deputy manager.
You think that's impressive?
What I think is you keep talking shit and you're going to find my foot up your ass.
Kiss my ass to fucking arrogant freak.
Say it again.
Say it again!
You cripple after I take your girl and blow your fucking head off.
Who's header you planning to blow off?
Stay nice.
Head of the Memphis stone group.
I'm a person.
The ear.
Jack Dyson?
Mr. Jack.
May I bring number?
No.
Mr. Dyson.
A long time no see.
What's the occasion?
Mom?
Dad?
What are you doing here?
Well, we came with Mr. Dyson to welcome the heir of the thorn group.
Why you here?
The heir of the thorn group.
There's no pawns here.
This is just me.
Look at these leaves and this broke back loser in the chair.
Mr.
Leo.
Sir, you know him?
He does not deserve your attention.
Respect me.
Shut up Joseph.
I did not expect you to get in such trouble.
Ok.
I'm long in trouble.
Ma'am.
Sir.
I am very sorry.
Sir, why are you bound to him?
Mr. Dyson.
Bailey's are all fools.
That man in the wheelchair.
There's nothing but a crippled beggar with only a court to his name.
You must have the wrong person.
Yeah, he's right boss.
These nasty people don't deserve your respect.
If they're nasty people, what does that make you?
A dirty piece of shit?
Boss?
As general manager of the Memphis thorn group, I offer my sincerest blessings to Mr. Leo.
The esteemed heir of the thorn group.
Welcome home Mr. Leo.
Kevin?
Did I hear that right?
That's the heir in the thorn group.
This will ripple Leo.
What?
Jim?
I'm having a nightmare.
This?
The heir in the thorn group?
This guy?
Shut up Joseph.
You have seriously messed up.
No.
No way.
Mr. Vina, I am such an idiot for declining your application.
I feel ashamed of my arrogance and foolish ignorance.
Please forgive me.
I'm not sure I understand what's actually going on.
Leo, are you the heir?
I know I should have told you sooner, but I just didn't want to scare you away.
This is crazy.
Leo, Dabina has done so much for you.
You have to cherish her.
Of course Daniel and Bill, you have my work.
And you and the important.
And everyone here who has helped take care of me.
I will make sure that your lives are easy and that you have everything that you want in the world.
Especially.
Now Jack, I don't imagine you came here empty-handed.
Show them the gifts.
Yes sir.
A gold mine in South Africa with gold reserves of two million ounces.
The value of assessment?
Over five billion.
Now we present it to the dear Mr. Vina.
Jesus, billion dollar gold mine.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I understand.
That's the line from Lucinda.
I don't say anything.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen, no need to make a fuss.
These are just small tokens of sincerity from the Thorne Group.
There are many more gifts to come.
Is that the legendary?
The Musaev Red Diamond.
And Patek Philip Ladies Watch.
Master Kelly designed and forged it with great care.
It is a symbol of status.
A one-of-a-kind gift we present to Mr. Vina.
Noah!
Vina get that!
The Red Diamond.
It's the Red Diamond.
Oh my God!
No, Chris!
Don't do this!
Do you like these gifts, Devina?
These are far too expensive.
Leo, we understand your intentions, but these gifts are way too expensive.
We can't accept them.
Don't worry about it.
Nothing in this world is more valuable to me than Devina here.
You waking up is the only gift I need.
I'm not wrong.
This isn't the heir.
This isn't the fucking heir.
I'm right.
Get him.
You heard the man?
Get him!
Oh no!
No!
Mr. Leo.
No.
Listen to me.
It's too late to apologize now.
Go to hell.
No!
To Leo.
Mr. Leo.
Wait!
Joseph didn't mean he didn't mean to offend you.
No, he's a hardworking kid.
You know, he's got a bright future ahead of him.
Please, please, please.
He needs this job to make a living, okay?
Please, just don't take his whole life away for one stupid little mistake.
Yes, Mr. Leo.
I beg you.
Please, forgive Joseph this one time.
He was just trying to teach some poor people a lesson.
He's never really made any mistakes before.
A lesson.
So for you people, making fun of the poor is just trivial.
Yes.
And what's wrong with that?
Those filthy beggars are just like rats.
Millions are born and die every day.
The desert was simply speeding up the masses.
Is that what you think?
What you're saying is completely outrageous.
David is right.
You people make me sick!
Jack, get rid of these scumbacks!
Get him!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
He's my son.
I can't let you take him.
Come on.
Mr. Leo can't we discuss this further?
Any terms?
Really.
So you're trying to negotiate with...
Fine.
You're gonna make me do this.
Call Drew.
Laura, call Drew.
You know Drew?
He's the senior commander of the Brandore Security Force.
Yeah, so, Mr. Leo, since you're so incredibly heartless,
you can take my family off of the Thorne group.
Alright?
And wait for Drew to find you.
Because he will.
Wait for Drew.
Mr. Brandore.
Leo has been missing for three years, but now he's returned home.
And he's a real man.
And now, I can finally make the announcement proudly to the medium.
That Leo is my son.
Air.
To the Brandore family.
God bless Brandore!
Move on.
It's time to welcome the pride of Brandore.
Excuse me, Mr. Brandore, I gotta take this call.
What food I hell would dare disrespect you and Joseph.
I'm gonna teach him a lesson that he ain't never gonna forget.
Conveniently, there's a mercenary from one of my teens.
You just hang tight.
He's on his way.
Brandore Security Contractors, the largest mercenary company in the entire world.
They're made of legendary.
Brandore mercenaries?
It's been said they are stronger than the Army.
They even have fighter jets and warships.
That's right.
My brother Drew is not some small man that the phone group can mess with.
He's a giant.
It's been something to help this yet.
The Thor and Air has nothing on these mercenaries assault rifles.
Make your stupid sister apologize to Mr. Joseph.
The Brandore group.
We didn't know what that means.
They could kill all of us.
Nina, just be quiet for a moment.
Why?
I am tired of having this fool drag me down.
Hey you, you and your man better go with Mr. Joseph.
And not drag us into it.
Yeah, Nina, it's right.
The Brandore group is mysterious and powerful.
Then we use mercenaries.
Nina, there's no need to worry.
Because they are the ones that should be afraid.
Is this fake tough guy still pretending to be the Thor and Air?
No, what am I going to do? I'm so scared.
Fuck you. Listen to me.
I'm going to take good people right now and there's nothing you can do about it.
And thank me later. I'll take good care of her.
Nothing.
Jack.
Teach him a lesson, help him learn this.
You're so fucking scared.
Mr. Dyson.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Drew is on his way right now.
If you touch me, you'll be the first to die.
Jack Dyson, you got mad?
I'm going to tell Drew about this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's going to teach you a lesson.
Drew Aiken?
He's just a watchdog.
Did you just call my boss a watchdog?
You crazy son of a bitch.
It's Henry.
From Drew's team.
I happen to be in the area on a mission.
And Captain sent me to help you deal with some trouble.
Well, that's them.
They're the ones that cause so much trouble.
Disrespected our leader.
No, no, don't shoot.
No, please don't shoot.
To beat up, Theo is the heir to the Thorne group.
And you can't hurt him.
And it's...
The regular mercenary doesn't give a shit about the Thorne group.
Say one more word.
And I'll send you to Africa to dig mine.
I don't know what to be, and I don't.
Here, I don't want to put you in harm's way.
Hey, I can't just sit here and watch you sit in danger.
It's okay, sweetheart.
It's okay.
And you...
No matter how strong or tough your team is,
you have to respect your elders.
Idiots!
Do you know who our boss is?
The Brindor group?
What connection could you possibly have with the Brindor group?
Shut up or I'll execute you right now.
Alright, let me explain.
Do you have any idea who Mr. Leo's father is?
He's a beggar, and his father's the beggar too.
Don't waste my time.
What are you looking at?
Do you want to die?
You pimp, or doomed you idiots.
Do you have any idea how powerful Mr. Leo's connections are,
or how important his background is?
Is the heir to the Thorne group important?
To me, you're just a piece of trash.
Joseph, how you want me to deal with these fools?
It's up to you.
I say, I take his girl right in front of him.
So that's the last thing he sees before I kill him.
It sounds fun.
You can't do that.
Oh dare you don't, sure.
Yeah, where do you die?
Go for it.
We'll shut him up for good.
You were so cold in here earlier.
How are you going to make it up to her?
No, stop! Don't touch me!
Your hands off her.
You're going to be a dead man!
What are you going to do?
Come on, Divina.
Let this cripple watch me take you.
Do you know who this woman is?
She is calling your boss.
I'm asking those wife's.
Make way for Mrs. Cynthia.
Make way!
Second Commander.
My apologies.
Miracle.
What a wonderful show of God's grace.
Leo.
Your legs.
Bullshit.
Still putting on a brave face?
Who can you protect?
Damn it.
Oh my fucking kill you.
Don't you dare hurt him.
I can't believe it my child.
You're in front of me.
Cynthia Thorne.
The chairman of the Thorne group.
She's here in person.
So sorry for making you worry, Mom.
That's Leo's mom.
Hey there, pretty.
Looking good.
So you're this beggar's mother.
Looking real good.
Just my type.
A little older.
I bet you are quite the treat in bed.
How dare you insult a man like that?
How dare you?
You know, that's the last mistake you're going to make,
Henry.
The last one!
Who the fuck are you?
How dare you pull a gun on me?
You're about to be a dead man.
You're a fool.
You've been away from the team.
Too long.
Too long, Henry.
I'm second commander.
Second?
Second commander?
He's second commander?
No.
That's impossible.
How could you be second commander?
Sully, are you Divina?
Yes ma'am, I am.
It's wonderful to meet you.
You're a lovely girl.
So kind and generous.
Leo will be blessed to have you as his wife.
First commander?
Henry, what's the matter?
Mr. Brando, we're speaking with the governor now.
I'm going to order to come first.
We'll be there soon.
Commander, we have a situation.
I ran into a second commander.
He's still against us.
He's siding with those who believe Joseph.
Nonsense.
What's that, Commander?
His name is Connor.
Bullshit.
Connor was assigned to protect his nonless top ranking figure
years ago.
How could he be there?
He's an imposter human, he is.
An imposter?
Stop, Henry.
Stop.
You want to be expelled from the team?
Huh?
You piece of shit.
You're not a second commander.
You're an imposter.
I should go right now.
You teach your lesson.
Get your hands off her.
Let her go.
No.
Let go of her.
You're going to pay for what you did.
Divina is about to become my wife.
And not only will she be the wife of the President of the Thorne
Group, she's also attached to her even more powerful, dangerous family.
I'll let her go.
I will make sure you suffer for the rest of your fucking life.
Keep talking crap.
You piece of shit.
The President of the Thorne.
What do you want?
Release Mrs. Divina now.
Well, I'm going to blow her brains out of shooter in the head.
You think I'm scared of you?
She's true sister.
If you don't care about her life, then let's vote you.
No.
You're not joking.
Two.
Three.
ze.
One.
Look who us Mrs. Laura, she's committed to you sister.
You can kill her.
Jill makes an old man with her lives.
Are you all right, Divina?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm okay.
Drew is an utter fool.
He can't even control his own man.
If I were to tell him to die, you wouldn't utter a single word.
Ball.
You're finally here.
They wanted to shoot me, Drew.
Let me see who's talking his bolt.
Talking is bullshit.
Oh, it's a woman.
Foolish woman.
Divina, we're in real trouble here.
Those mercenaries have really shown up
and they have the Brandore groups backing.
What do we do?
Isn't it obvious, Divina?
All this trouble is caused by your damn boyfriend.
Just apologize to Mr. Drew.
This is all my fault.
I don't wanna drag you all into this.
This is just on me, but, I mean, Leo and his bonds
to F for us, they've been an ally to us.
We can't just append in them.
Idious!
Kneel down, they've been for mercy.
Commander Drew is the leader
of the Brandore mercenary company.
Mr. Brandore's right-hand man.
The Thorne group is nothing in front of him.
Leo, what do we do?
The Brandore group is too powerful.
We can't append them.
I can do this.
Who are the bastards who've done this to you?
Connor, is that you?
What the hell are you doing?
You're trying to betray us all.
Commander Drew, I'm on a mission.
I mission my ass, holster that weapon.
The line before I slap you, right?
We're gonna do that or no?
Take it from the slap.
So, you're the commander of the Brandore mercenary group,
and you don't even know which people
you're supposed to be protected.
It's a shame all the Brandore money is going to waste.
Shit, how dare you disrespect the Brandore payment?
You're gonna pay.
Yeah, you are the one who is going to pay.
I'm court and death.
I've heard about your brave legacy,
but today you are acting very foolish.
You don't need to say another word.
Is that the truth today?
Your title is removed,
and you are gonna suffer retribution
for everything you have done today.
You're funny, honey.
And a bit dumb,
but you do got a nice little body there.
Since you heard about my legacy,
why don't you come up being my baby doll
and let me show your person, hey.
Don't touch her.
Keep your filthy hands off of me.
Oh!
What do you think you're doing?
Stopping a woman is a side of weakness.
Don't you think I won't slap me a woman?
You'd be honored to sleep with me, you dirty bitch.
You pathetic piece of shit.
Any woman that sleeps with you must be miserable.
You're gonna wish that you were never born,
even now God can't save you.
I'm sick of that little mouth of yours, boy.
How about I fuck your mama right in front of you right now?
Then when that mouth gonna say?
Mr. Brandor, good to see you.
The address you gave me isn't far at all.
We'll be able to see young Mr. Brandor soon.
How's the temperature in the car?
It's fine, Colbert.
But if you don't mind,
please make it a little bit cooler.
Certainly, sir.
Hello, my darling.
Did you miss me?
You flow old donkey.
Where the hell are you?
Someone here not only wants to kill your child,
but he's also sexually harassing your wife.
What?
Goodbye.
Cynthia, my darling.
Who's saying such things?
Tell me his name.
What happened, Mr. Brandor?
Someone just threatened my son
and threatened my wife with rape.
What?
Who?
Give me to the address in 10 minutes.
Governor, don't you think you owe me an explanation
as to how this is happening to my family?
Mr. Brandor.
I'll summon the state troops.
That way you have the right to command them.
I assure you,
anyone who disrespects Brandor
will be buried under Memphis bullets.
Do you think you're calling the honey your savior?
I ain't nobody gonna save you.
You're piling on the corpse.
When they get here
and realize they crossed the Brandor mercenary commander,
they'll piss their pants and run like rats.
You wait on my husband gets here.
Let's see who pisses their pants then.
Husband.
You hear that, Joseph?
We got a wild one here.
She won't.
It's recent.
How dare you?
You sexist scuff.
See that field over there?
When my father gets here,
that'll be your grave and else.
How dare you disrespect Commander Drew?
What you're just is delinquent is your father.
And when he gets here,
you'll die right next to him.
You should enjoy your last happy moment.
As soon as you won't even be able to cry.
Well, I've had enough.
Get down on your knees
and beg me for forgiveness.
Stop danger me.
That'll never happen.
In my daydream.
Is that what you say?
Joseph, I need you.
Rita, wake up.
He can't protect you.
Don't you get it?
Once I'm done with you,
I'm gonna sell you off to the broth.
That way you're broken just like him.
If you care so much about him,
let's let him watch.
I'm gonna belittle him right in front of you.
How's that?
Little Leo, come here.
Come here.
You fucking asshole.
Get down.
Beg me for your forgiveness.
Go ahead.
Faster.
You're gonna fall into a trap.
Don't worry, Anita.
Then you, Joseph.
I'm sorry to say that today's your death day.
We'll see you if it's buried first.
Drew, why don't you go ahead
and play close quarters with Mom here.
We'll see if he's still smiling.
That's the best idea you had all day, Drew.
Why not?
Faster.
Don't touch me.
Me!
Five.
Asshole.
You can't say that to Miss Cynthia.
You don't have the capacity to care for anyone else.
So I thought Drew takes care of Mom.
He's taking care of you.
I'll make him wish he was dead.
Yeah, look, he's going to scum.
You burning hell for this.
Police Miss Cynthia need to be done right now.
Daniel, are you crazy?
Daniel.
Put it down.
You're gonna make us kill you.
Cows ain't supposed to play with you.
Come here.
Move off.
You even know how to use this thing.
Let me show you.
No, don't shoot me.