Mr. Brando, is that the Lord Brando?
Focus.
Everyone speak and act normally.
We don't want to offend Mr. Brando.
The Brando or group is the most powerful organization in the world.
And if we offend him, not even Drew can save us.
Mr. Brando!
Mr. Brando, what are you doing here?
It's got the mistake of the answer. You shouldn't be here. You dirty your shoes.
Drew, weren't you attending two personal matters? What are you doing here?
Mr. Brando cares about me. It seems he values me.
It's likely I'll get a promotion sometime soon.
You shit-ass people, sir. They bully my sister and disrespect me and the Brandoar name.
That's a lie. You are the one who believe Leo and I'm disrespecting the Cynthia.
Show me these shit-ass people you just mentioned.
Damn it. Him. Show some respect, don't you know who this man is? This Mr. Brandoar.
Exactly. No manners at all.
Kneel down and beg for forgiveness from Mr. Brandoar.
See, Drew is vital to the Brandoar group.
Mr. Brando is here because of him.
Today you're going to learn that if you cross us, it's the biggest mistake you'll ever make.
So get on your knees and apologize.
You're going to fucking regret it now.
You idiot. You're all the fools that should be kneeling down in front of me and apologizing.