Leo, I'm such an asshole. I didn't know it was you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Thorpe. I mean, Mr. Brandor, I was wrong. Please don't banish me like you did, Henry.
Mr. Leo, sir, sir, I was wrong. We were so very wrong. Just please, please, please have mercy on us.
Will this give you all the money you want, sir? Just please, sir, spare us.
You think I need your money? Well, let me tell you something.
As of right now, I am confiscating all of your bank accounts.
No. No. That's our money. You can't freeze it.
No. You can't do the choice. No.
Now you can both live like the beggars that you both disdain so much. Take them out of here.
No. No. No. No. No.
I live without our money.
And you, you are banished from the Brandor group.
and I'm confiscating your bank accounts as well.
No, Mr. Brandore, please, I'm begging you.
Please forgive me for my foolish ignorance.
I can't be banished.
I've got a lot of enemies and those assets took me 10 years to build.
Let me tell you something. I don't care if you live or die.
I didn't know you was Mr. Brandore Jr.
Please forgive me sir.
Please, I was a mistake. I apologize.
You shouldn't be apologizing to me.
You should be apologizing to all of the women that you've manipulated over your entire life.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I said all them nasty things to those honorable women.
Please forgive me sir. Mr. Brandore, please.
I'm begging you. It was a mistake. It was just a big mistake.
You can't banish me. I won't last. They'll kill me.
That's just not possible. No, please sir. No. Don't move.
Please sir. What are you doing with me?
You ruined me. Because of you, I got banned.
Finish cousin. Mr. Brandore thinks I'll betray. I'm gonna kill you.
If you had come any later, you wouldn't have a wife in the trial list.
Forgive me darling, for being late. Leo, it's been so long.
You've grown into an outstanding young man.
Mr. Dad. All right. What are you planning on doing with these?
People. These people are going to wish that they've never ever been born into this world.
Jack Connor, take them away. Yes sir. I'm going to kill you. Mr. Brandore, please.
Please. And you. God. Please. We know we were wrong. Mr. Brandore, we really didn't know who you are.
That's why we offended you. If we had known, we never would have dared.
Who I am is not important. And as for Divina, she is not just
surprised that can be traded. How dare you force her upon Joseph?
It's not only kidnapping, it's rape. Leo. You worthless idiot. You really like
dangling your wealth over other people's heads? Well, as of today, I'm taking all of your wealth
from you. I am bankrupting your company and making sure that all of your future projects go
as long as I'm alive, I'll make sure all goes
take this quarter. Now it's the only thing that you have left to your name. Enjoy the slums.
My money. Mr. Leo, please. Just serious. We cannot live without money.
Get him out of here. No. He would have thought that Leo had such an old background.
Nina, I think you should leave. What do you mean? Are you trying to?
Your behavior has been ridiculous today. I don't think this engagement is going to work.
Are you asshole? What are you trying to say? I'm done. And I'm sorry.
Really? You think I have to marry you? You'll regret this.
Nina. From now on, we have no more obstacles in our way. And like I said,
I will always protect you. Leo, I trust you. You are a hero.
Mom. Dad. Devina's the one who took care of me those long three years while I was in a coma.
She worked tirelessly every day to pay for my treatment. She's my guardian angel.
I want her to be my life. Leo, you're not being very genuinely. You haven't even asked
dear Devina if she's willing. Right. I'm sorry. I got too excited. Re-mariny.
I will. Leo is back and I will host a grand well-comptie for now. And we will announce that Leo
and Devina are getting married. That's a brilliant idea my dear. Dear friends,
please invite all of your family and friends to make a major announcement
that Devina will be a member of the Brandoar family. Mr. Brandoar, we might not do it this way
because we don't have a lot of money. We don't have a big family or a lot of friends. Dear friends,
they distance themselves from you because they're true foliage. Well, because of anything you do.
Yes, they're going to miss a huge opportunity for sure. Thank you, Mr. Brandoar. This door?
Well, in that case, I'll call everyone I know and invite them to Leo's welcoming,
worry. I want Leo and Devina to have everyone's blessing. Well, that's a great idea, Barton.
Let's do it. Devina, why don't you invite your friends to the, to the party? Friends,
they all are situation is worse than you think. No one will associate with us
outside of my uncle's family. Hi, Bob. This is Barton. I wanted to, but how did it go?
He hung up. You see? Mr. Bailey, what do you think in Leo? I was thinking that
maybe I should send out the invitations for the party with the Brandoar name on it. Maybe it'll
be more community that way. Of course, everyone's going to answer an invitation
for the Brandoar, Alan. Yes, and that way we don't have to make any calls. All right, Leo,
I know you don't want to leave Devina, but you need to return your family first.
Your uncles are extremely worried about you. They spend a lot of money trying to find you.
Of course, Dad. I'll see you at the party. I'll see you at the party. Send an invitation to
Devina's uncle's family, but do not mention my relationship with her. Sir, do as I say, my reasons.
As you say, sir, I'll handle it. Lovely place. Oh, Barton, this is my first time in a place like this.
Do you think Bob and the others will come? Well, they would have to, right?
It's an invitation from the Brandoar. There's really no reason for them not to. Guys, it's okay.
Leo knows our situation, and besides, even if no one comes, it's not going to affect our loved
masses. Our look is finally changed. Brandoar's invited us to young Brandoar's welcoming party.
This is a chance to meet some big names. My boyfriend, Billy's father, is a hotel manager here.
Maybe he can accuse us around. Absolutely. Maybe. We can even meet the family,
members of the Brandoar family. You know it. My dear, I knew you meet the perfect boyfriend.
You're a thousand times better than that, silly Divina, and her terrible Bailey family.
You know what? She can bring herself to leave that losing boyfriend of hers.
She's not even qualified enough to be compared to me. You made it. Barton, what the hell are you
doing here? Why did you even get an invitation to the Brandoar party in the first place?
Even though it's been a while, I knew you would still come.
Yes, Uncle Bob, I really appreciate that you're still willing to reach out to us.
No, no, no. This has the reasons we are here, have nothing to do with you at all. Bob, I tried
to call you yesterday. Young Mr. Brandoar will be announcing his engagement to Divina. I tried
to tell you, but you hung up, or would you just shut up? Do you even know what you're saying?
This is unbelievable. You're disgusting poor people. How serious do you think of such delusions?
Leo, did you tell Jack not to mention your relationship with Divina in the reception
invitation? That's correct. We will spoil Divina's family and friends with a typical
Brandoar family hospitality. But until then, I want to conduct a little test.
To see where Divina's family and friends loyalty lies. Oh, I see. I'll be heading down to the party.
Governor Colbert's and father should be finishing their congress safe. I suggest you meet me down
guys, we're serious. Divina is going to marry Mr. Leo Brandoar. Didn't you see it on the
invitation? This is Mr. Leo Brandoar's welcoming party. It is not a wedding announcement. So I
don't know what the hell you're talking about. Daniel, you and Martin need to shut up and stop
spreading rumors. Did you hear that? These idiots actually think Mr. Leo Brandoar would marry this poor
girl. I think they've been reading many fairy tales. The young Mr. Brandoar would be better off marrying
me. But it's true, Divina, these wealthy and powerful people don't accept us. Maybe it was a
mistake showing up. I can't believe Leo didn't tell Bob's family about the wedding. You think
he's having second thoughts about the marriage? No. I don't know. We have to trust Leo. Mom,
we have said we were the guests of honor at the party just like himself. Idiots.
Mia, east the relatives of your uncle family? What a bunch of losers. Like you said,
they've ruined your good mood. I don't like that. Do you want me to kick them out?
Security. Take out the trash. Wait, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, you threw us out. Idiot.
Billy's father is the owner of the hotel. If he wants to teach you a lesson,
he just has to say the word. Right. Mia isn't as stupid as you are wasting all your time and money
when you're pathetic boyfriend. And now you break into this noble party, pretending that Mr. Brandoar
is going to marry you? That it can't be. Your stupidity is a ploy. You're the most ridiculous person
in the world. Bob, watch your mouth. Divina is not stupid. We never lied. Everything we said was
the truth. Oh, Barton. Being promised to remind your brain. I actually feel sorry for you.
Not really. It seems that we should have attended that ridiculous
fundraiser that you threw. Maybe if we donated some money, you wouldn't be so dramatic. Don't
you dare speak to my father like that. We are family. How can you be so cruel?
Billy girls. Oh, and make cruel. There's some other slums on you all the way from here. You're
polluting the air of this pardon. Make me sick. Get the hell out of here, you favorite.
Just because you're wealthy does not mean you shouldn't insult others. Aubrey lies in your soul.