Let's see. I'm Chris Parker. I'm 50. I spend most of my free time hiking and collecting climbing equipment
I have a son and a grandmother on the way
Gildy that demo. You said you're 52 on the dating app and you're definitely 60 boys will be boys even in their 60s
Start with London then Paris and then Rome but all the way to Beijing three of us
Three of us you me and my life of course your wife
This is a date
My oh my you are absolutely stunning. What do you say we get together and have a baby before we get to wool chewy?
God, I'd like to see you try good. I always like excuse me boss. It's time for your date. Should I leave this here?
Where's this from? Well department store cheap as it gets on the car once used excellent
Is there anything else you need just keep this quiet yes, boss
No one will ever find out that the chairman and peak climbers is going as a date as an ordinary urban driver
Hi, I'm Jerry. What's with the glasses for eyes? Are you blind? Who the hell wants to be with a sick old man?
60% of your wages each month 30% will cover daily expenses 30%
We'll go to the bank to cover my mortgage. Oh
How generous you left me 40% no that 40% is going straight to my account
I'm thought in an hour. What's that if you want overnight?
I'm sorry. I'm actually looking through so much there half a million months any good or so
I think it's I'm Jerry some Chris Chris Parker. Let's get married