Tom, that's too much.
Sorry, Mom, I didn't mean to.
So that's what you think of me, Chris.
It's not like that.
Take care of yourself, sweetheart.
Bob, where are you going?
Anywhere but here.
It's raining outside.
Please, just gotta be kidding me.
What are you here?
What do you want?
Chris, it's me.
What's wrong?
Did someone upset you?
Sherry!
It's nothing.
It's not like nothing.
You're better.
Are you outside?
My shitty car broke down in the middle of the woods.
What?
In this weather, in the middle of December?
I'm going to pick you up.
No, no, it's fine.
It's no reason for you to freeze out here too.
Where are you?
It's the more of Lincoln Road, I think.
I'll be right there.
Don't move.
Go to Lincoln Road now.
Yeah, but how are you going to explain your identity?
What about me?
An overdrive as driver?
Sit down.
I'll drive.
Hey, baby.
You need a ride?