You promised me that you would never touch climbing gear again.
This is different.
I don't fucking care!
Please don't say that.
They're dead!
Dad and Emma are fucking dead!
Maybe if you wouldn't have fucking supported their stupid hobby,
it'd still be around.
It was an accident. You can't blame it all on me.
Is that not enough?
What, are you gonna take a new family up there to that death hype?
Or are you gonna reign until my daughter's poor and then do the same to her?
It's never my intention. Please don't say that.
Look at me.
You are never welcome in my home again.
And if you want to go die, go die alone.
No, Tom. Tom, wait!
Oh!
Chris! Chris! Chris! Chris! Chris!
Chris! Oh, Chris! Are you okay? What happened?
It's fine. Just family quarrel.
If this keeps happening, I'm gonna need to have a little talk with your family.
Oh, let me see that here. Come here.
Oh, what's your daughter?
Oh, 22.
Ever have any difficulties with her?
I don't even know where to start.
I have you.
What do you say we forget about those damn kids and go have a drink?
How about that?
I have a good back.
Everything all right?
Yeah, it just feels like this isn't the first time I've been born.
My home is home.
I wouldn't know.
Sometimes it's hard to recall memories, early ones, especially it.
They'll just kind of fall apart.
Have you gotten that checked out?
Yeah, Doctor says I'm fine.
It's just, I guess the old grain matters are seeing what it used to be.
Did you find yourself a pro?
Great question. Jerry, this is my buddy Antoine Heat bones this place.
Antoine, this is Jerry, my husband.
Your husband?
Wow, that's interesting.
Uh, beg your pardon?
I don't mean to be rude, but, um, I haven't heard Chris say the word husband in, like,
what, two decades?
Antoine.
He was also in my high school gang.
And if you can believe it, his mouth was even bigger back then.
Well, welcome to my place.
And there's only one rule here.
Chris makes all the rules.
Shut up Antoine.
You only say that when you're in trouble.
And those two drinks on the house, something must be really wrong.
Well, did you guys ever hear this real estate conglomerate called G5?
They want to buy this place.
So, take the money, go to Florida, meet some babes.
We get a new bowling alley.
Win, win.
I thought about it, but they're only offering half the going range.
Oh, hell with them then.
Sorry Antoine, you're stuck with us.
And unless they do something to force me.
Mmm.
Who's the boss?
That would be me.
Whoa.
Could I help you?
I'm Griffin.
Boss of the Griffin's.
Open your register.
We're taking your money.
That's not going to happen to me.
You were tired fat ass.
Put that thing down.
Shut your mouth grandma.
Mind your shit.
I'll blow him away.
Robbery is one thing.
Murder.
You can't come back from that.
We talk.
You business old bitch.
You have Jesus Christ in this fucking neighborhood.
When did Jesus pack a 45?
I'll shoot you piece of shit.
Nobody tells me what to do.
Young man.
Don't talk to me like a fucking teenager.
This isn't the first time somebody's tried to rob this guy.
Look, he may look soft.
He's not a coward.
No means no.
Shut the fuck up.
Wait.
Let's talk business, okay?
Bullying an old man?
That's not how a leader acts, is it?
What are you talking about?
Move on.
Take your business else.
Bullshit.
The fucking talking about.
Griffin.
The world doesn't work the way you think it does.
It's much more complicated.
I know Vlad.
Vladimir Markov.
You know who he is?
I doubt he knows who he is.
He runs the other side of town.
Like I said,
world's a complicated place.
Now what would happen if Vladimir find out you're messing with some of his friends?
How would that turn out for you?
Don't worry.
I got it better, right?
One that doesn't end with you at the bottom of a river.
What is it?
The block.
Between Mulberry Street and Lincoln has a ton of trust fund babies, right?
Deep pockets and lots of addictions.
You know what to do.
Thank you, sir.
May we have your name?
Fuck off.
Now.
I think that'll keep busy for a while.
So that's your secret?
You're one of them?
One of those bastards?
No.
Well, you just told them to go sell drugs.
Are you crazy?
Hang on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't be such a judgement so quickly.
Do you know who lives on that block?
Devin Jones and Alex Shaw.
The mayor and the chief of police.
Thank you.
Two of the most conservative guys in town.
Oh, they'll just love this dude slinging drugs outside his window.
Wait, you just did that?
Jesus Christ.
You really are a bad boy.
And Officer Alex packed to be one of my old friends.
So, so you better tell them these crazies are heading towards their neighborhood.
Chris, I like this guy.
Where'd you find him?
Had a random coffee shop.
It's a long story.
I bet it's a good one.
With me?
Always.
You know, I'm just, I'm just happy I found another good man.
You know, um, kind of reminds me of Jerry, his late husband.
He doesn't like it.
No, not his looks.
You know, he's five, how he carries himself.
But a Jerry never really died in that accident.
No!
Jerry.
Jerry is dead.
My bad.
If he was alive, he would have come looking for me.
You okay?
Fine.
You, you look different.
I do.
It must be all the excitement.
Well, I am planning to have a Christmas dinner at my place.
I want you to come.
Meet all my family.
Would you come?
Of course.
It would be my honor.
Mom.
Please.
Come in.
Tom.
I just want to quickly say.
Mom.
I'm so sorry about the other one.
It's just Tom's been working on a hard case and you know, we have a daughter on the way and
it's just been a lot of pressure.
I'm really sorry when I said.
It's okay.
I made a lot of mistakes.
And some of them, some of them I can't fix.
But I didn't come here to talk about the past.
I can't tell you.
I'm, I'm married.
You're married?
That's wonderful, Mom.
He's the sweetest man.
I know you're going to love him.
And I want you to meet him at Christmas dinner.
We would love that.
Dad would be so happy.
I mean, he was always getting trouble and I'm sure he's out there looking down with a smile.
I think someone has your back.
Yeah.
What is it?
Something wrong?
No, it's just Tom.
After all these years, if you ever saw your father again, do you think you'd recognize him?
Yeah, of course I would.
I mean, he's in that picture right there behind you.
I mean, I look at him every day.
Anyway, it's getting late and I have to go.
But I will see you guys at Christmas dinner.
Yeah, of course.
Looking forward to it.
Why, I'm the lady.
But this place is cute.
Is it new?
It's just open.
My daughter recommended it.
Well, she has great taste.
You must have raised her well.
For the last 20 years, it's been her and I against the world.
She's my angel.
Can I tell you something?
Of course.
Sometimes I wish I had a girl instead of boy.
Boys don't think.
Like, it's not with their brains.
I'm on John's head.
Are you with them?
Emma?
Dad?
Emma.
John?
Dad, do not look at it.
Look at me.
Go.
Emma, I told you.
Stay away from this alcoholic.
Can you just leave us alone?
Okay, because my life and what I do with it is none of your business.
You're free to date whoever you want.
But not him.
Remember what happened last time?
John nearly burned our house down.
That's my life and my business.
Not to mention it.
He nearly got you killed.
You know, where do you get off?
Okay, because maybe.
If you knew the first thing about love, ditch us.
20 years ago.
You don't know what you're talking about.
What I'm talking about?
Well, Bob didn't ditch us.
Then why is the only thing she left this old photo?
Hmm?
Did you teach her this shit?
Get out.
I don't even want to fucking see you again.
Then I'm going with him.
Hold on, honey.
Let's talk.
And who the hell are you?
That boy's.
Give us a space.
You didn't mean to do that, did you?
Of course not.
But how can I?
You know, he doesn't trust me.
It was strong.
What's that last time your father mentioned?
So my dad invited John over for Thanksgiving dinner.
Right.
And John's a shy boy.
He didn't really know what to do.
So his friends started giving him some advice.
And that's when everything hit wrong.
Tell me everything.
Well John doesn't drink much.
His friends suggested that maybe a little liquor may help him loosen up.
But keyword a little.
John got so drunk.
And he drove me home.
Fashed the car straight into my dad's garden.
Dear, I can only imagine how Jerry reacted to that.
But whatever you're imagining, it's way, way worse.
I mean, my dad's actually a really respectful man.
You know?
I mean he didn't even say anything about the car or the garden.
He just, he even invited John to come in.
It's over up.
But John was like, I mean like blind truck.
So he stumbles in and knocks over a candle
and sets the curtains on fire.
Yeah, it's a nightmare as well.
But you know, like John's not like that.
You know, John is gentle and smart and caring.
Yeah, but he's not a drunk.
Okay?
He was just one mistake.
One time.
My dad won't let it go.
Gotcha girl.
It was just a misunderstanding.
I don't understand.
You know?
Who are you?
How do you know my dad?
Baby, you look a bit drunk.
You gonna ride home?
Go away.
Is none of your business?
No.
Fuckin' you, granny.
Go home and fuck yourself.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Oh my God.
You're coming with me, huh?
No.
I'm sorry, man.
I should have jumped in sooner.
I'd like you kid.
Get her home safe.
I'll take care of her old man.
Thank you very much.
You want me to hear me?
You ready to go home?
Yeah.
Oh.
Jerry and I are hosting a Christmas dinner.
I would love for you to come.
Do not be late.
Thank you.
What a cute boy.
Where is my husband?
There's the old bitch.
Oh, you've never learned the home, man.
Hey, your boy toy beat me at the bar.
And now you're gonna pay.
With that thing down.
Fuck you bitch.
Give me your money.
Take off your coat.
Where did you get that thing?
I came with my truck.
You know, to fix the car.
I almost forgot your driver.
Oh.
Fuck.
They know how to get yourself into trouble, don't you?
Maybe I should start carrying a gun in my truck.
Shut up.
Er, John and I'm gonna be okay.
Hmm.
John said you agreed to let him take Emma home.
He's really not a bad kid.
I think he should give him a second chance.
You know he almost got Emma killed?
He was like a monster.
I think that's just an excuse.
Of course.
You would have a problem with John no matter what.
He could be a doctor, a lawyer, a senator.
You'd still hate him.
Because what you really can't stand is suddenly taking your daughter away.
You're probably right.
Probably.
You are.
If John deserves my daughter, then I'll dance if they're wedding.
Can you still dance?
Let me show you.
Hmm.
Paul, cancel all my plans for Christmas.
All of your appointments.
That's right.
Boss, you're invited to the White House for dinner on Christmas.
So how many more reports come up?
Tell me.
What's more important than the President?
Stop!
You're early.
Today's meeting is too important to be late to.
But I am curious what's more important than the President.
My wife and I are hosting a Christmas party.
You should come.
Oh, thanks, Mr. Smith.
But my mother would be furious if I missed her Christmas party.
That's all right.
Say hi to your mother for me, okay?
And tell her, I wish I had a son like you.
Really?
I wish the melons were right.
That would be nice.
The table.
Ooh.
This one's right.
Think.
Yeah.
This one's right.
Think.
Yeah.
Do you think we have enough for Christmas now?
Thank you so much for coming with me, sweetheart.
It's the least I could do after the other day.
Tom really went overboard.
If I let every silly thing that boy said bother me, I would have been dead 100 years ago.
Let's go.
What else?
Fill the cap.
Now, do it.
Everybody down.
I went through your hands.
What should we do?
The title transfer from party A shall not.
No.
What?
Mr. Smith, are you all right?
Fine.
Said a weird feeling about something.
Like a bad feeling?
Not sure.
What should we do?
We're pretty close to the entrance.
Just follow me when he walks away.
It's a good run.
Don't move.