Even if I'm robbery inside a local store, are you okay?
You know what, I'm just broke.
Don't shoot.
That bastard.
Oh my God, Mr. Smith, I need to get there as fast as I can.
I'm going with you.
Get the car ready.
Missa?
This country needs gun control.
Let me get my weapon.
With the gun down.
Get underneath, now.
Okay, okay.
What do you want?
If you want money, you can have it.
There are your pockets.
Please, my daughter's about to give birth
and please just let us go.
We won't do anything, I promise.
Please, please, please get up whatever you want.
Just don't hurt us.
Leave your phone, wallet and purse.
And get out.
Don't tell anybody what happened here.
Yes, thank you so much.
Okay, of course.