If you shoot us, there won't be an arrest.
There won't be a trial.
They will, police will just tell you where you are.
Well, if you didn't call the fucking cops,
it'd be halfway out of town by now.
It isn't too late to change your mind.
Think of your family, right?
They do think you're a murderer,
and they'd be heartbroken if they knew their son
was a murderer.
Keep my family out of your mouth.
I won't let those fucking cops catch me.
I won't be a jail for the next 20 years,
and then below let you.
Do not bear your cursed life with mine, OK?
I'm not a failure.
I'm not alone, and I'm not a certified felon like you are.
Oh, God, if my husband was alive,
he would shoot you right on the spot.