Merry Christmas. Merry Christmas, buddy. Oh, look at all this. Thank you. Watch out. Be careful now
It's my special mac and cheese. Come on. All right. Yeah, you look nice. Thanks coming through
Tom, my man
Haven't seen you around the bowling alley lately. I know you really missed you
Me and Lisa are busy. Oh
Little too busy for his uncle Antoine. We just had a baby. What? Yeah
Oh my god
Congratulations
Remember Antoine's mac and cheese
Amazing, I'm sure it's great, but mom please there's something that I really need to talk to you
Just give me a moment to tell you always just a little busy right now. Why don't you um, go watch the football with Antoine