May I come in, darling?
Is this Tom Cruise?
His, uh, I can expect Jerry.
You're part of the family now.
Don't let him adapt.
Dad!
I went and dream of it.
Follow me, boys and girls.
You're sweat early like good, but...
Jerry! My old friend.
How are you?
Very well.
Now that we're finally, all we get.
This is Antoine, my best friend.
Hello.
And this is Tom, my son.
I believe some of you already know him.
Great to see you again.
I'm so glad that we're truly a family now.
Nice to meet you again, Mr. Smith.
I'm afraid there's many things that you have not told my mother.
Tom!
Mom, did you know that your new husband is the richest man in the state?
I didn't mean to...
Tom?
Come with me.
Could we just have one day of peace and quiet one day
when you are trying to play some game?
I just found out yesterday.
I had to say something.
Mom, I know you.
Okay?
You wouldn't be with him if you knew about his past.
You would think he's way out of our league.
Did you know he's supposed to be having dinner with the President,
the President of the United States?
I mean, the press is already wondering why he's missing and where he is.
If they find out that you two are married,
you're going to have journalists sticking their noses in every aspect of your life.
They're going to take away your freedom.
Wow, you really are a liar.
Oh, this isn't a joke.
Do you really want to be a fixture in the tabloids because you will?
Tom?
What?
I mean, beyond everything I just said, have you thought about it?
Have you thought about why he's keeping this from you?
Why he's hiding it?
That man doesn't trust you.
I do trust your mom.
I trust her with all my heart.
It's just that everything happened too fast.
I couldn't find the right time.
Bullshit.
Everything.
Mr. Ober driver.
Mr. Smith, I've worked for you for many years and I trust you as a boss and a father,
but I can't sit by and let you lie to my mother.
I swear.
I just...
Tom, they appreciate you telling me.
I should have waited one day just one more day so I couldn't have my Christmas.
What's the use of marriage if nothing's ever shared?
You said that before, didn't you?
I'm really sorry.
I'm just...
I never met for any of this to happen.
I was trying to find the best moment.
I need some time.
Some space.
God.
This is bad.
Tom Schitt, you know, brought that up at Christmas.
I mean, if someone was lying to my mom, I'd probably do the same thing.
Emma.
Not the time.
I'm sorry, guys.
I ruined Christmas.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I...
I was screwed up.
Where did that photo come from?
It's a family photo.
When I was younger.
Your family?
That's your father, your mother, your sister, and yourself?
I don't understand what's the big deal.
Don't push up your way.
I've searched for 20 years to find someone like you.
You make me feel young.
And alive.
You have to understand.
Ever since the tragedy, I've only lived for my daughter.
She's the only thing I have left.
Now she has John.
My job is done.
She's safe.
And loved.
But I have no one.
No one except you.
Please.
I don't want to stand.
Be about the tragedy that 20 years ago.
Where did you get this?
This is the last thing that my mother left me.
She died in a landslide 20 years ago.
On the land side, where?
Maple.
So the barren mountain, 40 miles north of Anchorage, Alaska?
Yeah.
It's exactly where Dad said that she...
Dad?
Mr. Smith?
No, no, there's no way.
He looks completely different.
The landslide nearly crushed his skull.
The doctors had to give him a whole new face.
This is Christ.
He's my dad.
20 years ago.
My family went up to a barren mountain.
Like today's not crazy enough.
Jesus.
I'm gonna kill whoever is at the door.
Mom.
Mom, wait a second.
Do you remember our family photo on the wall?
Yeah, of course.
What about it?
Oh my gosh, just look at this.
Do you recognize that photo?
Why is this photo water damaged?
Huh.
Chris says, what is your book?
This is your Christmas gift.
What are you talking about?
This is what you get.
I'm gonna kill all of ya.
Get some rope.
Fuck you all.
What the fuck up?
That was enough craziness for one day.
Let's get this asshole out of here.
Just wait here.
John and I got this.
Big thanks on playing here.
Let's go.
Well, looks like someone made the naughty list this year.
What happened to you?
Why do you look so different?
Why didn't you come back to me?
What's the song about?
Is she?
That's Mom.
It's Tom.
That's right.
I didn't recognize you before.
You're my son.
Tell me this is real.
Please.
You're my wife.
Chris that I married.
Did you hide Fankridge 20 years ago?
Mount Maple.
I guess so.
My memory.
The accident.
I can't remember who I was.
My backpack.
My ID.
All gone.
The only thing we have left is...
And her.
Oh my god.
How did you survive?
Hunter.
Found us in the woods.
Injured and cold but alive.
I thought...
I thought you.
And Tom?
I thought you were dead.
I thought you were dead too.
Tom, get in here.
Group hug.
Come on.
I came to this day a million times over but...
I never thought it would actually happen for real.
It's a...
A Christmas miracle.
A miracle.
Can I give me some?
Darling, are you staying tonight?
Of course.
I waited over 20 years for this.
Thank you all for joining our family here today.
It's been a long road.
Strange journey.
But there is no place I'd rather be.
After 20 years apart, fate has given us the best Christmas gift of all.
Each other.
Merry Christmas.