You sure you want to go back in there?
My life's a mess right now, and I don't think it's fair to get you involved
We barely know each other like this dress costs more than everything. I've ever owned
combined
Well, you don't owe me anything. Okay
Just just call me if you need me at least
please
Fuck if you've been what are you wearing just a gift some cheap counterfeit you need to chip
In if you want to stay here, Sarah
Those could go for a few bucks for what so you can buy more booze and cigarettes you watch how you speak to me, lady
I raise this family all by myself. You wanted to sell me to the mob if it wasn't for Elliot
So you got yourself a rich boyfriend, and now you think you're better than all of us. He's not my boyfriend
But he's rich just ask him for money
I'm not gonna ask him for anything, and I'm not gonna give you another dime
away from you crazy bitch home you calling crazy