Sarah, oh my God, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Is the baby okay?
The baby's fine.
But I'd advise you to rest here for a few days.
Any stress, physical or emotional could affect the baby.
Doctor's right.
You need to rest.
Get out of my house.
It's okay.
You're not in trouble.
You're gonna talk to your mom.
Because of you, Sarah's in the hospital.
It was an accident she fell.
Shut it.
You've been abusing it for years, haven't you?
But it's up to me you being the emergency room.
Trust me.
The fake IDs.
I wish you to disappear.
Make sure your son is the best lawyer
and to make your neighbor's college tuition is paid for.
And if I see your face again,
I'll make sure the next time Sarah sees you's in the morgue.