How the fuck did you get in here?
I'm so sorry, Luke. I thought you wanted to surprise me.
Honey?
Surprise!
What a surprise!
Luke, who is she?
What is she doing here?
What do you think you fool?
She's not getting it.
We'll have to spell it out for her.
Darling?
Luke and I just had the most amazing sex on that bed.
And we came back here for...
She's lying. She's lying.
Does it look like a lie to you?
No. No.
You can't do this. I'm your wife!
Hey!
Watch your tone.
I didn't invite you here. You asked for it.
Luke, baby, we got to get going.
The banquet is about to begin.
banquet?
Oh. She doesn't know.
My company just went public.
I'm now officially a billionaire.
My company went public and you didn't tell me?
I didn't tell you because it's not your business.
Why don't you go eat a salad or something? You look pathetic.