Hey, don't touch my man.
Woo, I am begging you.
Don't you please don't do this.
Okay, I'll give you a chance.
What?
I'll give you one chance to get your blimpy ass out of here in the next minute
before I call security.
It's official, Matty.
Our marriage is over.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Before you go, there's a quarter of a mill on it.
Why don't you take that and disappear from my life for good, will you?
So this is what our three-year marriage means to you?
Axe, fine.
It's another quarter of a mill.
Just remember to sign the divorce papers right away and never set foot in our house.
I mean, my house ever again.
Nope, and nope.
Blimby Butterball, is it worth a nickel?
What did you call me?
Yeah, that's what we call you.
You didn't know that?
Oh, one more thing.
The ring.
Hand it over.
What?