Matty?
Meg.
What happened?
I just got back from my house and...
And?
What are you doing with all my stuff?
Get off me lady.
I'm just doing my job.
What are you doing here?
You.
That's what I should be saying to you.
Get out of my house this instant!
Your house?
Not anymore.
What?
I thought we made it abundantly clear.
I'm divorcing you, Matty.
And according to our prenup, this house belongs to me.
You can't do this to me.
This is my home.
Yeah, sorry about that, but this is our home.
You recognize this?
We're getting married this weekend.
Oh, and don't forget to take all your shit.
Otherwise, we'll find your house.
I lost everything.
Including the house.
I have nowhere to go.
Well, fuck him.
And her too.
You can stay here as long as you want.
Really?
Thank you Felix.
Do you have anything to eat?
Help yourself.
Wow, you can put those down.
Do you want a plate or bread?
I've got some cups if you want one.
Man, come on.
Slow down.
Welcome.
Always said I hate too much.
I don't know about it.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Look, there's nothing wrong with being fed.
With a big girl body.
Look, there's nothing wrong with a big girl body.
Everything's wrong.
It's a book based on an ancient Chinese diet therapy.
Four?
Losing weight.
It belonged to my mother.
So yeah, she used to be a bit, um, a bit, you know.
You can't say it Felix.
Fat.
A Chinese friend of hers from work.
Knew that she was struggling with her weight and gave her this little booklet.
So she gave it a try.
And what happened?
Here.
I'll show you.
Hey, hey, hey, where are you going?
Oh my god.
My stomach.
You lost any weight?
A little.
What about now?
Have you lost my weight?
Some?
No.
Oh my god.
What's wrong?
See, I already look unbrokenizing.
Yes.
Look like a completely different person.
Even my voice has changed.
You know what that means?
I can finally get my revenge on Luke.
How exactly are you going to do all of that?
I can fall in love with me.
And once he's badly in love, he kicks Olivia to the curb.
And then I dump him.
That's the Matty I know.
I just, I don't know how.
You know what?
I might be able to help you with that.
Now you need a new identity in order to do all of this, right?
Right.
So what if you were my sister?
I'm here for you Matty.
He licks Raphael.
Huge fan of yours, man.
What a pleasure.
Well, if it isn't the new billionaire on the block.
Or have you already lost all your money on half-baked purchases?
Ouch.
I hope not.
Just about a house in the Maldives and a yacht to go with it.
Exactly to my point.
Anyways, bud.
Enjoy it.
Well, it lasts.
What do you mean?
Who is that woman?
God.
I'll give you one chance to get your blimpy ass out of here in the next minute before I call security.
It's official, Matty.
Our marriage is over.
We need a gendier ex-husband.
Felix.
I'm afraid you haven't introduced me yet to your charming girlfriend.
Ah, girlfriend.
No, no.
I'm his sister.
Raphael?
Pleasure.
Pleasure is all mine, Madeline.
There's something familiar to you.
Have we ever met before?
I'm afraid not.
Madeline's been out of the country for some time now.
Doing her studies abroad.
Oh, well, it's great to have you back.
So tell me.
What are your plans?
Well, I'm looking for a job.
A job?
Your brother hears the owner of Lumina Tech.
There's no better place to get a job than there.
Well, I admire everything my brother has accomplished, but I would like to carve my own path.
Impressive.
Actually, I've done some research on your company.
Nexus Enterprises?
And I have to say, I would love to work for you.
Really?
Well, we'd love to have you.
Here, I'll make some calls, see where we can place you.
No, I would love to work for you.
Maybe as your assistant.
Assistant?
Do you have what?
Yes.
I mean, no.
Yes?
Yes, yes.
But he recently quit.
Today, actually, said he needed to spend some time with the family.
So, no.
No, I don't have an assistant.
Great.
Oh, that means I could work for you.
Yes.
I mean, yeah, they could.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Great.
Let's celebrate.
Later?
Thank you.
What the hell?
I'm so sorry.
Quit.
No, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Excuse me.
I'm going to go clean up in the bathroom.
I think he's taking the paint.
Time to reel in.
Hold my drink.
Waiter.
A little something for you.
You do.
It was supposed to be for my brother.
I had it in the car and it felt so bad.
I figured you could use it.
You sure?
Of course.
Here, why don't you take that dirty shirt off?
Actually, why don't I take it off for you?
My wife is going to love me.
Help me that shirt.
I'll have a dry clean for you.
See you Monday, 9 a.m.?
Monday.
I'm your new assistant.
Right.
What?
Look.
Yes, boss?
You're fired.
We're here.
Relax.
I told you I'd be late at the gala.
I have been sneezing and coughing here.
And you didn't even think of at least calling me?
I am your wife now.
Hey, hey, I told you I would be late.
What are you wearing?
Close?
No, Luke.
You're shirt.
You did not leave the house wearing that shirt.
Shirt, Luke.
Look, look.
I was...
Some stupid waiters filled wine on me.
Alright?
And then it got dirty and so I had to change it.
What?
What's wrong?
Crazy?
It works.
Look, it's not what it looks like.
Okay?
You were sleeping on my couch tonight.
Leave me at no.
Just stop it.
Okay, it was the waiters filled.
Just listen to me.
Leave.
There's something new to you.
What's up?
I'm having this aura.
A aura?
I see what you're doing.
You can't pull that off on me.
I'm no sucker like Luke.
You know the greatest way to get your revenge
is by just living your best life, right?
Don't you think that by trying to pull this whole thing off
you might not get what you really want?
I feel like I know exactly what I want.
I have no idea what Luke did to me.
He dumped me.
He tried to ruin me.
Because I was fat.
I feel that.
I know what you went through.
No.
No, you don't.
I do.
Remember how my mom used to be fat?
Hey you!
I didn't know there was going to be an earthquake today.
Whoa!
Yeah, keep walking.
I can't tell you the countless times people bullied my mother
because of her way.
And is that why you want to help me so bad?
Yeah.
And why I want you to live your best life.
Forget him.
And your past.
You need to move on.
Thank you.
And I am sorry that happened to your mother.
But you didn't live my life.
And my skin.
Luke is going to suffer.
And his mistress.
And his mother.
And his company.
I've lost my appetite.
Well, if it isn't Miss First Day on the job herself.
Come on in, Madeline.
This week's agenda, I've arranged all your meetings
and she's all a day to do weekly miracles.
You are something, aren't you?
Well, anything for my boss.
Come on in, Anthony.
Good morning, Luke.
I just wanted to pop by in.
Give you this.
It's a gift from my wife for taking the company public.
And for your new marriage.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Anthony.
I'd like to introduce you to my new assistant, Madeline Raphael.
Madeline, Anthony is our vice president.
It's nice to meet you, Anthony.
Hello, Madeline.
What do you feel right if I had a piece of that?
Well, yes, of course.
Okay.
We'll catch you guys later.
Thanks again.
It's all yours, boss.
Enjoy.
What happened?
Broke down.
I'm just going to go grab an Uber.
No, I mean to your leg.
It's actually my ankle.
I have really weak ankles.
Well, get in.
I'll take you home.
Are you sure?
No.
I don't want to be an inconvenience.
I won't take no for an answer.
No.
You're actually like historically bad at this.
Hey.
Okay.
I am undefeated.
Your brother's got quite a palace for himself, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I'm just staying here temporarily until I can get settled.
Oh, I got something for you.
Thanks.
I have yours inside.
If you want to come in and wait while I get it for you.
All right.
Sounds good to me.
Careful.
Thanks.
If you just want to wait right here, I can go up and grab it for you.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Let's just have a seat and I can check your ankle.
Hey.
Can you give me some ointment?
I think I twisted my ankle again.
You wouldn't be twisting your ankle if you weren't carrying all that baggage around.
What's going on?
Nothing.
Just checking on Madeline's ankle.
She's got weak ankles.
Isn't that right, Madeline?
No.
Interesting.
You're the CEO of Exis Enterprises.
You don't have more pressing matters than ankles.
Well, I just wanted to make sure she felt cared for on her first day of work.
Oh, the deluxe treatment, huh?
It's a first-of-foot massage.
What's next?
Full-body rub-down?
Hey, Lewis.
Well, I think I better get going.
Don't worry about the shirt, Madeline.
You can return it to me at work.
I hope you feel better.
Don't worry about the shirt, Madeline.
You can return it to me at work.
I hope you feel better.
Thanks.
Watch the attitude.
I don't want to see him touching you.
What's that?
Because.
Because why?
Come.
What's next to me?
Do you have something you'd like to say to me, Felix?
He's a two-faced asshole.
And I don't want to see you around him.
I'm getting jealous, sorry.
No.
No, I'm not.
I...
I just want...
Felix, he has to see me around you to really buy that we're siblings.
My plan has to go off without a hitch.
Then what's your plan?
The company has an important bidding meeting next month.
I can stop him if I can get a hold of the tender proposal in advance.
You mean the multi-billion dollar city garden project?
If he fails, his position as CEO of Nexus is at risk.
Oh, you're a smart cookie.
Ow!
Oh my god, the ankle thing's real?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
I'll give some weight in it.
Ah, no.
Feel better.
I think it's time for Olivia to meet Madeline.
Hi.
I'm just calling for Mr. Moss's office.
Who is this?
You must be Olivia.
Oh, I was just calling to say that Mr. Moss might be coming home late tonight.
Seems like we'll be having a very long night.
This bitch thinks she can steal my man.
I'm going to show her.
Please come in.
What do you got?
Oh, nothing.
Just a little nourishment for my hard-working boss.
Is this yellow to go?
Yep.
This is my favorite.
Yeah, how'd you know?
Well, that's what assistants do.
It's our job to know you inside a doubt.
Well, I'm not going to be able to eat all this sushi by myself, much less.
Finish an entire bottle of champagne.
I think I might need your assistance with this.
Anything for my boss?
So, what shall we toast you?
How about the future of your company?
Well, to the future of my company.
It's so good.
Well, boss, it's getting kind of late.
Don't worry about it.
Go home, get some rest.
Great job today.
Fun has just begun.
Where is she?
You're a bimbo assistant.
Oh, well, she, I mean he, he left a long time ago.
Don't you lie to me.
I know it's a she.
I just spoke with her.
She's here.
Where?
All right, I'm telling you she left.
So you ate all this sushi and champagne all by yourself?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, I guess.
You don't want to be with a snap of a finger.
You dare threaten me.
That's right.
You're messing with the wrong woman.