Has anyone ever told you you have the prettiest eyes?
Good Disney?
Luke, are you ready to discuss the city garden project proposal?
Yes, of course. Let's do it.
I should go.
Oh, no. Please stay. I want you to join us.
It's imperative that Madeline here knows everything about the deal.
I have to say, Anthony, those are some great ideas.
Look, this has been a very productive meeting.
I think we have an excellent shot at securing this proposal.
Oh, and here. This is your copy of the drafted proposal, so you have the exact numbers.
Absolutely perfect.
I'll take a look at this later.
Say Madeline. Anthony? You hungry?
How about we all grab some lunch?
My tree?
Sure. Let's do it.
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah, you know what? I'll stay here alone and clean this up.
Why don't you guys go ahead. Just order me something?