What the hell is wrong with you?
No, no, no, no, baby, no.
It was her fault.
I was trying to throw the coffee at her.
Madeline?
She's my assistant.
Look, how dare you disrespect her and me.
I want you out of my office now.
You're kicking me out of your office.
Luke, remember, you don't want to mess with me.
What do you think I am, huh?
I'm a fucking billionaire CEO.
You are nothing without me.
Now get up.
Oh, dare you speak to me that way?
I am your wife!
No, no, no, no, this is my chance.
What do I do?
You crazy bitch!
Get up!
I will not forgive you for this.
Olivia, don't forget your bag.
You're Madeline.
I'm so sorry for her behavior.
No, no, this is all my fault.
None of this would have happened if it wasn't for me.
I'm so sorry for her behavior.