Hey Olivia, it's Jacob. Got some news for you. Turns out Felix Raphael does not have a sister. He's an only child.
I knew it!
Great job, Jacob. Now I want you to find out exactly where this metal line lives.
You got it.
Let the fun begin.
Here you are, Olivia.
You are your mousey little hoe.
Don't talk to me like that.
You fraud. I just found out who you really are.
Oh no, she knows.
Oh, Kat got your tongue.
You thought you could fool us with your little story about your billionaire brother?
You're no billionaire. You're a gold digging tramp, and it's just a matter of time until everyone else finds out.
I'll make sure of it.
Well, good luck with that. You can hardly keep your own man.
You can barely keep his hands off me.
I'm going to make your life a living hell.
You did this to me once before.
And now it's my turn to do it to you.
What the hell is this slut talking about?
Running cutie?
Hey. Hey, red's right there. You can make your own toast.
Someone's upset. Want to discuss?
There's nothing to discuss. All's good.
Are you upset about last night?
Why'd you come back so late?
I was working on my plan. It requires dedication.
Going to the bar with your ex-husband at midnight? That's dedication? What would you do?
Well, he was drunk.
We went back to his hotel room.
You went to his hotel room?
No, it's not.
That doesn't matter. Don't tell me I don't want to know. I just want...
What do you want?
I just want you to let this go.
Your plan?
Feel like some. This close. This close to my revenge.
It won't be much longer.
You promise?
Promise.
I don't want to see you get hurt again.
The people you're dealing with are insane.
I won't.
This dirty little gold digger is trying to seduce everyone.
I'm going to put an end to you.
Madeline. What's going on?
I'm resigning.
You're what?
I'm leaving, Luke.
Someone let you know that I hate some of the best experiences of my life working here.
No, she's doing this to you. Olivia's pressuring you to quit.
But she's right.
I should have never sent those pictures out.
That was you?
I don't know what I was thinking. I'm so stupid.
God, it's just that I have a crush on you.
You do?
Oh, Madeline. That's totally fine.
You have no idea how special last night was for me.
Me too.
Oh, God.
But that's not all. There's something else.
What?
I'm Madeline. You can tell me.
Maybe Felix's sister, half sister.
Olivia found out and now she's threatening to tell everybody.
Look, I don't mind one bit.
Look, and as far as your job's concerned, you're absolutely safe here.
You got it?
Why are you so good to me?
It's because I'm in love with you, Madeline.
Got you where I want you.
Aren't you going to say something?
Well, it's just that I'm so happy and also so sad at the same time.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm happy because I feel the same way about you too.
Anyway.
But I'm sad because we're married and...
That means we'll never be together.
Yes, we can. We'll break it off with her. You'll see.
Okay.
You're so beautiful. You know that? Can I kiss you?
Not until you're divorced and single.
I agree. I'll start working on it right now.
You will?
Yes.
I'm going to go back to my place, grab my things. I'm moving out.
What you mind joining me?
It is a beautiful mansion, isn't it?
Although, now that I'm a billionaire, I'm definitely going to upgrade.
My home. So many memories.
Madeline. What's wrong?
It is beautiful.
Well, I'm going to get some things from the garage.
You mind picking out some clothes of mine from my room?
Oh, is... is she here?
Oh, Olivia? No. No, she's probably at the spa.
Come on.
Luke and I just had the most amazing sex on that bed.
We came back here for...
How's it going? Almost finished?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
You know, I just love this shirt, don't you?
This feels familiar.
Hey, Luke. You got your new shirt. What do you think?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, hi.
Hey, come on. Let's get out of here.
Bitch! I'm going to make your life a living hell!
You did this to me once before.
It's my turn to do it to you.
My bedroom.
Finish up that gold digging bitch once and for all.
Did you watch the video?
And?
She's been lying to you this whole time.
That's not Felix's sister.
That gold digging whore is trying to seduce him as well.
There are siblings.
Hello? Hello?
Divorce? What?
Yes. I think Luke wants to divorce me.
That's impossible. But you two just got married.
It's because of his new assistant, Madeline.
She's manipulated. Luke seduced him.
Don't you worry about this, Olivia.
I will make sure this gold digging whore disappears from my son's life.
You have no idea what you're talking about. Just stay out of this.
Luke, ask your mother. It is my job to look out for you.
Now you know that I want what's best for you.
And what's best for you is to stay away from her.
You need to fire her.
But you don't even know Madeline.
Speak of the angel.
Sorry to interrupt.
Luke, I just wanted to confirm your three o'clock conference call.
Madeline, please come in.
I want to introduce you to someone very special.
You are a disgrace.
It's very nice to meet you, Bunny.
Watch your manners, young girl.
You addressed me as Miss Moss. Got it?
Mom!
Luke, I must say I am quite disappointed in your hiring practices.
There are far too many gold diggers out there trying to sleep their way to the top without any qualifications.
Excuse me.
Excuse you.
Mom, mom, mom, mom.
Madeline here belongs to the Raphael family.
Raphael family?
The billionaire, Felix Raphael?
That's her brother.
She's an heiress.
Oh, my.
I am so sorry, Madeline.
Please, you don't have to apologize Mrs. Moss.
Oh, no, no.
Please, call me Bunny.
And come here.
Give me a hug.
First time this bitch has ever hugged me.
Luke, forget everything I said earlier.
And Madeline, please.
I would love to have you and Luke over for lunch tomorrow.
Oh, and bring your brother Felix over as well.
Sure thing.
Bunny.
They're good looking.
What do you want?
When much just came to ask you out on a date?
Really?
A date?
It's my brother.
Oh.
Luke's mom invited us to lunch tomorrow.
And what is the reason for inviting your brother?
Well, I need them to buy this whole plan so that I can drain them of every punny that
asshole and that old bitch have bankrupt them.
But don't have any idea how.
Any ideas?
Easy.
It just convinced them to go all in on a stock which will soon collapse.
Oh, it's stock.
You know what?
I'm a little too tired to think.
I wish I could somehow get a massage that would just help me clear my head.
A massage.
A little down.
And then left.
Here.
Right there.
Oh, yeah.
Ow.
Still sleeping?
All right.
Come on.
What stock?
Don't worry.
I got you.
Welcome you to Mr. Raphael.
What an honor it is to have you here.
Mike.
Your sister is one beautiful woman.
Did you know that?
Why couldn't you have married someone like Madeline and not that peasant fool of Olivia?
Oh, Mom.
Don't you worry about that.
Please.
Come in.
So, Felix, what are you currently working on?
Actually, my company is currently heavily investing in logos time.
Well, that's a publicly traded company, isn't it?
It sure is.
Why do you want to invest in that company if I may ask?
I'm not sure I can share that information.
Oh.
We're friends, aren't we?
Come on.
Felix, you can trust Bunny.
And look, they're solid people.
Well, in sight of where it is, they're about to finalize a revolutionary AI algorithm that
kind of drastically improves machine learning capabilities.
And this algorithm has the potential, in fact, is expected to be a game changer in AI.
There's billions to be made.
You can't tell anyone.
And I mean anyone about this.
We promise.
See, I told you you could trust them.
You think they bought it?
About the logo's check investment?
Absolutely.
Now, the question is whether they invest their end.
Hey, Mom.
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
What?
The logo's desktop.
Felix mentioned I invested a few million last night, and the stock is already up 200%.
200%.
Wow.
Okay.
Listen to me, Mom.
I need you to put all of your money into that stock.
All right?
All of it.
You sure?
Absolutely.
Listen to me.
I need you to invest all of the company's cash reserves into logo's tech stock.
Vuk.
Well, frankly, that sounds like a very risky idea.
What if the stock fails?
God, trust me.
I have insider information.
You have no idea how crazy the profit will be.
The profit from this investment will finally silence the board of directors.
And that means I'll remain CEO for good.
Hey, CEO for good.
Make it happen.
Yeah, okay.
Hello, boss.
Happy today.
Oh, it's a fabulous day, Madeline.
Fabulous.
Oh, by the way, I wanted to make sure you were coming to our annual company party this Friday.
I'm there.
100%.
Great.
And make sure you invite your brother, huh?
It's a shame.
What?
That I'm just your brother?
What else did you want?
Oh, you have no idea.
Come on.
Let's go get those fools.
There you are.
My God, you look gorgeous.
Mind if I borrow her for a minute?
Is everything all right?
More than all right.
Ever since I met you, Madeline, my life has completely changed.
I feel like a new and better man.
And because of that, I wanted to do this.
Will you marry me?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Me too.
You are a pathetic...
Oh, digging.
She's right.
I always knew you were a gold digger trying to steal my fortune.
I can't believe I married you.
You cheating asshole?
Well, it doesn't matter now because we're getting a divorce.
I'm having my lawyer draft up the paperwork as we speak.
Luke, no.
Please come on.
Oh, all right.
Fine.
What do you mean fine?
This is for you to disappear from my life.
Forever.
No.
You are not doing the exact same thing to me that you did to your ex-wife.
You dumped your ex-wife for her.
This is all your fault.
You stupid psychic.
You stole mine!
Stole your man.
Sounds like you're the one that stole that poor woman's man.
And you.
You cheated on your wife for three years.
Only to treat her like a dog when you dumped her.
Because she was a little overweight.
Blimpy Butterball.
Madeline.
What are you talking about?
Whoever told you that is lying.
That's not true.
Madeline.
Come on.
Pay no attention to that nonsense gossip.
My son is a good man.
And he will treat you right.
That's what counts.
She's absolutely right.
And not to mention.
You are the ultimate upgrade from that thing over there.
I knew at the moment I met you.
A classy and beautiful woman.
What are you looking at?
And why are you still wearing that ring?
It's no longer yours.
Here, look.
This belongs to Madeline.
Thank you, Mother.
Wait.
Is this just me or does this seem really familiar to you?
For sure.
Remember a few months ago?
It was literally right there.
But it looks like this time the roles have reversed for that woman.
Baby.
Trust me.
I'll treat you like a queen.
My dead body!
No!
I'm great!
Jesus!
She's just pretending to be an heiress.
What is she talking about?
Listen, Mom.
It's true that Madeline is an illegitimate child.
But she still belongs to the Raphael family.
Isn't that right, Madeline?
Actually, I don't.
I'm not a part of the Raphael family.
And Felix?
He's at my brother.
And?
Fat ex-wife of yours.
You're looking at her.
My God, is that that fat girl from last year?
No, it can't be.
Good one.
Very funny.
Madeline, if I could kindly remind you that this is no place or time for a joke like this.
Well, I'm not joking.
I may have lost all the weight, but I'm still the same person you humiliated and mocked.
Unmaddy Moss.
No.
No way.
That's impossible.
It's really me.
And now I've come back to make sure you all pay for your evil deeds.
I knew it.
You disgusting tub of larb.
You were stupid enough to fall for her.
I guess it's what you deserve.
What?
It's the stock.
The price is collapsed.
It's not even worth five cents a share.
You're saying this stock is worthless?
I don't know what we're going to do.
The company's insolvent.
We are going under.
You did this.
You're responsible.
And you.
You've played me.
Like a flute.
You touch even a hair of hers, I will break you in two.
You finished.
Broke.
That's not even the worst of it, is it Felix?
Indeed.
Looks like you're going to have to lawyer up.
Your misappropriation of corporate funds is going to land you in jail for half a lifetime.
You take one more step and will ensure the other half.
Can't wait to sign the divorce papers.
I'm going to take everything you have.
There's nothing to have.
What do you mean?
I invested all of my personal fortune into that stock.
What?
It's gone.
All of it.
A few weeks ago there was something you wanted to ask me, but you didn't.
I remember.
Tell me now.
It's not so much something I wanted to say.
It's not just something I wanted to do.
And what was that?