Yeah, this place is way expensive.
We should probably go somewhere else.
You didn't close your eyes this time.
No, I didn't.
Is this expensive?
Of course it is.
You couldn't even afford that if you sold your to the kidneys.
Yeah, I didn't know they allowed people who shopped at Goodwill in here.
No wonder Dan dumped you.
She's right.
You look like a homeless person.
This place is way out of your budget.
Actually, I think we'll stay.
Thanks.
Right, Phillip?
Wow.
You sure do move fast, don't you?
Not even two days after breaking up and you're already handcuffed to this loser.
Shut the hell up, Dan.
You still have some of your baby teeth.
Ellie did say her ex was the biggest mistake of her life.
Seems like she was right.