Do you have any idea you were messing with?
Apologize now. Do you think a simple apology is enough? No, you should be begging for my forgiveness in your dreams
Give me the manager now
Where the hell is security? How can I help you guys out? Don't worry. I got this
Get these two cockroaches out of my sight. Take us out
You think you have that authority miss what seems to be the problem? These two do not belong here and I want them gone. Mr
Miss mr. Wesley my my sincerest apologies
At least boyfriend is a Wesley as in the Wesley group. Is it this restaurant owned by the Wesley group?
Could could he be? No, there's no way the Wesley air grew up abroad and I heard he's hideous
Why bail on the engagement?
He can't possibly be the Wesley air
So she's the woman my mom forced me to get married with and she bailed on that engagement because of some rumors
Good ingredients
Throw them out