Sorry Philip, I've been really busy recently, forgot to call you back.
Turns out that Ellie ran off of Braun a while ago.
Your sister went abroad?
Yeah, the very day you came back. She didn't even show up at the bar.
Your sister's name is Ellie, right?
That's right.
Could she have been pretending to be Ellie Murphy this whole time?
Give me a file on the new hires of the company. I need details on an Ellie Murphy.
Leslie Graham really lives up to its reputation.
Impressive.
I heard today's the first day for the mostly heir, a CEO.
Wonderful, get lucky enough to see him.
Oh my God, don't get too excited.
Rumor has it the hot words cancel their engagement because he's a hideous.
CEO?
It's you.
Mr. Wesley, there's no Ellie Murphy among the new hires, but there is an Ellie Harper.
Ellie Harper.
I'm a sticker for someone else, so she wasn't pretending to be poor.
Then what did she think I was?
You took my advice and got a proper job?
The CEO's coming.
You quiet.
Ellie.