Fill up.
What's so urgent?
When are you finally getting married?
Mother, I already told you that's my personal business.
Don't try to fool me.
If you don't bring me home a daughter-in-law this week,
I'm going to disown you.
Married in a week.
The CEO's been coming to this department a lot lately.
All thanks to you, Director.
Oh, it looks like somebody's online for a promotion.
Let's keep it together. Let's keep it low-key.
We're having a team dinner tonight.
Didn't expect it to be so boring.
Don't party too hard.
What are you doing over here all by yourself?
It's a party, can't you see that?
You know, I've always seen your potential.
It's the first day that I hired you.
Who do we discuss your future in private?
People look around. It's a party.
I appreciate the offer, but I prefer to keep things professional.
Are you seriously turning down a one-on-one with the director right now?
Come on, Ellie. Don't be such a buzzkill.
He's trying to help your career.
Guys, guys, guys.
Don't pressure, Ellie.
If she doesn't want some career advice, that's okay.
I can handle a little rejection.
But please, Ellie, stick around.
Have a drink.
Show a little team spirit, huh?