Whether he's willing or not, it is not to him.
I'll make the decision.
Gloria, I would like to work at the Wesley group.
Get closer to Philip, spend more time with him.
Good idea. You young people need more time to build a connection before talking about marriage.
I was too hasty.
Ellie, I won't let you succeed.
Philip is mine.
Can't believe I just married the CEO.
Why not? Is it so hard to believe?
Mr. Wesley, I'll pay you back to 300,000. I know this is just a marriage of convenience.
We won't interfere in each other's lives.
And if you want to end the marriage at any time, we can come back and get a divorce.
I won't go tell people on your wife enough.
I won't cause you any trouble.
Mr. Wesley?
Mrs. Wesley.
Are we really that distant that we are talking about a divorce right after we get married?
Okay. Baby.
Joanna came by today.
Oh, did she?
Yes. What's going on between the two of you?
Joanna really likes you.
When exactly do you plan on getting married?
I'm already married.