Are you deaf?
I'm speaking to you.
You're fired.
Pat your crap and get out.
Well, first of all, I'm not a home wrecker.
Second, I did not leak company secrets.
Well, we got an anonymous tip last night
that our competitors' internal data matches ours completely.
So why are you denying it?
How could you be so sure I'm the one who leaked it?
Couldn't it have been you?
What the hell is going on?
She is Mr. Wesley's fiance.
How dare you accuse her?
A home wrecker with such nerve.
I mean, how the hell did you even get hired here?
I said you're fired.
Pack up your stuff and leave.
And if you don't go now, you'll end up behind bars.
I stole your boyfriend once, and I can do it again.
You're no match for me.
You have no shame.
Ellie's acting crazy.
You should just act with me in front of these colleagues.