Apologize now!
What's going on here, Joanna?
What happened?
Philip explained this.
Mr. Wesley, Joanna's guilty.
She stole the Wesley groups' confidential information.
Gave it to another company.
But I brought her here to apologize in front of you.
How could you, Gloria?
It's all a big misunderstanding.
Mr. Wesley, you and I, as you know,
we've worked together a lot before.
Please have mercy.
Interesting how your daughter doesn't seem to be the least bit remorseful.
I mean, even now, she says this is a misunderstanding.
I... I...
Workplace bullying.
Miss Treating new employees.
Accusing others of stealing company assets.
What seems to be the misunderstanding?
Jo!
How could you do this?
This talk of it.
It will matter to educate it.
It was all an act.
I did think I... I considered you to be my daughter-in-law.
I never would have seen you again.