Ah, look everyone, it's Ms. Wesley, my daughter.
She won't even call me Dad when she sees me.
Stop this nonsense, whatever this is.
We can talk about it privately.
You think I'm stupid?
You're just afraid I'm gonna make a scene and ruin your reputation as Mrs. Wesley.
Isn't that it, huh? No, no.
Let's talk about it here and now.
She always seemed so kind.
Turns out it's just an act.
She won't even acknowledge her own father.
Guess she really just wanted to marry Rich.
Enough. You just want my money? I've given you everything I have?
What more do you want from me?
You know, damn well, why don't want to see you?
What's wrong with the daughter providing for her father?
I mean, if you don't have the money, Philip does.
I mean, just ask him for it.
Please, Philip's money has to do with you.
I'm not gonna ask him for money to fund your gambling addiction.
You've never been a good father to me.
Why should I help you?
All my life, you've done nothing but treat me like shit.
You've even tried to sell me to an old man.
You want a grateful child spewing such lies.
You've pushed me the edge.
I no longer want to live.
How could you do this to your father?
You're not even her biological father, though.
How are you?