Oh, so you must be my son-in-law.
Well, quite the catch.
You know, Ellie won't be.
Yeah, I cut the act.
You don't share a single drop of blood with Ellie.
You're just a parasite.
What are you saying?
We handle this.
How the hell did you...
Security.
You get this piece of shit out of here.
Guys, no.
No!
Ellie, no!
Listen!
I need my malle, I need my money!
Brian was a heavy drinker and gambler in his early days.
Ever even married.
You and your sister were abandoned and articulate.
I should not.
No matter how hard I try to, you always hated me.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble.
I'm here now.
I will not let anyone hurt you ever again.
Is this how you greet people now?