How dare you hit me?
Oh yeah, I got a juicy headline you guys have been waiting for.
The wife of the Wesley group's CEO is nothing but a conniving home wrecker.
Ms. Hopper, is it true that you slept your way to the top?
The Wesley's were set to marry into the Howard family twice.
How did you manage to steal away Mr. Wesley against Joanna?
Answer us. Did you know you become the home wrecker?
That's not.
The reporters are all on my side.
Welcome to your public disgrace.
Mrs. Wesley, there is trouble at the company.
What is it?
It appears that the young Mrs. Wesley is involved in some sort of scandal.
The company's stock has been plummeting since this morning.
Contact filled immediately.
I don't care who it is that he married. Tell him to divorce her.
Yes ma'am.
It's her.
Okay, let's take you to the clinic.
So that's the one that he married.