You've lost your memory?
I'm kidding.
You scared me to death? I thought you really forgot me.
How are you? How are you feeling?
I overheard you yell in for them to find who did it.
You sounded pretty intense.
You heard that?
Yeah. I think I know who did it.
Mrs. Wesley, we found them at the airport before they boarded their plane.
Oh, thanks to you.
Please forgive Joanna.
She was drunk last night. She didn't really mean to-
Excuse me, Mr. Howard.
Since when does being drunk justify hitting someone with a car?
So, my husband is seriously injured and no one faces any consequences?
You're right, Mrs. Wesley.
Mr. Wesley, I didn't mean to actually hit you.
You weren't trying to hit me.
You were aiming for my life, weren't you?
I've been putting up with your shit for too long.
I'm over it.
Have fun rotting in prison. Take them to the police.
Yes, ma'am.
Mrs. Wesley, please forgive us. Please, Mrs. Wesley, please.
Please, should it mean it?
I don't know, and we'll try to keep us apart.
Are you looking for this?