Happy birthday, Nolan.
I have a present for you.
Happy birthday, honey.
Nolan, not right here.
This is a public event. I'm still your Luna.
Not anymore.
Nolan?
I, Nolan Heming,
Alpha of the Blue Ridge pack,
reject to you,
will Heming about for,
as my mate and Luna.
Hi.
Nolan, we've been mates for a year.
I gave up everything for you for the pack.
So what?
I deserve your she-wolf who matches my station.
The meal here is the daughter of our beta.
And you're just a peasant.
Ting your child.
You observe my child,
except my rejection now.
Why cry?
I know I'm hard to leave, but-
I accept your rejection.
You are a demon,
and you deserve to be with a bitch like her.
I-
No!