Willa, Willa, Willa, Willa, Willa, Willa Minabelle for.
Who are you?
Your second chance is close by.
He has been searching for you for the past seven years.
You're the moon goddess.
Okay, listen, that whole faded mate thing that you set me up with, it nearly got me
and my son killed.
Is that not enough for you?
I don't want a second chance.
I don't want another faded mate.
You understand me?
I am done with your games.
From now on, I'm going to choose my own mates.
Leave me and my son alone.
Tragedy is part of your fate.
Just like your upcoming happiness is part of your fate.
See?
He's waiting.
You're not going to make another decision for me.
I reject him.
Remember.
Black hair and red eyes.
He is noble and wears a red ring.
He will take you to the most miraculous place.
He will meet his end.
Because of you.
Shut up!
You're not going to make another decision for me.
I reject him.