Willa, I love you.
What are you doing?
I was told humans give rings when they start relationships.
I said that we're in a relationship.
That is too fast to put it away.
Right.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that familiar with humans' love rituals.
You know, our race doesn't have to do these things.
Okay, well, our hands just touched and no red line appeared,
so it looks like I'm not your mate.
Perhaps you should go and find your faded mate.
I tried.
I tried looking for her for a long time,
but she never came.
So I decided to find my own.
Why me?
Shall I compare me to Summer's Day?
They're all more lovely and more temperate.
They're all twins.
God, stop.
You are embarrassing yourselves.
Do that anymore.