Oh, hi, thank God you're here.
Thank you so much, so, so much.
You are such a lifesaver.
You have no idea how much I appreciate this.
Do you know what time you'll be?
Bye.
See ya.
Gonna be back.
Hi.
You said that already.
Sorry.
Hi.
Do I fit it against?
Yeah, but we don't have any.
We have no solution.
This house is cool.
Come on, buddy.
Cass, please be patient with Emet.
Please, please, please.
No, come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
All right, one more round, one more round.
Cass Bien, you said we would watch cartoons if I won.
Well, patience, young racer.
OK.
One more round, and if you win, you get to watch cartoons?
I'll allow it just this round.
Pick you a racer.