The night calls, there's only one place for the fucking town, where will the burgers,
where we take the wildest country without a legendary wolfback burger,
sink your teeth into a beast of a burger, with a juicy maddie, melted cheese, and fresh, crisp toms.
I thought that male werewolves were supposed to be possessive.
Guess who we're good there?
Let's go to another meal.
Why not?
And he becomes Max the Whale.
I'll show you.
What do you think of Emmon?
Emmon?
Amazing.
If he was mine, he'd be my best friend.
He's a blessing.
He really is.
Yes.
Yeah.
Do you really love me?
Everything about me?
With all my heart and soul.
Then you were my chosen Caspian Draco's.
Mark me.