After dropping out for school, I take you to the office.
I won't introduce you as the new Luna.
Missed about four, Alpha Tree Coast.
Welcome to Crescent Moon.
You two are the perfect match. It's an honor to have you guys.
Thank you.
I know you two had a hand in this relationship.
I appreciate it.
Oh, so there are two more things left to do.
Hold them and make announcements to all PAC members.
Let them know that Willin is to be the new Luna.
And Griffin is in a notarized letter to Alvin Noah.
Be clear that he no longer has any more rights from my son, haven't you?
Alpha, I dropped to it last night.
Well done.
Send a message to Blue Ridge back immediately.