You're stronger than I thought Willabelle for, but didn't anybody ever tell you not to
play with other people's mates?
That's really funny coming from you.
You uh, tell your little servants about your love story, or are they fucking you too?
You're pathetic.
No one even showed up to help you.
You're like a stray, wandering around like a beggar.
Get ready to die, Willabelle for.
Don't you dare.
It's fine.
I'm here now.
I'll kill anyone who tries to hurt you.
Dear Prince Dragos, I'm Camille, the Luna of the Blue Ridge.
We met seven years ago.
Do you remember?
Camille, you were charged with insulting the royal family and intentionally causing harm.
Your judgment will be delivered at the next alpha meeting.
Insulting the royal family, Prince Dragos, I didn't insult you.
How did you become a Luna?
Miss Balfour here is the Luna of Crescent Moon and Princess of the entire race.
No, she can't be the Princess, she's just...
And as for you, Nolan, since you're an awful leader to the elders,
it's really a little strip of that title very soon.
Come on, Princess, let's go.