20 miles in three minutes must be a little tired to kill you
Sorry, I was late see you home trade that plane might be a little too simple for me, buddy
Three four trade deal that one's your deposit. I'll give you the other two later deal
Our sons are gonna make a good businessman one day
Yeah, you will. How are your tests gone all days of course alpha
We found out no one's base is on Coyote Street downtown. He left this morning, but he comes back every night
Griffin you come with me. Make sure no humans or worlds get involved hold him
Stay and look after the pack
Any questions? No alpha. You're just missed and the goddess be with you
Cuz I really bad feeling about this. Why can't we just get the elders to you no Nolan? No, it's my job to protect you name it
I need to end this sooner rather than later. I'm serious Cass
Nolan's a psychopath. He's gonna do anything to hurt you. Well, that's the case
You're more danger than I thought
I need to finish him off sooner rather than later. Cass you could die
It's a small price to pay for your safety. It's okay
You're making
Your partner doesn't invent some word
Descent us
tonight
Medicaid in did you find the weapon? Yes alpha Nolan
Check it out
This is a cursed dagger one scratch will kill even the strongest of one whoops
What did you find this the King's dungeon took me a while to break in
After I killed that arrogant prince will regret her decision
And come crawling back to me. It's time
Baby, I'll be fine
Promise come on. We're not a scratch. Luna. You're made as the goddess has chosen warrior goddess has chosen warrior. Cass just show her
Black hair red eyes
Noble
Where's a red ring?
He will take you to the most miraculous place. I don't want another faded mate. You understand me
We'll meet his end because of you who wears gasps
I'm sorry Luna. They just left. No
No, no, he's stopping. That is an order. Luna. I'm following the Alphas orders
I don't give a fuck about the Alphas orders. You are going to stop him that idiot is gonna die
Oh my god, please don't leave me believe
Caspian won the battle he killed no one but the best of stabbing with a fucking dagger
Luna
Alpha Drake goes lost a lot of blood. He needs a blood transfusion immediately. Then what are you waiting for do it?
There's not enough blood in the blood bank. We can't find enough blood
Take mine, but Luna. He's an alpha. He needs a lot of blood. It would be extremely dangerous that I said take mine
Caspian
Cass
Hey, can you hear me?
Don't you hurry. Why are you doing anything?
Please
No, you have to stay with me. You have to stay with me. Okay. This is not how our story is supposed to end
Seems like the fallen chapter for me. That's a good life. Met him by grace
Good friends
Asteries with remembering. Take me back. Take me back to them. Let's go home. Mom was waiting. I don't believe it
It's a miracle. Alpha Drinkos is alive
You would a meteor shower some web
Save my life
That's his gift power of resurrection and redemption. He's a son with the meteor
The moon goddess is greatest gift. What do you're looking at? Pretty someone in the whole world
I'm a platter. I need you to tell me something. I'm not your food in me. Yes. Yes
It's the only way I could keep you
Sorry a lot. I love
Can't say a regret of this
Can you forgive me? What are you willing to do?
I mean, everything
I guess you're stuck with me then
You're my reward for all my past sufferings
I was born through and I loved it. You've got your degree a new job a husband
It's a fairytale ending
No, go get your happily ever after
Well, I mean a bell for when you protect these people not only as their Luna, but as their princess
upholds not only the values of the crescent moon, but also the royals I will
From now on you will be the princess of all werewolves the Luna of the crescent moon
It is my absolute pleasure and honor to present my grandson
Prince Emmet Draco's of the crescent moon path