Maybe I should give her a chance to explain herself.
I guess I'll just surprise you, man.
Any idea what to bring on a date?
No idea, sir.
Maybe ask Michelle.
Michelle, a CEO would like to speak with you.
What gifts would I bring on a date?
I think it depends on your relationship with her.
She's my wife.
Have you bought her gifts before?
No, I haven't had a chance to yet, but I'm going to make it up to her.
Well, I mean, girls love sparkly jewelry.
Maybe diamonds would be a good choice.
Even if she doesn't wear them, she could use them as like a collector's item.
That's good. They do like diamonds.
That's a great idea.
Well, I have a pretty unique diamond ring, so...
Get her anything else you might like and make it a limited edition.
Now I have to serve the best.
You got it.
Hey, Michelle.
Look, I know the boss is being very nice to you,
but you can see how much he loves his wife,
and I don't want you to think that you can replace the Mrs. ring.
No, don't worry.
I'm here for the job and the money, not a shot at the CDO.
Good. Well, once you grab everything, you can leave.
Okay, thanks.
Your wife's house boss?
I actually like it.
Hey, can you go to the store and give me some size house?
Please, I need it for the recipe.
No, I need to...
Hey!
Go with you boss.
No.