My husband is paying.
Then we can wait for your husband, then.
Here you go.
If anything doesn't fit, you can come back any time to exchange.
Thank you, Jeffrey.
Excuse me, are you serious?
She gets to leave without paying, and I don't.
She is the owner of this store.
Why would I charge the owner?
Look, I'll pay.
You can just mark it under your sails.
Oh, thank you, Mrs. Herbert.
Mrs. Herbert?
He knows Michelle and Lucas are married.
I can't let Lucas come here.
You find everything you do?
Yeah, yeah, I did.
This is everything for the business trick.
Anything you want?
It's all yours.
Just, uh...
Consider a pain right of force to sit.
I'm just doing my job.
I should go.
Hey, so anything she wants?
50% off.
Actually, do you want anything she wants?
Put her on my job.
Thank you, sir.
Your wife is a lucky woman.
My wife?
Isn't that who we were just talking about?
Here you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
What?