Please don't comment, I'm just disgusting.
You can't even recognize your own wife, Lucas.
You'll always be in my palm.
So she's trying to get close to the boss.
No wonder she was making fun of the sister.
In.
I'm sorry, madam.
We don't welcome you here.
Please leave.
No one wants to shock your gross storm anyway.
Have a good day.
Yeah.
Lucas, your wife agreed to walk out of the marriage with nothing.
I thought she was being reasonable.
It's all an act.
Yeah.
Get this.
She hasn't used her credit card in four years,
and all of a sudden there's a $50,000 charge on it.
You know what that means?
What?
Now that we're getting divorced,
she's finally showing her true colors.
She hasn't seen it coming.
Hold on a second.