Mrs. King, you can't just...
There you are!
I'm so sorry, sir. Mrs. King insisted on seeing you now.
What's going on here?
Lucas, are you okay? I was so worried.
Mrs. King, Lucas is just recovered. He needs to rest.
I was talking to Mr. Herbert.
Who are you to interfere with our conversation?
Actually, my secretary can speak for me any time she wants.
And if you have a problem with that,
well, I don't think we can work together.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Lucas. I was just being silly.
Listen, I came to drop off a formal invitation to our family banquet.
I was hoping to see you there so we could properly celebrate our new partnership.
Yeah, we'll be there.
Wonderful. I'll see you tonight then.
I look forward to being your date.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Okay, come on.
All right.
Well, get ready to go to the banquet with me.
I thought Mrs. King was going to be your date.
Not really in the mood for another allergic reaction.
And Lucas's drink, and bring it to him.
Lucas, welcome!