Hey
Why are you here? I should be asking you that
Thank you for this. No, you can keep it. I didn't think the tough girl that just chased down a thief this morning
I said just outside to her
Hey, you're you're here for an interview, right?
Why don't you go ahead you way in the break room, okay? Oh?
Look and lady. Hey
He works here too. He's kind of sweet
What's your hold on please? What is she doing here? Are you still tangled up with your eyes?
No, no, of course. I she's probably here for an interview or something. She's like, why would I be interested in her when I have you?
Baby, look at you. Yeah, that's true. It is. No one can compete with me. No
No one. Besides, I bet she doesn't even know that daddy is VP of Grace and Group. Oh VP, huh?
Don't forget.
Oh my God, seriously.
Hello, Mr. Dennis, you gotta help me. There's just someone trying to fire me. Who who's trying to fire you?
Mr. Grayson's fiancee. I accidentally offended her and I didn't even know we had a fiancee. They're trying to kick me out
Mr. Grayson, that's a fiance