Mr. Gracie and NASA Piancé?
What?
I've been trying forever to get with him, and now some chip just waltzes in and takes
him?
If it's Mr. Gracie's decision, I can't help you.
All right, you're on your own, buddy.
That's weird?
Yeah, no, it's very weird.
Since when does he have a...
I don't know.
We'll go find out.
Let's go together and...
Wait.
Before we do that, I have to take care of someone.
I have to talk to Liam.
Tell him not to hire that bitch.
Get with him.
Okay.
I'm with it.
Ooh.
Let's go.
Ooh, he's so evil.
Nice.
Sam, come in.
We've dealt with the security guard.
The director he's connected to is a new hire named Simon.
From what I understand, you got into the company through his relationship with Davis's daughter, Jennifer.
Okay.
Liam, for now, he's a small-time director, can't cause much trouble.
I want you to bring in the girl from the break room.
I'm sorry.
Remember the girl that was bragging at the entrance?
I want you to bring her in.
I want you to tell HR that I want to make him my secretary.