What the hell is going on here?
Could I land Simon so now you're after Mr. Grayson?
What?
He's Mr. Grayson?
Liam.
Don't let this woman fool you.
He's Mr. Grayson at work.
Mr. Grayson!
Don't let this woman fool you!
I mean, you can see what she's trying to do.
Clearly she's trying to seduce you.
Since when do I need your approval for hiring decisions?
Hey, I'm Alice.
The CEO's new secretary?
The CEO's secretary?
A slut like you?
Hey, enough!
Your dad may be a shareholder, but you're not.
Stay out of the CEO's office.
You'll pay for this, bitch.
Thank you for the save, Mr. Grayson.
I'll go check in with HR.
Ooh, not so fast.
It's not that simple.
What do you mean?
Today's the day your dreams come true.
I am going to officially make you my fiance.