That bitch, Alice. How dare she seduce Liam?
What? Liam, Arab, the Grayson group?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Could she be the so-called fiance?
Yes, impossible.
Liam's mother has ridiculously high standards.
Count with socialites and nobles
didn't make the cuphouse short.
Possibly!
It's time to chance her.
I need to call Miss Grayson.
I am going to officially make you my fiance.
What?
Beyonce? No, no way. I don't even know you.
You know, I thought this is what you wanted.
Wait, did he overhear me bragging with security?
I'm... I'm sorry, Mr. Grayson. I can't.
Well, yeah, okay. Um...
Listen, what if I told you, right?
I told you this is the only way you're going to get the job.
Then I would say that I can't work here.
You can go.
Did you change your mind already?
Uh, no. I, um...
I actually accidentally got some lipstick on you earlier.
Any shirt?
It's, um...
Hey, uh, could you give me a new shirt, please, now?
Oh, no, actually.
Honestly, it's my fault. Just...
Let me buy you a new shirt, Mr. Grayson.
Okay. Uh...
Yeah, fine. Um, you know what?
You go to, um...
James and Jackson on the next block.
I'm awesome.
You've always had custom tailored shirts and suits?
What if James and Jackson doesn't fit?
Yeah, come on. You know what it says?
It's this low price, average quality,
but then, come on, it's got decent style.
It might be cheap for you, sir,
but, uh, it might be a lot for ours.
Tim.
Thank you.
That's why I'm going to take care of so much about that girl.
You know what you see, huh?
What do you mean?
I'm going to officially make you my fiance.
Snap out of it, though.
Where is James and Jackson?
Ken, no worries.
I'll just ask Liam to explain this whole fiance.
Watch out!
Ah! Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
I did this.
I'm sorry, ma'am. I didn't see.
Thank you, sweetie. You have quick reflexes.
No worries. Are you sure you're not hurt?
Yeah, I'm good.
What's your name, sweetheart?
Oh, I'm Malice, but I'm sorry, ma'am.
I have to get back to work.
Take care.
So she works at the company, Alice.
She'd make a fine daughter-in-law.
Then begin.
What are the chances?
Excuse me.
Do you have a shirt for a man who's about 6'4?
We might have one that fits.
Please wait a moment.
Well, if it isn't your ex, since when
can she afford to shop at a place like this?
Hey, Alice.
We heard that you are trying to seduce the CEO.
Dream on, Mr. Grayson already has a fiance.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you know who she is?
Definitely not some bottom feeder like you.
You're way below the Grayson family standards.
Ma'am, your shirt is ready.
That'll be $18,000.
$18,000 for a shirt?
Mr. Grayson didn't give you his car.
Oh, that's so sad.
Even if you try to buy his paper, you don't have the cash.
If you beg me, I might consider paying for it.
After all, $18,000 is just pocket change for me.
Why not make your investment worth it?
Like, you know, Alice can trade with you and go to tonight's
banquet with Mr. Hodges.
You've not been feeling well, if I recall.
Do you ever, you've been feeling ill?
Did Simon give you one of his nasty diseases?
What?
You know, some of those can be incurable.
All you can do is get to die.
No, that's not true.
All that talk won't get you that shirt.
If you can't afford it, just get lost.
Liam doesn't want a streetman like you.
Is that so?
Because I wasn't aware that I didn't
care about my own fiance.
Oh, wait.
I don't want to tell them the fiance?
Mr. Grayson, you must be joking.
Did anyone ask for your opinion?
Shut up.
Hey, baby, I forgot your card.
Be my fiance to help take the pressure away from getting
married from my family, and I will
give you a job as my secretary.
And this, which can give you anything that you want,
including all this respect.
I guess you're right.
Oh, babe, you're right.
I was in such a hurry I must have forgot it.
That is a limited edition black card.
He really gave it to you.
I'll leave you and your lady to your shopping.
Simon, let's go.
Oh, hey, who says you can go?
Did you just try to pimp out my fiance to some shabby banquet?
No, no, no, Mr. Grayson, I'm so sorry.
I offended your fiance.
I'm so sorry.
Are you apologizing to me?
Are you apologizing to Alice?
Alice, I am so sorry.
Oh, wait.
But what was that I couldn't hear you?
Alice, I was wrong, and I'm sorry.
All right, that's it.
He apologized.
Can we go now?
Yes.
Sir, you packaged the suit you came in with
for the one you're wearing.
Sir, cash your card?
Oh, Jennifer, did you pay for the suit that I'm wearing right
now?
Oh, my God.
What gold user?
Is that a no?
The card from the car.
Whoa, wait.
Where are you going?
You can't leave.
You haven't paid.
Well, I just got a great idea.
Why don't I buy the suit?
You can put it on my card.
Take it off.
The full suit.
Alice, we were so close.
Close?
Why don't you say?
I'm engaged now.
Simon, don't take it off.
I'm going to have to call the police.
Yeah, OK, OK.
Here's the suit you wanted to miss.
Thank you.
Hey, Simon, come by the office later.
OK.
Process your resignation.
And why don't you bring that security guard buddy to yours?
Alice, you won't get away with this.
Thank you for today.
And you can take Simon's suit out of my paycheck.
I don't need it.
Now that we made the deal, black eyes yours.
I can't spend your money like that.
So you just want to blow your own money on a suit?
Your ex-boyfriend is worn?
That's not what I meant.
OK.
Listen, as my fiancee, there's one more rule you must follow.
No inappropriate relationships with other men
before our agreement ends.
And you don't have to wear high heels to work anymore
because I'm going to miss a shoe anyway.
These are beautiful.
They look good.
Thank you for everything.
Hey, Mom, what are you doing here?
If I hadn't come, how would I know
that you suddenly have a fiancee?
Well, listen, now that I'm engaged, please,
can you just stop with all the matchmaking?
Honey, I know you hate the idea of marrying for status.
But I have found a really wonderful girl this time.
She's beautiful and kind and she even saved my life.
Hey, I made up my mind, OK?
I'm not marrying anyone else but my fiancee.
Nonsense.
The Grayson family cannot have some random girl
as a daughter-in-law.
Mom, she's not just some random girl.
She's all so beautiful and she is kind.
And if you'd like to meet her, I can arrange it.
Hey, Tim.
But I want you to meet the girl that I picked out too.
Yes, boss.
Bring Alice here.
Wait, are you both talking about the same Alice?
Mr. Grayson, do you have a secie?
It's you.
I'd like to see you again.
So you know each other?
Yes, this is the girl I want to set you up with.
OK, so do you approve of her as my fiancee now?
Approve, of course.
But I have one condition.
You must register your marriage.
Two day.
What?
It looks like me.
You know, we got no choice.
We got to get married.
It's a little part of the plan.
Hey, listen, you know, we'll just, we'll, we'll, um,
hey, I'll give you more money.
I didn't even thought I'm not being married yet.
Hi, Mom.
Your sister's getting worse.
Didn't you say that you got into that pharmaceutical company?
Can you get the medicine early?
Don't worry.
I'll figure something out and be at the hospital soon.
OK.
I'll marry you.
Can you get me some of the new drug
the company's been producing?
Yes, the one for the nervous system?
Of course, I'll see what I can do.
And when can we get divorced?
Let's figure that out later, OK?
Let's just, you know, let's just get through this crisis first.
I've already made an appointment for you too.
Go get married now.
Alice, come have a dinner with us tonight.
I want to introduce you to everyone.
Sorry, ma'am.
I have some things to take care of.
You young people are always so busy.
Fine.
But you must come next time.
Of course.
OK.
All right.
I won't bother you too anymore.
I'm leaving now.
Can we get the medicine now?
It's definitely here.
Your sister's going to be OK, right?
Don't worry, Mom.
I have the medicine.
Hi, Ms. Black.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to make sure someone delivers
her daughter's medicine regularly from now on, OK?
Alice, how is this?
Oh, Mom, this is my boss.
And she's the one that got us the medicine.
You're such a good person.
Oh, I heard that this medicine was so hard to get even,
even for someone who has money.
Actually, Alice and I are officially working together.
I will definitely be able to afford
Betty's medicine from now on.
Mom will you excuse us, Liam and I need to discuss
some work matters.
OK?
Hey, am I so embarrassing to you?
It's not that.
It's just our relationship is an agreement
that will eventually end in divorce.
And I don't want to get my mom's help up for nothing.
Fine.
Yeah.
I remember what you just said.
This is an agreement between both of us and nothing more.
So don't get attached.
It is absolutely unheard of for anyone
to get this medication.
If you keep it up, there's hope your daughter
could make a full recovery.
Thank you, Dr. Brown.
Don't thank me.
I think I'll ever provide it this.
Mr. Grayson, thank you for arranging the VIP room
for my sister.
I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
It's OK, look, I don't even think it.
OK, but this, you know, comes to the price.
They've been around for me tonight.
Is something wrong at home?
Mom left me a message.
She said that Jennifer told my grandfather
about our marriage.
So he's angry.
Just, you know, come for the dinner tonight.
OK.
Yeah, I'll try my best to help.
Dad, this is Liam's wife.
Good evening, Mr. Grayson.
Nice to see you again, Alice.
Jennifer, what are you doing here?
Is that how you speak to a valued guest?
If it were for Jennifer here, we wouldn't even
know about your secret marriage.
Of course, Jennifer came to title.
All right, enough chit chat.
Dinner's ready.
Alice, come on.
Let's go.
Liam, how long have you two known each other?
I've, what, two, three hours?
He means we got married two or three hours ago,
but we've actually known each other for years.
Yet you only introduced me to your wife
after you're married.
You clearly have no respect for me.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
Liam's just been so swamped with work.
Did I ask you?
Typical.
Just what you'd expect from a woman with no class.
No, Ms. Cox, is stealing someone's boyfriend
how you show class?
How dare you speak to my life?
How dare I?
Are you Liam's wife or am I?
Enough.
No bickering in our thing.
Grandpa, say no more.
I hear that Alice is your current secretary.
Starting tomorrow, Jennifer will take over that room.
Mr. Grayson, I don't think that arrangement is appropriate.
How dare you?
You have no right to meddle here.
Dad, don't be so hasty.
Let's hear Alice out.
I just mean that for a company as big as the Grayson group,
hiring is a rigorous process.
You can't just hand a key position,
like the CEO secretary to anyone.
I'm sure I can handle the job, thank you.
OK, well, why don't we put that to the test?
I can go over some of my qualifications.
I graduated from Harvard Business School.
I won the BCN Global Finals, and I could speak five languages.
Chinese, French, Japanese, Spanish, and of course English.
What are some of your qualifications?
I believe the company values ability more than a...
OK, well, let's put some of those abilities to the test as well.
Honey, could you hand me that document?
See, our company's top client is a Chinese firm.
If you could translate this Chinese document,
we'll consider you qualified for the job.
What is all this?
Didn't you understand it, Ms. Con?
Mr. Grayson, this woman is deliberately making things
difficult, OK, to try and embarrass me?
Ms. Cox, is this how you plan on negotiating with future clients?
By whining?
Here, let me teach you a Chinese proverb.
Mayo, jin ganzuan, bia, lan, tichu, or, which means,
if you're not qualified, don't come for my job, rookie.
Did she just call me a whore?
Jennifer, enough.
I think you'd better focus on your current job.
Oh, that was delicious.
I'm done, bye.
That was impressive.
I did not expect it to be so eloquent.
There's a lot you don't know about me, Mr. Grayson.
Alice, it's getting late.
Why don't you two just stay here for the night?
Sure.
What am I supposed to do now?
Are we going to sleep together?
Was that on purpose?
Because you're not wearing any heels this time.
No, it was an accident.
Oh, really?
Could you open the door for me, please?
I'll need tea for you too.
Drink it before you rest.
Thanks, Ma, I'll take it.
Well, I forget myself.
So I want to see you drink it before I leave.
Thank you, Mako.
All right, I'll eat you guys.
Good night.
Oh, sleep on the chair.
I'll be holding my grandchild soon.
Why am I so dizzy?
Feels like I've lost control of my body and mind.
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't control myself.
Where are you going?
I can sleep somewhere else.
Why is this locked?
Now it must have been my mom.
We're married now.
What are you so afraid of?
But it's just a big marriage, though, right?
It'll eventually end in the divorce.
I'm interested in you anyway.
I'm going to take a shower.
It's you.
You want to meet the first move last night?
OK, I'm sorry.
I almost forgot.
It's OK.
What?
Make it up to you?
Don't you want to come on to me last night?
Right.
Shouldn't you take responsibility for what you do?
OK.
What do you want me to do?
You should have mentioned divorce anyway.
I get ready for work.
Tim, are you incredible?
I appreciate you.
Thank you.
I'm going to grab a coffee.
Do you want anything?
Watch out, Tungo.
I don't mind.
I can get it myself.
I'll see you at the opposite.
OK.
You ruined my life.
You're not going to get away with it.
You want to make sure we solidify these contracts
the night when you get it done, OK?
Lee, I wanted to apologize for what happened yesterday.
Jennifer, you're disrupting my work.
Please leave.
I won't bother you and Alice anymore, OK?
I promise.
But it's it.
Answer it on speaker.
Answer it.
Jennifer, I've got Alice.
I'm going to strip her naked and live stream.
It's ruined her reputation.