Where's Liam?
This meeting is about our strategy against HDS Pharmaceuticals.
Is he fawning us off with the secretary?
Mr. Grayson is an important meeting with potential partner.
He'll be with us shortly.
You bitch!
You leaked company secrets.
Jennifer, we're in a meeting right now
that you weren't invited to.
So please leave and don't make accusations without proof.
You said I don't have proof.
HDS Pharmaceuticals just announced their new partnership.
With the supplier, we now used to proof form.
How's this possible?
We felt a bit in there?
Who did the proposal?
This new secretary did.
She even colluded with HDS and leaked the purchase proposal.
Take a look at her emailing your secret or something.
Jennifer, is this true?
Yes, it is.