Someone at work is messing with me.
What happened?
It is that new Secretary that leaves him on.
She is just out to get me.
Yeah, I heard that Liam was, uh, paying someone special attention to his new Secretary.
I'm still a major student.
Now, can Daddy do?
Deputy, I want her to disappear.
That wraps up the meeting, anyone have any questions?
I have something to say.
Mr. Grayson here.
Sure.
Uh, without realizing it has been favoring his new Secretary to the expense of his other employees and the company.
For the sake of fairness, I believe that we need to let her go.
Does everyone agree?
Mr. Grayson, for the sake of the company, I recommend letting her go.
Okay.
Um, um, what if I disagree?
Well then, sir.
I'm afraid that I just don't see a future with this company and I would have to attend to my resignation.
Alright.
Fine.
Davis, you can go ahead and you can hand in your resignation.
Don't forget to, um, liquidate your shares.
Sir.
Have you lost your mind?
You're going to side with the Secretary over one of your major shareholders.