Hey, Mrs. Grayson!
You know, since you are the CEO secretary,
you and I are gonna be spending a lot more time together.
Mr. Cox, you're sitting in a seat that doesn't belong to you.
Doesn't that make you rather nervous?
You still think that Liam can protect you?
Oh, you're just gonna have to learn how to watch him now.
Please, Leaf.
Who do you think you are?
Oh, that's right.
You're my secretary.
Here is the agency agreement from Grayson Group,
signed by George Grayson, starting now I am the acting CEO of this company.
Is he insane?
You're an outsider, I have the second most sure effort, Liam.
That was just a copy.
The moon will be sent out shortly.
Do you know anything about running a company?
Do you?
I heard you bankrupt seven companies in the past three years,
losing millions of dollars of Grayson family money.
If you don't back off, I'll send my legal team out to you.
Liam, what about all those promises you made?
Flowers, the ring, the proposal?
You haven't kept any of them.
Why aren't you awake?
Where is that?
Quick, I saved my grandfather.
Go!
What happened?
He's flatlining.
We need emergency assistance at the VIP room,
emergency assistance stat.
Trying to resuscitate Mr. Grayson, please leave, he needs space.
Mr. Grayson, Mr. Grayson, what's going on?
What's, talk to me, talk to me, look at me, look at me, look at me.
Stay awake, stay awake.
Nurse, nurse, get in here now.
And that concludes our recent internal adjustments.
Are there any questions?
Meetings adjourned.
Oh, I have a little something.
This is a 20% equity transfer document.
That is, stand by, George Grayson.
Now, with my initial 10%, that makes me the largest
shareholder, which means I'm going to be calling the shares.
I don't know what underhanded tactics
you use to get those shares, but you are not the largest
share.
Liam still holds 30%.
Liam is a bad shaball.
So it's either me or the guy who eats through a tube.
Who says I'm a vegetable?
Liam.
You've been through so much.
Wow.
You should know that you're not the only 30% shareholder
anymore, so you're also not the only one about me.
Because you killed the chairman for 20% of your shares.
I have no commitment.
The chairman is dead?
How'd this happen?
Wait, what are you saying?
I couldn't save grandpa in time.
Because that night, I saw Mr. Cox leaving grandpa's room.
You didn't notice the cufflink that was missing
on your right sleeve?
It's just like the one on the other sleeve.
I can't believe anyone would be so ruthless.
Kick him out.
You have a cufflink.
Oh, big deal.
Well, guess what?
I was the only one at the hospital that night.
You were there, too.
Maybe you killed him.
I have proof as well.
I was worried about someone trying
to hurt the chairman or Liam.
So I had surveillance cameras installed
in both of their rooms.
You know what?
I have time for this ridiculousness, what do you think?
What do you think you're going?
I already contacted the police.
You can tell them your side of the story.
Does it hurt?
You just let all the hospital.
Shouldn't you be resting?
I've missed you so much.
I heard her stalk tanked after Jennifer
pulled out the talk's family's investment.
Well, I won't back down, though.
You know that painkiller that they've been secretly
producing overseas?
Well, it doesn't mean international standards.
So grandpa, you look the other way for years
because of old ties.
But no, I won't have any part of it.
I have a plan.
Yeah?
What is it?
Well, since Davis is in custody,
I'm sure a lot of people, including Jennifer,
don't know that you're out yet.
We could put on a show.
It's Cox's year.
Jennifer, Alice?
Long time no see.
Let's cut to the chase, all right?
I want to talk about a partnership.
Partnership?
What partnership?
Your painkiller product line.
Liam's never been interested in that particular project.
Yeah, well, I'm not Liam, OK?
Well, we have other investors now.
We don't need grace and group support.
Well, you might want to look at the terms
first, just to make sure.
I didn't expect Mrs. Grayson to be so generous.
Considered a gesture of goodwill.
You know, I'm still getting my footing
with this whole CEO thing.
Right, well, I will take this with me,
and I'll have to consider it.
We'll have to consider it.
Of course.
Right.
I look forward to hearing from you.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Hey, are you sure about this?
Not really.
Their privately developed drug has always
been sold on the black market, but with the Cox family's
limited funds, my offer should be tempting.
You'll just have to wait and see.
Looks like they took the bait.
This is a gesture of good faith from us.
This is definitely more detailed in my investigation.
Of course, this is all confidential information.
Wait, what?
You investigated us?
What?
Ms. Cox, where are you?
The company swarmed with police.
They say they're investigating our privately produced pain
killers.
What?
Do you have anything else you'd like to say?
Liam?
You're awake?
Hey.
This?
Jennifer, come on.
Cox family's been producing illegal drugs,
and now we've got concrete evidence.
How is you, bitch?
You nasty little porn.
How dare you walk over me?
I dare.
Because I've done nothing wrong.
Everything I have, I've earned with my own merit.
I have been resting at home for seven months,
and the doctor said it was good for me to go on some walks.
I'm just bringing Liam some lunch,
and I'll go right back home.
After all, it is our one-year anniversary of our meeting.
I at least gladly am draggy, I hope.
OK, Mom.
Love you.
Excuse me, ma'am.
No entry without all the drinks.
Are you new here?
I am.
How's you know?
I'm the chairman's wife.
Can I go in now?
I'm about, I mean, I can call.
Boss, this security guard is now.
Trotato?
Wait a minute.
You and those sneakers?
Even if you were the chairman's wife and bragging about it,
you'd at least say you're the CEO's wife.
Well, I was the CEO's wife.
What?
Look, stop daydreaming before I have to call for backup, OK?
Who is it?
Mr. Grayson.
I'm actually glad you're here.
This woman right here claims to be your wife.
Really?
I'm in a good mood today, so I won't fire you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Much happiness to both of you.