How could you do this?
Aren't you afraid that we're gonna report you to the Union?
The Union?
Have of them work for me. You think they're gonna side with you?
Mrs. Walker, please don't blame my daughter.
It's all because of me. She only got her into you into it with your son because of me.
Please let her go.
I don't have time for you filthy bottom feeders.
So, are you gonna do it or not?
Security, hold her down and make her apologize to my son.
Sorry, Mrs. Walker.
I don't blame her. I'll slap myself if that'll work.
See this railing?
If you jump, I'll let you down to go.
Heck, I'll even throw in 10 grand.
Jump already is just two stories tells anyway.
Is that like you're gonna die?
No, Dad, please don't do it, okay?
Please, I'll let myself just don't let him jump.
If you don't jump, I'll fire a daughter.
Press charges into a rotten prison.
You don't want that.
Fine. I'll do it.
Dad, no, please don't do it. Don't jump.
Walk along. Jump? What are you waiting for?
Mrs. Walker, if I do this jump, you promise to let her go?
Kill him.
See ya.