Dad, are you okay?
It's awful.
Still alive, huh?
Mr. Walker, I jumped.
Can you please let my daughter go now?
And my paycheck.
Your paycheck?
You smashed my car.
You owe me money.
It wasn't his fault.
You pushed him over the railing.
How could you be so cruel?
So what?
I don't get the ten grand.
In three days, he's going to jail.
No, please.
I'll work it off, okay?
Please don't send him to train.
Get out of here before you journey up my company anymore.
Is that worse?
Yeah.
You're...
Forget it.
Granny's gonna go to the hospital.
You're getting worse.
It's nothing.
It's just a fall.
But...
We don't give money to doctors.
I just want to go home.
There's something I have to give you.