Now that you're both adults, it's time to take on the family business.
Tomorrow we'll be celebrating the 20th anniversary of the company at the Los Angeles Hotel.
And I'll be announcing that each of you will be managing one of the two branches.
And in three years time, whoever performs best, will take my place.
I'll do my best to fall on your footsteps, Mom.
I'm so happy to have you all grown up.
Let's celebrate.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers, Clara.
Don't worry.
It's coffee, not alcohol.
We don't keep any booze in the house because we know you're allergic.
So it's like having you here with us.
Clara, how I help you with this for real?
You're the smartest.
If you come back, you beat the perfect edge of the Walker group.
Where are you, sis?
You saved my life back, Mom.
I'm straight in mind for you as if I could.