So, Jackson, what do you think about her?
Her cornea is good enough?
He's bright, beautiful eyes.
I'm very pleased.
You never disappoint Walker.
Look, I agreed to donate my cornea,
but when am I getting the half million dollars?
Greta, don't worry.
We've already signed the contract.
As soon as the cornea is out,
the money will be in your account, all right?
Greta, everything's ready.
We can proceed with the surgery now.
Here, you can make the transfer.
Half a million is a pretty good transfer.
Come on, Caleb.
You don't really expect me to pay her, dude.
What do you mean?
She's just a poor nobody.
And the fact that I'm willing to take your cornea
is a privilege to her.
Expecting pain was a joke.
Look, man, I did it.
Come on, Caleb.
You know the parties we can throw
with half a million dollars.
I wasted on a worthless nobody.
Just leave it to me, okay?
She's not going to be expecting a dime from us.
Trust me on that.
As bastards,
I have to stop Greta before it's too late.
Keep his eavesdrop on us and get away with it, old man.
I should kill you for this.