Did you find Clara?
False alarm.
What happened?
It was this stupid Greta, always causing trouble.
Hayley lost her diamond hairpin at the banquet.
And Greta, desperate for money,
thought it was valuable and tried to keep it for herself.
Greta doesn't seem like the type of person to do so.
We've given Greta too many chances.
Tomorrow we'll settle her wages and fire her.
By the way, where's Caleb?
He left a little while ago.
Caleb's been in a car accident.
Your father's condition was bad enough.
Now with this injury.
I'm not sure he'll make it to the end of the month.
Dr. Ora has been an accident.
Caleb Walker was in a car crash.
He's lost a lot of blood and he needs to transfusion immediately.
His blood type is AB negative,
but we don't have any in stock anymore
and we don't have time to fix this.
AB negative?
If something happens to him,
Mrs. Walker will have our heads.
Dr. Ora, what shall we do?
Greta, come with me to save Mr. Walker.
This could be a way to pay for your father's treatment.