Doctor, how was my son?
Mrs. Walker, Caleb has lost a lot of blood.
It's helping, but it's not enough.
And she's already given more than she should.
If we take any more...
Take it!
My son's life is worth more than hers.
If I have to, I'll pay her off later.
Mom, that's just way too risky.
Greta might not survive.
And you remember how grandma ordered Clara's blood to be drained.
Don't make the same mistake.
Shut up!
She's just a janitor's daughter.
Her life is not worth more than Clara's.
If her blood can save Caleb, it is her honor.
And we'll just pay off David later.
What are you waiting for?
If anything happens to my son, you will pay.
Draw the blood.
Mom, you can't do this.
Draw it!
Mrs. Walker, I cannot do that.
If you can't do it, just leave.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you, Dr. Scott.
Dr. Scott, this will put Greta's life in serious danger.
Mr. Walker's life is more important.
Do it. Get out.