You don't have any left. There's nothing more we can do.
No, take mine. I know. I can do it. Take all of my blood if that will do it.
Your daughter has AB negative luck. Not just anyone can donate to her.
Look, I have a badge.
I understand how much you want to save her.
But AB negative is incredibly rare.
When she was young, her child was just a child, she almost bled out.
I saved her with my blood. I can't. I may be negative.
I can save her. I'll take full responsibility if anything was wrong.
Follow me. There might still be time.
Could it be? Is Greta really?
He's awake. My brother's alive.
You've been terribly injured. You need to just rest and stay put for few days.
You have to be more careful from now on. AB negative blood is rare if he hadn't been so lucky this time.
Who saved me? Who gave me blood?
You just need to rest. Dr. Scott, how's Greta doing?
Her life has been saved. But she'll still need to be closely monitored.
It's best if she's not disturbed.
Dr. Scott, are you sure that Greta and David are related?
Could there be any chance that...