From a genetic standpoint, they both share the same, very rare,
ab-negative blood type. They must be related.
So they're really our father and daughter. I'm just hoping that...
Mom, I have an idea how we can find Clara. There's too many people at the banquet to
check individually,
but if we offer free health screening to all the employees
and compare their DNA to ours, you might find a match. If none of the employees
match,
we then can extend our offer to the banquet guests, or by when we can find Clara.
That's brilliant. Let's do it.
Dr. Scott, your hospital can handle the screenings.
Of course, when you won't let your dialysis walk.
And cover all of David's medical expenses.
I don't want any debts left unpaid.
In other words, they'll cling to us forever.
Understood.
Clara, hold on.
We'll be reunited soon.
No, good. I think you should quit the Walker group.
You know, I've always taught you that there's a
shard of goodness in everyone, but the Walker family,
maybe they're just too cruel.
Mr. Scott, you're here.
Yeah, Mrs. Walker is covering the cost to your dad's kidney transplants,
and I'll be performing surgery.
Get ready.
We'll do the operation in the next few days.
I do know I trust them, or who knows what they're planning this time.
Mrs. Walker is helping you to settle a debt.
She doesn't want any ties with you in her life.
Don't be ungrateful.
Dad, look, I really think you should do it.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
Besides, I already gave my blood to Caleb.
So if you don't go through with it, then I would have suffered for nothing.
All right, I'll do it.
Let's just hope the walkers aren't planning to deceive us this time.
You should be grateful that you're even considering helping me.
It is an honor for family like the Walkers,
to help other family substitutes.
That looks like...