Wait doctor Scott the only reason I was late was because of traffic stop playing the victim and get lost
What's going on here miss Walker? It's Greta
She was late and miss the health screening and now she's asking doctor Scott to do it just for her
The daughter of the gender with dirty trashy blood thinks that she deserves special treatment
My brother survived a car accident because Greta's blood saved him and you're calling it dirty. What Greta saved mr
Walker's life Greta is a hero to the Walker family and if you bully her again, you're gonna have me to deal with mrs
Walker I may be negative blood is extremely rare
Keeping Greta close might just save Caleb again in the future
shut up
Greta go get checked as long as I'm here
No one will dare mistreat you