It's all my fault. You were here the whole time and I didn't see it. I even scolded you earlier today. I'm so sorry
It's okay, mom. I'm just happy that I'm home. So Haley is our sister. That means the ring at the banquet that was lost was for yours
So if the ring was yours, why don't you come look for its dinner? The banquet was chaotic
I thought I lost it somewhere else and I've been losing my mind ever since
Don't worry about that now. I'll make it up to you. Mom
It was all Gretta's fault. We should fire her
Mom
Gretta saved Caleb's life
If we fire her now might make us look cold-hearted
Yeah, we should wait till I'm fully recovered. I mean who else we're gonna use if I hate blood later
She's the only one with my blood time
If you fire Greta, you'll have to find someone else for Jackson's cornea transplant. He might not buy it
Better keep her around
Mom, I just said it in the moment. Sis and Caleb are right. We should see the bigger picture here
Don't worry sweetheart
We'll get rid of Greta soon enough
Greta you little rat. I'll make sure you're out of here