I have an objection.
Father?
Gentlemen.
Tristan has been secretly meeting with outsiders
to sell our company shares.
I mean, someone like that shouldn't even be in the company.
Let alone running it.
Just stop this nonsense.
No, Ted.
But for yourself, all the evidence is right here.
Signature there, there, and there.
Tristan, what's the meaning of this?
I don't know anything about this.
I was never informed of these documents,
and I would never sign anything like that.
Looks like your signature.
Going behind the company's back to sell shares, I mean.
This could lead to the media and seriously harder reputation.
Mr. Hamilton, I think you should make a conclusion
after a thorough investigation.
You're right.
We will conduct a thorough investigation.
And until this matters resolved,
Tristan will be suspended from all company duties.
This is defamation.
Why don't you just explain?
Yes, it doesn't matter if it's true or false.
But come on, let's go home.
What's going on?