If the lights weren't being so weird, I wouldn't have lit so many candles.
You don't think I'm being wasteful, do you?
Oh, she's not.
And a little scaredy cat is afraid of the dark.
So what are you going to do next?
Do you have a way to deal with Josh?
Even if I had a way to take Josh down, it wouldn't make me happy.
He's my baby brother.
I feel like we've both just been pawns
and my father's schemes for the business.
Forget about your family.
What do you want?
Well, I thought I wanted to become the top perfume company in the world,
but I feel like that was my father's dream.
And not mine at all.
When I was five years old, my mother taught me how to make my first perfume.
I called it Miss B.
I don't know if it was my mother that pushed me to be a perfumer,
but all I know is I truly do love it.
You'll find that too.
You just need time to discover your own path away from your family.
Well, luckily I am some time, and luckily I have you too.
If.
If what?