I let you compete. You were never supposed to hurt each other.
No. He's right.
This is your fault.
All you ever cared about is this company.
Nothing else you compare, not even your own sons.
You were gonna let us fight it out,
and see who could become the better tool.
Tool?
How can you say that?
On my own.
I always trained you to take my place.
Tristan was always your replacement.
Why not me?
How can you compare yourself to Tristan?
You've never done anything that satisfied me.
Then why did you let me compete?
Huh?
Why did you encourage me?
You always told us that you would treat us the same, right?
You gave me hope, time and time again.
And you denied me again and again.
But I get it now.
I was just a tool to sharpen Tristan.
You used me to train him.
Bullshit.
You'll still refuse to admit your mistakes.
Your mind is twisted.
You wanted us to compete, right, Father?
So let's go.
Right now.
I'm gonna show you who the real man is.
Come on.
Let's go.
Stop it.
Josh.
Stop.
That's enough.