Quora, something happened.
I know.
Josh blew it.
Tristan's vision is returning.
What?
Now Josh is useless.
Who knew Blind Tristan would put up such a good fight?
Quora, what should I do?
No worries.
Tristan was never our enemy.
After all, isn't he still Quora's husband?
My husband?
You mean, let Ashley come back?
How can I let Ashley come back?
I want her to disappear from Tristan's side completely.
That way when Tristan wakes up, the first person he sees is me.
The real Quora.
I'm the one who's been by his side.
I'm the one in love with him.
Quora, can't we just stop this?
Now you want to be a good mother?
No.
No, we're in too deep.
She's also my daughter.
Your sister.
What would you have us do?
Sister, she took everything from me.
And you.
I will take everything from her.
Hurry up.
We gotta go.
Perfect fit.
Tristan, Tristan.