Hi, table for two please.
I'm sorry about what we have booked until the end of the year.
Fancy restaurants are always so busy.
This was just a wasted trip.
Of course. Please, this way to the VIP section.
Wow, you really have some influence here.
You must bring all of your customers here.
I'll just have this thank you.
Oh, certainly.
I didn't understand what the menu said,
but I think the first line were the special dishes.
Excuse me, miss.
You're on the catch-off.
Uh...
Any requests?
Volvicki are there.
Uh...
They have la finiche, la coda de Bianca.
Yes, sir. We just got it.
We'll start with the white phoenix tailfish,
and then to have to start, we'll have the American ham.
Certainly, sir.
Miss, you have excellent taste.