Wow! That ranted suit is quite impressive, but your tie's a little bit crooked.
Why do you pick out a dress?
Or maybe I should buy one for you.
Acting just like a qualified boyfriend.
Keep it up tomorrow.
I'm very sorry, but I can't do it tomorrow.
I can shine on my own.
It's too far.
Isn't there too much of a show?
You didn't tell me it was going to be a picnic.
Well, where's your boyfriend?
He, uh, he couldn't make it.
Couldn't make it.
Well, just doesn't exist.
He used to be the beauty of our school, Bella.
What happened to you?
Right?
We were classmates, but this way.
We won't be no illegally anymore.
You're not welcome at all, I really need.
But to leave quickly.