So, you're missing everything, I love you.
You've got a bit of food?
Yeah.
Fun. Why would you take people over this to me?
In my world, isn't it usually followed by a can?
200k? A day?
Harry, we're going to be late in front of us.
Hey, who's kisses?
Better. You're late for work.
You're missing your allowance for the day, it's punishment.
But, supervisor, there's a boy here.
Is there a brother?
Bring your family to work costs £100 fine.
Supervisor, he's not my brother.
Aaron's. Do you have that contact?
My mum left me when I was a child.
Everyone I meet, laughs at me.
It's okay. Is there anything I can do?
I'm really hungry, really.
Let's go grab something.
Okay.
Boss, the new interview was late for work,
and she even brought her family to the office.
It's very unprofessional.
Our company promotes flexible working hours.
Besides, employees who have care into what some of the teas are allowed to bring in their family if they need to.
Instead of nitpicking your colleagues, focus on your own work.
I have to go pick up my uncle on the day.
Finish off the Venus Project, will you?
They're an important client.
Sir, you just wait.