Bella, what are you doing here?
You're not made are you?
Your mum's made.
Seems like everyone runs in the family.
What are you doing here?
Alistair invited us.
Bella, where are you going? You're not going to serve as tea.
You don't deserve tea made by her.
You must be Alistair.
Sorry, we didn't mean to order your maid around.
She's not my maid.
She's my woman.
So, she's your girlfriend.
Music cooperation deal is set then?
Actually, on second thoughts, from now on,
I want our cooperation to end.
Our family ties, now cease,
so I kindly ask you to leave.
Well, it's the why.
Because of your condescending attitude to Bella.
Cousin, we're wrong.
It's feet for us.
Bella is kind,
and I won't tolerate any disrespect.
Now, get out.
Cousin, we're wrong.
Can we speak for us?
Get out.
I believe that someday you'll be a strong woman.
But for now, may I support you.