Close your eyes
Focus on the beating of my heart
Now call for your wall
Give your dominant. I
Summon you later come forth
Why is nothing happening?
Try again. I
Summon you later
Come forth
In present pain Natalia
Yes
Yes, you can
Natalia, how do you feel? I feel like I can do anything
Be careful Natalia
There are people out there who will seek to use you or worse hurt you
Trust your wall and summon her when you need her. I will it here take this
What is this I realize how disconnected you are from our true community not to worry you will learn
It's a wall spade
Take it and promise me you will be safe. I promise you. Oh, it's like a ring my mind
Founder boss. Are you sure it's her? She's supposed to be dead. Oh, yeah, it's her