With the company girl
Emma, I'll call you back
What do you want?
You're a bitch
You should be very careful
You call in a bitch
You should be careful with that pretty little mouth of yours
You're catching trouble
I ain't afraid to hit a little girl
I told you
Be careful how you call in a bitch
Bitch
I could have handled that, you know?
It'll be too easy
What's the fan on that?
Tonight
The biggest ballast advocate
In all of New York City
For us
You know, I couldn't have won this case today
If it wasn't for you
You are my family
Would you like some more red wine to go with the chains?
Um
Excuse me, Emma, just one sec
You should answer that
You haven't spoke to him in two years
It's time
Day