You coming in?
So Blake, guess what?
What?
God of the cold with Natalia.
And?
And she's just a damn little kid
because she's so stuck up on her new life in New York.
She's not even thinking about going back into our work.
I was just thinking, you know?
This might be the right time of you choosing your true owner.
Who do you think I should choose?
You.
Why not?
We've been doing this thing for a while now, and it's good.
You really think that I would choose a sad, orphaned little witch?
Stick to your job.
You're such a dick sometimes, you know?
Yeah, and you like that dick, don't you?
It's about Alfred Ray White's down there in your office waiting for you.
He's still alive?
What does he want?
He says I'll only talk to you.
Okay, tell him I'll be five.
All right.
I can't do it.
I won't do it.
You're not in position to bargain a woman.
These are my terms.
And without me, your pack would be wiped out.
The moon howler survived ten years ago because I sent my daughters away.
If I bring her back, old wars will start anew.
No one believes in the white wolf myth anymore.
All moved on.
You should too.
I don't think you understand, Blake.
If this new army, the outcast says they're calling themselves.
If they take out the moon howlers, who do you think is next on their list?
It's you.
We're the dark stone moon pack, the biggest in California.
You really think they can stand up against us?
Haven't seen this clan, Blake.
I have.
I fought against them and I barely survived.
You know why?
Why?
Because for some reason, they allowed me to.
These are my terms, right?
Taking my living.