Leah, what are we gonna do?
I'll tell you what we're gonna do, Natalia.
We're gonna try two years ago.
Fight. Protect our pack.
We don't need my contact.
I can't believe he actually thought I would marry him.
He's delusional.
Always was. Always was.
Hey, Auntie.
Long time no speak, dear niece.
Yeah, must be interesting.
I've missed the salary voice.
He's not doing too good.
Sorry. Are you back from your vacation?
Just bored and hangover.
And then I saw you looking spaced out.
Something up?
Just, you know, family problems.
Family problems?
You haven't spoken to your family for like a couple of years.
Or have you?
Well, I heard from the mother yesterday.
Do you remember that guy I told you about from back home?
My sister was going to marry,
but she ran away off with his brother,
so he abandoned us in the middle of a battle.
Yeah, how could I forget?
Well, girl.
Listen to this.
My father has arranged for me to marry him.
Like, what the hell is that?
Some kind of like 1800s or something.
Wow.
And what are you going to do?
We're going home to deal with this outcast ourselves.
Aren't we, Nat?
But what I do know is my father would never cold.
And ask me to return unless it was a matter of life or death.
So, I think it's time.
Time for a work to go home.