Shit. All right, chain them up. I'm a boy
What are you going? Where are you? I'll tell you I
Don't fear old man Ray Ray White is not my helpful. I got this. Oh
What are you doing here? If you really want this place you must understand something
I am not the type who will stay on the sideline
Does kidding me angry give you a fucking high or something either we are to you or we're nothing
Do you guys need some privacy? I can leave did your daddy not teach you manners your hierarchy is bullshit
It won't last for much longer. It's our time now Blake
I had a little brother who thought that way once you didn't end well for him
Now it's time for you to tell me everything. I'll take us anywhere. Let me try. I can find out here's plans
I'm not leaving you alone with him. Please for once
Trust me. I'll be outside waiting
Remember idiot no matter how scary he is or even if this bitch tries to seduce you
Don't tell them anything about our plans to attack the darkness don't back. Oh, I can assure you
free me
My bite is much worse
than a snare you can hear my wolf
I'm not your typical princess
Now tell me everything you know about this attack on darkness don't back
Shit
Why did you attack the moon pack was a deep way?
Isn't it obvious so we can lure Blake away from the dark stone pack take his territory and displace him as alpha
Do you think it will be that easy a bunch of words like you to take now play content?
No
But my alphanals play he knows his tricks
Tactics his weaknesses he knows everything about him. So cool. So you
You will find out real soon
Italian are you okay in there?
That's what I do really make a taste pop. What do you do? Fuck him? Of course not
I don't know what they've been. How?
Blake just trust me. Okay. You're asking me for a whole lot of trust without giving me any okay
You know the attack on howlers was a deep way decoy
Yes, and they're planning to attack the dark moon stone back tonight at midnight tell that's not a funny joke
And I'm not joking. I heard him and his wolf
You heard his inner wolf. Listen trust me. Don't trust me. I don't care
The only thing I want to know is
Tell that's not a funny joke and I'm not joking. I heard him and his wolf. You heard his inner wolf
Listen trust me. Don't trust me. I don't care. The only thing I want to know is what are we gonna do as a mole?
Head back to the pack house. We got trouble. What are you going to defend my pack?
I'm going with it. No, you're not
Yes, I am. I am the only person who knows what their canvas and if you want to be there before they will attack the moon dark moon
Stone pack you need me coming out to play Wolfie. You know me
What is she doing here? What is she doing? But why what the boss has boss
Their question in you they think if I am my father
You're probably wondering why I asked people to come out tonight
We're fighting old red white battles again, huh? Yeah, it worked out real well last time, didn't it?
What the fucking moon hollers? Yeah, we're here because the outcast came on our land. Yeah
Yeah, fuck what are people? Yeah, I told you we were ready. Oh, that was nice. Good care of you
What are you doing here? What is this place? I leave with a dark moon stone pack if you're you're talking, right?
My best friend is a werewolf and she didn't tell me why oh, no, I'm not a werewolf
I'm a witch and what you're scaring me right now. What is a witch has to do with my roots? Well
Blake saved me one day from the mountain tales one day to cover the territory
I can say that he gave me a family. So you were spied the whole time
Unfucking believable. So what you're gonna do with me? Oh
My job is done here
Just like ask me to
Spare you to knock you out
so I did that and
Now you're free you can go. Oh, so
Is there anything that I need to know?
I want you guys both of you
Why would you know anything about us? You know exactly right? You shouldn't have come here
Where you going? I'm gonna find Blake
Seven Minitalia allow me to fight and defend out. Do you think Blake loves her? What are you talking about?
Witch that's not important. Oh, she loves him. I can tell girl. You need to stop. Blake Hunter is the reason your brother is dead
He's the reason you were sent away. Maybe you're right, like
Blake
I saw what you're there come forth
Until next time brother. What are you doing here? Well, you're welcome. I didn't just save your life on anything
Are you purposely defying me?
Yeah, it is. Now is the perfect time to tell him that he needs to know that his brother is the one using the outcasts
You know, Blake, I have a friend who I thought was praying. Why'd you do in that?
Tell me what?
Reveal yourself
That kind of sarcasm because it is like I don't get it. You really don't know do you? No what?
Prophecy of the white wolf. I didn't believe it back then either. I thought it was a myth. Now. I know it looked like a
So are you gonna tell me or are you just gonna sit here monologuing?
20 years ago
An alpha fell in love with a moon god. I had a kid. The kid grew up
Came the white wolf. Man alpha
Who married the white wolf who chose her as his luna came the king of both kinds. I know it sounds crazy
Like stop it. It's true. You're lying. No, I'm not. Why would I lie to you?
Because my mother bled out and died
Well, give her a birth to me.
Apparently not
So you mean my father lied to me my entire life
Well
You are the white wolf
Felt your power
Trust me
It wouldn't be the first time your dead lied to you is it?
What is that supposed to mean?
It means back then
I didn't withdraw my forces because your sister rejected
How it drew them because your father refused to let me marry you
Now I know why
That's not true
It is true
Think about it. Tell
If we could have been married back then we could unite the pecs
And study sent you away
Well, I was here. I was the one fighting for you
Where are you going?
To confront my father
Are you sure your father's not?
I have to find out more before I was still Blake
Think you're doing
Did my brother sent you to finish the job?
I saw you the outcast camp. You tried to give Blake
Do you know who Blake really is?
If you did, you would be on my side
What do you even mean?
Do you know how many girls Blake has in a single week
Or a single night?
You're bluffing
I could see it in your eyes
You love him
Now I know you're bluffing
Well, too bad
It would have been a great ally
The great white wolf
Time to take out the hierarchy what's up
I'm ace now
I dropped him in once I got all the ties from back
Oh
Where's my sister?
That's a story for another day
You need to tell me
I will when I don't work
Where have you been?
Hi, I just had to clear my mind
Did you find the runaway outcast?
Not away
You know, I've been thinking
Yes
I will marry you but under one condition
And what's that?
If I'm gonna be a luna
I want to participate in all major discussions about the dark moustache
Why is it funny?
I used to work in the best little fear in my new york before I came here
It's just never been done before
And it will be it
Okay
You're the white wolf
You wish
Is my command
You need to tell him that you converse with the brother he hates before you marry me
You need to confront him about animal
Otherwise, you emerge with humans
Are you leaving my mother?
Because I could actually use the mother on the advice right now
What about some following advice?
I have nothing to tell you
I didn't know who she was
How could you not know?
She seemed normal
Introduced herself as Aria
A pure blood exhale by her pack
She loved
She really loved ACDC
Bon Jovi
All the classics
Really?
Seriously
And she was beautiful
My god, she was the most stunning woman I'd ever laid eyes upon
How did you meet her?
It's a long story
And one for another time
What matters right now is you
Blake
And securing our lives
By the way
Why didn't you tell Blake
That you ask Dylan to take away this one?
Where's my sister anyway?
I'm telling her
You don't like hates Dylan and Dylan
I'm hates you
How do you know about Dylan?
Have you lost connections for a little bit of children?
What do you know about Dylan?
It's all you
You ready for you?
Well, look at you
What's this?
It's an offering
Don't smell it
I told you not to smell it
It smells like death
Yeah, and it tastes even worse
You're nervous
Focus on me
I don't think you're the best
It's all you
It's my grandma
Alison
It's my master major
My child
My life
You're dreaming of this?
Imagine us again
You'll go first
Remember you and I'll femme fatala me
and try to poison me with waltz man
I didn't try to poison you
Yes, you did
Our hunter life
was from Celine
This means we have some
certain in-one abilities
We have to
It's time
Alpha Blake Hunter
Will mark Natalia White
As his chosen mate
They may not be fated
But we ask
You are not the moon
You know it'll be easy if you relax
Out
I don't want to
What you do, don't you?
Who is it?
It's me
Speaking of the devil
Damn
You need to talk
What do you need to talk about?
I want to go home
I want you to come with me
No sarcastic comment enough
Blake stop
Let's tell you something
The wolf
They'll attach you to the Alka's camp
Yeah, we think it was the alpha
Yes, but the alpha, the Alka's
You know him
How do you know?
My wolf there
She will hurt him
Blake will steal him your brother
Couldn't be
How would him know him?
It's him
Why didn't you just tell me?
I didn't know how to tell you
You should have told me when you found out
Tell
He betrayed me
He ran away
With my fate and mate
He tried to kill me
Like
Is there something else you want to tell me?
I don't know, I'm having murderous thoughts right now
How are you going?
I got no fucking idea
I'll tell you when I get there
Blake wait
You really want to come?
Of course where's your brother?
Fucking
Get him
We need to track him down
The brother who costs you your mother
You need to kill him before he kills you
Why does he have a good reason?
Goddamn your wolf telepathy
Spit it out
It makes sense that Dylan would do this
He always hated the hierarchy
Who better than be the leader
Or punch a rogue werewolves
Than a fucking hybrid
Blake watch out
Shit
It makes sense that Dylan would do this
He always hated the hierarchy
Who better than be the leader
Or punch a rogue werewolves
Please watch out
Shit
Don't look just him
Blake
It's easy
Oh he will see my wolf
Follow me, Ned
I can help
Please see it, help me
Close your eyes, Ned
You can bring him back
You've had the power within you
You, we, are the white wolf
What happened was driving
There was someone in the road
It was sort of, oh shit
Are you okay?
I'm like, how the hell am I so alive?
You help me a little
It's gonna take more
They're just the car accident to kill him
Blake
Nice enough
Your heart stopped, I built it
Don't try to get me
Kill this motherfucker
Sit or be done
I want to pick his flesh from my teeth
You feel me?
To give him
Also make us a list of allies
It's time to body up
Gotcha
I ain't never want to come closer to those in you again
We're all new now
Blake
I've heard about my system
No, not since I lost such a villain
How do you know about Blake?
Tell me
How do you know about my question?
What are you even doing here?
I can feel the darkness inside of a few
It's deep, it's like you've been touched by death
Are you okay?
Emma, you're crazy
What do you want?
On what do I want?
It's Friday
And we have fun on Friday
Not anymore, we don't
It's over
Why?
Oh, is it because of her?
Are you pushing me away?
For her?
No, no, no, no
I refuse to be the fool
We have to get to your mark, Anthony
Emma
Okay, no
Blake, you are completely forgetting yourself
By your side through all these years
It was me, not anyone else
Every battle
Stop
Get it through your head
I was using you
And I'm sorry for that, okay?
But not Talia's my wife
You think, babe?
Skill from 1 to 100, how pissed you think she is
I'd say she took it pretty well
Stupid question, stupid answer
So basically, you were using this point a little bit
to spawn
While having something on the side
Really, we take the floor
You can't get me out of own bed?
You deserve it
That girl
I have shoots
Shit things
This really means something to you, doesn't it?
No, not really
Fuck
Never say sorry
The floor sucked anyways
It's just a nightmare
I have it every now and then
I've had it out for California
It doesn't have any one nightmares
No, I do
All the time
You too?
Yeah, I'm not in vulnerable pain
I mean, I wish I was shit
What are they about?
If I tell you, you gonna tell me?
My mom
You never told me
I remember it like it was yesterday
My dad was actually with your dad
They were planning their next conquest
So my mom took Dilla and I to the park
We were planning to stick the wing game
and see who could throw it to farthest
And I was winning every time
Of course
But then eventually, we ran into some wolf hunters
A human trap
But I used to live with humans
And I can't even imagine them doing something like this
Well, they were definitely wolf hunters
Anyways
My mom told me and Dilla and she said run
Run like your life depends on it
And I did
My little brother, he's not as fast
They eventually caught up with him
But Dilla, he's fine now
Yeah
Because my mom went back and saved them
In the process, she got killed
I don't want to hate Dilla and I don't
My mom doesn't
She never did
He makes it so damn
He'll get bored of you, you know
Excuse me
Blake
Yeah, he does that from time to time
He will find a new toy
He will play you for a week and then come back to me
Because he always comes back to me
You are the most two-faced person I have ever seen
The fact that I thought of you as a friend as a good friend
You know, besides sticking shit, all you do is fake
I know you're hiding something from him
And I will find out what you're hiding sooner or later
Yeah, you do that
And we got the moon hollers and leaguers now, but
Help array
He's old, he's weak
He has 10 able-bodied men
I've invited every alpha I can think of to the wedding, so
You should be good
So you know, pecs dynamics
But you're also making plans about my wedding
Without me
The bride?
Hell, not everything's always about you
It's bigger than that
Okay Blake, there is something else I have to do with us
Dylan, he's no name is Ace, he's one
Dylan and Ace are the same person
And you guys both fucking knew about this
Wait, Ace and Dylan are the same person?
That means that
The hybrids and the outcasts are both run by your brother
How the fuck do you know that?
I met him in the castle
But he and his men managed to escape before he got there
Tell you're holding stuff from me again
How am I supposed to ever trust you?
Anyways, what do you mean you met my brother in the cabin?
Yes, and he cornered me with his wounds
And I couldn't find a straight answer about Elizabeth
And that's it, that's all I know, okay?
And I didn't tell you first because he told me that you were a womanizer
So I wanted to find out for myself
And, and it's true, focus yourself
Why do you think I was so conservative when I saw you and me?
And you still agreed to marry me?
Because part of me is a warrior
And I need to marry you
To make sure that I will get what I want
Besides, Ace
Is also a great wolf
The one who killed my brother, Zach
So, off of him, waiting
We'll take a fight to Ace back
Hell, Zach died protecting you
The last thing we need is another white wolf order
The best thing we can do is take Ace out
Before the shit get down
Then let's take him out
How exactly are we supposed to do that?
You always thought that the white wolf would make danger
Yeah
What about your pack?
What about other elves?
Probably
So let's do it
Present me
That's the white wolf to your pack
Boss, this could actually work
If the other elves see that you got the white wolf as your lunar
They'd have no choice but the one day see you as king
You see, my small grizz