You sure she's okay?
She's fine.
I don't know, Grandma.
One moment she was okay and the next she passed out.
Physically, she's fine.
We'll know more when she wakes up.
Until then, why don't you have a rest?
I won't be able to sleep until she's up yelling at me and pissing me off.
Grandma, why are you looking at me like that?
The last time you looked at me like that, I was made alpha.
You love her, don't you?
To admit it, you know.
You two may not be fainted, but she is your soulmate.
Are they not the same?
No.
Your grandfather was not the person that the moon goddess chose from me, but he was my soulmate.
And if I can see that Natalia is yours, soak in the pack too.
I bet she doesn't like it.
Grandma, stay with Natalia.
Where are you going?
Not a heart to heart with a witch, that's for sure.