Massimo, you're a pure blood, right?
Yeah.
Back in the day, our forefathers ran these forests.
All pure bloods.
But then some of those dudes couldn't get their dick in their pants.
Got with some humans, painting our bloodlines.
That's the history.
Can't rewrite it.
But you can change the future.
Uh, enlighten me.
For millennia, our people have been fighting each other.
Wolf against wolf.
Over what?
Mates.
Territory.
Wasting our day on time.
Failing to see the true threat.
Humans.
Humans wouldn't know a werewolf if it bit him on the ass.
We're just mythological creatures to them.
That's it.
No.
All it takes for one human.
And he's gonna tell another.
And then he's gonna tell another.
Yeah, and the full moon comes out.
And a werewolf bites a human and kills a couple of them.
Chaos.
Exposing our people.
Massimo.
And then what happens?
To wolf hunters.
That's the cycle.
It's inevitable.
Unchangeable.
Nothing's.
I see your vision, man.
I mean, I'm with you.
One United wolf pack.
I get it.
What about the hybrids?
The turn?
We're just gonna kill them?
What you gonna do with them?
That's what you know of me.
I'm not a dictator.
They can mate with the purebloods.
Pure find their bloodlines.
Hybrids like Ace.
The outcasts.
They stand for everything that we've been working for.
Everything!
We put our blood in sweat into.
They stand for chaos and destruction, Massimo.
So I ask you, what are we gonna fight for?
A world plagued by war.
Death.
Destruction.
Wolf.
And wolf.
Stand together.