Natalia, you're better.
I'm messy.
That's enough.
You got it.
Hell, I'm really glad you're better.
Can I ask you something?
Of course, anything.
What happened that night of the accident?
Massimo told me my heart stopped.
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
I had to. You needed me.
I don't need anyone.
You died and I brought you back.
How'd you do that?
I don't know. My emotions took over and it just happened.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't want you to react like this.
How the fuck do you want me to react?
Buy you a fucking present?
I need a brother fresh airy.
Please.
Sit, Aries.
You're falling in love with her.
How is it possible?
Far in love with a woman who pisses you off so much.
That, I don't know.
I can't do it, Aries.
I can't let myself fall in love with her.
I don't think you can stop it.
I really have to.
She kept a couple of truths.
She eventually fessed up.
It's not that, Aries.
It's that I'm not her true mate.
One day her fate admit will come claim her.
Then she'll leave.
Everyone always leaves in the end.
Good talk, buddy.