Oh, hey, hey
Sorry, I should have told you no don't say sorry your power. It's amazing you
You're amazing
You know, I've been thinking a lot about when I cleaned Elizabeth as my mate
What about it? It's hard to me for a long time
Like no that I got to get this out your face
When I claimed her the tears in your eyes a little crinkle you get your forehead when you're upset
Had it broke my heart so you mean you have a heart I do
That's not the point the point is
I've loved you. I've always loved you since we were children and you wore that bail on your head saying you want to marry me
What are you doing?
Something I should have done a long time ago. It's all your weight. I love you. I've always loved you. Will you marry me?