Blake!
You're boring, beautiful.
Don't worry, I handled it.
You mean you had the pack made it without me?
Yeah.
Blake!
You're looking so peaceful, I don't want to wake you.
You promised me that I will always be involved in the pack meetings.
Besides, if I'm going to be a woman, you need to be involved.
You might be pregnant. I want to do the rest.
You can't have the pack thinking I can't have airs.
It's not 50s anymore, Blake.
I'm not some kind of housewife.
Sit by, idle, and pop up your kids.
It's not going to work with you.
Trust me, tonight I need you ready.
My dad's coming.
We need you to be able to meet him.
So now, he wants to involve me.
Do?
I love it when you're mad at me.
Well, I don't know.
What do you want?
I need to talk to you about what?
Now, why don't you just go get some breakfast?
I'm going to talk to Emma a little bit.
Now, what's going on?
Well, are you sure you want to talk?
What? Emma, come inside. I want to know.
Now, it's just...
Well, I'm pregnant.