What?
I'm pregnant!
And you're the father?
No!
Why would I lie about this?
You know how much capital a child needs?
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh, it's okay to tell you.
Well, we used to sit on his balcony and talk about starting a family.
It was our little dream, wasn't it?
Seriously.
She's lying.
She's pregnant.
You know what?
I felt bad.
So bad.
For keeping the truth from you.
But the secret is that I kept.
I kept to protect you.
And it's nothing to compare to this.
This is not a fucking moral competition, Nat.
Can't you see what she's trying to do?
She's trying to break this.
Us.
Up.
Put your eyes in that.
She's trying to drive the woods between us.
Okay.
Is it possible that she's pregnant with your child?
Who are you guys like?
Yeah.
She'd be weeks on by now.
Where are you going?
I need to process this.
Damn it.
You need to make right chance, Blake.
If you want to unite all of the pucks in California,
and then lead them, you need Earths.
And I can't give you girl.
Just listen.
Am I?
You better hope this kid comes a turn.
Because if it doesn't, fuck it doesn't.