She has to go tell.
She's pregnant with your child, Blake.
It's fake. Like everything she does.
Can't you see, tell? It's manipulation.
Take a stand, Blake.
Stop letting this woman walk all over you.
What's your tongue? Wolfie.
Alright, okay. If you want to send her out, just do it.
But I'm going with her.
No, you're not. We had an agreement.
Well, yes, but agreements can be broken, you know?
Not by a possible child. It was before you were here.
It still hurts the same, Blake.
No, I don't want to hurt you.
I know it. Fuck, Blake. When those words escape her mouth,
I was in so much pain. I thought I would die.
Do you think about you guys were together when she was pretending to be my friend in New York?
I can barely look as she wishes around.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that. As long as she's here, I'm not going to marry you.