Tell, all that shit happened before you were back.
There's nothing to do with you.
Look, this is what we're gonna do.
Emma's gone.
If there is a baby, we're gonna keep it.
And you're gonna be its mom, my wife.
You know, he was right, like,
your shake gives you an air.
She's the one you shouldn't hear me.
Tell, let her go, Blake.
Your pump is more important.
What the fuck is this?
Is that shadow book you're telling me about?
Yes, it is.
What the fuck, Emma?
What are those?
Shut up.
Now I can cook.
Fucking crazy, Emma.
This is what killed your mom.
How would you do this?
How would you risk your life?
Because you left me no choice.
You always have a choice.
It's his, isn't it?
That's him all.
It's his baby, right?
Damn it, Emma.
Nobody has to know the truth about the baby,
but it is in yours.
Because he's gonna be the most powerful king.
I know it.
Blake, I can...
He's gonna control the shadows.
And he's gonna become the most fearful.
Just like his father.
Do you think you're fooling, Emma?
Look at Massimo.
Look at me.
We look nothing alike.
The one's the good thing is my damn baby.
You're going nuts, Emma.
You gotta stop this shit.
No, I just realized I have spent so many years
just to try to win your approval.
And now I just realized that I was actually never gonna get it, was I?
And it's just because I'm not here.
What are you doing, Emma?
What do you think she's gonna do if I tell her what happened between us?
Do you think she's gonna marry you?
What's your tongue?
If I cannot have you, neither can she.