Blake, wait!
I knew this would happen.
I knew your mate would come and take you away.
I just didn't think it'd be him.
I don't care about him.
Well, I do.
I hate the way your heart beats fast and you get all numb when you're around him.
It makes me sick.
Yes, I felt it.
And it was euphoric, but not.
I feel nothing.
It's not how the mating bond works, Tal.
Maybe he's right.
I did do terrible things in United Paks.
So tell me.
Tell me every single table thing you have ever done.
And I will love you anyway, because I do.
I love you, Blake Hunter.
I don't want to be with you.
I don't want to be with him.
I, the white wolf, has chosen you.
So you're going to be the king.
Hey, Tal.
You're my weakness now.
He knows that.
And Ace is going to use it against us.
Anything, everything right now.
But I can't lose you.
You're not going to lose me.
You don't know that.
I do.
Because we're going to take Ace,
and he'll cast him together.