Blake! He really doesn't know anything.
It's exactly what Emma wanted. Your child.
Then why wouldn't she just use Ace?
How could you understand?
What you mean?
Because of you, I almost had to kill my best friend.
Kill him! He'll only betray you a little. You can punish him, but killing him.
That's my point, Tal. You betrayed me too. Now I'm going to kill you.
You defy me at every turn. How does that make me look in front of my men?
How about I join Ace, just like Emily? How will that make you look?
He wants you. An eye for an eye.
What is that supposed to mean?
Don't tell her. It doesn't know good.
Yeah, way too late for that.
Back when I left Dylan to die. His wife was pregnant.
She had a hard labor. She was bleeding out.
I guess he didn't make it back to her in time.
His wife, your sister died because of me, Tal.