Oh, I can get used to this.
There isn't much point, not if you can't convince the LIL first to fight alongside you.
Ah, Jackson!
My dear friend, come sit, sit, please.
Your non-civilized monster, like Blake Hunter, knows how to welcome his guests.
A poly chase.
How does an Irish small single sound like?
My mouth watering already.
Well, I thank you for your prior services.
A word for cash, not whiskey.
Spit it out.
I thought you'll be grateful for someone like me who turned you and made you into the alpha of your cursed rich pack.
Ace?
Or is it Dylan?
You're a fucking outcast too.
We're equal.
So no need for me to thank you every time we meet.
Well, Blake Hunter has married Natalia White.
Won't be long until he's declared himself king.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not a king.
You'll never be.
Natalia White is my mate.
Is that a joke?
You're a rogue alpha with an army of rejects.
What's your plan?
No, like a beautiful dove.
Natalia White is incaged.
A cage may be made of gold, but it's the cage nevertheless.
First, I plan to set her free and then mark hers as my mate.
And declare yourself as king.
No, no, no, no.
Before I take everything Blake Hunter has and make him watch me take everything he loves.
Then I'll kill him and declare myself a king.
What's in it for me?
Well, I suppose if you support me, I give you my word.
Your pack will be never attempted.
We'll never seize.
And as long as I live and as long as my beautiful children lives, your pack is sacred.
Why could there be a fucking word?
The way I see it, Jackson, you have two choices.
Trust me or wait for Blake Hunter to come and kill you.
You're right.
We need to put an end to Blake Hunter once and for all.
Say no more.
Let's change to that.