Yeah, I've got food in here, Billie.
I know. I gave you a head slot.
Oh, you did it.
Everyone knows you got the short and the sick in all areas.
Hey, that's it. I haven't hit puberty yet.
I didn't cheat.
Yeah, you were a cheater.
Oh, man.
You don't do anything just to get ahead of me.
You know?
What are you doing?
Looking at my kingdom.
Your kingdom?
Who do you think you are, Simba?
Yeah, so.
I will be king.
And when I'm king, you'll still be nothing.
You know, for a werewolf to be a king, it's impossible.
You have to unite all of the packs.
If you can dream it, anything's possible.
Would you get that from Oprah?
Yeah, that's what I like over there.
Unless you talk so much.
And you don't fuck face.
You know?
I didn't mean it.
But you mean what?
When I said I'll be king,
there'll be nothing.
Because no matter what,
you'll be my little brother.
And that's something.
I'm answering.
Maybe it's for the best.
It's how you being gone.
It is her who makes you weak.
No.
It is she who makes me strong.
You've changed.
That's what happens when you fall in love Aries.
Boy.
It's how you?
What the fuck do you want?