I can't talk about it, it's too painful.
If you cannot talk about my sister, we have nothing to talk about.
Oh, but we have so much more to talk about.
Bless him.
I've got eyes on lace.
All right, stay close, but stay safe.
And Natalya's here too.
Looks like there's square now.
You've listened for yourself.
You know what?
Once upon a time, I was like,
I hate little girl, but guess what?
I grew up, and now I'm not buying your bullshit.
And what bullshit is that?
You're acting like your hands are not as lusty as books.
But you've killed people, a lot of people.
My family, my friends, my pack included.
Yeah, sorry about that, but rise to power to man's sacrifice.
Especially when you're fighting monster like that.
A monster is not a monster when you're rewarding.
Little Blake is not a monster.
You're mine, not his.
If you're not coming with me really, I'll take you my headphones.