I sense Luna is not in good hands.
Grandma, she's in danger.
We need to find out all these whereabouts.
I need a talisman.
Grandma, what is it?
The goddess has blessed us.
Blessed us?
How?
She's with cubs.
cubs?
Like multiple?
Yes!
But no wolf has had a litter in over four decades.
Well, Natalia is no ordinary wolf.
What did you see, Allison?
I saw three children running free in wolf form.
This is your future, Blake.
Grandma, cubs can't transform until they're of age.
Well, yours can.
You must find her now.
That's what we want to know.
Where the hell is she?
In an abandoned building on Crescent Lane,
at the foothills of mountain tales.
That's it.
Let's get that bastard brother of mine.
Go!