Talk to me. What's the move?
Oh, this.
Keep doing.
The House of Hunter is a pure bloodline.
We have certain invorabilities.
You drink this, you'll have one too.
Fuck it.
Something you should know.
No, you're only supposed to keep not Natalia, not me.
You forgot?
What good is a human to you anyways?
You're all right.
But you're a witch.
And you betrayed me.
Witches be witches.
What can I say?
Wait for these hours soon.
The Blake Hunter.
And the Dark Moon Pack will be ours.
Blake Hunter and the hierarchy will be no more.
Let's choose to that.
Blake Hunter.
And the Dark Moon Pack will be ours.
Blake Hunter and the hierarchy will be no more.
Still going to puberty?
Fuck you, Blakey.
You're not?
What am I?
Who is Blake?
It isn't humans, huh?
I thought you were better than that.
Innocent.
No humans are innocent.
You thought me that well.
It seems like your balls have dropped.
You've changed.
You're the one who's changed.
Oh, I have changed, huh?
You left me to die!
You left Mom to die!
Oh, I left my mom to die, huh?
I remember that when you left her, I saw her in my own eye.
He told me to kill my sister with your bare hands.
Is that true?
No.
You promise?
I trust you.
I came back.
You'll be gone for a minute.
I brought you a healer.
Can you fix it?
Long time no see, young wolf.
Wherever?
This is bad.
Did Blake do this to you?
Yes.
If there's anyone who can heal you, it's her.
The white wolf?
Never!
You're all right.
You fainted.
Massimo brought you here.
Oh, you can sense it.
Yes.
Like his mother.
You're a little not too far into you.
I can sense it.
Yes.
But a little different.
Different?
How?
Let's just say I have certain abilities that the white wolf doesn't have.
And vice versa.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
Have you ever delivered health human, health wolf baby before?
Once.
And what happened to the baby?
I was totally fine.
That the mother?
She didn't make it.
She died.
But I died too.
That I do not know.
The baby is fine.
Her body is struggling.
She needs rest.
Oh, I'll make sure she does.
You know all that's her we are.
Don't.
You know what hurts me most?
You're someone like magic.
And fact yourself.
You know, I'm a jealousy.
Kills everything around it.
You were just too reckless.
I liked you.
I could win.
We were good friends.
It's just when you threatened to take away Blake.
We were friends.
And the best of friends.
I just wish that you could have been more honest with me.
Well, I wish I didn't sleep with Massimo.
It wouldn't be dying right now.
You are not dying anymore.
It's easy for you to say.
You have brain and women freaking white wolf baby.
Actually, I am.
You are?
I am pregnant.
Yes.
Of course it's Blake's.
Unlike you, I can focus on one ticker at a time.
Come on, that's not my point.
Well, obviously you're this powerful, pure, blood, white wolf.
And I'm just weak friend human.
He's gonna get killed by the embryo inside of me.
It's already fittest.
How long will I be pregnant for?
It's not a new song.
Probably through it.
I don't want to die in it for you.
You're not gonna die.
Promise you.
Hey, Blake.
Thank you so much.
You were so good, sorry.
Are you sure you've been working out while you're pregnant?
Well, if I'm gonna throw three babies out, yes.
How's Emma?
Not good, you know?
She's a human.
She has a wolf baby.
It's never good.
I'm sure she'll be okay.
She got Massimo Watson there.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
Oh, shit.
That's never good.
Oh, shut up.
I think we should turn her.
What?
Turn a human?
You know how I feel about that?
It blew us the bloodline.
I thought you were a new man.
What about the Massimo in his speech that he made before they all cast?
Wasn't that your idea?
I never said that.
That was him.
Whatever.
Let them think what they want.
Keeps them out of my hair.
But Blake.
You know what?
Well, deal don't we get there?
You just focus on getting ready, all right?
I've missed you every day.
You know he would play something, don't you?
It doesn't matter.
We got the Cursed Ridge pack.
We're one step closer to your knight in all the backs.
The best way to unite them is why you're knighted.
What do you mean?
I don't like it can be with packs.
Like the Cursed Ridge or not guests.
Head off of the Hunter Bloodline.
But you also possess the strength of the White.
I can't eat my own pack.
Don't get carried away on skinny.
Aren't you supposed to put on ways when you're pregnant?
He's just not talking.
We are so cute when you're awkward.
Mate.
But I gotta go.
Soon.
Massimo.
I'll do that.
And I need you sharp.
Ready.
I can't have you preoccupied with some human girl.
She's not just some human girl.
All right, she's my mate.
My wolf chose her.
I heard.
How is this even possible?
I don't know.
But what I do know is, the mating bond is strong.
Powerful.
And it can make you do some crazy shit.
Trust me.
Yeah, I know.
Tonight we're going to Curse Ridge.
Stand with me, brother.
Fight by my side.
If we both survive, I'll go with you to save your girl.
Alpha, man.
Why do you care?
Curse Ridge back is now yours. Congratulations.
I'm no longer a threat to you, man.
Not so fast.
The party's just getting started.
I'm your ally now.
That's not what you're in a wolf is saying.
It's telling me that you might regroup.
A little army against us.
I don't know.
What do you think, Massimo?
Well, we definitely can't have you being a martyr of race either.
You are a part of these lands.
This has nothing to do with you.
That's funny.
I'm a pure blood just like you.
Oh, wait, though.
You smell different.
You wanted them turned, huh?
I ain't got shit doing shit.
Jackson.
Does this mean that hundred other alpha can treat you the dual?
That's all.
Make it.
What it does?
All of us.
It's good.
Shoot me.
You know who this is?
Blake Hunter.
You're welcome.
If you will bow down and accept Blake as your alpha.
Look, I know it's hard to trust someone who you don't like.
So let's put it this way.
Don't do it, it's hard.
Make the bow down.
Brick down.
If you really cannot accept him as your leader, you can use this door.
So give families a few musts.
You can never come back.
You're bound.
Us.
All hail the king.
I'm sorry about earlier.
You need me now.
And I can't keep running away.
You know, everything I've done in my life, I've done it myself alone.
So, Burf in a werewolf baby that might actually kill me, I can do that alone too.
Are you doing?
Not anymore.
You're not going to want to tell your life.
It didn't take me.
You know, I never thought things would actually turn out like this.
You mean you never thought it would actually unite the facts?
No.
I just never thought that I'd actually like you.
You've always liked me.
Ever since the day you sent Amethyst by a million.
You may be a rain, but for real though, I thought that you would come back, reject my proposal,
to move others against me.
Oh, I see.
Where's it coming from?
Well, I did try to poison you anyway.
So, you finally admit it?
Well, okay.
You know, I didn't like you at first, but then when I came to my father's office and I saw you in that...
Tied feeder.
Red.
T-shirt.
Oh, my lord.
Suddenly.
Every worry.
Reservation.
And then what was I thinking?
That I had towards you, just now.
Damn.
I wish I had that effect on everybody.
But then, this place were killed.
It's like, if I will forgive you for providing our pack, I'm ready for the most.
It was like I was laying down.
Zack.
Oh.
Zack would be so proud of the woman you become.
I'll just say, I am.
The older you get, the softer you become.
I ain't soft.
Now, or ever.
But really though, you need to remember, I will never ever abandon you.
Consider me, you're werewolf orpheus.
You know, I'm really glad it's you fulfilling this dream with me.
Uniting the packs.
Think about it.
We got the mountain tails.
We got the curse ridges.
All we got left are the night stalkers.
And my mother.
I ain't worried about him.
Ain't that right, little guys.
When grandpa meets you, he is never going to reject this.
You clearly don't know who my mother is, do you?
You think I'm stubborn?
Well, he is worse.
Where do you think I get this from?
I'm pretty sure he's not going to give up his pack that easily.
Blake, what is this?
I'm glad we could catch up again.
I will never forget the depth of gratitude I owe you for
entrusting your daughter to me over Blake.
If she wasn't in love with you, who knows what would have happened?
Hey, she was always too good for me though.
She was, wasn't she?
But if you go back, would you do it again?
You know, I don't know.
What Blake did to you, that was a terrible thing.
I still don't approve of their marriage.
I was Elizabeth, by the way.
Oh, you don't know?
What happened, Ace?
Well, when I found out she wasn't the white wolf,
I left her pregnant in a lot, but Blake thought it was actually his fault.
But actually, it was me who left her behind when we moved on.
At least for a hero's soul.
It seems like you're not in contact with your children, you old man.
I love you.
What is it?
It was him.
Massimo, get the reinforcements.
It is true.
I cannot sense him.
Let's go get him.
Together.
How much longer, healer?
About two hours.
How did this happen so fast?
You in burst on much faster.
Their bodies can't handle the wolf pops.
But this is two weeks.
She's no, she's a witch.
Ah, the baby's coming.
What are her chances, healer?
About one in ten.
What?
Let's go, Massimo.
You have trouble.
This is my battle.
For people to think.
I love you, Emma.
I'm not going to let you die.
I love you too, please.
The downfall of Blake Hunter.
Just like I did to your brother.
I forgive you for that.
It was boring.
I forgive you for my sister.
Because you were injured and you couldn't help her.
But I will never forgive you for my father.
She will never forgive you.
Except your name.
Oh, I've changed all right.
I used to be naive, but now I know the truth.
Oh, the world is full of assholes.
And why shouldn't I be one of them?
Oh, well, the little white wolf is wrong away.
Cute.
She's perfect.
Can I have her?
She looks just like her father.
My precious baby.
You are so long.
I did have to take everything for you.
You always get everything out of her.
Okay.
Out back.
This is why I became an outcast.
I wanted to stupid hit you, but you chose this path, Dylan.
So did you.
And no one had better done it.
So dad did it.
All the old things pushed me this way.
I feel so strong.
Even that.
And even the shadows have stopped.
I feel like this is the miracle we needed.
You know, I've been thinking.
You should come back with us.
Join the pack for real this time.
You mean to be the part of your family?
Yeah.
What do you think?
Great.
But Nick would never accept that.
Oh, Blake's changing.
I see it.
I mean, we are too.
It just takes time to do these things.
But I know.
As a family.
A real family.
We can do anything.
I'm sorry about your brother, man.
Don't be.
Friends of the family you choose.
I do think Dylan was onto something, though.
I onto something.
I'm an outcast.
I bought that whole taken down the hierarchy.
Getting rid of the bureaucracy.
I mean, this whole time.
I've been making you and other guys my betas.
But what's the point of a wolf pack?
It's to come together to be stronger than when you're alone.
So I want to use this opportunity to formally invite you.
You want to run this pack with me?
Alpha.
What about Emma?
Your family's my family.
Well, hard feelings not to give the baby the family.
I will.
They care of real free pops as well.
Hey, if you need any help, let me know.
Blake Hunter.
Alpha of the dark moon stone pack.
I crown you.
Alpha of all wolf kind.
And king of the tribes of California.
Natalia White.
Luna.
Of the dark moon stone pack.
I crown you.
Our precious white wolf.
Luna.
Of all wolf kind.
And the queen of the tribes of California.
All heck.
All kings.
And queen.
Neil.
Before you all king and queen.
Rise.
I'm sure you all notice.
That we're not standing.
We're not hiring.
Or one is better than the other.
But a circle where all are equal.
Long gone are the days of a broken bureaucracy.
No longer are we alpha's dominating betas.
No longer are we pure plus.
Hitting those different than us.
Hybrids.
Turn.
Humans.
All are welcome here.
All are family.
What is a king?
Queen.
You are all king and queens.
All alpha's.
All.
And together we're going to create a better world.
In return we ask for loyalty.
Creativity.
And most of all love.
Love each other.
Respect each other.
And we will live in harmony side by side.
As we always say most.