Ow!
Where'd you put the necklace?
Where's the necklace, Catherine?
What necklace?
I literally just had it, and then Catherine told me it was missing.
What?
I didn't say that.
What necklace?
Liar.
Just admit it.
You're nothing but a thief.
What the fuck?
You set me up.
Oh, Catherine.
If you really wanted it, I would have gifted it to you.
You probably needed it more than I did after that.
So you can make stunt you pulled.
Shut your mouth or I'll shut it for you.
That necklace was supposed to be a $10 million gift from Mr. McGuire to his fiance, a source
of inspiration.
But you as a peasant would know anything about that.
Oh, peasant.
Really?
She is not my fiance.