Who are you calling a peasant?
She is not my fiance. I never even wanted this arranged marriage.
Oh, Mr. McGuire, uh, you didn't need to come in. We, uh...
Oh, crap. Has Mr. McGuire met his fiance?
Is he gonna expose me? I should just play along.
Oh my god, goob. I'm finally here.
Find the security footage.
I need to see exactly who took the necklace.
Um, like, maybe this is all, like, a big misunderstanding.
You know, like, I'm, like, super generous, so...
I'm okay to let it slide this time.
Hey, how about dinner? At the Morgan's.
I think we could all use a little break.
I've still got some work on my plate, but, uh, you guys...
What?
Maybe there's still a chance with her.
Wait, Morgan's, like, the three-star Michelin restaurant?
Why is she getting so worked up about a Michelin star?
Did they start this era set of films?
Kate, uh, you studied in Milan?
Yeah, uh, totally. I was there for, like, five years?
Sorry to interrupt, ma'am. Are you ready to order?
Yes. Yes. I would like the lasagna.
Lasagna, olive, and basil.
Anything pronounce a common Italian dish?
Who is she?
I love the papa daleo, papa mijama.
I, uh, I used to watch the soccer matches at Inter Milan San Siro Stadium.
Did you ever catch a game there?
Yeah, of course. It's, like, always packed.
Actually, San Siro is Ace Milan's stadium, not Inter Milan.
Fucking bitch.
And you are?
Catherine, nice to meet you.
Red. Come on, like, what's Italian without wine, right?
Ryan is picking up the bills, anyway. No way I can afford it.
Look, sorry, guy. Something came up. Enjoy your food.
How is everyone doing?
I will just leave the check right here whenever you're ready.
Try this one.
Well, the clam to be.
And he will sort this out.
I need to report my missing cookie.
Still the clam.
It has to be your machine.
Maybe we should just split the bill.
But the wine alone was, like, two grand a bottle.
That's more than my monthly rent.
I'm just going to want to show you.
I'll settle the bill on that table for me.
Ma'am, your bill's settled.
What?
I guess Ryan was to call it and pay the bill.
Let's go for one.
Actually, Mr. McGuire is fiance.
Seems really weird that none of our cards work last night.
What do you think, Mary?
I don't know.
Maybe there was some kind of mistake or something.
Sorry, everyone. I left way too early.
Yesterday.
Kathleen, let me pay you back for the bill.
Did any Catherine say that Ryan had already paid for it?
Um, I had a little issue with one of my cards, but one of them went through.
I think so.
No worries.
I shouldn't have taken care of that.
And sent.
McGuire's fucking blind.
I swear.
She's the real heiress to the Foden family.
Catherine Foden.
David's fiance.
Better not reveal this yet.
If I play my cards right, she might end things with David herself.
David herself.
Station on the next project is coming up.
No, I expect everything to go smooth and floss.
You got it?
It's going to be Wednesday.
Isn't it your turn to go get everyone in some sweets?
Yes, I've been craving that for you.
Especially the pistachio ones.
And bubble tea food chat hours?
Catherine, can you get some?
Lose some weight, guys.
You've just ate chocolate.
And you had a milkshake an hour ago.
Whoa.
How can some of these stingy and fat shaming at the same time?
Catherine.
It's MG's house rules for the interns to go get the co-workers' teas.
Don't know, don't care.
I forget MG to make money.
Not spend it on your cheat days.
Oh my god.
You can't even afford bubble tea.
Maybe I should tell Mr. McGuire's he doesn't just hire any cheap losers.
Stay calm, Kate.
It's not worth it.
Just do it.
Dad is going to pair you with some rich asshole if you get fired.
Second time, don't screw this up.
Nice guts as you got there.
Presentation, moral?
Sorry, I didn't mean to start with you.
I just couldn't help but notice your work is inspired by Milton Glazer.
Wait.
You know about him?
Yeah, of course.
Eye-catching psychedelic inspired work, right?
That's all you want to talk about.
Yeah.
Gosh.
He looks.
Can't screw around with someone else's fiance.
Here.
That's exactly what I was aiming for.
Thanks.
What?
I decided to take a long walk during work hours.
Don't bother coming back.
Sorry, the line was long and I thought the present was...
Save it.
You'd better have something great for this presentation or the boss will shit can you himself.
He's watching.
Alright.
It's time.
Kathleen, why don't you come up here and show us what you've got.
Seeing an ability, we will have...
Who even are you to accuse me?
What, like, corn or gas college you go to?
Yeah.
Why should we believe anything you say?
Who do you have to sleep with to get this internship anyway?
You people are violent.
You're just jealous because I'm better than you.
Yeah.
I'm getting you fired for plagiarism.
I know he's telling the truth.
Ryan, please secure that.
Ms. Catherins idea not to be your range fiance.
I think he can just order me around, David.
I heard from David, Al Ross, that Kate ran the ideas by him a couple days ago.
See guys?
I told you.
She's lying.
Not you.
I'm in Kathleen.
I'm not sure where you get your ideas from, Catherine.
But, David, surely you mentioned you.
Clean the toilets for a week, Catherine.
What?
That's your punishment for lying, David.
And as for you, Kathleen, you owe me the prominent Italian designer in the Glo Constellini
and show him your designs.
How'd you use counting on me for this new deal?
I would just die to meet Nicola Constellini.
You're so lucky.
You know what?
I'm pretty sure you can take along.
No big deal.
You probably don't even know who Nicola is.
As if you're going.
Mind your own business, you thief.
Yeah, go clean your toilets, loser.
This like, super famous Italian designer.
Oh my god, I feel like I'm going to be rich and famous soon
and own that limo that you drive your boss around them.
Yeah, and also, oh my god, I've been my boss.
David, I think you see him coming into me.
Her dad is a limo driver.
Guess you are not the rich girl.
Everyone thinks you are.
At this, like, English designer when I was little, you know, to, like, design all my clothes.
Seriously?
I bet she has her nails done at the dollar store.
Yeah, I had, like, Barbie dresses, Gucci belts.
Here, do you want to see a picture?
Yeah.
Why don't you take everyone to go meet Nicola and your limo Kate?
I mean, I'm sure they'd love to see that grand entrance again.
Oh, yeah, can we?
Please, Kate.
Please, I've never even taken a photo in a limo.
Sure.
I mean, yeah.
Let me just go on my driver real quick, and I will see you.
I need you to pick me up with the limo.
What?
If I go on a personal that I don't own the car.
Right now, or I swear to god, I'm going to jump off this building.
Oh, shortly, let's start packing up.
You're the best, Kate.
Be the warehouse peasant today.
Take those to Nicola.
But no, she's not coming with us.
Ew!
I'm so sorry, Kate, but we're short staff today.
She'll be a good little doggy.
I'll make sure of it.
Please.
It's not going to be here today.
Paul.
You got it wrong.
Let's get going, girls.
I wish I could slap your daughter for you, Paul.
No way.
Is she picking up my trash?
I threw that out for you to go.
Wow, Kate.
I know.
Everyone says so.
Wait, but the girl in this picture is brown hair.
Does she come up?
She must have died of it.
Oh, yeah.
I died of blonde a few years back.
It suits me better, honestly.
How do you handle this one?
Sorry, guys.
My boss needs the car.
You'll need to get a new bar or something.
It's gonna be my dad.
He's, like, super busy.
We'll get another car.
Are you doing that?
What am I gonna tell my coworkers?
Why are you keeping this up, Kate?
We're not even rich.
I need a sports car.
Okay?
I don't care how you get it.
Just do it.
That's ridiculous.
I can't afford that.
It's tough enough trying to make money.
A lot of her is something, Dad.
Oh, this is how you can sell it.
I'm sure he's a bunch of useless,
pricey stuff laying around.
Almost here.
I'm sure he'll send us a car.
Pilling us.
Does Mr. McGuire come in a lot?
Come on, Kate.
We're gonna be late for Mr. Constellini's appointment.
Shut up.
Come pick us up.
David is way too busy right now.
I'll be right there.
Your fiance is in trouble, sir.
They were on their way to the appointment
with Nicolo Constellini and got stuck on the road.
I'm gonna go help them out.
All right, then.
Welcome with you.
Meryl drive the rest of you.
Kathy and Catherine, you're out with us.
I don't think that you've met your fiance yet, Kathleen.
David.
I'm not really interested in our age marriage, Kathleen.
I think you should talk to your father, Mrs. Phone about it.
Wait.
David is the fiance dad set up for me?
Shit.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, in this day and age, I just don't really see the point.
Do you?
So she was pretending to be me.
And she's not the boss's fiance.
Wow.
Kathleen, you are the dumbest bitch I've ever seen.