You have no idea what David's doing to me right now.
Whoa, Catherine, what's going on, sweetie?
I run out.
I'm the real heiress, okay?
Let's screw David over and start fresh.
I want to help you build your empire.
Of course.
Okay, but first, we need to hit him more at parts.
There's a black box in his office that carries all his dirty little secrets.
To get to it, we need to bypass the lasers.
And you have to do it naked.
Do you think you can handle that?
Of course.
I don't fucking anything, Catherine.
I hate David.
I turned his stuff to shit.
Good.
Make it happen.
And then it's pictures and martinis for us.
I'm a little hurt by your insults.
Hm.
Learn how to take a hit.
Big guy.