Claire, you can forget about this whole moving-out game that you're playing.
I know it's a bluff. Three weeks is long enough.
Come back home now.
Or...
It's lawyer time.
I won't tolerate this behavior for you.
Really?
I won't tolerate this behavior from you.
It's over, Miles.
Claire?
No, Claire, we need to talk.
You need to talk.
To my lawyer.
Here's your number.
You are part of the historical record of my life, Miles.
Your archaeology.
Claire?
Claire!
You can't survive without me.
You have no job, and how are you going to pay your grandmother's medical bills?
Two words, Miles.
Divorce, settlement.
When the judge sees those pictures of you and your mistress at the bar,
he's going to grant me a nice fat settlement and that money's going to go straight to Dr. Andrews.
Claire, why are you doing this?
Because I don't want my kid to look like you, Miles.
Now fuck off, you cheating asshole!
No matter what you say, you still love me, Claire.
I know it.