But wait, let me get this straight.
You want a baby in the next year?
Yes, but you just dumped your scumbag husband.
Yes, I did.
I wasn't surprised to hear that you're leaving miles
for the scumbag, but how does that work?
I promised my grandma.
She doesn't have much time left.
Oh, I get it, but you're putting the cart before the horse
you don't think.
That's why I need to drink more.
This was probably my last time drinking in a bar this month.
Are you short on money?
Miles has money.
You're going to get a good deal.
No.
Even with the money from the divorce,
I can't begin to bake around this treatment.
I don't know how to get a better job now,
but I've been a housewife for seven years.
Ah, I've got some good news for you.
You got me a massage?
Girl, you think I would print you a hotel room
for just a massage?
Two nights, prepaid.
Have fun.