The CEO of SuperAI wants to offer him a partnership on a joint venture, but he needs to speak
with you right now.
James, I have told him many times, when I'm going to see Claire, I don't want to think
about anything else but her, okay, no distractions, all I want to think about is her.
You know what?
Tell Mr. Musk that I'm busy right now, that I will talk to him, what did I get at that?
Where are you, Matt?
My contacts are out, you can show up now.
How's it going?
Sorry.
It's just my interview got canceled today for no reason.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Who's the company again?
Millennium Media.
Millennium Media?
The one that I own?
They're so unprofessional.
They said I had no class.
Like, what is that supposed to be?
The CEO's name is Anthony.
What kind of dumbass did he hire?
Um, no, no, you know what?
Listen, I think that you are one of the classiest women that I know.
I truly believe that.
Yeah.
A former housewife who's unemployed?
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't say that.
Okay, listen, it takes time, okay?
You know what?
I'm going to get you an interview there.
Yeah.
Who are you, the CEO of Millennium?