No, I'm blocking your way.
You seem to be confused, Claire.
This is a prestigious company for women of class,
not street trash.
This prestigious company offered me a job.
Today's my first day.
You what?
If you think Millennium Media would ever hire
some trashy nobody like you, you're delusional.
I may be a trashy nobody, Gina,
but you're a cheating bitch.
Call security.
Then set your phone to record.
I like a video of the guards throwing her out
into the gutter where she belongs.
See how many likes I get when I roast it.
Is this how you treat me when you're used to?
It sounds like a conversation I might have to have with HR.
What?
I just got an email.
You're just on our team yesterday.
What the fuck?
She's straight from the CEO's office.
Apologize.
Excuse me?
Apologize to me.
Right now, we're all good at HR.
How dare you speak to me like this?
I don't know who you slept with to get this job,
but I'm your supervisor.
That means I can either make your time here easy
or I can make your life a living hell.
Oh ladies, I see you've met the new hire.