Why does Anthony like Claire so much?
She just started, she's completely inexperienced,
and she's a total skank.
What if she's sleeping with him?
Come on, how else would she snag such an amazing job without an interview?
You must be right.
I'm going to catch them on camera.
See how Anthony's wife likes that.
The worst house on the street.
Let's wait and see who you're sleeping with.
That's not Anthony.
Who is Claire's secret lover?
I told you, we're over.
I have some news you might want to see.
Take a look at this.
What the fuck?
Claire was cheating on you during your marriage with this man.
Who the fuck is this guy?
He knows where she lives.
Would somebody invite a new boy toy to their house?
Especially one that looks like that.
I guess Claire's not the perfect angel you thought she was.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going to find my wife and sort this out.
Your ex?
I haven't seen them miles lately.
I don't miss him.
The two of you, okay?
Still?
Yeah, of course.
You're just busy, you know, with preparing for the baby.
Hello, grandma.
Claire.
Like Claire was saying, our marriage is going great.
Yeah, we're like two little lovebirds.
Right, honey?
Right.
This line is true.
How are you doing here?
Oh, just listening to you tell your grandmother that everything's fine between us.
You're quite the liar.
Oh, but you're not lying about having a baby, are you?
I know you're having a baby with someone.
Who is it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, you don't.
Who's this?
Are you spying on me?
It's called surveillance.
I'm going to get a restraining order against you.
Really?
Yeah.
You can't stop thinking of you.
See you tonight, Matt.
So here he is.
How long have you been seeing him?
You were sleeping with him while you were married to me.
No.
You better tell me everything, Claire.
Otherwise, this is going straight to the judge.
You can kiss goodbye to the divorce settlement you were going to use for your medical bill?
I never so much as looked at another man, but we were married.
What I do now is my business.
Yes, I have a lover.
Yes, I'm having a baby sucking up miles.
No.
I hate you.
Matt, this is Claire's husband.
If I catch you within a thousand mile radius of my wife, you are dead.
You hear me?
Maggie, hey, where's Clara?
Hey.
She's probably visiting her grandma.
What's wrong?
Okay, which hospital is she at?
Let me check.
Looks like Miss Newton's grandmother has massive medical bills.
Maggie, I got to go.
Right.
Boss, I have a suspicion that the reason Miss Newton is so eager to sleep with you is because her grandmother wants her to have a baby for her.
Why did you tell me all this earlier?
I'm sorry, I just stuck it up.
I didn't know that she was going through all this.
I want you to take care of her grandmother.
Pay for every single medical bill and I want you to bring the best specialist to make sure that she's okay.
Yes, sir.
But don't tell her that I did this.
Tell her that.
Tell her that Anthony paid for her.
Anthony paid for her.
Claire.
Hi.
My grandma's here.
Oh, I'm visiting her friend.
How was your grandmother doing?
She's gone through something.
I'm so sorry.
I hope that she gets better.
Thank you.
Oh, I, uh, these are for your grandmother.
Really? They're not for your friend?
No, no, he doesn't.
Thank you.
I mean, they're beautiful.
You're welcome.
Sorry to interrupt Miss Newton.
I just want you to know the bills.
Oh, oh, I, I know. I'm sorry.
I just, I need a couple more days that I'll cover.
No need.
Sorry?
I was going to tell you the bill has been paid in full.
And Dr. Andrews is working with the best specialist in the country on Mrs. Robin's treatment.
Wait.
Sorry.
The bill has been paid.
By who?
I believe it was a company.
Millennium Media?
Excuse me.
I don't know.
I think, um, I think my company just paid the whole bill.
I'm going to go, uh, tell my grandma.
Yeah.
Yeah, uh, it was good to see you.
It was really nice to see you too.
Yeah.
You do not have an appointment with Anthony.
Go back to your office.
Claire, nice to see you.
What can I do for you?
I just wanted to thank you for, um, for making my grandmother's medical bills.
Oh, it's not me personally.
The company has funds to sign full employees' medical expenses.
It's our pleasure.
It, um, it means a lot.
Well, I hope your grandmother feels better soon.
In the meantime, why don't you, uh, come in.
Have a seat.
Tell us how we can develop our business.
Sure.
This will teach her not to mess with me.
Who's Matt?
How's everything going with your Escort service, Matt?
Any luck making a baby yet?
An escort?
You're perfect.
Your ex-wife is a shameless slut.
You know who she's been sleeping with behind your back.
An escort.
That means...
I'm leaving love by some girl snacks.
I have a lot of things that I introduce you to, but I will see you soon.
You dropped something.
What the hell are you doing, Dominic?
You're such a coward and a liar.
You need to fix this.
You know about the board meeting, right?
Well, I want you to prepare the presentation for me.
You're my supervisor.
Don't you tell me.
Seriously, let's just get along now.
It'll be easier for the both of us.
Friends?
I can't believe this bitch actually believes me.
Like a lamb to the slaughter.
This slut actually thinks I believe her.
As if.
Boss, this is the agenda for the Millennium Media Board meeting.
Sir, I do not advise meeting with Miss Newton while you're there as her learning that you got her the job might upset her.
You know, I am so tired of hiding from her.
I just think that it's time that we tell her everything.
I do hope that she will understand, but who's my cufflink?
I'll look for it.
No, you know what?
Never mind.
I need to get to a meeting.
Just...
Claire, I have something that I want to tell you.
It's okay.
I understand.
I love you too.
Where's the other one?
Claire.
Don't say anything.
It's you.
Matt.
You've been lying to me for weeks.
Why does everyone think that I'm so stupid that I'll believe whatever bullshit they come up with?
No, I don't think that you're stupid.
Then what is this?
Is this just some college fantasy to get me in bed?
Is Miles in?
No.
Then what are you doing here?
For the meeting.
This is your company.
Yeah.
You arranged for me to get a job here?
No, it makes sense now.
I was just trying to help.
Stop helping me.
Do you know how many people have helped me along the way?
You need to learn to accept it.
The last person in the world I want a lecture from right now is you.
And the last person I want help from right now is you.
I'm turning in my letter of resignation after the board meeting.
I will be out of here tomorrow.
And Dominic.
Would I leave here?
Never want to see you again.
Claire.
Please.
No.
Don't.
Claire.
There's something wrong with Gina.
She's sick.
Can you help please?
Please.
It must have been the shrimp.
When I think I have food poisoning, I'm afraid I'm not going to be able to give the presentation.
Only you can do it.
No.
I just started out the company.
I don't know anything.
You made the presentation just read it.
Well, so then why can't they do it?
Oh, don't volunteer me.
Don't stare at me.
Claire, this is about the management and the CEO.
Anthony's nice to you.
You don't want to shame him in front of the board.
Right.
I'll do it.
Use my laptop.
It's okay.
I've got it online.
I made changes to the presentation.
I only saved it here.
Use this.
What?
Do they work here?
Oh, that was a mistake.
I should be more careful about where I placed Claire.
Those bitches must have been making out of life hell.
Angelica, can you call CVS?
Let's move on to Gina's presentation.
On-marketing.
On our board members, I am Claire Newton and I've been asked to fill in Morgan's presentation
today.
The marketing strategy of Millennium Media.
What the hell?
Where's all the content I made?
The bitch set me up.
Get survey to assess online viewers' content consuming behaviors and preferences.
I'm so excited to share with you the results.
The behaviors and preferences of our online viewers.
In conclusion, there was no presentation for you to give today.
However, if there were a presentation, I would thank you all for coming in.
I'm assuming points that we've got and next quarter we've got some budget happening and
support for stuff and I would love.
Thank you.
Great job, Claire.
Now, time to start a war.
Excuse me, everyone.
Excuse me, sorry.
I have something I need to say.
This is not on the agenda.
It's urgent and it involves Claire.
You see, according to Corporate Regulation 32.12, if an employee, such as myself, knows of any
inappropriate conduct by a fellow employee and that inappropriate conduct could endanger
the reputation of the company, we are required to report it.
So, I'm sure you all understand why I have no choice but to tell you.
You see, gentlemen, ladies.
Claire is having sex with a call boy.
Sex with a call boy.
This Claire, right here, is having regular sexual encounters with a call boy.
Thought she pays for sex.
Are you out of your mind?
You're bringing my personal life into a board meeting.
Nothing here is private.
You see, Millennium Media is a listed company and you are on the marketing team.
If this became public knowledge, it would cause a scandal that could rock the company and
cause our stock prices to fall.
What I'm saying is Claire must be terminated.
Gina, do you have any proof of this?
Yes.
I have absolute proof.
Sorry to interrupt Claire's husband, or ex-husband, and she has been in a sexual relationship
with an escort, Matt, and it ruined our seven-year marriage.
You two have put a lot of work into this show.
How dare you?
Gina, did you spend work hours putting together this against Claire presentation because it is truly amazing.
You're only doing my job as your supervisor.
Claire?
It's role-playing.
You heard me?
Now, this so-called call boy escort that you speak of Matt.
Well, I'm Matt, and Claire is my fiance.
What the fuck?
Claire and I are both consenting adults who met in college.
Yes, we have had a completely appropriate relationship in which sometimes we have engaged
in role-play.
Yes, it has helped spice up our relationship from time to time.
Does anybody in this room have a problem with my personal life?
Mr. Bridges, my apologies for bringing your private life into a board meeting.
What's wrong with you?
You're gonna bring an outsider into a confidential meeting?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm trying to help the company.
You're trying to help the company.
Just turn this meeting into a disaster.
Get out.
No.
Wait.
Claire?
Why don't you tell everybody in this meeting what actually happened?
Actually happened.
Gina told me that she had food poisoning, and she asked me to fill in for her for this presentation.
She insisted that I use her computer to do it and deleted all of the work I had put into
it.
That's what happened.
Gina, is that true?
Anthony, she's lying.
She just opened the Powerpoint presentation from the wrong folder.
How dare you blame that on me?
You know, I was so nice to you, and I gave you an opportunity to speak at this board meeting,
you dirty liar.
My company never should have let you work here.
Your company?
No.
This is my company.
James?
Call security.
Gina has been harassing Claire for way too long, and I am not going to put up with any longer.
Why would I waste my time harassing this woman?
It's not my fault.
She's terrible at her job.
And what about your henchwoman, huh?
Are they going to back up your claims?
Now I have told you too.
Many times not to harass Claire.
Now you better both start telling the truth.
Or I'm going to make your life a living fucking hell.
No.
Ladies, don't listen to him.
There was Tina.
She's been trying to get Claire fired ever since she started.
She even sabotaged Claire's interview.
You know what?
You're fired.
I'll make sure you never work in this industry again.
Mr. Lee.
No.
You have to put bitches.
Or just jealous.
Come on.
He's your best friend.
Begg, please.
You know I didn't mean you any harm.
You meant a lot of harm, Gina.
And I'm never going to forgive you.
Security.
Oh.
No Claire.
It's just a myth.
No, it's not.
Thank you for experiencing.
Now I had told you to.
What would happen if you made me angry again?
You're fired.
Both of you.
Now I'm going to make sure that you never have another job in this city again.
Get out.
That was receiving a good one.
And you're your shameless bitch.
You're sleeping with my friend?
She's not your wife.
And I am not.
You can't punch him anywhere.
Yes.
That's right.
I'm with him because he is hotter than you.
Richer than you.
I'm smarter than you.
Kinder than you.
And he has a big particular.
You stay away from her.
Hear me?
No.
You stay away from her because you treated her like shit during your marriage.
And then you kept harassing her during your divorce.
I'm going to make you fucking pay for that shit.
James, I want you to destroy Miles's company.
I mean you when I say it.
I'm going to fucking destroy you.
Is what you said.
True.
Which part?
And smarter.
Kinder.
What you said true.
The part where I'm your fiance.
Is what you said true.
Yes.
I have thought about it every day.
For seven years.
You've done so much for me.
I'm sorry I didn't see it.
Well you didn't have your contacts in.
I see you clearly now.
I want to be with you.
And you can help me as much as you'd like.
Well if you ever have a setting urge for a cowboy, I can reprise that role for you.
Something is wrong.
What?
All of our providers cut us off.
How is that possible?
I just received the news.
The worst thing is we also owe our clients $50 million since we can no longer fulfill their orders.
They signed an exclusive contract with the Bridges group.
Goddamn Dominic Bridges.
Babe.
Visiting the bridal shop to check on my wedding dress.
Are you coming with me?
Babe.
I'm visiting the bridal shop to check on my wedding dress.
Are you coming with me?
It's all your fault.
You dirty bitch.
You cost me my marriage and my company.
What are you talking about babe?
I saved you from your shitty marriage.
Once we tie the knot, it'll be smooth sailing.
Smooth sailing?
Dominic fucked up my company.
What?
I'm bankrupt now.
No.
You promised me that wedding dress.
It's couture from Paris.
I hate to break it to you.
You don't need a wedding dress.
The wedding is off.
No.
Miles?
You can't do this to me.
Fuck off, Gina.
I never want to see you again.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
Hi.
This is Robbins.
My name is Dominic Bridges.
Is this your new husband?
Grandma.
Sweetheart, you can't lie to your grandmother.
I knew you and Miles weren't okay.
And I am so glad you dumped him.
Oh.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Oh, I'm lost the pregnancy.
So you knew everything.
Sweetheart, I had three children of my own.
Don't you think I could tell?
I just wanted to make you happy.
All right.
The truth is I dumped Miles.
And I'm not pregnant.
And this young man?
This is my boyfriend.
Boyfriend.
Aren't you going to propose to her?
You know, I've been thinking about it.
But I've been waiting for a witness to be around someone like, I don't know, a grandmother.
Hmm.
Maybe.
I'm here.
You are here.
I am.
You know what that means?
It's a perfect time.
Claire.
Our love story is just beginning.
And I want to continue to write that story with you every single day for the rest of my life.
Will you make me the happiest man in the world and marry me?
I will.
It's the biggest diamond I ever saw.
Is he a billionaire or something?
Oh, young man.
One more question.
Are you fertile?
Grandma.
Well, you need to get busy and make a baby with my granddaughter.
I am too.
Grandma.
I have no time to wait.
Or a little bossy.
Oh, you're going to have the most beautiful baby that I am absolutely short of.
I am planning on sticking around for it.
I'm not going anywhere.
Yeah.
Uh-uh.
Not for a very, very long time.
You just said it.
I love you.
I'm so happy for you.