Drop the act. Isn't this what you want to hook up with the rich guy?
Don't look at me like that. You were the one who left me for money. Do you remember that?
Bruce is still hurt from what happened. I have to tell him the truth
Even if I no longer deserve to be with him, I still can ease his pain
Doctor, my mother, how is she?
Stable but still I'm responsive. Unfortunately, a comic had last months or even years
Even with insurance your family should prepare for the cause
Mr. Morgan get out. I know you don't want me here. I just have one thing to say and then I'll leave
You've come into my office
Unannounced and you think that I'm willing to hear what you have to say just because you're my ex doesn't mean you get some sort of special
privilege
I'm sorry. I'll step out and knock
I am not the same man that you knew before
And I'm not going to be at your back and call and even if you did want me back
You don't deserve me
Darling did you?
Jade?
Regina?
Miss Spencer. This is my fiance
Regina Spencer
You're engaged