I really should thank you, sis.
If you hadn't ditched Bruce for such a rich rando,
I wouldn't have ended up such a fine man.
Don't you call me that!
I am not your sister!
Ever since your father cheated on my mother and me,
and kicked us out of the house, I got ties with all of you!
I'm sorry, weren't you supposed to tell me something?
I'm resigning.
Are you?
Well, it sounds like you haven't read the contract because...
because there's a special clause in there that states...
You have to pay me half a million dollars if you were to quit without my permission.
And I don't think you have that kind of money.
Do you?
You wouldn't.
What I did.
Jade, go get me coffee.
This is not in my job description.
You listen to what she has to say.
Here's your tip.
Poor.
I'm gonna go live the life that I deserve.
Stop, Dexter!
Stop!
Take this!