Uh, how can I return this to you?
I'll walk you home. You can just give it back to me once we get there.
It's my fault. I want to make sure you're okay.
Sure, thank you.
Nah, keep it. It looks cool on you.
Ah, that's sweet of you.
And thank you for walking me home. Good night.
Bye.
Who was that guy?
Who you following me?
Answer the question. Who was the guy?
That's none of your business. We're over.
Don't make yourself look pathetic.
Hey, Jade. Think I sent over here?
Mrs. Bruce.
Where's Jade? Put her on the phone now.
I'll give you one guess.
Where is she, Bruce?
She's a little bit busy. I wore her out.
I need the next flight out of LA.
Mr. Morgan?
Command.
Mr. Morgan, I left my phone somewhere here last night.
Any chance you found it?
Yeah, you didn't go through it, did you?
I just answered one call.
Relax.
I told him nothing happened between us.
Even though I don't know if your sugar daddy bought it.
He talked to Dexter? What else did you tell him?
You seem to be very concerned about him.
It looks like he really is your sugar daddy.
The Morgan group's assets more than ten times is.
So why don't I just be your sugar daddy instead?
What are you doing? You're engaged to Regina.
Even if I was married, it wouldn't matter.
It'd just be another thing.
I would never be just a fling.
You write any number on this check and I'll sign it.
Take your money. I told you. We're over.
You can say you're a little crocodile, too.
They don't work on me anymore.
And even if you won't be with me, I have ways to keep you on my side.
Enough!
How dare you touch her!
What are you doing here?
The second I saw Bruce picked up your phone, I knew how to get over here as soon as I got it.
What gives you the right to speak for her?
Mom, let's go.
She's not going anywhere.
Unlike Bruce, I respect whatever decision you make. The choice is yours.
I'm sorry, Bruce.
No.
Thank you for helping me.
Jay and I...
Listen, we're such good friends.
And we'll always be good friends.
I don't want you to bother helping me like this anymore.
Do you still love Bruce?
After everything that's happened to me and things have done, I just...
I don't even think I can be loved anymore.
When you're ready to be loved again, I'll be here.
And when you're ready to love again, I'll still be here for you.
I scheduled the FaceTime call with the doctor in Switzerland.
We're gonna talk about your mom, okay?
What do you want, Bruce?
Hi, in the shade?
Yeah? Who's this?
I'm working at Night Rest Bar.
This guy is really drunk and you're in his emergency contact.
Could you come pick him up?
I'm his, what? Bruce.
Wow, I must have drinking one too many drinks because...
Jay, this can't really be you, is it?
It is. I'm taking you home.
No, no, no. Hold on one second. Hold on.
I've accomplished a lot.
And I've had a lot of successes and you still don't want to be with me.
Because after all these years, we should have learned to focus on the future.
You're supposed to be my future and I hate you.
But I hate myself even more.
Keep asking myself why I can't forget about you and about us, about what we could have been.
But you know what I've given up on trying to forget?
I have. I just want to know.
Why can't we start over? I can be better. I promise that I'll be better. I'll be better.
How are you five? I'll take care of my love.
Bruce, where's the key? Where's the key?
Hold on.
How do you know what was there?
Old habit.
Which means I'll be taking care of him. Good night.
Guess he doesn't need me anymore.
Because she dumped you for another man. Why do you still have that?
What are you doing?
Darling, so you're not drunk?
What?
Are you using me to get Jay Jealous?
Jealous?
I'm the one you're engaged to. Doesn't our relationship mean something?
Don't make me say it again.
You look tired. Didn't get much sleep, huh?
Oh, well, my love had a bit too much to drink last night, so I stayed over.
Not that he would have let me leave anyway.
Men are so needy when they're drunk.
What's the matter, dear sister?
Are you jealous I was at my fiancé's house last night?
It's a weird thing to be jealous of.
Your private life is your own concern, Regina. I'm not interested.
Oh, is that so?
Well, how come I remember you taking me home last night?
What? Did I say something strange?
Why can't we start over? I can be better.
Nothing.
We're gonna have our wedding next month.
You should be the bride's maid. You are her sister, after all.
We are gonna have such a beautiful wedding.
No, it's okay.
Come in. You don't look well.
It's because my announcement upset you.
Have you changed your mind about us?
Neither. I'm here to resign.
My resignation letter.
You want to leave me?
What's wrong with you? You just announced your wedding.
You have to let me go.
I will never let you go.
You can never leave.
You're hurt.
It's none of your business.
I'm off the clock. My arm is injured.
But why do I only feel pain in my heart?
Hello?
We've run into a problem.
What happened? With my mom?
Your mother needs a specific medication for her treatment, but we don't carry it here.
Okay, well, how do I get it?
I'm sending you the details. It's in limited supply globally.
Jade, I'm just on my way to come back.
Have you been crying? What's wrong?
My mom needs medication and I don't know where to find it.
What's the medication?
It's this.
Okay, I've heard all about this. Don't worry about it.
My friend and pharmaceuticals told me all about it.
I can definitely get a look.
Really? Thank you so much.
Let me know how much it is. I'll be you back.
You don't need a look about it.
Bruce, why are you still fooling yourself?
She already belongs to someone else.
Bruce, what are you doing here?
It's been for me?
Of course. We have a cake testing to go to.
For the wedding.
Do you guys plan on coming along?
Jade and I actually have friends.
Stop.
Bruce!
You can go to the tasting of your own. I'm busy.
Jade, I won't let you win.
Competitors are already contacting Greco Group for partnership deals.
Why are you just sitting around? Get on it.
Head of Greco Group never takes meetings.
Let's see what Bruce has to say when you come back empty-handed.
I'm from the Morgan Group's marketing department.
I'm here to see the head of the pharmaceutical division.
Appointment confirmation?
I don't have any.
No appointment. No entrance.
Can you maybe make an exception for me?
Move it along, Bruce.
Morning, boss.
It's okay. You can have that.
Boss.
You're the head of Kekka?
That's right.
And since Morgan sent you for this project, I'll make sure you get it.
Thank you so much, Dax, for helping me with the project.
My pleasure.
The dinner's on me.
I'll write it to whatever you'll think.
Don't mind if I do.
Look who it is, my dear sister.
The Greco Project is in critical condition yet.
You have time for a date. You must really care about your work.
Let's go. We can find someplace else to eat.
No. We have the space. Why don't you join us?
Unless you're held up in the past.
No. He's right.
Jade, how was it going with Greco's room?
Tell me you haven't made any progress today.
You haven't heard? She killed the project this morning.
That's impossible.
Sweetie, it's actually not.
I got the email earlier this morning.
It must you get everything.
Why?
Blind? Watch where you're going.
So sorry.
Is that for Mr. Morgan's table?
Yes, please give him my deepest apologies.
I'll bring another one out right away.
You're in for it now, Jade.
Hope you're not still allergic to peanuts.
Not a problem.
Actually, could you have them remake it and this time add some peanut butter?
Oh, Mr. Morgan loves chocolate and peanut butter.
I don't know if we can.
Just do it.
Bruce, you have to try their shrimp. It's their specialty.
You know what? I hate peeling my own shrimp, girl.
Don't worry. I'll peel it for you.
You're eating them faster than I could peel them.
Let me do this.
You should have some for yourself.
No, I don't mind.
I actually really enjoy peeling shrimp.
Really?
Yeah.
It means I get to see you enjoy it more.
We're the best.
What is your favorite?
To celebrate the success of the Gaka Project.
It's really sweet of you, Dex.
Thank you.
Jade, is everything okay?
What's wrong with this cake?
Jade! Jade!
There's peanut butter in this cake.
Is this how you treat her? There's peanut butter in this cake!
I told them no nuts!
Jade!
Bruce!
Get out of my way.
It was you, wasn't it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm not playing these stupid little games anymore, Regina.
You're the only one dumb enough to try and pull them off like this.
Even if it was me, there's nothing you can do about it.
I'm gonna give you your first and final warning.
If you ever try to hurt Jade again, I will end you.
Understand?
Let go.
You hurt me.
Don't tell her that I was here.
How was my sister?
You're scaring me.
How dare you hurt her.
Shut up.
If anything happens, then I promise we'll make your life a living hell.
Do you understand?
Jade, you won't be so lucky next time.
You know, maybe you should say another night.
Rest up.
Make sure you're feeling okay.
Jade, you must be discharged by now, right?
Don't act too concerned, Regina.
Since you've recovered, why don't you come with me as my maid of honor and help pick out wedding dresses?
What?
What's going on?
Regina wants me to go wedding dress shopping with her.
I'm a maid of honor, remember?
That's insane.
If I don't go, she'll never let it go, so I'll be fine.
All right, well, I guess I can pick you up when I'm done at the office then.
These are all our new arrivals.
This one's gorgeous.
Bruce, what do you think?
It's okay.
Drive safe.
I'll see you soon.
Bruce!
Yes, I'm sure you'll look incredible at all.
Or if you'd like a longer train, we also have these.
You don't deserve that.
So, do you see anything you like?
No.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, wait.
One day, I will buy you the most magnificent dress with a ring to match.
Did anyone ever tell you how sweet you are?
No, because I'm always sweet to you.
You don't deserve that.
I don't want it.
Come help me change.
Buy the whole store?
Listen, sweetheart.
If I ask Brucey to do just that, he would.
So keep being a cute little pack mule and stay quiet.
Duxter?
Looks like I came just in time.
The bullying's done.
What the hell?
Jade won't be joining you anymore.
And why not?
Because we have our own wedding planning to do.
What?
You two are getting...
Engaged?
Of course.
Don't tell me you didn't know.
Excuse me, miss.
Yes.
My fiance would love to try your most extravagant necklace.
Of course, sir.
That's what I wanted.
That's mine.
It's gorgeous.
Do you like it?
Perfect.
I'll take it.
Oh, excellent choice, sir.
You're right.
It looks stunning on your fiance.
Just keep playing along.
Oh, and by the way, your mother's just boning really well to the treatment.
You can face something they did not if you'd like.
Oh, my God.
This means so much to me.
Thank you.
Happy to help.
You certainly are easy to please.
Getting this worked up over a mere necklace.
I don't know about you, Bruce, but I'm happy to give Jade anything she wants.
Oh, and word of advice.
Those who can't give.
They just turn out better.
Come on.
Do you see anything you like?
Not really.
Well, we'll keep looking until we find your perfect dress.
Speaking of, what is your perfect dress?
It's silly.
No, please.
Come on.
Tell me.
Well, I always wanted a dress covered in a million diamonds.
And with some tool.
So it looks like a night full of stars.
Bruce, I'm still here.
You once told me the same thing.
Nobody move.
Hands up.
Get on the floor.
Empty the register.
Take everything out the cases.
Put it in the bag.
Whoa.
Please don't hurt me.
The girl in the pink dress has the most expensive necklace on.
You.
Take the necklace off.
Bring it over here.
Jade just toss it to me.
Stay back.
You get over there.
Hey, lady.
We don't have all day.
Jade, don't.
Jade, Jade.
You too.
Cross over there.
You're fine.
Hey.
Get the shit.
I'll come out on one.
No, no time.
No time.
I'll try.
Let's go.
Come on, Jade.
You're fine.
How is she?
We've retrieved the bullet, but she's lost a lot of blood.
So we're going to need some donations.
I can donate.
We have the same blood type.
Oh, negative.
Good.
Go with me.
You're giving her your blood?
It's obvious.
You still love her for us, but I won't let you have her.
You passed out while donating blood.
The doctor wants you to rest.
Where's Jade?
She's fine.
Why do you care so much?
Because I need to find Jade.
Here.
Take another bite.
You need all the nourishment you can get.
She says good care.
I'll do anything for you.
I'm doing.
See that?
She's so ungrateful.
You just saved her life.
She doesn't care about you.
She's so busy flirting.
Don't think that I haven't noticed your little stunts.
I am the one who makes the decisions on how to treat her.
Not you.
I'm the one who makes the decision on how to treat her.
We clear?
And when we get back to the office, you can clear out your desk.
Don't make me say it again.
Get over her.
Can I help you?
Oh, director.
I mean, Regina.
Oh.
Miss Spencer.
Mr. Morgan requests that you delegate your criminal.
Miss Spencer, you delegate your current projects.
If you could get those transferred by the end of the day, that'd be great.
Thank you.
Mr. Smith.
I have those compromising videos of yours.
I'm willing to return them.
Under one condition.
Oh darling.
I'll make you see how Jade sells herself for money.
Let's see if you want her after that.
Great.
The contract for the grandpa project is officially signed.
My bonus comes next month.
I should finally be able to start paying Dexter back.
Hey, Dax.
I just wanted to confirm how much was my mom's medicine.
Jade, I've already told you not to worry about it.
I'm not worried.
I'm just curious.
A hundred grand.
Okay.
I'll be back in installments.
So, including previous expenses, I still owe him.
Almost a million.
What do you want?
You're to finish me off.
Don't be dramatic.
I wouldn't be here if I didn't need to be.
I'm resigning.
First told me to distribute my project to other employees so this one's yours.
Resaining.
I'm about to be the CEO's wife.
I have bigger responsibilities than working alongside commoners like yourself.
Anyway, you have until the end of the month to get complete and if not, you don't get your year-end bonus.
Of course, you can refuse the project altogether, but there may be additional consequences.
I'll get it started.
Take care of yourself.
Okay.
I'm gonna completely ruin you.