This is going to be the heat of my year.
I can't believe we're going to make that look.
Edward's today.
Yes, Mr. Edward's our alternate investor in President of the War and Grinch.
Although, no one here has met him yet.
I heard he's super cute.
I can't wait to meet him and wish him a merry Christmas.
Alright everyone.
Mr. Edward should be here soon.
I want you all to look your best.
Oh my gosh.
Young, rich, and handsome.
You got me.
Perfect.
Thank you very much.
It's very good to see everybody, but I have a question for you.
It is Christmas.
What are you still doing here?
Merry Christmas, Mr. Edward.
We are so honored to have you back in Ravenham.
And I wanted to invite you to our welcome dinner.
Well, you know that.
It's very kind of easy.
I actually just had a meeting with the governor and I am running late to meet my wife.
So I will see you guys all later.
Thank you very much.
I like getting mine.
I totally understand, but before you go, will you please accept these gifts we put together for you.
Yes.
There's a diamond broach, vintage bottle from the halls vineyard, an exquisite porcelain pieces.
You know, I did not get a Christmas gift from my wife this year, which means I could probably be in trouble.
So, thank you very much.
This is perfect.
It's my machine.
Hey.
You know what?
My wife worked at the automobile bank.
I'm going to send you her information.
Can you please take care of me?
Yes, sir.
Of course.
Bye everybody.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
His wife is Caroline Baker.
I can't believe it.
He's a Christmas.
Draven doesn't really like mine.
I'll take this one.
Yeah.
Um, we're, we're put together slow.
I thought it coming through my Christmas.
Who's this?
Hurry up too.
You can finally get a divorce in Caroline.