Doris very nice to see you very Christmas
Yeah, and a chit chat here
Sign the divorce pay
The look came all this business with us. Do you really have to do the sound spend Christmas with us?
Oh, we don't need his company
We'd be so much happier if you were around
Doris enough mom
Stop being so mean to him. I want to force you
We just asked Andrew here so that you help us get her gets to me. You are so naive
Mary the loser who can't even earn a dime and here you have a wealthy and handsome suitor right here
And we're still living with this loser
the suitor
chairman
Andrew is the R&D director of the Ravenham autoclad and his father is the deputy
Manager and if you hadn't come along Caroline would be married to him and she'd be a rich wife
Come on doors. I know you're right, but let's not take it hard on the court. What's the matter boy?
You got a problem with me?
No, I just want you to stay away from my wife and for four
I don't think you know what you're talking about. Oh, what else could you be?
And you can't even afford a car
And here you are telling Andrew to keep his distance from Caroline
He's just stopped talking
I'm speaking the truth
Philip
You can't even afford
You'll never have something like that your whole life
You're right. I would never have a problem. At least you know your place. Yeah, this is the chief
Porsche, right? Yeah, I didn't even make it in last year's international auto Expo. Yeah, I would I would never ever
buy a car