Yeah, we'll get Mike a brand new Thunderblade 9x and with the toy car that comes with it.
And it will be a Christmas gift from me too.
Oh, by the real ones you get in the toy, oh my god, I think that's gross, but this is
gross.
Hey Mike.
Come on over here.
How about this?
I want you to pick out any car that you want and the car that you pick out.
The new one and the toy model, we can call it a Christmas present for you.
Yeah?
I want you to take this and put it in your pocket, okay?
Awesome.
Wait Mike.
You jerk.
He's going to be devastated.
I told you not to marry him.
You piece of trash divorced my girl and get out of my house.
Doris, it's Christmas.
Stay calm.
Philip, I've got an old friend Bob.
He's the auto-plans deputy director.
I'll see if he can get you a decent job.
Dad, listen, I appreciate you trying to help, but I don't think Bob can find a job that
kind of job do you want?
President of the Wharton Group?