That's a limited edition phantom, because at least eight figures in them.
Am I dreaming?
This is real, right?
I mean, there's literally no way that they'll manage to get that power.
This is unbelievable.
Mike, where did you get it?
I didn't mystery him in this snow, like this.
He took me to take out the car.
He told me the signature on it was really important.
Signature?
What signature?
Can I see the note?
Sure.
Can I go to my room, play with my new thunderblade night next now?
Yeah, of course, buddy.
Oh my God.
I get it now.
I know exactly how Mike got the con.
What kind of dirty trick thought was playing here?
Oh my God.
What are you talking about?
He's a damn fraud.
Nick, if you know something you should just tell us.
The key is the signature.
You forged the warring group's executive signature.
Didn't you?
You tripped that man into giving Mike the car.
Oh.
So you can just whip up a fake signature like that?
It's clearly not your first time.
You're a connoisse.
You are a piece of trash.
Oh my God.
Guys, hold on.
There's got to be some kind of misunderstanding.
Right?