No, how could you hit me?
You okay?
Did you play the hero of now?
Let's see if you're full of shit.
No!
I swear, if you hurt Mr. Edwards, you won't see it tomorrow.
What the fuck are you thinking you can talk to me like that?
You want to die to that too?
Go fuck yourself!
Andrew, put the gun down now.
Dad, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be meeting with the manager from the horses.
Now, the manager of the horses is right here in front of you, idiot!
Now, you apologize, Mr. Brown.
Mr. Brown!
I'm so sorry, I just lost my head for a second.
It was his fault!
He was making a scene.
I was just trying to teach him a lesson.
No.
Philip didn't do anything wrong.
They were harassing him.
You calm down, Missy.
Mr. Brown can judge for himself.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I had this man thrown out right away.
Cody, I've had it after this shit.
Can you please take care of me?
You lost your tone when you talked to Mr. Brown.
Mmm.
Philip's just upset.
He really didn't mean any disrespect.
You forgive him, sir.
Missy, you don't have to apologize.
Save it, Caroline.
He isn't going to forgive your stupid-ass husband.
Oh, babe.
Don't you worry.
You don't have to take it much longer.
Miss, I'm not in any position to forgive Mr. Philip Edwards.
Whatever he wishes is my highest command.