Philip and Andrew got into a fight. I'm so sorry, but we just really need your help to break him up.
Wow, thanks. Why can't he give us a break? I know. I'm so sorry. I know Philip is wrong for this,
but he was really just defending me, I promise. Well, idiot. He has completely lost it. Doesn't he know?
He could take this whole company down? Take the whole company down. I'm assuming it can't be that
serious, right? I'm gonna go and check it out. But I have to finish these financial reports before
the banquet dinner. Do you think you could handle it? Yeah, yeah, whatever we need. Just, but please
don't be too hard on Philip. Sam, what are you out standing around for? You really think it's the
big boss? Get him off of me right now. You're all fine. You scumbag. I bet your wife's running
the fair on life now. She's the only one of us who's met the president. She's gonna take no
shit when you would be dragged into court for any person. Yeah, what she tells the president,
the real president, he'll deal with you himself. You're gonna lose everything. Probably he'll end up
dead. Fucking instinct. You're ready to die. You're crying. You had your chance to fight for mercy.
Yeah, that's tough. I can't wait to see Pharaoh. He doesn't all be gonna see him back again. Fuck