The van good will start soon. Okay, so I'll see him soon enough. Oh, the president is here. I've got to go. Bye
That girl is falling way too hard. I need to call Philip. Sir
I forgot to mention that my nephew Kurt works in the corporate business
Administrative office and he's the deputy director on vacation in Philadelphia
When he found out about your banquet. He came back immediately
Okay, I got it Cody. I will keep an eye out for your nephew for the promotion the director
Thank you, sir. Oh, and since of Barra handed over the banquet arrangements to me. Here's your personal invitation, sir
Thank you
If my wife's family shows up tonight, just just let them in. No problem, sir
Hello. Yeah. Hey, I was just about to call you
Everything's taking care. Don't worry. Oh, and hey, I heard that Farrah is helping you with the audit
Yeah, I can I can help you with that. No problem. Okay. All right, bye
Hey, so I think I'll have the banquet and away from my wife. So don't need a drive
All right, sir. I'll see you at the banquet
Cornell, Doris very lovely to see you. What are you doing? Don't get the wrong idea. I'm not here to see you
We're looking for carolines. This is Kurt
And he hasn't seen her in a long time
Dye and catch up with her. Yes, that's me. I used to be carolines. Maybe we must be carolines husband
And you are even more pathetic than I imagined