That is amazing!
We would be so delighted to go to the President's banquet.
It's my dream come true.
Kurt, my man, you've made my year.
Kurt, this is really sweet of you.
My parents have been dying to go for a while.
Thank you.
You want this mess?
Sure.
Yeah.
It's just one catch.
Caroline needs to be my date to the banquet.
She'll go with me.
No.
She will actually not go with you because she's my wife.
You know, if you're nobody, you're not even invited.
Kurt, this isn't right.
What is it right?
I mean, Philip can't go to the banquet anyway.
Doris.
I actually was invited.
And Caroline, I didn't mean to tell you something for a long time.
The thing is, is that I'm a...
Yes, you are a dumb ass.
You can't get in the banquet by just flashing that stupid little card.
Doris, you need to listen to me.
You...
Listen to me.
Kurt is in the Wharton Group's finance department and is on goal.
He was the manager there.
It would be a privilege for Caroline to be his date.
And we would all be...