for all of us. Mom, Philip is right. It's not appropriate for me to go with her. I mean, I'm married.
Don't listen to the loser. You can come up with her together. It's not. I just need to get you
a new dress. This Kurt state is going to be a star. Okay. Don't worry. David and Tassil will be there.
I'll find them. Okay. Airline, let's go. I'll see you later, I promise. You know, tonight,
all of you are going to get a really good surprise. Merry Christmas, David. I knew I'd see you here.
Your Wharton's Finance guy in Raven Ham, after all. Yes, I am. And Merry Christmas to you too, Tessa.
Well, it looks like you're doing pretty good with the Wharton group. And a couple more years,
you'll be in the consortium for real. This banquet is for the successful few.
Looks like we're the cream of the crop from our class. I guess so. But where's Bowen?
Thought he was a former at the auto park. I didn't expect him to miss this.
I don't know. I guess he didn't make of a cut. Well, well, well. Look who it is. Our old class
made Philip. He was top of the class. Now he's bottom of the barrel. Oh my god. Is he still in
between jobs? How did he even get in here? I don't know. Let's go see what that schmucks up to.
Oh, I'm so sorry. Hi, Philip. How on earth did you get in here?