You guys do know that the banquet starts in about 10 minutes, right?
Yeah, so...
You're gonna humiliate yourself in front of the president?
No, actually.
In approximately 10 minutes, all of you are gonna be on the floor,
begging me, and your hands and knees,
and then the floor is gonna be drowning in tears.
You bastard, how dare you?
This is a high class event, and losers like you should be gone!
Where is security?
Get this punk out of here, kid!
This is the Wharton Hotel owned by the Wharton.
Causing trouble here is a death wish.
Are you the head of security?
That's right, and you offended our VIP guests,
so it'll give me the chance to crawl out of here.
I'm sorry.
What was that again?
I said crawl, you idiot!
Do I need to show you how?