My mom just texted, apparently Philip showed up with a big credit. He's in a lot of trouble.
That loser must have snuck in somehow.
Oh, he's in real trouble this time.
Would you continue helping?
Please, get on the floor and show me how to crawl out of this room.
Go ahead.
What the fuck? Looks like I'm going to teach you a lesson.
You know, a lot of people keep asking for an ass beating today.
Do you even know who the fuck I am?
Tell him Carl.
And you know what? I don't give a fuck about who you are.
Because the Wharton group just seems to be hiring a bunch of idiots nowadays.
And you know what I'm going to do?
Maybe.
I'm going to write a review on your management policy.
And you better wait.
You idiot shut up already.
You hit the head of security and you're ruining the banquet.
And you're letting me see.
You know what Doris?
I'm not the one that needs saving.
You are.
And man, walk it.
Guys, get over here.
Throw this piece of shit out and feed him through a pulpit you have to.
Stop it.
Your husband isn't nobody.
Why do you even care?
I would be happy to help him find a job as long as you meet my terms.
It's money.
No, Carol. All I want is you.
Carol, what a bitch.
No one believes any of your nonsense.
We're all high ranking members of the Wharton group here.
And this is how you talk to us.
When you die, I'm going to bring a bottle of piss to pour on your grave.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be the way to do it.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Let's just see that guy.
What happened?
Carol, I agree.
There you are.
Sir, someone is causing trouble at the welcome banquet.
Kurt.
You're the highest ranking member of the Wharton group here.
Only you can deal with this loser.
Hey, and don't let this cocksucker off easy, all right?
You parasite.
I don't think you'd actually show up here.
I have more of a right to be here than anyone here.
And also, if I want any last one of you to leave, I can make that happen.
Caroline, you see this?
Your husband has nothing but a violent, lying-ass clown.
Kurt, don't say that.
I don't even have to say anything.
I can just stand next to him, you know, with superior.
I'm the vice minister of the Wharton administration.
My uncle is the president, and you're just a pro-lying-ass clown.
Kurt, if you keep talking, you're going to lose your job.
Not only your job, but you're going to bring your uncle down with you.
So good?
What the fuck did you just say to me?
I think you heard me.
Caroline is mine.
She will divorce you in coming running into my arms.
Okay, let me tell you something.
You're never going to put a finger on her again.
Or I'm going to rip your fucking head off, and I'm going to display it in the middle of the party tonight.
Sound good?
What the fuck did you just say to me?
I think you fucking heard me.
Caroline is mine.
You're nothing but a worthless, lying-ass clown.
Now you see?
That is all the hell.
What were you saying about Caroline?
You've filled me straight off.
If you have any idea who he is, you're going to be way over your head.
You idiot.
I'm going to ask you one more time.
Who is with Caroline?
Philip, stop, let me go.
It's okay.
You see, Caroline has more sense.
You want me to sit again?
Fine, I will.
You don't deserve Caroline.
She's all mine, and you're just a worthless woman.
You're a fucking terrorist.
I'm calling your doctor.
What are you doing?
How can you be the reckless?
You're going to go to jail.
Caroline, what are you doing?
Get away from him.
He is a criminal.
Mom, I will always stand by my husband.
First of all, I'm not a criminal.
Caroline, thank you for always waiting for me.
You're being there for me and supporting me.
You are my greatest fortune in my life.
Finally saying your goodbyes.
Oh, sure.
Look at me.
You trust me?
No.
These people are a little cocky.
And I can make them go away very quickly.
And you give me.
Philip, just when I thought you couldn't get any more ridiculous,
you're proven me wrong.
Doris, please sue me.
Don't let anyone know that we're classmates.
I cannot afford my reputation to flip it down.
What do you think?
Want me to give you a try?
This isn't the time for jokes.
Oh, I'm not joking this week, huh?
Great.
I got what I wanted.
Now let the show be taken.
You didn't sound of a bitch.
You kissed my girl in front of me.
I swear I'll kill you for this.
Okay, Kurt.
You're not going to have a chance to kill me after this.
Bullshit!
Let's see.
Hello, everybody.
Um, hmm.
Oh, we have the Vice President of the Wharton Group.
Right here.
Yes.
Representative of Ravenham, the auto branch.
Mm-hmm.
And a senior member of the Wharton Finance.
Oh, and we can't forget.
Captain of the Wharton's Head Security.
Look at that, everybody, huh?
Are you just listing all the people you pissed off?
Well, too bad for you.
Looks like you're not getting out of here alive.
Well, uh, quite the opposite, Tessa.
You see, um, this banquet, yeah, it's actually for me.
And I can make all of you guys disappear at any moment if I would like.
Oh!
So, are you saying you're actually the guest of honor for this banquet, the President,
and when I had my own volunteer lunch, I was touching the President's book.
Is that right?
Yes, Kurt.
And you have made a very bad mistake.
And you know what?
It's going to cost you everything.
Enough with your bullshit.
Stop making a fool of yourself.
Haven't you taken this far enough?
You snuck your way into this banquet without permission,
and we were willing to grant you that.
But then you make a big deal, yeah.
Attack, Kurt.
You attack Carl.
And now you are saying you are the President of the Wharton Group.
You are completely insane.
And if I had known that it was going to go this far,
I would have done everything in my power to keep you from marrying Carl.
That was great, Doris.
But you know what? I think it's time.
Cody!
Yes, Kurt.
Yes.
The party is about to start, so please, come over now.
But you are not here in five minutes.
Don't bother showing up.
Yes, sir. I'll be there right away.
I wonder why Mr. Edwards was so mad.
Did I do something wrong?
What are you doing?
Don't you get it, Caroline?
He's still lying.
He's pretending to be the President of the Wharton Group,
and he just disrespected Cody in front of everyone.
Listen, maybe you wouldn't sound so pathetic.
You would talk to somebody else.
Do you know who Cody is?
He's the manager of the Wharton Group, and he's my uncle.
And is that supposed to make me scared?
Of course, you should be on the ground, because you might feel like the little worm you are.
Okay, Caroline.
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
Uncle Cody, it's good to see you. It's nice to have you here.
Let me introduce you to everyone.
Everyone, this is Cody, the manager of the Wharton Group and my uncle.
Merry Christmas, Cody.
Merry Christmas, sir.
You didn't cause any trouble, did you?
Of course not, I was putting this cloud in his place.
Wow?
That's right, him.
He's been causing trouble at the welcome banquet, and he's claiming he's the President of the Wharton Group.
Can you believe this line? He's a trash water joke.
Hey, Cody.
Can you please put this advantage in place?
How dare you disrespect my uncle.
You're finished. I'm going to kill you, and Caroline will be mine.
Uncle, how did you do that? You should be punishing him not me.
Philip Edwards is the President of the Wharton Group.
Think I knew who the President is?
I'm sorry, but you had to find out this way.
So, this entire time you have been the most horrible person in the state and you have no idea.
Yes.
But you know, sometimes a bunch of idiots just have to learn the hard way.
Secrets out, right?
I am so sorry Mr. Edwards.
I had no idea, Kurt was so disrespectful.
I'll have him removed from the Wharton Group immediately.
No, Uncle, please, I'm here enough.
You're helping me treat you like this?
Not anymore. I want nothing to do with you.
It's impossible. How can you be the President?
You know, Kurt, I can ruin your fucking life.
And I can make sure that your entire family tree disappears like this.
You want to fucking try me?
Oh, no!
Please, I beg you.
David, Pessa, you know, we could have been friends.
And I could have supported your careers.
But you had to let money and power blind you.
And another thing, I've seen how you treated people that are poor.
It's shit.
You know how you know? You know we're just joking.
We were stupid, but we're still old friends, please.
Just for you guys.
Please, we won't do it again.
We were never friends.
Heidi and Nick and Cornell and Doris.
You guys are my family.
And I used to love you.
And I used to trust you until you bullied me.
Knocked me down and treated me like absolutely fucking shit.
Doris, you've even tried to meet Caroline.
Leave me for somebody else.
I am sorry.
I really never showed up because of you.
We had no way to avoid the president!
Tell us!
Well, if I had tried to tell you, I would have never been able to see your true colors.
Now, I think that it's time that you both learned the consequences!
And you know what?
There's still my family.
Okay? There's still my family.
Please, just don't be too hard on them.
You know, I think all of you...
Oh, Caroline, a big thank you.
And I never want to see any of your ugly faces and raving him again.
You got it!
You won't.
You are my son-in-law, Thela.
And you and Caroline, it was a perfect color.
And you!
Oh, we're just getting started with you.
Get him the fuck out of here.
Yes, sir.
Oh, look who it is!
I almost forgot about you.
The head of the Wharton's hotel security.
I'm going to tell you something.
You have ten seconds to get out of my fucking door.
No!
Eight!
Seven!
Now you guys can get rid of me.
They're going to be Uncle Cody.
Please!
Listen, I had the worst luck.
So it's great in my car.
That's why I was late.
Also, I heard your loser husband crash those welcome papers.
Where is he?
I want to give him a piece of my mind.
Mr. President, it's so good to see you again.
And Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
I'm actually Caroline.
Loser.
What?
I just found out today, too.
Your Caroline's husband, who was broke and was gone for three years.
And you're the wife the President traveled all the way here to spend Christmas with?
Oh my God.
Oh my God, it's right.
Caroline.
Listen, I've been consumed by work for the last three years and I have not put enough
time into us.
And everybody has been taking me down and not giving me enough time to show who I really
am.
I apologize for that.
And I want you to know that I love you and that I'm happy with you.
And that I want to continue being with you.
This is so feels like a dream.
Well, you know what?
It's not a dream.
Merry Christmas.
And from now on, as we Christmas after this, we are going to spend it together.