She vilified me to put water on my shirt. See?
I don't know. Oh, um, yeah, I can see that.
It was an accident. She bit me. She's so mean, Brian. Don't be fooled by her.
You know, there's security cameras all over the place. They could check the footage if you want.
Okay. I apologize to Lisa.
I'm sorry.
Louder?
I'm sorry. I forgive you.
Okay. It's over.
You dismiss yourself to go back to work.
This one just Brian cared about all of his trifles.
Dear Lisa, do you pardon me?
As an apology, I would like to pass you the most critical case in green. Take the chance.
Why is she nice to me? This fish is where we'll even grab it in this world.
I don't want to allow more people to be here, can I?
Still early to cut the bond with Mr. Wark?
I will meet my first.
The murderer is brutal.
Everyone related to the case has either died or been badly hurt.
You're doomed, Lisa.