You can't escape Ms. Rosemary!
Look who's back!
My dear sister, did you really think you could run from your wedding?
It's your wedding. You are supposed to marry into the Vinci family, not me.
Oh, sweetie. I'm not marrying those brutal werewolves.
And yes, as the adopted sister, you get to take my place.
I heard Austin Vinci's old and ugly, but at least he's rich.
Lucky you!
Over to me, Ted.
But...
Enough!
This marriage was arranged 20 years ago by the alphas to secure their place in the human world.
Do you understand what will happen if you cross them now?
What are you trying to get us all killed?
I'm not your puppet. You cannot make me do this.
You need to start getting a grip of what your place is in all this, Lucy.
And after 18 years of raising you, you will be paying us back finally.
Raising me?
You mean locking me in a closet and treating me like you're made for 18 years?
You ungrateful rat!
Now they're asking for you. The Vinci elders are here.
Tomorrow you will be going with them, whether you like it or not.
Such a pretty face, huh? You should use it, sis.
God, is that a icky?
You are such a slut, huh?
Better help your old husband doesn't find out about your dirty little secret.
Or he might tear you apart!
I miss you so much.