All right, damn weddings tomorrow.
Alpha Austin, do you take Ms. Rosemary to be a love-related wife?
This is an arranged marriage.
I already have a meet, so do yourself a favor and stay in your place, human.
To have and to honor.
Yes, I do.
Ms. Rosemary.
You would like this marriage?
Well, finally, something we can agree on.
Would you like to take your worst possible pick for us, Pat?
A foster-lawful husband.
To have and to hold.
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, with the power vested in me, I'd like to pronounce husband and wife.
Alpha Austin, you may kiss the bride.
There's no way Austin's kissing much.
Ramp.
It's just for show.
It doesn't mean anything.
He's not even looking at her.