That's enough.
Austin, you have no idea what she said to me, she was so rude.
No, you've gone too far.
What?
She's human.
You know better than to use your wolf against someone who can't defend themselves.
Plus, you're my mate.
I need you to protect the pack, not cause problems.
Right.
Look at that in mine.
Dress.
Whoa!
You seem to be putting yourself in the middle of everything and get ready for the party.
You'll see what it means to cross the werewolf.
I need a new dress.
I think I have something that will work for tonight.
So, I heard you say that human girl from some trouble.
I had to say I've never seen you so worked up over a girl.
It's kind of refreshing.
I did it just for the pack. That's all.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever you say.
Seriously.
Did Ariana almost shift into her wolf in front of that human girl?
I mean, really?
Yeah, it was kind of weird.
It's almost like she couldn't take the human without reverting to her wolf.
What are you saying?
Just, do we really think she's my mate?
Maybe Ariana's just feeling threatened.
Jealousy can make people do crazy things, you know how she gets.
Why can't I mark her?
Why can't I feel my bond anymore?
Something doesn't add up.
I need you to look into it.
By the way.
Tonight's the first full moon since you found your mate.
So you're probably going to mating heat.
And it's also your wedding month.
So, what are you going to do about that?
I can't wait to watch that bitch make a fool of herself.
Her ready dress was soaked.
She'll work right up or showing her face.
Absolutely.
The time she learned really belongs here.
Oh my.
Is that Austin's bride?
She's stunning.
They make a perfect couple.
No way.
I gotta say, you're a lucky man.
Looks like your bride is quite the center of attention.
I couldn't care less.
I told you, Austin doesn't give a damn
about that sludge for us like a total whore.
Absolutely.
No matter how much attention she gets.
Austin won't even blink.
No, no, of course not, Austin.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
So you enjoy being docked at?
What?
What did you just say?
Who gave you permission to dress like that?
Fruit went to my dress.
This is all I could find.
My dress is a family tradition worn only by the Luna of the back.
Are you so desperate to be my Luna?
No, I didn't know that.
My have found it for me.
She was just trying to help.
I'm sorry if there was a misunderstanding.
You are my wife in name only.
Distress right now.
Happy?
He's just gonna drive me crazy.
No.
You're disgusting.
Austin, here's the dress you requested.
How thoughtful.
Braille, return your precious dress as soon as I take it off.
I should feel that way only about my mate.
No matter how special she is.
Ariana is our mate.
I knew some folks aren't afraid to get their hands dirty.
I need to dig up a few old contacts.
The rogues.
I've talked to all of my friends.
But give an eye out for us.
Don't worry, Lucy.
We'll find your parents.
Thanks, Maya.
I don't know what I do without you.
It's not a big deal.
You know, werewolves have more ways to track people than humans.
Sight, sound, vision.
It's very easy for us to find someone.
So, you and Austin, huh?
How's it going?
Is it being nice to you?
Um...
Just normal.
Normal?
No way.
Werewolves go all out when they mate.
Especially in Alpha.
You're human, are you?
Sure.
You can handle that.
Come on.
Tell me.
Excuse me, Miss Rosemary.
Alpha Austin wants to see you in the garden.
He said it's important.
Oh, wow.
You two can't stay away from each other for more than a minute, huh?
What's he up to now?
Didn't he mess with me enough last time?
Is this another one of his games?
Alpha Austin?
Are you here?
What do you want?
We're just here to teach you a little lesson, sweetheart.
You should have known better than to mess with someone out of your league.
So...
Which arm do you use to flirt with men?
Because we're gonna make sure you never use it again!
It seems so tense tonight.
Maybe I can help you relax a little.
Not tonight, Ariana.
Go get some rest.
What was that?
It's a howl.
It's a full moon tonight.
It happened.
Look.
I've got to go.
Say or another.
You're mine.
You took something that didn't belong to you.
And now...
You're gonna pay.
It's just so unfortunate.
We have to ruin that pretty face of yours.
Oh, no.
Touch our hand only the last thing you ever do.
We're gonna make our way out.
No trouble.
No.
All right.
Out of here.
If I see you again, you're a rat.
Humans are so fragile.
You're safe.
They're gone.
You're the last person I want to bond with.
And I don't want to be your luna.
Fine.
Then I'll leave you here just like you want it.
And fragile.
How was that?
I can walk.
And you'd be crawling by morning.
What are you doing?
Trying to.
Moon didn't apply some ointment.
You thought what?
Nothing.
It's just...
I don't need ointment.
My wounds feel pretty fast on the room.
Being strong doesn't mean you need to be reckless.
This should help prevent infection and speed up the healing.
He's actually kind of handsome when he's not being annoying.
Maybe he's not as bad as I thought.
Did I hurt you?
No.
No, it's fine.
I just don't need that much treatment.
Well, just keep it dry.
I should heal up nicely.
Lucy, I'm not trying to argue.
But really not feel anything in the-
Feel anything?
Nothing at all.
Why?
He already has his mate.
Can't fall for him.
He doesn't need to know what I'm feeling.
It's nothing.
Night must just be exhausting.
Yeah.
There's no way I could have a mate bond with a human.
It just doesn't make sense.
Well, you seem to be more than capable.
Taking care of yourself.
For a second, I almost thought he was being nice.
Brain.
Want some tea?
I'm stepping out for a while.
Thought I shouldn't give you a heads up.
What?
You're leaving the pack?
Oh my god.
I am so sorry.
Uh, yeah, I'll be out for a while.
Probably won't get home until late.
Sorry I dropped.
I didn't see anything seriously in the tiny world.
Nothing happened.
Turn around.
Are you sure you two are done?
I can wait outside if you need a few more minutes.
No.
It's just a huge misunderstanding.
I just spilled tea.
I'm just going to get out of here.
Okay.
Let me see.
Oh, well, right.
We got the results on why you can't mark Ariana yet.
I talked to the elders about it and they said it's rare but not impossible that mates can't fully mark each other.
I see.
It's been two weeks.
You still can't mark her.
What's going on?
I don't know.
I just can't complete the mark.
I don't even feel the bond with her, Alex.
It's just not there like it should be.
What is wrong with me?
There's one more thing.
You're probably not going to want to hear but the rose that attacked Lucy.
They've got ties to Ariana.
What?
So you've been seeing other guys behind Austin's back.
Such a little tramp.
Austin.
You have no idea what that little tramp has been up to.
Is that Lucy?
And her new boy, Toy.
They're meeting at the blue owl tonight at eight.
You have to go catch him in the act.
I warned you to stay away from Lucy.
But clearly you can't control yourself.
Listen.
Did you send the rogues after her?
No, I didn't do that.
You obviously don't know how to behave.
So I will have to teach you.
Guard?
Ariana is on house rest for the week.
She's not to leave this room unless I give permission.
Austin, I'm your mate.
You can't do this to me.
Austin!
Maya's got a call.
So where should we start?
You said you know something about my parents?
Yeah, I reached out to some old contacts.
They said about 18 years ago,
a couple in the area lost their daughter.
Thought it might be worth looking into.
18 years ago.
That's when I was adopted.
They could be my parents.
Yeah, but there's something else.
A couple.
They're werewolves.
Werewolves?
Can't be right.
I'm just human.
Yeah.
I know it sounds strange, all right.
But somewhere wolves don't show their abilities right away
or even at all.
Hey, I still think this lead my worth looking into.
Don't worry, okay?
I'm all here for you.
So, you left the pack to sneak out and watch see this guy?
You really are good at playing the victim, huh?
So sweet and innocent.
What?
Are you talking about Marcus?
Is he here to help?
Help?
What kind of help?
The kind of help that makes you forget that you're married?
What is your problem?
Isn't it your business who I talk to?
None of my business.
You are my wife, Lucy.
I have every right to know what you're up to.
Your wife, in name only, remember?
You've got your precious mate, so stop acting like you have any
sayin' what I do.
I am done with this.
I am leaving.
No, Lucy!
Stay away from her.
Austin, stop it!
Do you have any idea what is going on?
I am the one who brought Lucy here.
Marcus was just trying to help her find her family.
What?
Any idea what Lucy has been through?
The Rosemary's treated her like trash.
Barely clothed, barely fed, and bullied by her step-sister every
single day.
And now you, her so-called husband, is just making her life worse.
I do.
No!
You're being a total jerk.
All she cares about is finding her family.
And all you care about is your stupid jealousy.
You're right.
I messed up.
It's gonna be okay.
I'll find Mom and Dad.
I just have to keep believing.
I say not.
I'm so sorry.
I-I didn't mean to get anything worse.
Just go.
Leave me alone like you always do.
You were spending the night together.
No running off, Austin.
Maya, it looks like we're stuck together for the night.
I'm so sorry.
I'm an idiot.
I should never have tried to control you like that.
I just-I don't know what came over me.
I couldn't stop it.
Promise.
Find your parents.
I have more resources.
I-I know more people than Maya.
I'll do whatever it takes.
You're not alone in this.
Can I trust you this time?
Why am I doing?
I shouldn't deny the moon goddess, but I just want to kiss her.
He's so dangerous.
But why do I want to believe him?
Austin, are you okay?
What are you doing here?
I heard you got locked in, so I grabbed the spare key.
I hope I'm not too late.
You got here just in time.
Thanks, Alex.
How was that?
It's like you should get some rest.
It's so helpful.
What?
Austin didn't punish them, and now he's sending people to find Lucy's parents?
I can't let that happen.
You're locked down.
I need you to find someone for me.
I'm no see.
Dear sister.
Emily, what are you doing here?
What do you want?