Get out! All of you!
You can't even bring Austin back your useless face!
You seem to be doing perfectly fine.
Austin, you're here. I knew you'd come. I really haven't been feeling well.
You cut the act, Ariana. I know you're fine. This charade ends now.
Austin, I've been grounded for five days and you've never came. I really wanted to see you.
Look at what you've done. You're my mate and all you've done is bring chaos to the pack.
Keep this up and I'll be forced to reject you.
You can't go against the Moon Goddess as well.
I don't care what the Moon Goddess says.
We are not a fit and I don't love you.
If you rejects me, the Moon Goddess will punish you.
You lose your wolf, Austin. Are you willing to risk that for your astute little human?
Yes. So, let's go ahead and get this over with.