If you lose your wolf, Austin, the pack will see you as weak.
You'll lose your business standing.
Who would want to partner with a werewolf who lost his power?
Austin, no.
You can't lose your wolf. You can't take that risk.
It's okay. Don't worry.
This is your last chance, Ariana.
Do something like this again,
and I don't care what the moon goddess does.
I will reject you.
What are you looking at?
You think this is funny?
Stupid little twerp!
No, no, I just...
I just thought the lunar assembly is coming up
on the office and their luna, so I invite it.
Maybe it's a good opportunity.
You're right.
I need everyone to think I'm Austin's luna.
Not some stupid little human.