How do I look?
I bet all the she-eels will be able to take their eyes off of you.
I'm not interested in other women.
She's the only one that matters to me.
The car is ready.
The room is all set downstairs.
The reception for the assembly is about to kick off.
Alright, here we go.
Ariana, what are you doing here?
You need a plus one for the lunar assembly.
I'm going with you.
Do you like my dress?
Who said you were going with me?
Austin, I'm your maid.
Of course I'm going with you.
Who else would?
Wait.
Are you going with that bitch?
Hold your tongue.
Lucy is my wife.
If I hear you disrespecting her like that again,
it'll be much longer than a week.
Lock down.
You said only your mate could be your Luna.
And now you're backing another woman!
I wish I never known you were my mate.
And I know you were this cruel.
Trying to steal my man?
You're not getting away with that.