She looks just like I know, but apparently they moved to Europe after they lost their daughter and no one knows where.
I'm sorry Lucy, I wish I had more.
Um, Lucy, there's something you need to know.
I'm sorry. I'm just not in the mood right now.
No, I promise it's good news.
They can wait a few days though.
Besides, there's something I need to take care of first.
Damn it. She's luckier than I thought. The whole plan is ruined.
Are you sure that Lucy has his mate? Ariana, this is a dangerous game you're playing.
I'm sure. She has the mark.
I can feel it, Mom. Every time she's been around, Oz has been so cold and distant.
He can't find out I'm not his true mate.
Ariana, toxic woman. Why not have you been hiding from me?