Were you at the Robertson Hotel last night?
Robertson Hotel?
Anyways, you're probably nervous.
Don't worry, I'll take full responsibility for what happened.
This is a $5 million check.
Acceptance requires signing a non-disclosure agreement.
Or you can move into my state and I'll cover all your expenses,
as well as providing you with a $20,000 monthly allowance.
We can see where it goes.
You must have me confused with Katie,
but I can't miss this opportunity.
It's karma for her constant looking down on me.
I'll move in tomorrow.
What's that for?
I'm moving in with my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Since when did you have a boyfriend?
I didn't want to tell you about it until I knew if it was serious or not.
I'm going to be all alone here.
We all need to grow up eventually.
So tell me about your day.
I got a new job.
They're going to pay me $150k a year.
Oh my god!
I'm so happy for you.