These are you?
Could you go grab James at that French restaurant
in Broadway?
His business dinner there.
John is busy running errands for one.
James is a girlfriend, so James has a girlfriend?
Not just any girlfriend.
She's the first girl to ever move in,
and he's probably going to marry her.
Hey, Richard.
Oh, I don't even know where to start.
I mean, I got a new job, and the boss is such a jerk.
He has a girlfriend, but he's like sleeping around the whole time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
Slow down.
How do you know he's sleeping around?
That was my old boss, actually.
No, no, no.
My new boss is so great.
He's very good at his job.
Super professional, very talented.
You're not making sense.
Wait, is your boss around?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gotta go.
Bye.
James, what's up?
Pretty thing.
You shouldn't have sweetened the deal at this, girl.
Okay, sure.