James, I made breakfast.
Why are you doing this circus show?
It was all past.
James, today is Valentine's Day, and I was wondering if you wanted to get dinner together.
No.
So what are you gonna do after work?
I'm meeting some friends tonight, some friends, or a friend.
No.
Sir, should I get Miss Anna a Valentine's gift on your behalf? Whatever. Make Lindsey do.
Katie, come to my office.
He's not gonna ask me to pay for his medical bills, is he?
I need money to pay for your medical bills.
What, medical bills?
I can't. He has a girlfriend.
I don't mind if you want to compensate me for that.
No.
No, I forget.
How can I help you?
Come with me.
I want to buy something.
Wow.
It's a pleasure to see you.
See when your girlfriend makes such a beautiful couple.
Oh, I'm not his girlfriend.
I'm sorry, so how can we help you today?
I'm here for a purse.
Sure, let me show you the latest collection.
From the world to the various weather, and we're one of only three couples.
Which one do you prefer?
How do I know?
It's a slashery brand.
Wrap it up.
Give it to her.
Isn't it a bit too much to make me carry your girlfriend's stuff?
It's for you.
I can't accept such an expensive gift.
It's not a gift.
Your purse?
It was damaged during working hours on company affairs.
A driver?
Company compensation.
It's a pleasure to finally meet the future Mrs. Thompson.
Help me put on my shoes.
If you ever need anything, just let me know.
And don't forget about me when you become Mrs. Thompson.
Thanks, Fox.
We should grab a bite before getting back to the office.
Sorry, I can't.
I'm meeting a friend tonight.
Paul, meet me at our usual place.
What service is that?
I really shouldn't be joking with you.
What do you mean?
It's Valentine's Day.
We're fully booked.
Everyone's celebrating couples, friends with benefits.
Circuit Daddy, Circuit Babies.
Maybe not married couples, but...
I've got to go.
What?
You've literally arrived two minutes ago.
Remember when chicken wings used to cost 25 cents?
We would spend all of our lemonade sand money on chicken wings and pizza.
Although I never understood why we have to give out anything.
I mean, she never gave us anything.
My cousin.
We were three orphans who found each other.
We're family.
Speaking of family.
Kitty.
I want to see you.
What?
Redo the summary for the toxicology testing clinical trials on micro-rats.
Tonight.
Why?
John will pick you up in five.
You can work on it at my place.
Oh, sorry.
I got to get back to work.
You work for the Nazis?
Miss.
This is Katie, James' new project coordinator.
Katie, this is James' girlfriend.
So he likes sexy girls.
Who's your boyfriend mad at you for bitching him on Valentine's Day?
Why?
Does it matter to you?
Not at all.
What matters to me is you doing your job.
Yes, sir.
Working on it.
What's that face?
Protesting the overtime work?
I like overtime work.
Do I get overtime pay?
No.
Your position has flexible work hours.
You know you'd have finished already if you didn't have a date with your boyfriend.
I would have finished already if you stopped asking me questions.
Your job's to answer my questions.
I'm sorry for interrupting, sir.
But Miss Anna is sick.
You might need to check on her.
It looks serious.
It's just hyper acidity.
Give her some that acid, she'll be fine.
James, wait.
Please don't leave.
Can you just stay with me for the night?
No.
What was the point of asking me to live here if you're just going to ignore me all the time?
I'm here now, right?
Look, you're free to leave at any time.
If it's about the money, then just sign the ND. I'll double the amount.
It's not.
I grew up as an orphan.
I was always neglected.
And all I've ever wanted is to love somebody.
And for them to love me back the same way.
And that person's you.
Did you change your perfume?
It smells weird.
It's not for you.
Are we done here?
I need to work.
It is the same perfume Katie wears.
Why didn't it work?
Katie sent me the toxicology and clinical trials last night.
Do you want me to fire her?
No, she did well.
With her potential, she might have been so fast.
You want to go?
Let her handle the distribution strategy somewhere.
No.
That's surprising.
Why?
She's a smart girl.
Have you set the contracts to the Ryerson Hotel?
I'm meeting Paul this Tuesday night.
I was going to hand him over personally.
You know what we need for them.
You don't need to be there.
Katie will come to me on that meeting.
Just send him the contracts before I meet him.
Your last summary?
I'll provide summaries for marketing.
This is a wad.
Oh, that's just how corporate works.
It seems that Katie's our common enemy.
Let's work together.
You know, I hung out with James on Valentine's Day,
midway through.
You ditched me.
I know.
He asked me to work overtime on Valentine's Day.
Paul, are we going to keep talking about how bad I am on it?
All right.
Let's do something fun.
Let's play the Never Have I Ever game, right?
All right.
Okay.
So, if I have done something that you have never done,
I'd say?
Yes.
Also.
Never have I ever had a one-night stand.
With each other?
I never thought you'd be the type of person to have a one-night stand.
And what type of person has a one-night stand?
Deer type?
Mm-hmm.
Hello.
Could we continue with the game, please?
Your turn.
Never have I ever been to Europe.
Never have I ever fallen in love.
Really?
Never?
What have you been all this use?
Ah.
See you've been in love.
As tens.
Why are you so curious about my life?
Lots.
My turn.
How have I ever...
Such a somebody while I was drunk.
Okay.
I'll take it.
I got it too many.
I think I got it too many.
Let me stay here tonight.
All right.
Two.
We're joining.
Where have you been?
Where have you been all this time?
What are you talking about?
Oh, fuck.
Did we do it again?
If we...
If we did anything inappropriate last night,
could we just forget about it?
I assume it was just from the alcohol last night.
Well, what happened last night?
Do you really not remember what you did to me?
Then last night.
Why is the room spinning?
I don't know.
I'll buy you a new one.
It'll cost you a month in your shower.
In that case.
I will get it cloned for you.
There's no need.
John will bring us both in your set.
You should be here in a minute.
Take a shower here and for one.
I saw Katie and James get out of the same car today.
Do you think they're dating?
I don't know.
But she might replace Lindsay.
You had a gossip all day?
Lindsay!
We were just saying that no matter what Katie does,
she'll never replace you.
Absolutely.
I mean, James even asked you to handle the product lunch.
That's like the most important company of it in years.
And how are the preparations for the product lunch conference?
Huh?
Katie fired.
Comes to the product lunch.
Lunch is here.
Ready?
Hopefully it's so hot.
We can eat before everything starts.
You get chicken?
Yes.
Okay.
Coming together.
Looks nice.
Did you get the chicken?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just going to leave the rest of those right there.
Let's go.
Hi Lindsay.
I got your lunch.
And I just wanted to say good luck on this speech.
Today I'll don't disturb me.
Okay.
Everything's done.
I'll let you cream.
Mr. Thompson.
Lindsay needs help.
She can't breathe.
Who was in charge of the lunches?
You'll be able to breathe normally in a few minutes.
I actually have that allergy too.
How could this happen?
You do these on me.
I am so sorry.
I reminded the restaurant twice.
Lindsay can't give the opening speech now.
What do we do?
Maybe.
Katie?
Can you do it?
Me?
I believe you can do it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll try my best.
Alright.
Get her dressed and ready for the opening.
Okay.
Get her.
Oh.
Okay.
Give me a dress and makeup.
I need hair now.
Why hasn't it started yet?
I've never seen you so nervous before.
Ladies and gentlemen, colleagues, esteemed guests, and valued customers.
I'm thrilled to welcome you to the launch of our newest pharmaceutical innovation.
She has a boyfriend.
Why do you come here?
Mr. She can't worry about your employees.
I'll ask myself.
I have the funniest thing I'll find away from around.
Especially you.
Throughout Thompson's pharmaceutical's 70-year history, we've always believed in empowering patients through breakthrough solutions.
That's beautiful.
What?
That's not the speech I approve.
Our products reflect our steadfast commitment to making a positive impact on the world.
Inclusion, join us as we embark on a new era in healthcare.
Let's push boundaries and create a healthier, brighter future for all.
You look beautiful today.
You should look like that more often.
If I dress like this over day, won't I get fired?
I only fire people for their work.
Not how they look.
That was an amazing speech.
Do you freelance?
We have your Insta.
I don't know my phone with me.
Oh, what about what's happened?
Because this is more professional context.
We're currently drafting our contract.
She gives speeches for us exclusively in her new salaries 20,000 a month.
Oh my gosh.
Sorry, Katie.
I'm going to have to work 10 times harder to hopefully be able to afford to hire you in the near future.
You can forget it.
Because I'm not going to give you that opportunity.
There is no speech?
Yeah.
So, we had to improvise.
Wow.
We're even more impressed.
Why does she smell so familiar?
Can it be?
Sorry.
Are you at the Robertson Hotel on February 11th?
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm fine. I just need to use the bathroom.
Check the surveillance footage of the Robertson Hotel on February 11th.
I need to be sure who she was.
Lindsey, how long have you been serving this company?
Ten years?
Yes.
Ten years and 28 days.
I'm looking forward to the next decade.
Then why did you try to set up Katie at the risk of ruining our product launch?
Uh, I don't understand.
Then why is the speech page blank?
I know for a fact that you of all people would never make such a foolish mistake.
You should have known better.
It wasn't an honest mistake. I promise it will never happen again.
I will never do this again.
It better not.
Because if it does, I won't let you off the hook easily.
And never ever put your little schemes on Kate.
Be nice to her.
You can go now.
Congratulations, Katie.
You are pregnant.
Take care of yourself.
No drinking or smoking.
Prescribing a special course of prenatal vitamins and rules for you.
Nothing too dress.
It's not helping to keep you healthy.
They're there for us.
They're okay.
These are for you, by the way.
Richard, what do you mean?
I should have sat this a long time ago, Katie.
Here we go.
I want to spend every night like this with you.
Will you let me take care of you?
But I'm pregnant.
I'm pregnant.
Oh, it's...
How long did you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
So, I don't understand. What do you mean then?
I don't know.
All I can think of is I want to give this baby a good family and a proper home.
Katie, I know this might be very hard to talk about.
Did you get raped?
No.
If you did, it's completely fine.
No, no, no.
It's nothing like that.
But I did kind of take advantage of him.
It was all my fault. I initiated it.