Hey, Ellen's under a massive attack. Could you send his anti-hacking defense system over
to the Southeast?
I see.
And why not just tell him your tea?
Daddy, you know why. I want him to love me for me and not my background.
Know your talent or skill?
It'll just muddy the waters. Keep my secret one more time for me, will ya?
You want me to find true love, too, right?
Fine. Whatever you desire, my princess.
Thank you.
Only 388 hackers. A piece of cake.
Get it again Hermione.
Know with plenty of time for my hot date.
It's the tea's defense system.
The Brown family gave us access!
One system blocking through your hackers?
Tea is a damn GNIUS.
We need tea to upgrade our security firewall.
We're just gonna have more attacks.
Yes.
Agree.
Crisis averted.
Yeah, I'll see you at eight.
You never cared that I was just an assistant. It's time to tell him the truth.
I mean, together we might even be able to take over the whole industry.
Hmm.
He's never late.
Ellen, President Chris Evans and Lucy Brown, the eldest daughter,
Eris to the Brown family, announced their engagement tonight.
They even bother showing up.