Why are you even bother showing up?
Oh no, this is my favorite assistance, Angry.
Because we can't have that, you run my life.
Okay, listen, I'm sorry, I will totally make it up to you tonight.
You are engaged.
Can you stop watching the news, please? It's not good for you.
I'm not gonna be a mistress to an engaged man.
A mistress?
I'm gonna give you one chance to apologize for that.
I'm not gonna apologize. Why didn't you explain?
What do I even mean to you?
What are you doing here?
Come in to Chrissy, you?
No, I've come to take you home.
If I want to go home, I'm gonna go home by my own volition. Thank you very much.
This is your report from the hospital. They got sent to the house.
I thought you'd want to see it.