You think Lucy is Dr. T?
Yes.
She's not. She's lying to you.
Mother, what are you doing here?
If I hadn't come, Lucy's reputation would have been ruined by now.
Miss Evans, I think you owe me an apology.
Apology? Who do you think you are slandering Lucy like that?
You're what? A glorified secretary?
Does she help?
It's not slander?
If it's true, Lucy's not Dr. T.
Lucy is a student of Quentin's.
This is the full authorization of the defense system, signed by Dr. T herself.
Spread more lies like that, and I will rip that slut mouth right off your face.
Please don't be mad, Mrs. Evans.
I tried so hard to keep a low profile, it's only natural should have doubts.
That gave my authorization to the Brown family.
This really mess things up for me.
Chris, have to believe me. She's not Dr. T.
Why would I?
Because I am Dr. T.