Well, well, well, the real Dr. T.
What a surprise.
What do you want?
The only one who knew what Dr. T looked like was Dr. Quentin.
And he's dead.
So, with authorization in my hands, if you disappear.
Disappear.
Are you crazy?
Aren't you worried about getting arrested?
What about if Chris finds out the truth?
The truth is whatever people believe.
Do you know why the Brown family became lifelong friends
with the Evans family?
Because I saved Mrs. Evans' life in a robbery.
Ever since then, she's been trying to get Chris to marry me.
No, we said no.
Until yesterday, I became Dr. T.
Finally got him.
But you?
You're in my way.
Why couldn't you just stay his assistant?
Let's talk about this.
Just put the gun down.
I'll tell Chris that you're the real Dr. T.
Too late.
The dead tells no tears.