How did this bitch not even hurt a little bit?
Ms. Garcia, does your presence here mean that the Garcia family
is going to compete for Dr. T's patents?
Are you trying to take Dr. T away from Ellen?
Don't address questions to her.
Ms. Garcia, this is an internal meeting for LM.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
Actually, Hermione has been a part of LM for a very long time.
She's more than welcome to be here, sir.
This press conference is a closed set.
Yes, you.
You, can you please escort our guests to the seat near the door?
Great.
Now we can proceed.
Thank you, everyone, for joining us today.
Wait!
Plus, you've got to save your problem.
The service is under your attack again, and it's a whole lot stronger this time.