All right settle down we can identify the cause of failure and we can fix the problem, right boss
The hackers inside our building
Will then to find him the virus has penetrated our main system. We're losing millions by the minute Lucy
What can we do? What can they do the fence system is down dr. T. What do we do Lucy?
Upgrade your system or something and buy us some time to find the hacker all right Jesus
We might watch dr. T in action. I got to record this dr. T. Can we film your screen?
I uh I was the latter dr. T stage, right? I shouldn't have to handle such a minor virus by myself
I'll give it to her
I mean the Garcia family claims to be the father of a I with the most advanced system and algorithm the world has ever seen
If Miss Garcia's can't even handle a rudimentary counter hack, maybe the Garcia system isn't as up to where's we thought
That's a fair point