She did it.
The company's safe again.
Wait, so Ms. Garcia's Dr. T, and Ms. Brown lied about it.
Looks that way, doesn't it?
That's nonsense.
It was my auntie.
OK.
Quentin's depend system is super outdated.
If you want me to upgrade it for you,
it's going to cost you a fortune.
Hmm.
OK.
No, I mean a fortune.
You don't think that I can afford it?
$1 billion.
$1 billion?
Have you lost your mind?
Dr. Quentin's was only $10 million.
The delay you caused already cost the company $1 billion?
You know what actually wasn't done yet?
I want $1 billion.
Plus, a public apology from these two.
Why should I apologize to you?
Oh, because if I don't upgrade the server,
the virus will continue to attack LM until it just explodes.
Do you think I'm new to this?
The defense is already working.
I could hire global talent.
I'm sure somebody will be up for it.
OK.
But then you'll be responsible when, not if, when,
LM goes bankrupt.
System upgrade failed.
Main server under attack.
What is happening?
The outdated system has fallen apart.
We are under attack.
Mrs. Evans, you need to apologize now.
Do you really want to watch LM go to zero?
Her money?
Yes.
I was wrong.
I apologize.
What about you?
Lucy.
Apologize.
Clock's ticking.
I mean, Lucy.
Sorry.
I just, I couldn't quite hear you.
I'm sorry.
2 billion.