You want to sleep with me?
Grandmother dearest yes, I just returned for my trip Andrew you're a married man married to my friend's blind son remember
I know I've just been so busy with work
My chose a respectable young man to be your husband
Unlike those privileged young men you used to spend time with
They're supposed to be just a sham marriage to fulfill grandmother's wish is he really waiting for?
Now go buy him a present and visit him
All right, there are some things I need to discuss with them anyway
So I need to clarify something
Call me conservative, but I only sleep with those I love
We clearly don't share the same view
What if he fires me for rejecting him? I love to seduce
Plus I never force
Tell me what gift would suit a young conservative man like yourself
That depends on your relationship
It's my husband you have a husband and you're hitting on me