Has my so-called husband been lied to my grandmother all this time?
Hello? Who is this?
Frank, come join us.
Sir, how was meeting your new boss today?
Is he really as handsome as they say?
He may have a great body and be very charming,
but he's married, so I won't fall for him.
What a pity.
He did seem strangely familiar.
I can't remember where I recognised him from.
Don't forget, you're married too.
So what? His husband disappeared right after the freaking wedding.
We've actually agreed to get a divorce.
But now I can't find him.
Grandmother must be mistaken.
That man is very irresponsible.
The boss doesn't look happy.
Your date go well.
He's married.
Give up on your crazy idea.
I know.
But the marriage isn't...
Frank.
Come here. Take over for me.
Race is every time he bends over.
He's already turned me down so I better control myself.
Thank you, bro.
I can see you're really good with long sticks.
Maybe you can show me more of your techniques later.
Somewhere private.
I've got work to do.
Come on.
I can pay for those sessions.
Just name your price.
Sure you have one.
Not an interest.
Ouch!
Do you step on me?