Yeah, it's the same name as my husband. No wonder it felt so familiar. Could they be the same person?
I'll be waiting. I can't sleep until I see him tonight.
Okay, don't worry. I'm bringing to you as soon as possible.
Thanks so much. Don't go get a bottle of wine from the car. All right.
Sir, we're here.
Frank, what if it's really you?
Either just Frank Clark live here. Yes, and who are you?
Who are you looking for?
So my husband is fooling around with another man, and he doesn't even recognize me.
What's your relationship to him?
We've been together for years.
I'm so glad your husband's never around.
Got a problem with that. You better leave before I beat you up.
So you lied to grandmother about being single?
Disgusting.
Is it me, or does he look like my boss?
I stay with the most don't go get a bottle of wine from the car. All right, all right, I'm going.
That looks familiar.
Did you see some strange guy around here?
Common side is not safe. No, what was it?
Another heartbroken young man. What a waste of beautiful flowers.
Diamond clinks. I fit the jackpot.
Some straight guys came and asked for you, and it questioned my relationship with Lewis.
I didn't know bashes were still around. He was really weird.
But also, we had really hot. Okay, just go and brush it.
So he was looking for me.
Maybe it really was my boss.
Or perhaps my husband.
The flowers.
I must be losing my mind.
Why were the boss leaf flowers at my door anyway?
He'd give them to his husband.
Why?
Andrew, where's Frank?
Why have you come alone without him?
It's with his secret lover.
They've been living together for years.
Secret lover?
Really?
I saw it with my own two eyes.
I went to visit him and he was in the bath with another guy.
I'm divorcing.
Are you sure?
Don't make any spontaneous decision.
Maybe.
I only married him to fulfill your wish grandmother.
But it's done.
I don't need this marriage anymore.
Your parents failed marriage.
Doesn't mean all marriages are unhappy.
Want you to find love?
Love.
Maybe I will, but it's definitely not with him.
Do you have to divorce agreement immediately?
I might have made a big mistake.
Hello, sir.
This is Andrew's friend.
He needs your help.
Come to the red club's problem.
What? Now?
Yes.
He's very drunk.
So I guess part of being an assistant is picking up your drunk boss.
I'm just here to pick up Andrew.
I mean, my boss.
You're Frank.
Andrew never mentioned his assistant was so handsome.
Well, thank you.
You've got a boyfriend.
What?
If not, we could mainly go on a date sometime.
Let me just pick up my boss.
Damn.
You must be losing my charm.
Unless you're interested in your boss.
Do you find Andrew attractive?
Andrew was also over losing his charm.
First his husband cheats on him.
And now his handsome assistant is an even interested.
Actually, I don't know a gay guy who didn't want to sleep with him.
Listen.
I'm divorcing that bastard, okay?
And as for Frank, yeah.
He may be rejecting me now, but I swear I'll make him fall for me.
In fact, his heart will soon be mine.
Well, I hope he doesn't remember this drunk talk when he wakes up.
Be careful with Mr. Playboy's intentions.
He's never pursued or cared for anyone before.
You're a first.
Not interested.
For us men, physical attraction comes before feelings, too.
You can't fool yourself.
Okay.
You're all set.
I'm going to make my way.
Yes, sir.
You've got such an annoying thing.
You're the same, Frank.
She's dead old.
Damn it.
You just stay over there.
You need some time to sober up.
I guess no Frank can be trusted.
Just like my husband.
You're not like my husband.
You've got to resist this temptation.
He's my boss.
I can't make the same mistake again.
But I swear I'll make him fall for me.
In fact, his heart will soon be mine.
Me?
What's the best way to seduce a man like Frank?
Besides execute?
Did he fall asleep already?
With me, you'll have money.
A car, a house.
A better career.
I promise.
It seems like you thought about this story.
You know, my ex-partners never got this kind of treatment.
But you're a special Frank.
Relax.
I want to make you feel good.
Or maybe.
I can make you feel better.
Close your eyes.
Oh, it's this.
I'm putting you on trial.
First.
You're a superficial.
You failed to seduce me once.
You tried all these other lame techniques.
Money, power and physique are the biggest assets of a man.
You failed to seduce me because this isn't temptation.
This is a transaction.
Second.
You're arrogant.
Can't I die properly?
Then learn.
I invite a man you need to be served.
This isn't just about sex for me.
I want something more.
I value this job.
If I have to sell myself for it, I'd rather be five.
And tonight be the night you learn all this.
I'm in third.
You're a cheater.
You're the only one I lost.
Move north with me.
You little bitch.
You seduced my husband of five years.
You turned him into a cheater.
You're fired.
I just hate married men.
You cheat.
I'm getting so obsessed with you.
You're getting fired.
That's none of your business.
You failed to sleep with the boss.
And now you're losing your job.
Done.
How about it was the boss who tried to sleep with me?
Your husband has been the second relationship during this marriage.
So he wanted to pay two million composition after divorce.
This would be a proper punishment.
Especially for lying to grandmother.
Set up a meeting to discuss this.
Sir?
I can accept being fired, but you must pay me severance.
And you must not smear my reputation.
I don't intend to fire you.
What?
I've been reflecting.
I'd like to apologise for my recklessness and my arrogance.
Did he realise his mistakes?
Frank, I want you to stay in this position.
And I want you to join me for a party tomorrow night.
Are you really not angry?
So you've given up on your ridiculous plan to seduce me and trick me into bed?
No.
Well that's great, but...
I'm not sure if getting a divorce now is a good thing.
Considering this can encourage Andrew even more.
I remember you asked if I had a boyfriend.
But the truth is, I'm not dating anyone because I'm already married.
That's the most creative excuse I've ever heard.
I'm not lying.
My husband is...
Cruz.
Stop bothering my sister.
Whatever.
Cruz!
You must have heard everything.
I think I need to explain why I never mentioned my marriage before.
So, about my husband, Frank.
Do you really love your husband?
Andrew is not polite to ask people questions like that.
This Martin, Frank, Andrew...
How about we play Truth or Dare?
I'm gay.
I'm in.
I don't want to lie, but I don't want Andrew to keep pursuing me either.
You lost.
Truth or Dare?
Truth.
So tell us which cutie left these marks on you.
If you don't answer, your face of punishment worse than the dare would have been.
Punishment? I'm not afraid of punishment.
It was me.
I'd choose dare.
Frank, now turn around and drink this drink down to the last drink.
Enough of this game.
What a romantic moment.
But the dare isn't completed.
Game over.
And no one gets Frank into trouble.
Sorry.
I'm being impulsive again.
Thank you for helping me.
Well, I should be off.
Wait.
Frank, if you truly love your husband,
then I promise I'll force myself to suppress my desires.
But you choosing dare already tells me how you feel.
Forget it.
I'm not going to suppress the things.
Seems like nothing's going to change his mind.
I almost forgot I asked Jack to pick me up.
This be his husband.
Seems like he thinks Jack is my jerk of a husband.
Maybe that's even better.
Goodbye, sir.
You're totally wasted, aren't you?
No.
Just play a lot.
You're right.
You know we're not going to let anyone hurt you again.
Right.
Thank you.
They do look like hubbies.
Really?
I think Frank's just putting on a show for me.
Whoa.
Who knew the almighty Andrew could get so jealous?
Seeing him with another guy only adds fuel to my burning desire.
Okay.
For real.
Who thought this heartless playboy of 20 years would suffer to get a guy?
Well, you know I think this time something's different.
Maybe you're falling in love.
I've never been in love so I don't know what it feels like.
Besides, I can't get him to be even remotely interested in me.
I think you need to earn his trust first.
Trust.
I swear he has absolutely no shame.
Frank, quickly.
Check the company website.
These are clearly photoshopped.
Who repostes the company website?
So, he has a husband and a boyfriend at the same time.
Disgusting.
Juicing a married man at work shame on you.
My husband said that you came onto him.
Who knows how many men you've slept with.
You must be fine.
Hey, did I burn your hand?
Mr. Mann Hall.
You bastard.
You've been destroying this company's reputation.
You have the audacity to still be here.
Are those photos real?
It's the boss.
Come in.
Sir, I'm sorry about this mess.
I'll resign.
But I need to explain it.
Why?
Did you do something wrong?
Did you see the photos on the website?
The company's stock has dropped because of these.
I don't care about those rumors.
I trust you and I know it's all false.
I believe you'll prove me right.
Thank you.
Peter, tell the IT team to give Frank their full support.
Got it.
I need to trust him before he trusts me.
Sir, it was Darry.
You need to come with us.
Do you even know who my uncle is?
Hey, let me go.
Where are you fighting?
What?
Next time you frame someone, be more creative.
Don't just spread stupid rules.
I promise this is no one but let me go.
You shouldn't be taking you as well.
Gary framed me for my position.
Don't forget the boss chose me personally for this role.
So no one can take you from me.
Boss.
He's right.
Now get back to work.
Aw, so he likes being around with me.
Thank you.
For what?
I know you contacted the IT team.
Without your help, I wouldn't have figured out it was Gary so quickly.
The boss asked me to do it.
You should thank him.
I've been thinking, maybe I'm too biased against Andrew.
He's actually never headed.
Just level headed?
He's also answer.
I'm serious.
His body shaped like a real...
Like a real what?
Um, like a real gym buff.
I was just saying how great fitness is.
Is that it?
You know, abs are the only impressive thing about my body.
Please throw it through these documents in the next few days.
Sure.
Come with me.
You don't have to do this.
After all, you're my boss.
It's after working ours already.
Thank you.
For believing in me.
I just hope that someday you'll trust me.
Someday you'll trust me the way I trust you.
It's your husband.
No response.
Well then go to his house.
Do I need to teach you how to find someone?
Maybe I should leave.
Actually, he's house right now.
I've been knocking for a while, but no one's answering.
Okay, just give me a second.
It's William, your husband.
We need to meet and discuss the divorce.
I'm sorry sir.
I have dinner plans with my friends today.
It must be them trying to reach me.
That's all right.
Have a nice evening.
What am I thinking?
How could he possibly have received the message I sent to that bastard?
Hmm.
Thank you guys for cooking.
Looks like your boss wants you to work 24 hours a day.
No.
Believe it or not, he just cares about his employees.
Something's off.
You're defending him.
Are you failing for him?
What?
No.
Don't forget you used to love a husband you haven't divorced you.
That reminds me.
I totally forgot to reply to that message.
It's William, your husband.
We need to meet and discuss the divorce.
Where are you?
Why haven't you replied to my message?
Seems like my husband is losing his patience.
Why?
Trying to get rid of me as soon as possible.
Disappearing for so long only to message me about a divorce.
What an impossible man.
If you don't want your boss to keep trying to get in bed with you,
you can actually delay this divorce and then use your marriage as a reason to keep a distance from him.
Just forget that this silly marriage is more annoying than Andrew.
I've been busy today.
We can meet Sunday at 10am.
You think you guys?
Andrew.
Sorry boss.
Frank, what are you doing here?
I'm just here to meet up.
Hello?
Hold on, I'm coming. Right away.
It's urgent.
We've got to take the next flight for a business trip.
Come.
I'm sorry, some work things popped up.
When will you be free then?
I don't know.
Oh, cool whenever I can.
Don't play games to avoid this divorce.
Where are you?
Well, if you're going to speak like that, I might refuse to sign the agreement at all.
I'm doing it.
What you're doing here?