If you have no issue with this divorce paper, be a sight right here.
I've never signed a divorce agreement before, so I need to read this carefully.
Frank Clark must pay William Kensington £2 million in compensation damages for reputation damages.
Why the hell should I pay £2 million?
We both know what happens.
If you play dumb, you can take a more brutal way.
I'm not signing. If you want a divorce, we can settle it in court.
I won't stand for any false accusations, I won't pay him a penny.
Give me a second. I don't want to have any connection with him anymore.
It's fine. I just want to get divorced fast. I don't want to have any connection with him anymore.
Your husband just raved your conversation. Take a look at this.
Why does his handwriting look so much like Frank's?