I'm sorry, sir. Are you a family member of Mr. Cox?
Boss?
I'm sorry.
Apparently I forgot that he has a husband to take care of him and that I'm just his boss.
Peter, upgrade his VIP services and pay off all the Michelle's.
Where's your handsome assistant? It's been a while since I've seen him.
Why would anyone be interested in a married man?
Well, clearly I'm better than his husband would be.
Stop messing around.
I won't back down.
You haven't given up on him yet, have you?
I feel sad.
Why does my first love have to be so complicated?
So it is love.
You always say you'd be a playboy, it's not to get your feelings hurt.
I was wrong.
Is it too late to change my mind?
You're William Kensington for God's sake.
You're the most charming man in this city.
How ironic.
The charm clearly doesn't work on him.
Cheers. The true love.
Your boss isn't happy.
His damn husband hurt him again.
You should come and take him home.