His mother really likes me and our families have a strong connection
You think it'll end up with you because it does
Andrew's never been seen with anybody. He's a real playable man broke a lot of hearts
What do you think makes you special?
I have to be down to earth
Whether he's married or not. I might just be another experiment for Andrew and
Considering our backgrounds, maybe we're not really compatible
Where's Frank?
Wow, this is the first time I've seen you prepare food. It's not for you
It's been so fucking long. Don't you remember the old times? What are you doing?
Damn it. I can't spend a second without thinking about it. This needs your signature
The signature can wait. I can't resist you