I'm already married, and I love my husband.
He stayed the night at Andrew's immediately out of sight in your divorce agreement.
Oh, how you love your husband.
You've been spying on me.
I know everything about you, including your ex, Gint.
You just said?
The way I say you have two options.
The first is to resign and leave the city immediately.
The second is to stay and expect for your life to be entirely ruined.
Trust me, you will be miserable than you were three years ago.
I won't resign.
I won't need the city either.
Is that so?
Let's wait and see.
Should you tell Andrew about this encounter with us?
You should be very worried about what can happen to that grandmother of yours.
Don't you dare?
Thomas, I've got this guest out of my house.
Madam, he's just an assistant.
Why do you care?
Just an assistant.
He is the guy that Andrew married.
What?
Frank's Andrew's husband?
Why?
Why didn't he tell me?
He doesn't know.
Frank is up to something.
He can smell the money.
So Andrew doesn't know?
He mistook some guy for his husband, and wrongly assumed he was cheating, so he wants a divorce.
What do we do?
They've already signed the divorce agreement, but they meet in court next week.
Who knows what will happen after this?
We have to ensure that Frank's infidelity becomes clean.
I can handle that.
Did he hear a conversation?