Lucas, get him out of my side.
Andrew, I'm sorry about the other...
Oh, madam, madam, say something!
Andrew, my darling son, it's your birthday today.
And my wish for you is for you to get rid of that filthy husbandy husbandy husbandy.
Is that so? You abandoned me and my father when I was a teenager.
And then when he died, he manipulated me and grandmother to grab more of the estate.
Don't you ever mess with my life again?
And besides, Frank is my assistant.
So if you mess with him, you'll have to pay for it.
Andrew.
Madam, Frank's gone.
I don't think that Andrew knows the truth yet, so we don't have much time.
No worries, madam. I've already arranged everything.
Frank, get me a drink.
Now, are you deaf?
You gave you the right to order me around.
You're an assistant, that's your job.
Don't make me repeat myself or I'll have you running from the city in a minute.
Yet another person who wants me to leave the city.
First of all, I'm Andrew's personal assistant, not yours.
Second, I work for Crown Group.
So if you want to get me orders, maybe get a job at our company first.
Is that so?
Seems you don't really care about your grandmother.
Nasty people like you will get the karma eventually.
What's your language, you low-life?
Hey!