What's the language in low life?
Hey!
What do you think you are?
Frank is my guest.
So if there's anyone who's extra here, that's you.
You won't regret this.
Is there something you need to tell me?
I can't tell him that his mother is using my grandmother's safety as leverage.
I should go check on the other guests.
Frank, do you really think that there's not a chance between us?
No.
Maybe I'm just not cut out for love.
Maybe it's time to give up on this pursuit completely.
Frank, we're together in this game.
We will have our cards, so we've finished it.
Let's move to our respective rooms.
Um, you go first and we'll follow.
I don't get it. Do you want to be with Frank or not?