Cuesasás y Indo
Yet el Odhi here
Comencentre poraningo por te pudaine noussravita
Bueno?
Nousa en inguenacla cedadora
No podo dar de trotamento
que?
Estas loque verda
Bueno enro y deta eso y infarma
Pero Noustó loque
Solo.
Infarma de molour?
Buien
Mena morien enbothamamento noucada vie borki
Desen que quando conon sis la mores de probita
Te si entas me feliz
I am not an enemy, but I am very happy.
I'm not sure. But I just want to help you.
I am a very happy member of the universe.
I am very happy.
I love you and I love you.
I'm so happy you are a very happy member.
I am very happy that you are the one who was the first to meet.
I am very happy to meet you.
I am very happy that you are not a very happy member.
I would say, if I would have thought I'd have a chance to be here,
I'd like to know that I'm out of space,
I'll be here because I don't have a chance to be here.
In the future, I'll be here for the first time.
I'm not sure how to do this.