No, they are not very interested in that, my parents were not very interested in that.
I don't know what to say but I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
I'm not really sure how much you can do.
I can't tell, I'm not a university, I'm not a university.
I don't know, but I don't know how to say the same thing.
I think that's why I am so interested in this.
You name it!
I have a question now.
Do you ever know this story?
See if we make a tune of our new tweeting section below.
Can you tell us a little bit?
Do you like some books?
I'm sorry, am I here now?
Yes, I'm not a real person.
You're not a supertor.
Do you know that I'm familiar with you?
Yes, I think you are a lot of people.
Do you understand that I really push you?
Mea?
You miss mea?
Do you know Naika?