Oh shiny.
You have a friend who got left?
What's the matter?
Why do I do this?
Because I don't have a friend.
You have a friend in my career.
Is it a direct debt?
You have a member who has a friend in your life.
You have an entree.
You have a friend who comes here to see you right?
Oh, Bottom Brand, the second one,
the owner of the treasure registers.
Where are they hiding?
I had a friend who is missing out on me.
You had a friend who is missing out on me.
I got a friend here.
Okay, don't miss this.
John, don't just and you can't just have any warning.
It doesn't mean I was to look up a little but I'm supposed to have an idea.
Uh, No, no, no, it's perhaps I have no idea.
You know what?
It's just to be a little bit cryo.
No no much as I am.
I am not going to do it because I'm serious.
On this day's weather and I can make a lot of these.
I don't know how I am, but I just think I'm going to be a lot more than me.
Why don't you tell me why he is just not here.
I guess he doesn't stop saying that.
I see a good feeling of that.
Oh, and he lost my son's heart.
He's lost me.
What are you doing in this world?
No.
That's strange.
To be honest, that's a very strange area.
I don't know.
But I have to be honest, because I'm gonna put on this kind of topic.
No, I'm gonna be honest if you want to be honest but not positive.
Isn't this a good idea?
and I'm coming to the end of the day.
I've been well after my older life.
I've been that young girl.
I'm so glad that I'm here.
You're the first to know someone who has been in a situation.
I'm just a good girl.
You're the first to know someone who has been in a situation
where you can do something like this.
And then, the first to know something,
you can do something yourself.
You're the only one with me.
Never that.
I don't think I can do anything but me.
Ah, see.
Gracias.
Hey, son.
Hey.
Hey, right.
the game god's.
Eo Ido ke la Señorita cox,
the country group of the hoven n' hreikas, Ela Cidar,
comes her most apparent,
she'll always be that.
In Troy, no no no no Buessidade,
Elite, NISTA, Esta, Osenido, Salos, y si seis,
y esta crea un lud extraadina y ocorta fóllio
professional, auntie, Zegra, doerse.
Nousi huala las mariposa,
socieles, ela cesole los guztans fiestas,
ela spajan cettras.
Mo chapi de rizprayudame, seño.
Herizun, chase, herizun, polegema me chase.
We don't want to talk about this, we don't want to talk about it, but it's not enough to have a
Enjoy the time!
Cool, have a good day.
Hello everyone!
Let's see what happens in the video.
We'll go now.
You can film some of the material as well.
I've also been doing it technically.
It would be nice if you could film a video?
Yes.
I'm crazy too.
Do you like it or have a video?
Do you like it?
And now she knows we can run through the
hands of the new members of the city.
We have the possibility to protect
themselves from the darkness.
We have to know that we can
decide to get that right.
The moment all is dead,
we have to think so.
This is the time you have to go in
the streets of the city.
Then we will be the first city to
open in the city of the world
and in other services that we have
to make sure if the city has
been sent to the city
there are two ways to decide
how many words to let go.
Well, these are all the best things in the world.
Are you wowah?
I like it and you're really joking.
It is the best place we have ever been?
There's a lot of people.
Are you surprised?
But when we were in the market I had a good time.
And what was that?
Already.
And you're very careful.
Hmm.
I'm a fun and necessary.
But when you are in the interest world,
you're going to be able to find a world
that has no tax due to this part of your experience.
I'm not sure what I'm doing here, but also what I'm doing here is that I'm standing on the left side of the street
and I'm just looking forward to the next step that I'm going to be going to the next step
and I'm looking forward to places where I'm going to work again
I'm going to go to the next step that I want to work on
And what are you doing here?
You're doing great. I'm doing great. I'm going to work here.
Let's go.
did you order to go here for the last time?
would you like to visit me?
no, you don't know about this anymore
I thought I'd be the first to know
you want to meet Elento
I'll got money back in the morning
I'll have a year for you
that's fine
we will get our own SHEKOS
never done this
where we can see her
yes, it's the same trend
yes, except the other side
that's the same and the other side
that's the first time
We've been without you!
We're just gonna be the first to play in the game game!
Only if you play in the game!
You don't have to do that.
You don't want to do this.
You don't have to take me in the game game!
Here's the story!
Your voice is so beautiful!
All of these stories are from the beginning of the game!
It was no matter if you were in a game game!
And I would say that you can play in the game game
We will have the right to think about the same abilities we have.
We need to take care of the same abilities we have to make this out of the way.
What's wrong?
We have to go.
I'm not afraid of you.
You're not afraid of us.
I don't think anyone has to worry about us, but I feel that we are just going to be in this
way.
I don't think we can do anything more than this.
You know, Ciantos and your soldiers
And I can't remember
But...
Kate!
I'm not just a genius
So you can do it
What do you mean
Well, you can do it
I know, that's the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen
You know, I love you
But you don't have to be a genius
I don't have to be a genius
You're just a genius
I don't know.
I know that, that is something I can do,
but I want to make a decision.
But it is hard to remember.
All the money I can do,
so I'm going to try.
And I'm going to try the money.
Oh, dear.
How are you?
I'm going to try the money.
I'm going to try the money for you.
At the end of the day,
A number of people.
Yeah, but what I do?
What are in the heart of technology,
what do you do?
What are you going to do?
Get this person.
It's hard.
I like it because there's a lot of people.
Do you think people like those who live here?
Don't say that and what else?
I think the day has happened,
so we have the opportunity
to talk to people who live on the other side.
We're working with the EU and the EU and we're creating a new and alive political participation
and the attitude we've been doing to achieve this.
I'm not sure that we're going to win the first round of the game.
I don't know if I can even do this to you.
I'm a hot guy.
That's what you're doing.
What?
What are you doing?
What's the problem with the real world?
What's the problem with the real world that we have to do?
It's the real world.
There it is, so interesting!
Ahhh!
You can't be alone though, if you want to stay with me.
Yes, I imagine you have a bad mood,
and I'm not the best one to know about you.
I'm not the best, but I'm not the good one.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey!
Come on, Dad!
Good to see you, too!
And don't words to be named Badoc.
Badoc.
Badoc!
You want a boo?
Badoc.
I think this is a great idea.
You can tell us.
We were in the house.
I didn't know.
I thought it was illegal to be here.
We were in the house.
And I was in the house.
He just wanted to go.
He wanted to be a good father.
I thought I was a good father.
It was my father's father.
And what happened to him now that I'm a principal is not even going to do it.
What?
What are you doing here?
Because you're doing it a lot.
Oh.
You are going to do it for a bit.
You're going to do it for nada?
Who is going to do it?
Oh.
You don't know how to change your company anymore.
I'm a company you already know, and I'm very proud you.
Oh, there's a new company here.
They are also a personal employer.
What really happened?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't think it's the same.
But the other part of the story is that it's different.
I don't think it's even the same thing.
What?
Where are you?
See?
Oh, you don't have to be an architect?
You'd be happy to do this, girl.
Catherine Cough's it!
I've never heard of it.
Who, you've never heard?
No, I'd never heard of it.
I'll tell you the truth.
What do you want, my friend?
I don't know.
I've always heard of love about how we'd become.
What's next?
I know that there are many ways to connect the world with the world.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure that there are many ways to connect the world.
I love you!
I love you and I love you.
I want to help you with the music.
I want to help you.
But I want to help you with the music.
Why are you still here?
I'm not going to do anything like this.
But you don't want to be a good teacher.
You're a good teacher.
I'm a good teacher.
I'm not going to do anything like this.