These are the rare characters that are leading their own character.
There are many characters that support the characters of a character.
Are you really good at this?
If you want to actually get your own effects.
We'rema's first character who had a very rare character.
The truth is, there's no experience in the character of a character or something.
But yes, we will have a little patience.
But it looks like we're not going to get there.
And there's no idea.
But there is no idea for me.
No.
I can't see everybody's experiences,
and it's a very attractive relationship
when a facility is located.
It's a very attractive thing.
It's not like you're going to be able to look at.
Yeah.
Mr. Yaba, can I see the other thing?
Where is the street?
It's different.
I wasn't working here.
Because you're not working here for me.
I can't look at this.
So, I always experience this, but it's just like it.