Patrick, thought you were really injured.
Yeah, and you're all dressed up.
It'll make sense now.
You're all lying to Patrick again.
I was this woman.
I feel disgusted just looking at her.
And no wonder why.
Just saying it.
I'd need to make in false and defamatory remarks
about vegan children and her company.
What the hell?
I'm not starting this nonsense.
What?
What did you just say?
You never seen no to Patrick.
So you really want me to sign this?
You're me out.
Patrick, give me a second.
Jasmine Darlene, you can't just be my company.
Patrick and I worked so hard for him.
Jasmine, are you out of your mind?
Vivian, are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
Are you just trying to kill me?
Patrick, she's really scaring me.
You promised my parents you'd take care of me.
Jasmine, enough is enough.
Do you still want to be Mrs. Miller or not?
Ask me.
Ask I.
Vivian, are you right?
You better learn to respect Vivian
if you plan on being Mrs. Miller.
Looks like being married to my crush
was never a really big dream.
What a little joke of a marriage.
Wow, I didn't realize you were such a jerk, Patrick.
What?