Well, let's both just calm down, okay?
It's workaholic.
How come you're suddenly free to have a drink?
Your brother proposed to me yesterday.
What the fuck?
How did I not see that he was so into you before?
Well, of course he refused, right?
How do you know if you wanted mad at I know
that he still had feelings for Patrick?
What's happening to me?
I thought I hated him.
Do you remember how obsessed you were with him in college?
He was always in the library,
and you would come up with all kinds of excuses
just to bump into him.
My god, I was so silly back then.
Yeah, and he was so busy when his exams
that he couldn't even remember your name
for a mom.
But you didn't mind because you liked how serious
he was about his studies.
How could feelings like this disappear that easily?
Well, he doesn't sound like you're not supposed to
us being together anymore.
Maybe I just know that this grown-up, Jasmine
wouldn't lose herself over a men.
And you know what?
If you still have feelings for him,
you should be honest with him about it.
Then I will try spending more time with him.
Patrick!
He wants a divorce because you are planning to marry someone else.