What?
How could that be true?
Isaac is here?
No way, it can't be.
I genuinely painted the last painting what? Four years ago.
And then disappeared. It's got to be a hoax.
They said this art is behind that and countless other masterpieces is dead.
How could they be here?
Isaac, what are you insinuating?
Isaac is standing right next to me,
and her name is...
Jasmine Harper.
But this reprise, stop embarrassing me in public.
How could it be Isaac?
That girl is Isaac.
Come on.
Even she looks so shocked by that.
Don't you think their mind and campaign went too far?
Well, she's a pretty girl, I give her that.
But how can she be a genius artist?
You gotta be kidding me.
Jess, trust me.
Vivian was line, huh?
No wonder where she's always been after Patrick.
How low of her?
Sad.
So pathetic.
Hey, leave, leave, stop, stop.
Give us a kiss, save me, save me, save me, save me.
I think you have no rights to be here.
Leave.
Ah, God, you do this to me, pomis!
Make your regret!
I'm Isaac, the anonymous artist who vanished.
What are the things from the past how I've forgotten?