Mrs. Amson, this is the divorce agreement you requested.
Please also prepare the transfer documents.
Mrs. Amson, are you really going to transfer all of the inheritance Mr. Carter left you to Mr. Amson?
Where is it? Are you looking for this?
Thank you. Don't be upset.
My parents are gone, but I haven't cried.
Are your parents buried there?
Lily. Where have you been?
I lost my hearing aid. He helped me find it.
Thank you, William.
Lillian is lucky to have met a gentleman such as you.
Let's go. Say goodbye to William.
Yes. Just call me Lillian. I'm not Mrs. Amson anymore.
You already gave up the marital property.
And now you're giving away your premarital assets. You will have nothing left.
I owe him much more than that.
I'm home tonight. I have something to tell you.