How dare you come back here?
Three years of marriage, no heir for William,
and you want a divorce?
How will we have anything if you divorce him?
So you admit, you married me all for money.
It was the only thing you were useful for,
and you screwed it up!
Get out of my house!
Oh, and you can finally have a proper drink
without Lillian here to ruin it.
So where is she?
Back with a family.
And that's how it should be.
A disabled woman from a fallen family
could never measure up to you.
You've put up with her for three years.
That's far more time than she deserved.
Betty, I have nowhere else to go.
Oh, honey, you do not deserve this kind of treatment
from that dirt-eating, conniving, evil, parent-less.
Then it's only fitting he's married to a woman
who wants a baby from honey.
Well, as long as you're here, you're a free woman.
How are your ears?
Before you go completely, Deb,
I would suggest you spend time with the people that you love.
Let their voices be the last ones you remember.
Busy tomorrow night.
At the office, I'm interested.
Mind your own business.
I don't want to be with that boy, especially on you.
Lily's had it beyond tough growing up.
Her mom treats her like a burden.
Mom!
Nobody took her seriously.
Lily didn't even know that her mom set her up.
She's loved you all of these years.
Even if you can't love her back,
you should still treat her with some kind of respect.
She tell you to play the victim?
Why don't you tell her whatever's going on
in that puny little brain of hers?
She deserves it.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Samson is such an asshole.
You called him?
Yeah.
I wanted to give him a piece of my mind.
But it just goes in one ear and out the other.
You want a divorce?
Tomorrow morning, 10 o'clock.
Lillian's been out of parents for a while.
Isn't she coming back soon?
She's done.
We're fine for divorce tomorrow.
Congratulations.
You're finally free.
There's nobody else in between us.
We broke up long before I married Lillian.
You've never been in between us.
You've carried the Samson legacy alone for all these years.
But that's because you haven't had a competent person
by your side.
I risked my own life to save them.
You don't have to go through the rest of your life alone,
especially when you have people here who care about you.
I will never forget what you did for my family.
Lillian, I don't love you anymore.
Sorry.
We're taking up your time doing work.
Let's just get the soap on.
Don't come crying back to me when you regret it later.
We can sign the papers after the waiting period.
See you next month.
Take care.
I endured three years of this hellish marriage
just for her to end it on her terms.
You want to disappear?
So will the card.
Those Samson operations and the current controlling
shareholder of card room.
I now is our merger, the card into Samson.
See if you take dependent control, thank you.
It was insufferable.
How could he do that to you?
Dragged our family business down with you.
I'm so angry.
I can't keep burdening you with this.
But you aren't.
Lillian, why must you punish me?
All the news, regulations, those cards
are finally getting what they deserve.
That's my cup.
Weeks, and this woman still hasn't come to beg me.
Have you found Lillian?
Don won't tell.
Keep an eye on her.
I'll be right there.
It's OK, buddy.
I'm fine here.
I can't trouble you anymore.
What is this?
Are you staying in this hobo den?
William and I are pretty much divorced.
If you want to be with him, go for it.
Leave me alone.
You better not pull any tricks.
I don't want to see you near William again.
You mind?
I'm talking to you, you deaf bitch.
Let me go!
Never finds out you're worth the one who
almost saved his parents.
Stop fucking lying.
I have the scar.
I'm the one that saved them.
You know William never loved you, right?
But you could hide from your own mother?
You kicked me out.
Sign this.
And Carter is to marry Mr. Beard.
Stop on the Carter family.
Isn't D'Angelo the mafia boss?
He's almost 80.
You're lucky he doesn't mind getting used up sloppy sex.
You're selling me again?
Do you have any empathy at all?
Get ready for the wedding.
I'm doing this again.
You don't have to talk to me like that.
Sign it.
No!
I gave you your life.
You owe me.
I won't sign!
I didn't ask for this life.
You can take it back.
Are you threatening me?
I do.
I'm going to be back in three days, if you're still alive.
Lily, is that you?
That's it.
Oh, you've been.
It's been so.
Yeah, I just got back into town today.
Betty was telling me that you got the horse with William
or something.
How many drinks have you had?
Is that your first?
Take that.
Yeah, let me take you home.
Be careful.
Stay right there.
I'm going to bring you the goods.
Okay, well, Mr. Sampson.
Excuse me.
Wow.
You already found a new one?
Hey, so you know, you're still married, so I'm trying to do it.
Let's get you right here.
Carter's heiress has humble taste, noted.
Carter doesn't exist anymore, and neither does she.
Yeah, well, William's gone way too far.
I'm fine here.
Well, hey, if you need anything, just let me know.
I hate seeing him like this.
Okay?
Thank you.
Vincent, did you?
What are you doing?
You're hurting me.
Our divorce is still processing, and you're already seeing other men?
Who was that guy?
None of your business.
Have you been seeing him behind my back this whole time?
Is that why you wanted a divorce?
For three years, I gave up painting, gave up my social life, locked myself in the house,
waiting for you to come home every night.
What do you think?
As long as we haven't gotten the divorce papers, you're still my wife.
So now you want me.
Now that I don't want you, now that some other man cares for me.
So what if I do?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Please.
Look at me.
I can't handle your chemistry.
How are you going?
Find yourself a decent place to live.
I don't want people saying the Samson's mistreated you.
You'll have your papers.
Just a game for you this whole time?
By your solitary thought.
The guy's name is Vincent Miller.
This Lillian's childhood friend living abroad for years, he's a well-off independent
investor who owns more than half of the galleries and museums in Estonia.
So he's the RTFR team time.
I thought he was going to be serious.
Did you hear that?
Lillian is getting married again.
Where did you hear this?
Lillian's mom demanded 30 million and agreed to marry her after that mob boss, DeAngelo.
I was Carter's pulling that same marriage scam like that.
You're the best in the world, sweetie.
Don't let anyone look down on you.
You.
I can't hear you.
What?
I don't have a family.
Thing to say.
Please listen.
What do you mean?
If I had known you hated this marriage, I wouldn't have married you.
If I had known you couldn't let go of 70, I wouldn't have married you.
If I had known that you would never love me, I would have rather died than marry you.
I would have never buried such a piece of shit.
Lillian, where are you right now?
I'm left to live for life, there's no meaning anymore.
Dad, I miss you.
I wish I could go back to when you were still around, I wish I could see you.
Lillian?
Oh my God.
At least it was side note.
You have to go find her.
Okay, yes.
I get it.
I'm on it.
Don't do anything stupid.
But don't worry.
The divorce will definitely go through.
Lily, wake up.
Hey, don't fall asleep.
Who are you?
What are you doing with my daughter?
Oh, she's your daughter now?
Where were you when she was trying to kill herself?
Hey.
So she's here too.
You're whoever to this.
You won't get away with this.
How is she?
The patient pulled through.
But, is she aware that she's pregnant?
No more reckless decisions.
No matter what, you still have me invented.
Thank you.
We got you.
Oh, him?
William hates me.
Thank you.
He wouldn't want this child.
Lily and Carter's my friend.
Can you tell me what's wrong with her?
We're lucky we got her when we did.
She took too many sleeping pills.
Intentionally?
At least it didn't hurt the fetus.
The fetus?