I never had a child.
How's little Emma?
Not good. She's still in the hospital.
Please, my daughter is counting on you, Betty.
I can't bring her back with me.
Don't worry. You take care of yourself too.
You sure you want to face William again?
I need the cord blood to save Emma.
Once I get William's burn, get pregnant, I'll leave.
Mr. Sampson, you seem so interested in my past.
Do you ever love me?
Don't change the subject.
Come on.
Don't waste a beautiful night.
You seem to have gotten quite good at seducing.
Is that how you got Vincent?
Faking your own death?
It's how you have amnesia?
Tricks do you have up your sleeve.
I don't drink something to eat.
Now you're just a told to me.
Mr. Sampson, you wanted to see me?
What can I do for you?
You've been dressing like that for Vincent for the past four years?
Where'd you get the money for the auction?
From Vincent?
What are you talking about?
I earned my own money.
You?
You spent three years as my housewife.
I haven't seen you earn a dime.
I've been painting since I was four.
My work has earned millions across Europe.
But you still owe me three billion dollars.
I can debate it back, but...
Mr. Sampson.
Please.
Have some self-respect.
William.
William?
You're still alive?
I told you she was dead.
Can you leave?
Sure.
Just let me know when you're free.
That bitch is still alive?
It's so nice to see you back.
Excuse me, do I?
Do I know you?
I know you're upset that me and William aren't together now, but...
We're getting married soon.
And if you had any decency at all, you wouldn't go near him.
Sorry.
What is so funny?
When was William ever your man?
Just so you know, people around here?
He's still calling me Mr. Sampson.
William, William, William, hit me!
I heard everything.
I'm not deaf.
And she wouldn't have hit you if he didn't provoke her first.
William, you know how she treats me.
Come on, please.
What do you want from me?
Stay away from her.
Don't cause problems.
No leave.
Just a word of advice.
William disappeared with Sampson for four years, and nobody knows what happened to her.
Now she's back, and she's claiming amnesia.
Just make sure you don't get fooled at.
Baby, are you serious?
After this, you will get back with me.
You don't want William anymore?
I've already booked the pie ticket.
You want to go with me or not?
Wait for me.
I'm here to kill you.
You're something.
I'm here to start.
I'll kill you.
She'll run away with me.
She's lying.
I'm Mrs. Sampson.
If you kill me, she can bury me with a prison.
Promise me.
Then since people took her attacker away.
I can't lose you again.
Make sure she has the best care.
Spare no expense.
Lily, you're awake.
Hey, how are you feeling?
Is it still hurt?
Steph, she, uh, she tried to kill me.
It was Stephanie's ex-boyfriend.
But don't worry, I handed him over to the police.
Thank you.
Yeah, it was, um...
It was William.
Yeah.
He arrived first.
And took you to the hospital.
Just ate her all night.
And he left about 30 minutes ago.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I, uh...
And I died.
Again.
I'm here.
Don't be scared.
Thank you.
Mr. Sampson.
Millian, you haven't really lost your memory, right?
You hate me, and that's why you don't want to remember me.
Listen, if we divorce, would you marry Vincent?
If I let you go, would you truly be happy?
Yes, if I could.
Millian, you're still my wife, remember?
For three years.
Did you ever really consider it a marriage?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, I need a nurse, please!
Now!
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be alright.
Her hearing was fine.
I don't know why she's bleeding.
What do you think hearing loss is easy to fix?
Choose something more of a hearing because of you.
Move out of the way.
Let me do this.
Hey, no, give it to me.
I'm her husband.
Who bullies and abuses his wife?
Don't do it myself.
Mr. Sampson.
Hey.
I'll be back.
And then this for years.
You're gonna be okay.
And this condition has worsened.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Is your hearing again?
Take me back to our old house.
I just found out that Mrs. Sampson has a child in Estonia.
I'm not sure if it's heard of Vincent.
Millian, is our child still alive?
Do you remember when you threw a vase at me in the hospital?
I was already pregnant, man.
Child didn't make it.
You were the one who killed him.
Millian, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please don't hate me.
It's happened to China.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Is your hearing again?
Take me back to our old house.
I won't have a look.
I just found out that Mrs. Sampson has a child in Estonia.
I'm not sure if it's heard of Vincent.
Millian, is our child still alive?
Do you remember when you threw a vase at me in the hospital?
I was already pregnant, man.
Child didn't make it.
You were the one who killed him.
Millian, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please don't hate me.
It's happened to China.
I should have said something before I left.
Do you have a child in Vincent?
Did you get close to me on the purpose?
What do you want?
I just couldn't get over you.
I wanted to see you once more.
Well, you have me now.
Then, are you going to leave me again?
You don't understand what I want.
Then tell me.
You still want your love?
I start a new life.
You still love me, right?
Millian, give me a month.
If you still don't want me then, I'll let you go.
But I'm going to prove to you that I'm better than Vincent.
Okay, you have one month.
Just enough time to confirm if I'm pregnant.
Same, I know you.
I love you.
I want to show you something.
These are all my dad's belongings.
My dad painted me this.
I thought I'd never see it again.
I brought it all back.
Except for the emerald necklace you took.
Everything is back where it belongs.
Honeymoon trip.
I'm going to prove to you in one month that I'm better than Vincent.
Is this the childish and ridiculous, like, additive nature of the woman?
I'm going to prove to you and make you fall in love with me all over again.
It feels like we really are having a marriage.
I was one millimeter away from hitting a major artery.
Miss Stephanie's ex-boyfriend is also the one who attacked Mrs. Samson.
You attacked Lillian?
I'm sorry.
You will leave me and he just probably wanted to get back at her.
I know what she told him, but he tried to kill me.
I will never try to take William from you again.
What a performance.
Look at what you did to me.
Did it hurt when you tried to stop yourself?
Doug did try to attack Stephanie, but he got nothing out of it.
And Stephanie ended up breaking his leg.
See?
She knows all of Doug's movements so well.
I knew somebody tried to get him to kill me.
William, did you tell Doug to kill Stephanie?
He's Stephanie.
Doug, you're not in prison.
William, save me! He's going to try to kill me!
I did not!
Miss you manipulated me to take Lillian.
Then try to kill me to kill my quiet.
First, I've already booked the flight ticket.
You want to go with me or not?
I'm here! He's insane! I don't know who this person is!
I hope you actually die.
Vincent, can you get Doug out of jail for me?
I did it because I love you. I saved your parents, remember?
You saved William's parents.
Of course!
You're serious.
When they had their car accident, I risked my life trying to save them.
But they're trying to save them.
Now, listen, William, 20 years ago, I was the one who tried to save your parents from the accident.
I always thought it was Stephanie. I mean, she has the scar.
Don't sleep! The ambulance will be here soon!
William, take care of me!
My mommy gets car revision surgery.
So, you can't see it anymore.
The girl who called me ambulance is you.
What about your scar?
She must have faked it. How could a scar from 20 years ago still look so fresh?
I say her record is fake, and my scar is real.
Would you believe me?
I need to get out of here.
You knew Stephanie lied. Why didn't you tell me?
You never listened to me.
I was appointed telling you.
I will never do that to you ever again.
Are you okay?
Congratulations, Miss Carter. You're pregnant.
Really, that's wonderful.
Now that our mission's complete, we can go back to Estonia tomorrow and...
little Emma and Betty are waiting for us, so...
I'm waiting tomorrow.
Hey, hey, don't tell me you're falling for him.
Don't worry, Vincent. I'm not saying I won't leave.
It's just, you might want to know about the child, the father.
Don't forget, why Emma got sick in the first place.
He hurt you and Emma right after you got pregnant.
Do you really think that he deserves to be a father?
I've... I've lost my head. Go back to Estonia.
Come in and pick you up. I have a surprise for you.
What's going on? Why so fit in?
I'm returning your father's business to you.
Just the way you left it.
What I can give you is so much more than what Vincent can.
Sorry, babe. I gotta take this. We'll be here back.
Well, yeah. If only you had done this sooner.
Don't tell me you're having second thoughts.
Betty, would you regret missing out on love?
Men only realize what they've lost after it's gone.
Think about how much Vincent has done for you.
I don't disagree.
Why are you doing your hardest times?
Maybe you will, you should know about Emma.
Emma?
Excellent. Close the deal.
Mr. Samson.
I don't disagree, but maybe you will, you should know about Emma.
The child is mine.
But why wouldn't you tell me?
Mr. Samson is leaving for Estonia with Vincent.
They're flight leaves in a few hours.
Oh, no.
Lillian, why didn't you tell me about our child?
She didn't tell you because you were a terrible husband
and would have been a terrible father.
The child is dead, will you?
The child is gone.
Oh.
She was four years old and suffered from a severe disease.
Our condition worsened last night.
Babe, they couldn't save her.
Actually, I came back to ask you for a child.
As umbilical cord blood would save her.
So, you're pregnant?
Lillian, I'm sorry for all the pain I've caused you.
I didn't know how to be a good husband, but I'm, I'm learning.
Now, now that we're expecting, let's start over.
Okay?
Stop making excuses for yourself.
Do you even care about what you put out through?
Oh, you're gonna lecture me.
Enough! Enough!
It's my fault, Lillian.
But it's all over now.
Lillian, come home with me, please.
Where is that? The Samson Mansion?
It's never been my home.
For three years of marriage, you gave me the cold shoulder.
You never once looked at me.
You looked Stephanie bully me.
You took the Carter group to get back and you think
just saying it's over will make them disappear.
Goodbye, Mr. Samson.
Lillian, do you really not love me anymore?
I've been over you for a long time.