Right, after 20 years, I'm finally here to marry you, Ellie, just as I promised.
Broke it!
The school's crazy, let's go!
Don't worry, superheroes always spend their way to stand up again.
You're a lifesaver, Ellie.
You always take good care of me.
Because I like you.
I like you too.
And I want to take good care of you forever.
Will you marry me?
In 20 years, we can meet at the First Encounter Bible Shop.
Yes.
In 20 years, when we're grumps, I'll marry you.
Here, take this pocket, watch with my picture in it.
And I'll keep the one with your picture in it.
Ellie at the First Encounter Bible Shop.
She is, sir.
An all necessary person, I'll have been cleared out.
Excellent.
Right this way.