Isn't that the ring my boss just bought for his fiance?
No.
I can't remember any of this.
God, imagine if you were donating my boss.
We would be like, set for life.
What's up?
Matt.
Hey.
For real, Eleanor, we'll be passing through our kids.
And now you're being all secretive and like,
you're a wealthy boyfriend?
I...
I've seen him when you write.
It's hella fancy.
You didn't tell me he was rich,
and he drives us when you're dreaming for like, ever.
I bet you.
As soon as she moves into her mansion,
she won't ever acknowledge us as friends anymore.
Don't say that.
You know it's not true.
No.
Me Me and Amaro attended.
We'll be reading some clients to talk about our partnership.
And dress sharpened.
I hope we'll get you married.
Hey, what are you doing?
What's with you?
Mr. Croft.
Hold on one second, okay?
I heard you purchased the $150 million true love necklace
for your fiance at the charity auction.
This must be Mrs. Croft, I presume.
No.
There's been a misunderstanding, sir.
I'm Mr. Croft's secretary.
At least.
Hi.
Grandma.
Kelly, to me.
As soon as I'm done with this meeting,
I'll have Annie bring her to see you.
I never expected Mr. Croft to have such a haughty like you working for him.
And I mean,
I can tell you must work out with the body like that, hm?
Mr. Croft will be back any minute now.
That's okay.
Oh.
What do you think you're doing?
I am Mr. Croft's secretary.
Secretary?
You think a secretary is going to get in the way of a billion dollar deal?
As a matter of fact, I think he'd be flattered if I took an interest to you at all.
Flattered?
No.
Heroes?
Yes.
Ugh.