So Elise has landed a collaboration with Mr. Bianchi and bagged herself a $200,000 commission.
I thought you said it was good news.
It is good news. For Elise.
Actually, I wanted to thank you. No, really. If it wasn't for you, I never would have figured out that I'm also a Somalia.
What do you mean by that?
Meaning that I see right through your little scheme, and I will not let anything like this ever happen again.
Well, you got this wrong. Let me explain.
Oh, you know what?
Since you have such a talent for opening up gifts, Andy, don't we have a spot open in logistics?
I believe we do, boss.
Oh, great. What's the work like down there in logistics?
It's just wrapping, unwrapping, pretty much all day every day in a nice little cold warehouse.
Warehouse.
Great.
Mr. Croft, if I could just please tell you that, wait. No, Mr. Croft, wait.
Please, no. Not logistics.
Thank you for supporting me, Mr. Croft.
I better get back to work.
Wait.
Are you happy with these selections?
What is always?
This is for you.
I figured you might want some new clothes that don't smell like Yante.
Oh, you know, we could also swap them out if you're not a fan.
I'll bring a new rock right away.
Wait, no, these are fine.
Mr. Croft, what is this all about?
You're my secretary.
All right, you deserve a killer wardrobe.
But this is a lot.
Yeah, and a lot means that you got options.
You can't have you walking around the office in the same office every day, all right?
We'll take them all.
Charge it.