We'll take them off.
Ma'am, Mr. Croft said you can keep them all.
Then I will.
You said your girlfriend's birthday is coming up soon, right?
For her.
Ma'am, I couldn't.
Take it.
As long as you've got my back, I will take really good care of you.
Now hurry up and get Elise fired by any means necessary.
And if you succeed, I'll not lie, I'd remove you from logistics to VP.
Ma'am, I've got Elise by the short years.
I promise you, she's done for.
You know these people, they have no shame.
She's married, yet she dresses up every day for the attention of every man in the office.
It's so desperate, it makes me sick.
Are you talking about me?
You're a nerve, did I?
I didn't think being the center of office gossip would be such a problem for an attention-seeking whore like yourself.
Keep shaking that money maker.
Shake it all the way to the top.
God, it must be good to be a woman.
BAM!