Get lost. I don't work for you anymore.
Clyde, I'd stay out of this if I were you.
This is your last morning, unless you want to spend a long time behind bars.
Mr. Crowe!
Mr. Crowe! Mr. Crowe!
I never laid a finger on Elise. I swear I'm done with her.
Let me go! Let me go!
Check him to the police station. You know what?
I kind of believe a thing you're saying.
Yeah, there's any more trouble with Elise.
I'm only responsible. Come on, get him out.
You got it, Crowe! Let's go! Let's go! This is your motherfucker!
Hey, you okay?
Are you... are you not shook up from what happened?
I mean, I was... until you came.
Mr. Croft, you opened such a lifesaver today.
Here, have a donut.
No, I don't... I don't need sweets.
Try it. You've been so helpful and kind.
And I just don't know how to repay you.
You don't have to repay me. You just be the wonderful secretary that you are.
Absolutely. I will. I'll work my butt off to make sure you're the wealthiest man on the planet.
Marriage.
Elise!