Mr. Croft, we need to get you to the hospital.
No, that's okay. You know, look, I rest it off.
How can you rest it off? Look, there's a pharmacy there. At least let me go get you some meds.
Actually, my hands gone. Look, got my strength back.
Well, that's a relief. What's wrong?
You're in a hurry to go home.
Well, it's getting late and I have to get you pretty early in the morning.
Is she really worrying about picking me up early tomorrow? Where is she more concerned about
what her husband will say if she's out late with a boss?
All right then, take us back to your place.
I have to get you home first, Mr. Croft.
No, it's getting pretty late. I'd like to see you home safely.
Well, Mr. Croft, I am home safe. You don't have to worry about me anymore.
Of course, I have to worry about you because if I don't,
something happens to you, your husband will come after me next.
Husband? Mr. Croft, you don't mean Matt, do you?