Come on.
Elise, why?
Why are you resigning?
The job is too draining.
I can't sleep.
In my mind, my body, I can't take it anymore.
Okay.
Hey.
I'll lessen your workload.
Okay.
Whatever you need.
I'm sorry.
I'm still quitting.
Elise.
Come on.
We work so well together.
Why are you doing this?
Whatever it is, Elise, come on.
Just be honest with me.
Mr. Croft.
I'm really grateful for everything you've done.
I promise I will find a way to repay you for your kindness.
Elise.
Let's just leave it at that.
Mr. Croft, what are you doing?
Come on.
After everything that I've done for you, I didn't be so heartless.
Can't you see?
Can't you see how I feel about you?
Mr. Croft, I don't know what you mean.
Come on.
You know damn well what I mean.
You have a fiance.
Okay.
But it is a verbal agreement.
We're not really engaged.
Wasn't your plan all along to marry Eleanor?
Are you just going to abandon her?
Yes.
It was.
But I know now who I truly want and it's you.
You just caught up in the moment.
I'm going to pretend I didn't hear any of this.
I mean every single word of it, Elise.
Come on.
Don't you feel the same way about me?
Mr. Croft, Eleanor is my best friend.
As long as the two of you are together, I can't let you come in between us.
Okay.
Look.
I can handle it.
Find a way to make it up to her for what she did for me long ago when we were kids.
What about her feeling?
She is overjoyed planning your wedding.
How can you ignore that?
I, you know, I-
Mr. Croft, I think you need to figure out where your true feelings lie.
Before you go making promises you can't keep.
Yeah.
This is Matt.
Get in touch with Elise.
I've called her like 20 times.
I'm worried.
Elise, where are you?
Don't cry.
We fought off the bad guys, right, kiddo?
You know, when I was a little girl, I saved another boy from some bullies.
He had this little superhero toy in his hands, and these bigger kids came up and started
making fun of him.
He could have just handed over the toy to avoid it was coming, but he wouldn't back down.
That's what I stepped in.
You know, like super girl, we were so close.
And on this swing set, he asked me to marry him when we grew up.
I kept my end of the promise and waited for him for two whole decades, but it turned out
to be nothing more than unrequited love.
He never showed up.
He wasn't for you.
Well, I tried to move on.
I even started falling for another man, but he wasn't for me either.
He has his own Ellie, and it's not me.
I'm sorry, kiddo.
I shouldn't be telling you all this.
Just remember, superheroes always find a way to stand up again.
Superheroz always find a way to stand up again.
Wait, what did you two agree to meet?
First encounter, bridal shot.
I finally found you.
Ellie, I finally found you.
You were the one that I have always wanted.
Just you.
And you're the only one I ever waited for.
I'm sorry, but I thought Ellen over you, because she was in a wedding dress and she had a pocket
watch in her hand.
I was confused.
So after Ellen or pretended to be me, she turned around and lied to me about the messenger
and breaking off the engagement and taking back the watch.
Why would she do that?
There's more, Mr. Croft.
I did some digging.
Turns out, Ellen or was behind changing the Bianchi contracts, as well as turning everybody
in the office against Elifs and Rod helped her.
After all these years, I never thought.
Thank God we caught her when we did.
There's enough evidence here to go to the authorities.
No, that's letting her off too easy.
I want to handle this my way.
What are you going to do?
She wants to marry me so badly.
I'll give her a wedding she'll never forget.
Congratulations to the future Mrs. Croft.
The big day has finally arrived.
Oh my God, Mr. Croft is totally in love with you.
This is going to be the wedding of the century.
With all the celebrities and media outlets here, this wedding is going to be the biggest story
for weeks.
This was almost all yours.
I, being bad, never looked this good.
Alright, everyone, let's have a good, warm round of applause for our bride.
Did it.
I married Clyde Croft.
You all have permission to be insanely jealous.
Ms. Ellie, do you take Mr. Croft to be your husband?
Mr. Croft, do you take Ms. Ellie to be your wife?
Mr. Croft, do you take Ellie to be your wife?
He doesn't.
What's going on?
Who is this woman?
I think she's here to crash the wedding.
She's going to crash the wedding.
It's not her.
No, she's fine.
It's fine.
Isn't it obvious?
At least.
This is Mr. Croft, Mrs. Croft's wedding, and now you choose to show up and try to steal
the spotlight.
Are you out of your mind?
I know what I'm doing.
I'm here to fight for Mr. Croft, and our love.
Go ahead and hit me in front of all these people.
He's ruining our wedding.
Everybody is watching.
All out.
I'll handle it.
Everyone, I have a very important announcement to make.
I'd like to formally introduce you all to my bride.
At least, if you think you can steal him away at our wedding, you are way out of your depth.
I wouldn't be so sure.
And my bride?
My bride?
At least.
Look at this.
Stop.
At least, you're the joy of my life.
Will you make me the happiest man in the world and marry me?
Yes, I will.
Clyde, what the hell is going on?
Isn't it obvious?
Clyde's marrying me.
No.
No, this isn't happening.
This is a joke, right, Clyde?
I'm not joking.
At least it's my one true love.
I don't believe that.
Clyde, you made me a promise.
You said you would marry me.
I saved you from those bullies.
Stop.
At least it's the one who saved me 20 years ago, not you.
What nonsense is at least telling you now?
Don't listen to her lies.
I'm the one who saved you.
It was me.
Enough with the lies, Eleanor.
Friends, don't need this to be.
Still sticking to your story, huh?
If you're the one who saved Clyde all those years ago, then tell me when, where, how you
didn't.
I don't remember.
It was 20 years ago.
What?
How am I supposed to remember the stupid little details?
All right.
Then do you have any proof that you're the one who saved Clyde?
Of course.
The pocket watches.
We both have one.
You gave it to me?
I mean these.
Exactly.
There's pictures of us as kids inside?
Well, how come this girl looks nothing like you?
Besties.
Don't you?
Bestie me.
I'm so cold.
I'm still acting innocent after everything you've done.
What are you talking about?
All right.
You want to stick to your story fine?
Everyone, check your phones.
A video has just been sent to you.
Are you serious?
Gather your best men, and when she's off work, we'll teach her a lesson.
Wow.
What viciousness.
What an amazing term you do.
This is crazy.
No.
No, no, no.
That's a lie.
It's fake.
It's AI.
Need more proof?
Take a look.
This has to go viral.
No.
Off of me.
Let go.
Take her to jail.
Elise, please.
Please don't do this after all we've been through.
Well, then we've been through.
How dare you?
That is nothing compared to what you put me.
Elise, I'm sorry.
Okay.
I was wrong.
I made a mistake.
Just please.
Get her out of here.
No.
Please.