My name is Caroline, and I'm a top lawyer.
Five years ago, my parents fell to their deaths after being framed by the mother of the man that I loved.
Instead of feeling guilty, she insulted me.
John.
The man I loved cheated on me when I was pregnant.
After ten years, I want to find the truth and get revenge.
Mom, what are you thinking?
I'm thinking about what I could whip up for us.
I'm you in the competition today.
Awesome.
Just to find out.
Oh, okay.
Boss, J.C. law firm just said yes to our corporation.
And I heard the top of their case back.
It seems that she has a close connection with J.C.
With J.C.'s help, I have a better chance of taking back STM group.
Let's set up a meeting.
I want to see her.
How is that AI content as your organization?
This year's contestants are impressive.
I'm planning on picking the winner to E.M.'s project this year.
Let me know about that meeting.