You must be wrong. That woman ran off ten years ago. She would never come back.
Did you give any new information?
Nine years ago, when the founder of STM got sick out of nowhere.
That's when the eternal fight started.
I think your parents' deaths are connected to all of this.
Who's involved in the conflict?
John's mother and his cousin Victor are still in competition.
John started EM five years ago and he's really made a name for himself and AI.
His mother's backing him in his rivalry with his cousin.
The AI contest Leo's participating in today is sponsored by the EM company.
You and John might remain to each other.
You should get ready.
I have to go help her.