Why did you just up and leave without saying anything?
Did you find another man with more money?
Don't you dare talk to me that way!
You don't get to act, don't lie to your mind now that you're rich.
You know why I left.
No, I don't. We've been spoken in 10 years.
Hey.
Thank you. Who do you think you are?
Let's go.
Mom and Dad's meeting didn't go great.
I don't want to waste my time talking to them.
See?
Even though she's black, she still doesn't know what it's going on.
I'm curious about what Caroline's been up to for the last 10 years. She's been away.
How's your candestication going?
She's gonna be a promise tonight.
Can't get STM grouped back from Victor without K's help.
Can you book me a seat?
I want to meet this amazing lawyer and person today.
What do?