She exudes elegance.
Heard you had a baby.
Suppressed she kept her figure.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Kay.
As long as we can win her over,
victory is secured.
But you can call me Caroline.
Dear you impersonate Kay!
You're a joke.
Why would you even pretend to be Kay?
Caroline, stop messing around.
You know Kay is very important to me.
This is a high society party.
How does she even get in?
I got an invitation from EM.
But it seems that EM is not taking
a working relationship seriously.
Get the hell out of here.
Well, hold on.
Let's get things clear first.
This couldn't have dumped off that building.
There wasn't enough evidence to prove otherwise.
Your parents' case can only be closed as a suicide.
But we did find this at the scene.
It seems too chaotic to prove who was there.
This is the only photo captured by the nearby surveillance
camera.
And although the person is blurred in the photo,
the brooch was clearly taken.
I seduced my son.
Your parents killed themselves.
You're a small company when bankrupt.
And through school, all alone.
And then you were an intern at STM.
You tried to marry into money.
Rebecca was there that night.
Could she be the murderer of my parents?
A girl from a family like yours is no match for my John.
Elena will be his wife.
I need to stay and find out the truth.
You're daydreaming.
You wait.
I will have my revenge.
Daydreaming again.
Let's not do this.
I didn't want to hit an old person.
So this was for your mother.
You hit John and called him a cheating womanizer.
You need to leave.
I will take out your eyes if you speak to me that way again.
Which one would you prefer?
Your left or your right or perhaps both?
You're insane.
Get her out of here.
She's not the real K.
The real K went to Oxford.
Oxford is over, Rebecca.
I am going to teach you a lesson.
That's enough.
We can discuss these issues another time.
Please leave.
Now.
Not everyone gets the chance to work with me.
And my cousin.
What a fabulous boy.
The two cousins are going to have a real showdown today.
Now, since my dear cousin wants to kick out, K, how about you
let me have her?
What do you think?
Now, since my dear cousin wants to kick out, K,
how about you let me have her?
Seems like you're not having such a good time at STM.
And you have to play tricks on John.
Could Caroline really be K?
No.
This must be a trap set by Victor.
Please leave.
Both of you.
Your loss?
Victor, would you like to work with me?
It'd be my honor.
Meet me tomorrow to sign.
K, K. I'll see you tomorrow on time.
They put on a good show, but we won't.
You got K's picture?
What do you mean I know her?
What does Sam Hill say?
It's Caroline.
I don't believe it.
She has nothing.
You've been played.
Caroline, wait.
They're never going to believe I'm K.
Wait till the right moment.
And then release my father.
My parents were murdered by your mother.
You don't even know we have a son.
I've spent 10 years dreaming of seeing you again.
You look beautiful tonight.
I see you've learned how to sweet talk women.
I gave you a chance.
Now get out of my way.
They're all let's talk.
They want to talk about it.
You spent 10 years working to impress other people.
Why?
This is what you want to talk about?
Don't work for Victor.
He's got a crooked heart.
He's using you.
Look who's talking.
I work for whoever pays more.
$20 million.
What?
I'll pay you $20 million to be my personal lawyer.
You can set any other conditions as long as you don't work for Victor.
The contract will be one year.
And we'll be dealing with each other.
Besides, I don't like crowds.
So I better have a quiet office.
If you agree, what are you doing?
I'm afraid you'll change your mind.
What are you doing?
The contract is signed.
Where would you like me to be based?
I said I wanted a quiet office.
What are you trying to do?
In the whole building, nothing is quieter than the president's office.
Is this how you treat your partners?
I'll have Samuel move out tomorrow.
It's getting late.
Let me take you home first.
I'll put up with it for the sake of the confidential information.
With you under my nose, sooner or later, I'll know the truth about 10 years ago.
John, what is she doing in the CEO's office?
Caroline is now my personal lawyer.
And please watch her language.
This spot is reserved for the executive assistant.
It's not company policy to have her here.
I make Ems rules.
Why are you here, Elena?
Report from the project department is ready.
It needs to be thoroughly evaluated.
I guess since you're the lawyer.
I don't have the report on my desk by noon.
No problem.
Caroline, you'll never beat me.
Today, Caroline is going to stop by the project department to verify information.
Don't let her get off too easily.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to do that either.
You've been choked over you hit me.
I do not need to know who you are.
Would you need to know that your boss invited me here today?
Now, should I go get the materials for the project meeting?
Or would you like to get them for me?
I'll get them for you.
Thank you.
Here's a fake document.
If it gets to her, the evaluation data will have major issues.
Are you sure this is the right one?
Mistakes are legally liable.
Of course.
Okay.
Thank you.
Everything is set.
I gave her the fake documents.
Once she finishes her evaluation, make sure to swap the fake documents back.
Don't leave any evidence.
Got it.
Let's go to dinner.
But no, I can't.
I have so much work, I've got to get done.
Come on.
You're coming?
Oh, I'm good.
Thank you.
Mary.
I saw the evaluation report.
It's finished.
And I'm on my way to the director's office.
So I thought I'd deliver it for you.
So EM has started an artificial intelligence project.
Leo would be perfect for you.
Would you concern him for working in the lab?
No.
He's too young.
He has a talent for Matthew and Cody.
Who's child is he?
He's not.
You're me.
I lift you up.
You're not married.
Also, Leo is 10 years old.
Is that just a coincidence?
Ben.
What?
Ben is Leo's father.
It doesn't matter whether or not we're married.
As long as he loves Leo.
Hello?
John, the project evaluation report is out.
This afternoon,
S company is going to have a meeting to discuss it.
We all need to be there, including Kay.
All right.
We'll be there.
The vulnerabilities in the assessment report are so significant.
I wonder how she'll get out of this one.
Yeah.
She is missing the opportunity for cooperation.
John's definitely going to blame her.
Kay's reputation in the industry will be completely tarnished.
No one will dare cooperate with her.
It's okay.
Mr. Easton,
I have been working with your company for years
and I have never seen an assessment report this terrible.
Is this a joke?
Mr. Wessel,
there must be some kind of misunderstanding
but the project's been going very smoothly.
This is so unprofessional.
It is full of mistakes.
That report was written by the top lawyer, Kay.
So there shouldn't be any issues.
Right?
Caroline, care to explain?
How do you explain a lack of professionalism?
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid this means we can no longer be partners.
Mr. Wessel, you can't make that decision.
What did you just say?
Kay is right.
Robert, you don't have the qualifications
to decide who to cooperate with.
What are you doing here?
If I hadn't have come,
you would have missed out on a great project.
What does the president winch mean?
This is the assessment done by Kay.
What's your holding statement?
What?
The assessment is flawless.
Kay really is as good as they say.
Impossible.
Like, would you say that you knew
there was a problem with the assessment file
and insisted on giving it to Elena?
Or are you surprised that even with the fake data
that you gave me,
I was able to present a place where the assessment report.
Caroline, undoing me.
Care to explain this?
That's evidence of you sneaking into my office
and switching the documents.
You tricked me!
Mary, fired!
President, this is a misunderstanding.
You knew Mary was playing tricks.
Why did you let her do something so foolish?
It raises questions when someone
comes at you for no reason.
We've changed.
It's hard not to change
after everything I've been through alone.
That bitch calls me my job.
I'll never let her off the hook.
You know, there is an opportunity right now
for us to get revenge.
Mom, was work smooth yesterday?
I had some trouble,
but it's all smooth to open up.
What about that?
Did he help you?
Leo, I don't want to have to tell you again.
John is not your father.
I want a dad.
John would be good.
I'll think it over.
Carefully, now please eat your breakfast.
Mom?
Got a problem.
Someone is spreading lies about your own life.
I'm trying to harm your reputation.
I'll deal with this.
You go get ready for school.
I saw it.
The photos of Caroline and that man.
I mean, guys.
Are those rumors said online?
True?
Of course not.
They're rumors.
That man richer than me?
How much money did he give you?
You know what, John?
He did give me more.
And he's better in bed than you.
Are you satisfied?
Where did he touch you?
What made you so promiscuous
he's lasting years?
You've got me all wrong, John.
Move!
You're so stupid.
You can't even see such an obvious trap.
What's this?
You know what to do next, right?
Why give it to me?
Because compared to others,
you're a good candidate to be my dad.
You need to win my mom's time.
This is my phone number.
You can contact me any time.
Hand over all the evidence to the police
and let Mary know there's consequences for spreading rumors.
I looked into the transfer of the company's database
and I found evidence that your parents were killed.
Problem is, the information's at the core of the app,
which is nearly impossible to access.
You go first.
I'll pick you right now.
No, I'm going with you.
You can't do this by yourself.
And candidly, I don't trust John.
I think he still has feelings for you.
I'm still your boss.
Carolina, I want to apologize for my behavior just now.
I know you're not that kind of person.
Mr. Easton, if there's nothing else, I'd like to get back to work.
I've already sent the person who spread those rumors to prison.
Would you send your mother to prison for me?
I'm sincerely trying to apologize.
No, my behavior was offensive
and my attitude towards you was wrong.
But I was just angry that you disappeared for 10 years.
I've come to realize I can't help but care for you, Caroline.
Can we start over?
You and your employees have something against me.
There isn't the slightest bit of trust and you want to start over.
This is the key to the company's database,
which grants you access to all the core files.
I'm giving it to you.
He actually trusts me with this,
willing to hand over the core of the company.
To me, you don't have to do this.
It's okay.
I've waited 10 years and going a little longer.
If you must blame someone, blame your mother.
For killing my parents.
This is the contract signed between Rebecca and my parents' company,
with a price three times higher.
My parents' death wasn't an accident.
That John's mother spends the rest of her life prison.
How can I trust you?
Because I'm competing with John for the same position of CEO of the STM Corporation.
I think we would make great partners.
I'll get you an answer soon.
John, what are you doing in my house?
Mom, I asked them to come over.
Because the light bulb was broken and he came to fix it.
Well, it looks like the light bulb is fixed, so you can leave.
Are you okay?
You don't look well.
You need to take a few days off the rest.
I'm fine.
I would appreciate if you did not come into my home without an invitation.
Oh, the school is hosting a parent child activity that requires both parents to be present.
Can I invite John?
Oh.
The other kids have a dad.
Of course.
You can invite him.
Awesome.
Well, it's getting late.
I'll head home now.
I'll see you tomorrow, Leo.
See you tomorrow, Dad.
Well, it's ugly, but I appreciate it.
Tell me.
What should I do?
Oh, wow.
Here, make one with us.
John, if I send your mother to present, would you still love me?
What do you look at?
You want to present my mom?
What's your idea?
No woman can refuse a romantic marriage proposal.
My mom's birthday is coming up in a few days.
You understand what I mean?
I understand.
It's in tonight's dinner quite special.
Did John do this for me?
He still remembers me birthday.
Caroline, why are you here?
I'm trying to have a nice dinner with my son.
Why are you here?
Tonight is John and mine's engagement party.
This entire candlelight dinner was prepared for me.
God, everything was just wishful thinking.
Why am I so fantasizing about John?
Leo, come on.
Wait for me.
Will you take Leo home?
What about you?
It's time to put him into this.
You can't let him wait.
Look, I don't know what happened to make you leave in such a hurry.
But what I want to tell you is,
even though you left without saying goodbye for 10 years,
and even though you have a child with someone else,
I find that I cannot stop loving you.
So, will you marry me?
John, do you enjoy playing with my feelings?
Just humiliating me?
Accomplish anything for you?
I don't understand what you're saying,
but my love for you has never changed.
The contract ends in one year.
Then I'll leave.
And we'll just be strangers.
Victor, let's meet.
It's bad, John.
Your mother has been arrested for the police.