These are the documents from the STM and W Corporation project.
They might help you find the murderer.
What do you mean?
I found out that you left John because you suspected me
of killing your parents instead of because I told you to.
Don't worry.
Even without the information that you provided,
I was going to leave.
There's one other thing I have to ask of me.
This is a critical time for STM Corporation's succession.
Help John secure the investment for the project with company S.
The STM CEO position is very important to us.
Consider it my compensation for the hardback cost.
Thank you.
EM's business investment plan report, this time has been done well.
It includes a detailed risk prevention strategy.
This time I'm going to expose your true face, you wicked woman.
Let's take a look.