How could it have leaked? Do you know what company has access to the data?
It's a company run by Victor, but most importantly, go ahead and say it.
Elena, she's been released on bail and he seems she's the one who held that picture.
Of course Elena is involved in this.
Is that a problem?
When I was kidnapped, Elena told me that someone else had murdered my parents
and then Victor saved me.
It's not a coincidence that they're together now.
And if I can remember correctly, Victor was the person behind the scenes on the construction
product that SDM collaborated on with W Company.
There must be some connection.
Victor was behind the scenes this whole time.
I always thought someone else was in charge of that project.
Now it all makes sense.
Victor is probably the real murderer of my parents.
If it only had to do with the internal strife of the successors,
what does that have to do with my parents?
John, do you like the first big gift I've given you?
Get to it.