If it weren't for Caroline being in prison, I would consider meeting with you.
Go ahead.
What do you want to know?
It's an executive in your company named Peter.
Where is he?
After what he and Elena did, which severely affected the company's interest, I fired him.
And he ended up in prison for robbery.
Robert?
His mother is severely ill.
And after leaving S group, he did not enough money to pay for his mother's illness.
He took the wrong time.
Thank you.
Once this is over, I'm planning on proposing to Caroline.
I hope you won't stand the way of that.
What do you want with me?
Do you know Victor?
No, I don't know him.
You're lying.
You know, I know about your mother.
Don't worry.
I have arranged for the best cardiologist for her.
She'll be fine.
Alright.
So what do you want from me?
The trial is tomorrow.
I want you to judge everything you know.
I'll vouch for you.
Get you bail and then arrange a high paying job for you.