You filthy bastard! You are silver-blotted freak!
Which scambing would needed your mum to give birth to such a bastard as you...
You fatherless scam!
You were so tough last time.
Why didn't you use the silver-blocked to find me again? You! Lowy!
You are a pathetic bastard without a father!
You are nothing.
And I would better not use my power again.
Why my mum will literally kill me?
The fuck are you?!
I'm hooked up with the shit out in the...
Stay on the ground!
Are we gonna expect you anytime soon?
No!
Can you hear you?
I'm knocking me back!
Louder!
No, get the fuck out of here!
You too!
Get the fuck out of here!
Are you okay?
You must be popular as cool.
I handled them just fine.
Why didn't you fight back?
Because they are not wrong.