The Alpha set will keep you locked up, go to torture her, are you to find Alpha's orders, get off!
I'm dirty, stay away from me.
No, you're not dirty, no more how you live, for who you are.
Are you this gentle to all girls?
All girls? Are you jealous, personally?
No, I'm not, I don't care who you date.
I'm not dating anyone, personally means nothing to me.
You care about me so much?
No, I came here to look for my father.
That's what I care about, not to compete with some rules.
Because of you, I'm imprisoned in the world of back, waiting to get murdered.
I will get you out.
No, you're gonna get me out, you'll put yourself into more trouble.
Oh no, someone still cares about me, don't worry, I won't stop.
This is outrageous Alpha Gordon, electrationist act shall be punished,
and this little whore shall die.
How could you do this, Alec?
It's my Alpha, you don't understand your importance.
No Alpha, please, my Alpha.
I'm doing this for the good of the bloody moon.