Hello Caroline.
Who is here?
My name is Maya.
I'm your inner wolf.
Hey.
You're awake.
Are you feeling okay?
Don't tell him about me Caroline.
I'm fine.
I think yesterday I was just a little sugar.
Don't worry.
Maybe I should see you downstairs after I change.
Sure.
Okay, take your time.
Have a bird that Caroline.
Maya, are you here?
How come I cannot see you?
Underline in there Caroline.
Finally I'm free.
And so are you.
But there is one more surprise waiting for you.
Mr. Price.
Get dressed.
I will tell you about it downstairs.
Touch him.
I think you're doing it.
Jacob is your maid Caroline.
What do you think you're doing Jacob?
We didn't know Caroline turns out to be my mate.
Is this true?
You can't outrun fate Alec.
Alec.
Now, watch yourself Jacob.
I have an announcement to make.
I've decided to name my successor.
The next alpha of the bloody moon.
My son, Alec.
Yes, Alec.
No Caroline.
Wait, please, please Caroline.
Why did you tell me your Jacob's mate?
You can tell me you're an ordinary son.
What are you?
Alec.
Get rid of this bastard tramp already.
We both know she's just a stain on the bloody moon.
You don't have to label me peacefully.
Thank you.
Don't act all high in my tea.
Oh.
I'm not the one who's flirting with the next alpha.
But already has a mate.
Admit it.
You just want to be the next Luna.
This is pointless.
I'm down big herring really.
Good.
No Caroline.
Alec deserves better anyways.
Wait, please.
Shut up.
But bestly, don't pretend you care about me or the bloody moon.
You're selfish and ignorant.
If you come one more time, you're Caroline again.
I'm not going to go with you, you.
As long as I'm the alpha, you don't belong here.
Caroline!
But it's so hard.
Wait.
Talk to me.
Are you falling for Jacob?
That's why you keep hiding from me.
What do you want, Jacob?
Listen.
I didn't really want my mate to be a mix of bastard.
But I accepted the goddess decision.
If you stop fooling around with another man,
I will kindly accept you as my mate.
Not the most ridiculous thing I heard today.
If you want a place in the bloody moon,
you only answer to me.
Jacob.
If I want a place in the bloody moon,
I'm going to ask alpha.
Or the second alpha.
Alec.
And you are no one in here, so...
Why are you telling me?
Just stop it on ID.
For the first time,
a woman there to speak to me like that.
I like your attitude.
I make sure you become my Luna.
You are all in Jacob.
I guess the new bitch isn't taking directives while, huh?
I can get you resources.
Men.
Weapons.
Money.
Anything.
You can do what you want with Alec.
But...
You have to kill Carolyn for me.
How does that sound?
You want me to kill my own mate.
Oh relax.
It's not like you need her to be the next alpha anyway.
You don't get to tell me what to do with my mate Paisley.
Once I'm the alpha,
you're going to be dead anyways.
Now that everybody is here,
we shall get down to business.
Jacob,
state your case.
Our life's presence poses a threat to all of us.
Me and the bastard child of our alpha Gordon.
And a mix of breed.
The hunters will be at our doorstep any second.
We can let that scummy hybrid
taint our royal blood.
We have to kill her.
You fatherless gang.
This bastard tramp.
And you, Alec.
You knowingly brought a threat to our clan
telling formulas.
Why we should be a threat?
She's Gordon's daughter.
Why do you have hybrid keyed?
We don't know about it.
Gordon?
I didn't know I answered a you Mallory.
Leave my daughter alone.
I'll still have the bloody one.
You should have never mingled with the hunter.
Yes.
That offspring of yours.
Link's shame upon our clan.
Just tell me what I need to do.
Just stay with the blood on me.
Jacob,
state your task.
Now.
There's a med scene called the Panther Act,
which is hidden in the Grey Mountain.
It's pretty much immortalized a werewolf.
If you're dreaming the Panther Act to prove your worth,
you'll be your only option.
No rages.
I won't allow it.
I will do that.
I complete this task.
Will I be allowed to stay with the bloody moon?
Yes.
It's a death drop.
I'm not letting go.
I'm tired of being called names my whole life.
I'm telling my father, and yet,
I'm still being questioned.
I know that I can use my powers.
The only way for me out of this is to prove
that I deserve to be here.
Then I'm coming with you.
Don't you get it?
I have to do it by myself.
To prove that I will.
I will.
Protect you.
Till I stop breathing.
So, what's the plan?
My future alpha.
I like will be in Caroline's side
every step of the way.
Make sure it's still clear of her.
And what are you going to do?
Let's say our girl will be in trouble.
I want her dead.
How are you?
Help.
Oh my God.
I'm a shitty consensus.
Hunter.
Up into her.
Who are you?
Don't worry.
I'm also Hunter.
Hunter cleans her.
What are you doing here?
Shit.
He looks like he doesn't know I'm a hybrid.
I gotta make something up.
I'm just a rock.
My whole family was killed by the werewolves.
And I heard that Hunter started war with them.
Is it the truth?
It's been temporary truths,
but you've never seen I twice one another.
In fact, I'm just a root out of any trade
as to the hunters.
To revenge.
For my parents.
This of the hands of Gunnar.
Our pet.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry for your loss.
Let's hope I get out of this in one piece.
Airlines in trouble.
I can only go around the grey mountain to get to her.
How are you there?
A werewolf sense is coming back.
You smell that?
It's a werewolf sense.
Smells something rotten in here.
Maybe it's cause I bring the dish earlier.
Sit down.
It's me.
This has been a long day.
Stress gives you illusion
that where I was might be.
Everywhere.
I wish you well.
But hopefully,
we'll never have to see each other again.
Fall into my trap.
Everyone you think that you die in the grey mountain.
But lead the unknown.
Where did all the kids do, huh?
Here?
I'm not gonna force you.
You're going to be running to me.
sooner or later,
with an open arms.
We know stresses of Miss Caroline.
It doesn't look good.
This bitch was trying something.
What do you mean, son?
Bestly!
She was not going to be before I left the compound.
She must have been answered to Jacob.
We didn't fight him.
I don't feel like Jacob Caroline.
He's your mate.
How am I supposed to like him?
He's just that apple rotten to the core.
But being with your mate is your calling.
Why don't you want to answer your faith, Caroline?
Don't you want to stay with bloody moons?
It doesn't mean that I have to obey to bullets.
I've been doing that for my whole life.
You don't have to obey.
You just have to understand how to approach him.
You reminded me of something.
If I want to make her on for it,
then he has to let his guard down.
I thought you hated me.
It doesn't mean I'm going to be a side while you're bleeding.
Oh, Caroline, why'd you save me and hurt me at the same time?
What am I going to do to you?
You weak now.
Do you think that men can save you?
Get over here.
You know what you did.
Do you?
You may pass a nag enough to me because you're trying to take care of it, right?
Oh, really?
What you're going to do?
I'm going to do this place upside down.
But that's why I'm not cool.
Not the Alpha yet.
To search my place, you need to bring more men.
I dare you.
Even better.
Bring the Alpha.
Wait here.
You did shit.
Are you trying to start warmly free or something?
Maybe you think I must come back trying to overthrow Alpha Gordon.
But my family was once the strong and powerful.
If it weren't for the hunters who murdered them, I could have been the Alpha anytime.
Do you think you can just murder your way to the top?
Why not?
I will be the most powerful Alpha.
Bloody moon has everything.
And you will kneel before me and forget about that weak boy.
Alec, I'm the strongest.
Alec is not weak.
He's so much better than me.
He doesn't teach women like you are doing now.
It beats you much.
When I tear Alec into pieces.
Where are you, Caroline?
Even if we are not meant to be together, I'm still thinking about you, Alec.
Down up here.
Your boss brother will crush me big to you this day.
I will just come a week like ants.
I crush them many times.
The weak of you is going.
Tearing you both apart won't cause me a thing.
I dare you.
What the fuck you guys doing?
I have to teach you how to fight, huh?
I don't need it.
I have my silver blood ready to go.
Aren't you afraid?
Bleeding to death.
Listen.
Precision and strength are both important.
I will try.
I'm not going to do it this way.
It's your turn.
Do it.
You be my mate.
You have to act like one.
From now on.
Whoever dared to touch her will be sentenced to death.
Regardless who you are.
Consider yourself warned.
She's fucking crazy.
I have to get out of here.
How do I get out of here?
Why are you still alive?
You want to try and take me out?
Dare you talk back to me.
Guard send her to the dungeon.
What?
Jacob said nobody touches Carlisle.
For me.
And I'm telling you to drag her to the dungeon.
The last guy who touched her is dead.
I'm going to get rid of the guy.
But he keeps clenching onto me.
Well, why don't you just reject him as your mate?
Your mate can be rejected.
Well, yes.
Go on.
Try it.
What are you waiting for?
You're going to reject him.
He's going to kill me on the spot.
I guess you're not as dumb as I thought you were.
Here is a better idea.
Why didn't you let me out?
And I'm going to be out of your way.
You can have Jacob all you want.
I'm going to be here to get out of here.
Tramp.
Basically, it's definitely my best chance of getting out of here.
I have to find a way to spark her jealousy.
Me.
In the dining room tomorrow.
There is a surprise for you.
Jay.
Get that hybrid out of here.
And I'm not sharing my alphabet with any.
You don't get to tell me what to do.
Behave yourself.
You're nothing but a she move.
You do as you're told to do.
Now, tell me where we are yet with the weapons.
You're going to regret it.
If you don't do it, as I told you to.
You'd be too apt to do.
I can't wait to chop her head off once it becomes a new alphabet.
How spun the weapons delivery.
Jacob is going to tread on my dignity.
And I guess I'm just going to have to teach him a lesson.
I believe this letter is for you, Mom.
Come begging for me now.
I guess it's time for an apology.
Happy birthday to you.
What is this?
This is a birthday cake.
I picked it just for you.
I don't do birthdays.
Those are for the week.
Come on Jacob.
Listen up.
I know that your parents are never here on your birthdays.
So if you can consider this a special treat.
I even cut my hand when I was baking this cake for you.
Why are you so silly?
Wasting your time doing those things.
Are you going to take a look for me?
Why is Paisley still not here?
What the fuck?
How dare you?
No one lays a finger on me.
Jacob, everything happens the first time.
I've got to clean up for you.
I'm going to make them pay.