You're going to the dungeon.
I think you can get rid of me now, huh?
I'd say you need me now more than ever.
This rebellion has failed even before it started.
Weapons can be bought.
Men can be bought.
But this...
...is camp.
Enough with it. Go in.
Well then.
Waiting on you.
My opera.
It's time to draw up a plan.
Done yet.
Haven't seen you in a while.
I've been busy hopelessly.
Now that you have more time,
I think it's time to talk about some unfinished business.
I got your good luck charm.
I miss your Caroline.
If only I was stronger.
You have never been hurt because of me.
See Lee Hunty?
Protecting you is my duty.
You don't need to change anything.
I will become stronger, but always protect you.
Can you teach me some self-defense moves?
I want to fight alongside you.
I don't want to be a burden.
As long as you want,
and as long as I know,
I will teach you whatever I have.