Oh my gosh. They broke your head. What are you doing here?
I'm gonna save you.
How's Caroline?
Caroline is getting stronger than ever now.
Alec is the new alpha, and they're in love with each other.
Glad to hear that. You shouldn't have come. You should have just stayed home.
I had to. I lost you once I'm not losing you again.
All those years ago, you were separated by the rivalries of Hunter and werewolf,
bound by the identities of Hunter Princess and Alpha.
Others are in our love.
I wonder what my father is.
He's had the hunters. What?
What?
Your mother got taken by Daniel Merck, and he went to save her.
But why did he go alone? He should have brought all of us.
He wanted to step down so quickly, because he wanted to save her,
and doesn't provoke a full war at the same time.
Indeed. But he's very weak.
He's been pushing himself all this time.
And though he warned me many times to not tell you guys,
Alpha, Alec, please go to save him.
I have to go.