You're not dead in a way again hybrid. I dare you to try
You fail to identify your target once. There's no guarantee you won't do it again
You haven't seen this one before
But it doesn't matter never underestimate your opponent Daniel
Guess you're a nobody after all
By the degree of Hunter's tribe. I'm now
removing the king weight
As a leader
No fucking way
You are hybrid
How can you be the queen of the hunters yet?
You cannot even defeat me in a fight. You have no say in this from both sides
werewolves and hunters who can bring this to the making both sides stronger than ever by the power invested in me and now
Hand down my phone
To your new queen
Caroline carpet