Oh, Dad!
Caroline, help him!
I've been thinking.
No, I am the queen of the hunters.
She did it.
I can't believe it, Caroline.
You did what we all failed to do.
Let's get you out of here.
What do you want us to do with him, Mike Green?
It wasn't all a lie.
Our mom is in forest.
I already knew that you were after me that time.
So you think you're a flower, huh?
You're using me and playing me.
You're doing yourself much.
I'm done with you.
Lock him up.
I don't want to hear another work with him.
What did he do to you?
Nothing.
He gets my hand to you and shrugs the crowd.
No, it's not that, really.
He saved me from a fall and took care of me for one day.
And another one.
But I didn't know who he was after I realized
that he was actually hunting for me.
Escaped immediately.
I'm using some tricks.
Tricks?
Okay.
Don't believe me?