Oh, yeah.
What do you want from me?
I have a lot of work.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, cute shoes.
Trash collector and strike.
If you want a big company on time,
the sneakers will help you run faster.
Keep talking there.
My lawyers turn like every word of standard.
If you want to challenge me,
but how swan is an important sponsor of these events.
And I can guarantee you that your design will never appear
in this fashion show.
Because, you know, the big is different between you
and me that I have money.
And my money can turn your original work into a heroism
and make people who original believe you
commit perjury.
And even if you have money to get a lawyer,
what can you do to me?