Do you know why we need disinfected sanitations matters?
One wouldn't want unpleasant associations to infect a bloodline after all.
Don't bother trying to embarrass me. I'm confident enough.
To make a long story short, I called you here because I want you to disappear from Morgan.
After I got to know you'll become less and less like before.
I know who you are.
Come on, son. Left to go.
I think someone else is painting what to say to the great child.
She deserves a very shot. Why wouldn't you look at it?
I don't know if anyone wrote her.
He wasn't meant to linger at childish crushes.
True potential doesn't come wrapped in a cheap sentiment.
Morgan can always make the decision that it is best for him.
Your cleaning couldn't erase his talent. He was a true artist.
Enough. Accept it or erase you and your precious member.
Oh, I don't want it.