Goodnet? I'll show you how to use the housing system.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry that I break anything.
No, sweetheart, you didn't break anything.
I'm Seb's mom, Elizabeth.
Elizabeth?
Oh, please call me Eliza.
How do you like your room?
If it's not to your liking, Seb can take you to the lakeside villa.
This is fine.
Your family.
If you need anything, just let Seb know.
Everything's great, Mrs. Eliza.
Why don't you join me at the mall this afternoon?
I know Seb's fashion sense is lacking.
Would you like to keep the cupboard?
Sure.
Let's see what's here.
Oh, oh, look at this.
Try this one on Ella.
I thought we were shopping for you.
Oh, we're shopping for both of us.
Go on, let's try the mall.
Your absolutely stunning sweetheart will take the mall.
Don't we have to pay first?
I own this mall. Have them shipped from my address.
Of course, that was so much fun.
Let me eat.
Wear more blue, you know, more often.
Make your eyes pop.
Come on, let's get some food.
Yeah, what do you want?
Sebastian?
No touching unless you are buying.
I'm sorry.
No, this place is not for you.
Try Walmart.
That's more your speed.
Those are knockoffs, right?
So desperate to look rich.
They're knockoffs.
I just bought them here.
Oh, yeah.
Got any receipts?
That's what I thought.
Now get out.
Is everything okay, babe?
Mr. Sebastian Harrington, if you need anything, please let me know.
You want to try out some shoes?
No, it's okay.
Let's try out some shoes.
Can you help my wife put them on?
Get used to this, Emma.
Not her style.
Try the black pair.
No, not those ones.
Mmm, ugly.
I don't like them.
You can't do any better than that.
Maybe the blue?
Or maybe we should try a different shop.
Go meet Mom.
I'll catch up.
Mr. Harrington, I didn't know that she was your wife.
You're fired.
Tonight we have our finest beluga caviar, sourced from the Caspian Sea.
Go ahead.
Oh my God, did you see the way she ate that?
I bet she's never had caviar her entire life.
Miss, the caviar is best served with the seashell spoon.
Not necessarily.
You eat how you want, hold on.
Never let anyone tell you how to live your life.
No one's ever told me that, but he seems different.
Thank you.
Mr. Harrington.
Ella, wait.
Take that.
You've already given me so much.
And there will be more to come.
Like I said, I need to get used to it.
I'll see you in the afternoon, Ella.
See you, Mr. Harrington.
Hey, Ella.
Is Ella sitting with Aiden?
Oh my God, she is.
What is she wearing?
That looks like the new limited collection from Lemire Prestige.
How could she afford those?
Isn't Lemire Prestige like crazy expensive?
It is.
She must be wearing it.
Just use Aiden.
So, how does a low life like you even afford Lemire Prestige?
Is it the sugar daddy or something?
I don't know where you're getting that from, but no.
Sabrina, look at this.
This is the newest model.
It costs like 10k.
Just admit it, you sold yourself to some ritual fraud.
Hey, watch your tone.
Aiden, look at her.
Look at her.
She's all dressed up for what?
What was that?
Oh my God, is she pregnant already?
That's enough.
Look at her.
She's all dressed up for what?
You sold yourself to some ritual fraud.
I told you.
College is a waste of time.
Pregnant horse.
I'm coming in.
What's going on?
I have three assignments due next month.
I'm just tired.
You're lying.
I take a break.
No, I can't.
I can't afford to take a break.
I need to graduate so I can get away from my family.
Look, you're pregnant.
And this is only...
Yeah, I did this to myself.
You're not alone in this.
I'll support you whatever you do.
Please promise me I'll take care of yourself, okay?
See you at dinner.
Follow her.
I want to know everyone she talks to and everything she does on campus.
Select.
See, you're into an old man, right?
How much does he pay you?
Does he even pay you?
But do you sleep with him for free?
What's a leg sleeping with a fat old frog?
Can he even get hard?
You just let me go.
Not so fast, slut.
Ella, are you okay?
What happened?
Did Sabrina give you a hard time again?
I'll talk to the dean.
No, it's Hayden.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
You don't look okay.
Okay, so I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll see you.
Who's that guy?
Seatbelt.
Let's go.
Did I do something wrong?
Am I jealous?
What's wrong?
That's nothing.
Think I'm going to take a break from college?
What?
I thought you didn't want to.
What's this?
It's nothing.
I'm just tired all the time.
I can't keep up with my schoolwork anymore.
You don't trust me.
Fine.
Take a break if you need to,
but from now on, call me Sabrina.
Sabrina.
No one has ever treated me like this.
I should trust him.
Connor, I need a full report of what happened on campus today.
You got it.
Sir, I prepared some essential oils for Mrs. Harrington.
Which do you think she'd prefer?
Essential oils for what?
For stretch marks, sir.
They don't always work, but it's best to be prepared.
It goes on the...
On the belly, sir.
And the back of the thighs as well.
I'll take them down.
Of course, sir.
Would you like me to show you how to apply them?
So, which one do you prefer?
We have sea salt, lavender, and rose.
Essential oils to prevent stretch marks.
They consider it lavender sounds nice.
Light down?
No.
Not myself, you don't have to.
Do you know how?
You just rub it in, right?
It's a little more complicated.
Be good and light up.
Just relax.
I need to get your thighs, too.
There's nothing there I haven't seen before.
Okay, with stretch marks.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Babies.
This is just about the babies.
Are you okay?
What happened?
I just dropped my phone.
I'm fine.
Sorry I asked to take this.
Don't, mommy.
Did you hook up with some rich old dirt?
No, I didn't.
Don't lie to me.
Mommy, please, I didn't.
I don't care who's bed you crawled into.
Where are you?
You think you can just run off like that who raised you?
I want my money back, Ella.
Every penny I spent on you.
How much?
I don't have that kind of money.
Or I'll find you ruined everything.
Sam, Ella's been blown up and you need to see what's blown up on the internet right now.
What did your mom say?
I should tell her once.
Being horrible to me on campus.
You're spreading lies about me online.
I'm glad you told me.
I can help.
Because I want you to be the real Mrs. Harrington.
The real Mrs. Harrington should be someone you love.
You will be a great Mrs. Harrington.
I'm no match to your family or your status.
Yes.
Is there something on my face?
No.
Does this change?
It changed for the better.
You've changed me.
Did anyone see you?
I hope not.
Ms. Harrington.
Come here, Ella.
Do you need me for?
I want to make a statement with your old friends.
Care to join us?
My old friends?
Yeah, it'll be worth your time.
Ella, if at any point you feel uncomfortable, let me know, okay?
We can leave, Ella.
Sam, what is this?
A lesson for anyone who dares to mess with my wife.
I'm not done yet.
We have one more guest.
This is letting go.
Calm down.
Ella, will these men with you?
Or?
Mind your tone when you speak to Ms. Harrington.
Oh, now I see.
You're the one paying your bills.
Now I can make this really simple for you.
You give me the cash.
Ella isn't for sale.
No.
No, my design isn't she, uh, pregnant?
Sam, let them go.
Are you sure?
Don't she forget.
I am your mother.
Oh!
I've never heard a mother talk about her daughter like that.
Is she really your birth mother?
I'll look into it.
Under one condition.
What's the condition?
You move into my bedroom.
It'll be our bedroom.
I have my own room.
But don't you think a Mr. and Mrs. shouldn't be in separate beds?
We'll share a bed just to sleep in.
Come on, let's go.
Heard you dropped out.
What?
Complicated.
Can we meet up today?
Yeah.
Hey.
How are you doing?
I'm good.
How are you?
Good.
I didn't know you're married.
Engaged, I guess.
Ella, are you okay?
Is he a good person?
There's some rumors about him that have been flying around.
Yeah.
He's a good person.
He treats me very well.
That's good to know.
You're still failing that science class?
Yeah.
Same guy.
Makes sense.
He's a reagent when you're getting old.