Thank you so much for coming, everyone, to celebrate the birth of our two little girls
to our family.
Oh, Bridget!
Oh, God, let's stop.
I never thought you'd actually birth two heirs to the Harrington legacy.
Ms. Prescott, tell me, what drugs did you use to get him into bed with you?
That's not an appropriate discussion, Ms. Prescott.
Why not?
You are the one that crawled into his bed like a cheap little whore, and you made yourself
a container for his babies.
Tell me, how does it feel to know you're just a tool?
He'll never really care for you.
Well, what does that make you, then?
What?
You've exhausted all your resources.
You won't even look your way.
If I'm just a tool, what are you?
You need to leave.
Did you know she was seeing another man?