Is this all kind of joke?
I've spoken to my lawyer. She said we need to sign these forms to get the process started.
You can't at least have a reason?
I thought you'd be happy. It's what you want, isn't it?
No, I get it.
You suck enough money out of my family last time for you to move on, huh?
Believe what you want. I don't care what you think about me anymore, Nolan.
I've waited three years for you to see me properly, but that's never going to happen. I'm done.
What about my father, huh? He arranged his marriage. You know I'll hate this.
I love your father, but I can't live like this anymore. I've already signed them.
What? Yeah. No, of course. I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Dad's at a heart attack. We need to go to the hospital right now.