You think I'm in the tune?
Wow, um, that's my cue to go.
I'll see you later.
Team Leader?
You're not going to answer my question.
How would I know? You've never laid a finger on me in three years of marriage.
That was never part of the deal. No sex, remember?
I remember.
Wait, do you want me to touch you? Is that what this is about?
Why are we even having this conversation?
I agree to stay together until your father's surgery, and I'll stick to that, but this marriage is over.
Is that why she wants a divorce? She wants her marriage to be real. I've just never thought of her like that.
It's how you've gone to work.
All this time I've never noticed my contract with wife. It's a haughty.
Maybe I am impotent.
But what you said, you really want to throw out the rules. You really want to be with me.
I don't know anything in the law.
Just say something, sir.
I'm saying it, none. I'm going to do it better.
I can't say, hey, Robert. What's up?
What do you think? Should we give Nancy the guest room or...?
It's up to you.
No, no, no. You'll be here too.
Not for much longer. Do whatever suits you, Nolan.
I'm an old man. It's one thing for you to look after Tom's widow after he died on the job.
But moving her into your place, that's a lot.
She doesn't have anyone else, right? She says she's scared to be alone.
What did he just say?
Well, she said it was my call since we'll be divorcing soon.
Yeah, about that.
Since you guys are calling your quids, how do you feel about me asking her out?
What, Edith?
Yeah.
I mean, no offense, ma'am. She's harder than a bike seat in summer.
Um, well, she's her own person, so...
I'm not going to stand in the way of that.
Cool. Thanks, ma'am.
You are a lifesaver. Thank you for taking us in.
Uh, yeah, no problem. Just let me know if you need any extra pillows or whatever.
Is Edith home?
Uh, must be.
Damn it. I think I got something in my eye.
Let me see.
I have a date.
You look great.
Hey, man. Nice place.
Hi, Frankie.
Nancy?
We should go.
Sure.
Well, uh, see you at work, man. Yeah. See you at work.
Did you cook?
You sound surprised.
A buddy of mine knowed me a favor, so, uh...
Let me borrow his kitchen.
Nolan never cooks for me.
Well, I'm not Nolan.
My back is so sore.
Tom used to give me the best backrops.
You should probably go ahead, darling.
Maybe I will.
You, uh, got a little...
right there.
You?
Mm-hmm.
Just here.
I know.
Hello?
Hey, um...
I thought you might want to know that...
Oh, um...
Of course.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
You don't deserve Nolan.
Nolan...
Is mine.
How's it going to be?
Yeah!
You good?
Yeah.
Hey.
Well, I...
I didn't think I was going to see you today.
I thought you asked me to come in.
Um, doubters, you're saying how the doctors are really happy with these last blood results.
Uh, I told them that I was always, uh, you know, high achiever and...
I can't slap them now.
That's so good.
That's great news.
Sorry, but, uh, we need you for more tests.
Mr. Blair.
Oh, okay.
Don't worry.
We'll wait for you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Wait.
Oh, I'll go again.
Yeah.
Okay.
These are to say sorry for ending our date early.
Chocolate chip.
My favorite.
And you can make it up to me by saying yes to another date.
Um, you got around to ordering those new masks?
Need it?
Uh, no.
I was going to do it tonight.
I got a nice delivery cutoff.
I'll probably get on to it now.
Sure thing, boss.
I'll see you later.
We had to go get some lunch, if you like.
Okay.
What were you thinking?
You are.
We have a prenatal checkup today.
Remember?
Looks like you're busy.
Good luck with the appointment.
I keep letting my guard down.
And he keeps reminding me why I needed up in the first place.
Fuck him.
He's actually the dumbest man on the planet for cheating on you with that lovely bitch.
It's him.
He's asking me out to dinner tonight.
It's seven o'clock.
What are you going to say?
The nurse said that these tests probably won't be done until late.
You can stay with me, though, right?
Nolan.
I just hate doing these things alone because Tom should be here.
Yeah.
This is the last time you've ever let me down.
Time is up.
Where's Nancy?
It's to shut the scene overnight.
I'm really sorry about dinner.
Did you eat?
When you didn't come home, I had some breakfast cereal.
I texted the cancel.
She'd lock it, didn't send.
We were in the X-ray department.
The walls were thick down there.
She didn't want some pizza.
God, I love pizza.
I know.
It's why I got it.
Is that a problem?
No, it's just you usually don't care about what I like or don't like.
You probably don't even know when my birthday is.
It's in June.
Isn't it?
Okay, I'm not that good with dates, but not that bad.
Am I?
All you ever care about or think about is your work.
Duty, doing the right thing for everyone else.
We might as well be too stranger sharing this place.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry for making you feel unimportant.
I never thought I'd hear you say something like that.
Well, I'm sorry for hurting you or neglecting you.
You deserve better.
I just remembered I've gotten early start.
I'm seeing your dad tomorrow.
Do you want me to bring him anything?
Yeah, just tell him I'll try to get him to see him as well.
I know what you're trying to do, Edith.
But it won't work.
You've had your chance.
It's my time now.
Excuse me?
Stop clinging to Nolan.
I'm carrying his baby, Edith.
So get with the program.
He is still my husband, Nancy.
What do you think people would say if they knew poor, grieving widow
had been sleeping with my husband and is now carrying his child?
You bitch, you wouldn't dare.
What's stopping me?
Edith, lead me alone.
Pushed me.
You saw her.
I did not.
Oh, it hurts.
Edith, please.
You okay, man?
Sorry, sorry.
Do you know the severe impact?
Nancy is Miss Carrie.
You did this to me.
You took my baby away from me.
I didn't do anything.
You're a horrible monster.
A horribly jealous monster.
She is unhinged.
Don't say another word.
You did here today.
He's unforgivable.
You had my son.
You discussed me.
So he won't even listen to my side, your own wife?
Nancy just lost her child, Edith.
You and I have been married for three years.
How could you ever think I would be capable of anything so vicious and ugly?
He wouldn't even listen to me, Angie, in the way he was looking at me.
Hey, who cares what that piece of shit thinks about you?
Okay, if he wants to believe that psycho bitch, then they deserve each other.
Okay?
What are you doing?
What does it look like, huh?
I'm staying at the fire station tonight.
I can't be here right now.
I think you need to cancel the literacy fund raiser tomorrow.
Okay, it's just, it's too much with all of this.
I can't.
Too many people are accounting on me.
You sure you're up for it?
It'll be good to focus on helping other people.
I need to get on with my life and stop dreaming about Nolan.
Why would you ever say something like that about Edith?
Stay out of this.
You don't know all the facts.
I don't need to.
Edith would never attack Nancy.
Ever.
You're a joke.
Do you have any idea how much you're hurting her?
Back off.
Both of you.
Okay, good.
Good.
Excellent.
All right.
Thank you, son.
Nice.
Everything okay?
Uh, yeah, you know this stuff.
Got a lot going on right now.
You know what it is?
You're fighting?
Nothing you need to worry about that.
It's fine.
You know, watching you find happiness with Edith.
It's made me feel less guilty with a bad example that your mother and I set for you.
We're married.
God, I lost count of how many times you guys broke up and got back together.
All the fighting.
Edith could show you what marriage really was if you gave her a chance and treated her well.
I was right.
Thank you.
Can I grab a hug?
No.
Can you believe she blamed someone else for losing her baby and it was all caught on security
camera?
It's messy, then.
You lied about what happened.
You injured yourself.
No.
Has Edith been telling more lies?
Edith never touched you.
Then how did I fall if she didn't push me?
There's security footage, Nancy.
Do you think that I would hurt my old child?
My last link to Dom.
We'll discuss this later.
What are we dealing with?
We've got a class A fire at the community center.
Charity Ben.
Angie and Edith are there.
Hey.
We good?
Let's go.
You get low and cover your case.
No.
What about you?
I'm sure everyone is out and I'll be right behind you.
Go.
I did this still in there, okay?
You shouldn't leave until everyone else was out.
All right, go.
Come on.
Can you hear me?
Please eat it.
She's still alive.
You.
I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
Edith, you're in a fire.
You are the last person I want, helping me.
Hey.
Thank God you managed to save the books.
I mean, it's taken Edith months to get all those donations together.
When you think we can have access to the building.
Edith worked on a literacy fund raise of that.
Wait, why do you think we're here?
It's Edith's project.
You know, ever since she became a best-selling author,
she's been donating her profits and using her profile to help people.
Since when was Edith the best-seller?
Of course you don't know.
You know, I can't wait until she divorces your ass.
You can spend the rest of your life realizing just how badly you fucked up.
Hey, you feeling better?
I'll take you for a full checkup.
Since when did you care about me?
There's something you need to know.
There's security footage from the incident with Nancy.
It shows you never touched her.
And?
And I'm sorry I didn't listen to you.
It was for all the harsh bullshit that I said.
You're right.
I owed you better than that after all the years old now.
I bet you feel better with that off your chest now.
What do you mean?
I said I'm sorry.
Next time I ask you to trust me, I'll remember to bring this CCTV footage.
Is it possible?
My wife has had feelings for me this whole time.
She put the mail she cooked in the fridge.
Or when he got home to work.
He did so much for other people.
She wanted to do this small thing for him.
Enjoy.
One thing she loved was folding his clothes for him.
She pretended it wasn't a big deal.
But she loved touching his clothes, imagining him wearing them.
I was just about to bring you these.
It didn't have to do that.
Her favorite moment in the day was when he came home.
She loved his warm, brown eyes and dark hair.
She especially loved his smile.
Is it possible?
My wife has had feelings for me this whole time.
Hey.
Perfect timing.
I'm sure it's that coming right up.
Maybe it's slightly sure it's that.
There's maple syrup and honey if you are.
Sorry I'm not hungry.
Yeah, that's good.
Just once she wished he'd cook her her favorite pancakes for breakfast
or buy her flowers for no reason.
But she knew it was never going to happen.
Because the only thing he had room for in his life was his work.
What are these for?
The reason?
These don't change anything.
I'm allergic to roses.