Hey, did you know that, uh, he had a friend's little literacy charity?
No, I did not know that.
How long has that been going on?
Ah, a few years now.
You know, I've been wondering myself how you got into that.
You don't care about all of that?
Uh, excuse me.
I do.
You were an old man.
Maybe another time.
See you soon.
See you.
Still in the dark house, huh?
How do you know I'm the one who messed up?
I wouldn't freeze your hat like that unless you're done something bad, so...
Not bad, is it?
Yeah, I know.
I'm still trying to figure that one out.
Um, the question is, what's your best advice for getting in an anger moment for a given?
Huh?
What's your best advice for getting in a given moment for a given?
What about you just show off those muscles with yours?
Yeah, yeah.
Pilts are a primal.
It's better than a thousand words.