Look, with that being sick and a divorce, she's made me take another look at our marriage.
And?
I think maybe if you give me a chance, maybe we could save it.
Why would I give you another chance to ignore me for three years?
I haven't even... I haven't ignored you.
We've already established you don't know my birthday. You didn't even know I was a best-selling author and want me to keep going.
I wasn't deliberate, I was just focused on work.
You agreed to marry me because your father gave you an ultimatum to either join the family business or get married.
Then you blamed me for your own decision.
Do you have any idea how lonely this marriage is being for me?
No, you're right. I did blame you.
That was wrong.
I just said I... I never wanted to get married.
My parents pretty much hated each other, and I don't know what to mean, just seemed like a trap.
We are not your parents, Nolan.
I read your book.
No. It was really good.
Funny you from my antique. Pretty sexy too.
You're not exactly the target market.
I see a lot of you in it.
I just wanted to get to know you even more.
Look, I know I hurt you, but if you just give me a chance, I think we could have something really special here.