I can't believe you're asking me to forget everything that you've done.
No, not forget. Just forgive.
Please just give me a chance and I can make it up to you for everything.
Bye!
Some things are unforgivable.
You should be spending time with me answering.
I don't want to be, we can't see. I'm here with you.
How can you say that when you just lost your child?
What?
All right.
Given the circumstances, I think the best thing is to just stick to the plan.
We wait till your father's over his operation and we get a divorce.
And I'd appreciate it. If there are no more pancakes or you walking around like this, it doesn't help.
Wait, you think that's just having my baby?