No, hang on. Nancy didn't even fucking write this stuff.
What the fuck, man?
If you're not gonna look after Rita, then I will.
It's a fucking backup.
She's my white asshole.
Then act like a husband.
She could have gone blind tonight from those attacks.
Attack?
Edith! Edith! Edith, you okay?
I don't know when I'll be back.
Or even if I will be back.
Hey, where is she?
Frankie said she'd been attacked.
Okay, she's not here.
And even if she was, she does not want to speak to you.
Put in.
Now I want to see for myself that she's okay.
Why do you suddenly care?
You are honestly the worst thing that has ever happened to Edith.
And you know what?
I can't wait till that divorce is final
and you're left with that sick bitch, Nancy.
You two deserve each other.
No, wait, hang on a second.
When is all of this gonna be over?
You know what you need?
Some bambering.
And you have come to the right means.