You're the plagiarist, not Edith.
What handwriting changes? That doesn't prove anything.
Edith has a dozen other manuscripts in the same handwriting that proves this book is hers.
This bullshit isn't going to convince anyone.
Why are you talking to me like this?
Hey, Tom, chose you, trusted you, over everyone to look after me.
No, don't. Don't bring Thomas.
Well, he thought you were his friend. He made you promise on his deathbed to look after me.
You're supposed to protect me.
The only person I'm protecting is Edith, my wife.
You're seriously going to choose her over me.
You have 24 hours to publicly apologize, Edith, or I will
sue you for defamation and slander.
Is that serious enough for you?
Fire down town. We're rolling.
24 hours, Nancy.