You killed Andy!
That wasn't me. I've been on a fire all night with my whole crew.
I saw your car!
It just listened to me. Frankie was with me the whole time. He'll tell you.
No, no. I know what I saw. I know what you texted.
You killed Andy because you thought she was me.
You just wanted to get rid of me so you could be with Nancy.
I can't want to get rid of you, Ed. Please.
You're not making sense.
No, don't touch me.
Just listen to me. My car was at the station. My phone was...
My car keys, my phone. They were on my bunk when I left.
I mean, someone could have taken them.
I'm not listening to the bullshit.
Oh, Nancy. Nancy was there when I got the call out.
I mean, she could have taken my car.
Even if it was her, it's still your fault, and he is dead.
You let that voice and the psycho into our lives. This is all on you.
Thank you.