Our marriage has never really been happy.
No one always resented me.
Well, that's because I forced him into marriage
like a stubborn old man.
You were trying to help him.
You know, after he couldn't save his mother from that fire,
he became obsessed never to let that happen to anyone else.
Nolan is the most dedicated fireman I know.
And I hoped having a wife, starting a family,
I hoped it would change that.
Maybe I just wasn't enough of an incentive for him to change.
No, never say that to you go.
You were so, so lucky to have you.
Now, you tell me what you want to happen next, hmm?
Don't hold back on my account.
Thank you, for everything.
What have you been talking about for so long?
I told her to divorce you.
Chat has.
You what?