Umm...
Hmmm...
Anything to tell your daughter about us?
Oh, not that, man...
Yeah...
Mm-hmm...
I didn't expect her to arrive so soon.
I'm your girlfriend, James.
She was going to meet me sooner or later.
game?
No good train.
James?
We've been together for some time now.
Why can't I be your girlfriend?
As I told you in the very first night, there was nothing else that would happen.
It's just sex.
You told me you understood that.
Are you throwing me out?
I think twice, James. This will have consequences with my father.
Yvette, tell security to escort Ms. Sokova. She's not allowed back.
Yvette canceled my meetings until the driver will be downstairs shortly.