Bitch! Get off me! Get off!
Am I in your own business, old man?
Do you know who I am?
I will rule you in this town with a snap of my fingers.
Are you okay?
Thank you. I appreciate you stepping in.
No woman should be treated the way you were, Becca.
Always make sure you're okay.
Alright?
I'm gonna remove the trash.
Party's over! Chop top!
They said you made my dad kick up everyone for no reason.
Are you serious, Tally?
Out of all the years you've known me, what part of that makes any sense?
Fucking attacked me!
He tried to force himself on me after I repeatedly told him I wasn't interested.
I don't believe you.
He's a really nice guy and comes from a very wealthy family.
Are you fucking serious?
No, Becca!
I'm really getting sick and tired of you ruining everything.
It's like you can't stand anyone being happy.