What do you want to use?
What does that even mean?
Like, 1920s, like, she looks in a braille on.
That's just a lot of parties with us.
Okay.
It's a chat call.
Hey, gorgeous.
What are you doing?
Why do you care, Chad?
You cheated on me.
Don't be like that, Becca.
I missed you.
Listen, I was an idiot before.
But I wanted to let you know I'm coming to Miami for you.
What a chat, Mom.
So let me know he's coming to town.
And he wants to see me because he misses me.
He missed you?
Don't do it, Becca.
I mean, he's hurt you once.
He's going to do it again.
You want my opinion?
Stay far away from him.
It's obvious some other girls claiming him now.
You need some drinks.
You're starving.
Yeah.
Oh, I don't want that.
Alright, sit.
Sit.
It burns.