Come in. Mr. Valentino, did you finish signing the J-Bird report? Yes. Here we go.
Thank you. Yes, sweetie. I'm going shopping, daddy. Remember mom's birthday soon.
Can I have the A-key daddy? I want to take back in some friends to the keys.
Catherine said she can drop by in her way home and pick up the key. Sure sweetie
enjoy her shopping. You said Catherine? I have to pick up the key. She needs to
learn her way around the city. Good morning. I'm here to pick something up from
Mr. Valentino. Name? Becca Woods. He's expecting me. Right, of course he is. I
don't see an appointment so unfortunately you can't see him. Of course I don't have
an appointment. I'm picking something up. Not having a meeting. Can you just call
him and let him know that I'm here? Do you know how many women we get coming in
here trying to get up and see him? You are just like the others. I need to learn
to leave him alone. His taste is way above what you obviously are. Excuse me. I'll leave
now or I'll have you thrown out.