Good morning, beautiful.
Where are we?
My apartment.
I figured you wouldn't want to go back to my place, considering Talia's there.
And you were adamant about to continue my own fun, so I brought us here.
I do not remember that.
That's because you passed out in the car in the way here.
So you had your way with me while I was passed out?
No, Becca.
I too do have standards I live by and sleep in with an unconscious woman,
even when I have been seeing as a no-go for me.
What do you want like me, James?
Don't break my heart again, James.
I can't handle the heartache.
So, Mother says you have something to tell us?
Yes, it seems your ex-husband is in the apartment here at River Edge.
Now, the two of them were seeing going to the elevator.
We're guessing to this apartment.
So they're not going to stop seeing each other?
It seems not, miss.
Is there anything else you need to know?
Yes.
I want you to find out everything you can on Becca Woods.
If James won't stop seeing her, then I'll make sure she gets the message.