Don't pay the many mind by God.
You're dripping with elegance.
They are just jealous about you.
I'm a cancer charity on show.
I am mother died.
This is an original painting by Leslie Picelli, starting bid 20,000.
Do you like it?
It's lovely.
20,000.
Where are you doing?
100,000.
Yep, it's too much money.
It's for charity.
Soul.
Thank you, James.
It feels good to buy the item known that the money is going to a good cause.
It's something close to my heart.
Our mother lost her breast cancer fight a number of years ago.
My mom died of cancer too.
It was a couple years ago.
Of course.
Tying is the only way to get free from someone like you back up.
Yeah, James.
I said it.
Becca's a little bitch that no mother could love.
I think I should go.
I'm tired.
I go.
Perhaps you need to go back up north with your own kind.
Come with us, Becca.