What are you talking about?
We aren't married and my seeing her was recent. Have you been telling people I will sleep in with her while we were married?
I'm not going through this anymore Alison. Keep her assing Becca. So the hell out of you. Understand.
Oh sweetie. I don't know what I'm doing. That's so wrong.
I mean they've been divorced for years. I don't understand it. You did nothing wrong Becca.
Honestly, I was surprised by how James acted at the event.
He's a strong-willed man and usually puts his foot down with things. I'm leaving.
Allegra, I can't play these games with James anymore. I care about him. Yes, but I
Don't have time for this drama. This isn't what I signed up for when I came to Miami. Take some time to think about it. Okay?
It's never good to overreact to anything. I'm done thinking about James.
Alison's the woman he wants. He showed me that tonight. But Becca. Why Allegra?
Is he here right now comforting me? No, he's not. You are and I am grateful for that
But I this is just too much for me. I should have enough money for it like to get home. Don't be silly. You don't need to buy a ticket.
It's time to go ladies.