Hello and welcome to tonight's show.
What?
This place is not a tornado to the college party you had when I was gone.
You were gone for like a week, knowing all of the college parties.
I appreciate you letting me stay here though.
I love having you here Becca.
You know, I'll turn you over for my business to feel horrible.
Most bachelors at least are pet parents.
Yeah, to be honest, I don't really take you as a pet parent.
Oh, you and a lego have no faith in me, huh?
Now, have you eaten?
Mm, I'm actually making dinner.
So, do you think I can help you with?
No, I just need you to go to your room and relax and I'll call you when dinner's ready.
You want to have a kind Becca, do you know that?
You've had a long trip now, it's the least I can do.
I love having you here Becca.