We're going to have a very serious conversation telling because you seem to think that you're
able to dictate to me what it is that I do and that's not going to fly.
You're screwing my best friend and then on top of all that you made me look like a complete
fool by your actions.
Fool.
You made yourself look like a fool and how day you stand there and make such a big fuss
about me being with Becca went for over a year.
You went behind her back sleeping with her boyfriend and now you're knocked out by him.
How dare you say something like that about him.
He's going to be your future son-in-law.
You know, I'm your daughter.
Why don't you care about me feelings and my tears?
You have no idea how to take care of yourself.
You don't clean up after yourself.
You don't cook.
You don't even wash your own laundry.
So how in the hell are you going to take care of yourself, let alone someone else?
You think that you are so much better than everyone at everything, but you know Chad?
He's actually a really nice guy and comes from a very nice family and I just, you know,
I really don't understand what makes you hate him so much when you're willing to screw
someone like Becca.
If you marry that boy, your trust fund money is gone.
Remember?
The day you turned 18 I told you I will pay you a monthly allowance while you went to school
and after you graduated while you got set up in your career until you could support yourself,
I will stop doing that.
Fine.
Then I'm going to move in with Mother.
You are not my father, that bitch.
She changed you.
And I'm going to make her paper everything that she's done to me and this family.
Do what you must do.
Of course I will set something up for my grandkids so that way they have money when they turn
18.
But I'm not giving you another penny if you marry that boy.
Where do you want me to start?
I could explain how all my teachers were giving me nasty looks or how the Dean seems
to always have a snarky comment.
We're better yet how the entire school knows that I'm sleeping with you and everyone finds
me horrible for sleeping with my best friend's dad.
Oh, it was that kind of day, huh?
When are you coming home, James?
I hope to be the weather weekend sweetie.
I'm almost done with things here and then I should be able to come up for a few days.
I know.
My business isn't the concern of your boss anymore.
See, that's where you're wrong.
You don't get to decide when business is over.
Sergei respects you.
He doesn't want things to end badly with you.
So he's sent to me to talk some sense into you, considering how close we used to be.
Close.
I would consider what we used to do as being close.
Sergei and Allison, they may have gotten lunch together the other.
He felt bad for the woman that was cast aside for being too old.
Cast aside for being too old.
Allison cheated on me, which is why I divorced her.
But I find it interesting that Sergei took the time to speak with her.
What did he think he would get from it?
This won't end well for you, James.
A man like Sergei isn't forgiving.
The very fact that he's even giving you a chance to reconsider should shine in your eyes like
the illuminating factor that it is.
I was trying to help.
I didn't think that you knew.
What?
That you went behind my back and met with Sergei?
Crying wolf to a man I'm trying to get my family away from?
All because I'm sleeping with a woman that isn't you?
Have you lost your fucking mind, Allison?
You, James!
I did everything right.
You are the reason that everything went bad.
All I have wanted is for you to pay attention to me, for you to love me and want to make
things work.
But all you cared about was your business.
You didn't care about the family that you were losing.
So it's my fault.
My fault.
The only thing that was my fault was ever being with you.
I should have listened to everyone back then.
I sort of left your ass in the front steps of that house and walked away, never looking
back.
You ruined everything.
Don't you stay in there and you put this all on me.
I had no idea that your business is with him or over.
But, James, if you don't continue, he's going to kill you and I don't want to put
our daughter in that position.
Do you really want to risk her life?
Stay away from me, Talia and Becca.
You need to grow up, Allison.
But you know what?
You'll be happy to know that I have no idea where Talia is so I can't exactly stay around
her.
What?
You don't know where she is.
You're all fucking your little bitch up north.
She ran off.
And I have no idea where she is or who she's when.
The beach house is dirty but it's empty and I even went to your place.
My housekeeper has no idea where she is.
When was the last time you saw her?
Last week, after you guys got on to a fight.
I'll find her.
If I now stay the fuck away from all of us, you're not wanted.
James, a man just?
Hey, what's going on?
I'm in the middle of something.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to bother you.
I was checking in on you.
I haven't really heard from you today and you're supposed to be here tomorrow so I just
wanted to figure out what time so I could plan something.
I'm not going to be able to make it tomorrow.
There are a lot of things going on and they are just very complicated at the moment and
as much as I would love to be there with you, I honestly can't.
It's okay.
I completely understand.
I'll just figure something else out to do.
Do you know when you might be up here?
No, I don't know what I'm going to make it up there but I do really have to go.
So can we pick up this conversation tomorrow morning?
I have some free time.
I can schedule you in.
You guys tell me, are you ready to do it?
Come in.
Well, besides the fact that the entire campus knows that I'm screwing James and they also
think I'm sleeping with you too.
Ah, let's think.
Well, James is supposed to say me this weekend but he can't.
Yeah, I guess that's all that's really going on.
Oh, I did forget.
I now have to schedule in order to have conversations with James because he's too busy to deal with
me.
You know what?
I know that being there, I'll make a call.
Can you believe it?
I absolutely cannot believe that he got that little bitch pregnant and then brought her home
to me like I was supposed to do something about it.
Look who it is.
The little slut who thought she could get into my family.
You heard what I said.
I heard through the grapevine that you weren't coming back to Yale this year.
So what are you doing here?
I don't know who you heard that from but that definitely is not right.
It's my final year and I plan on finishing with honors just as I started.
You know, I've got to make sure I get those grades and then I'll take myself on to bigger
and better things.
I wish I could say the same for your son.
I wish you had had that kind of fire in you before.
Maybe I would have actually considered you a match for him.
As much as I would have liked that before, Barbara.
That will never happen now.
I'd rather be single than with an arrogant prick who likes to beat on your mind.
But what can I say?
Like father like son.
Film tonight.
Yay.
I can't wait.
I spoke to Barbara today and I used the term talked loosely.
But I think Tali might be living with her or at least staying at his apartment here.
Let me get Frank on that immediately.
And we need to call the hospital.
You need an ambulance.
No.
I can't go to the hospital.
I'll be okay though.
This isn't the first time it's happened to me.
He never hurts the baby though.
I just need my face.
How did you find me?
Oh.
It's not hard considering the rumors trickling around.
You have a keycard to get in here.
How late are you downstairs with me?
Just getting on the plane now.
I'll be there in a few hours.
I need to find Tali.
That's actually why I'm calling.
What do you mean?
Have you seen her?
You could say that.
James.
Becca.
Where is she?
Okay.
There's no need for the attitude.
Well, don't act the way you are.
You said that you had seen her now.
How am I acting?
She's on the couch in our living room.
You made the wrong choice.
Daddy, you're only going to make it worse, Daddy.
Please stop it, Becca.
He's only going to make it worse.
Becca, say out of this.
What the fuck is going on?
It's none of your business.
I am your girlfriend, James.
We're supposed to be a team and you involved me in all of this.
So yes, it does have to do with me.
Your daughter's in my apartment wearing my clothes.
And after everything she has done to me, I gave her a safe space to be, yet this doesn't
concern me.
Sha, did that to her.
So you plan to go and beat him up.
Acting irrational about this, that's how you want to handle it.
I'm not a good person, Becca.
I'm dangerous and I do dangerous things.
You would do well to remember this.
My life isn't legal and neither are my actions.
Your daughter needs you.
You need to start from the beginning and tell me everything that happened.
So after I left Miami, I went with Chad to stay with his parents for a few weeks, and
his mom really didn't want us to be together, and then his family tried to force me to get
an abortion, even though I didn't want to.
And then they realized after I went to the doctor how far along I was, and that's what
I got really bad.
How far along are you?
Six months.
Do you understand the complications of what you've done with all the partying and drinking?
The damage you could have done to that child?
We need to get you to a doctor.
No.
No, I can't go to a doctor.
I don't want him getting arrested.
I need to apologize to you.
I shouldn't have spoken to you like that earlier.
I was just so angry by everything that happened.
But Chad had done to her.
I lost control of myself and lashed out at the one person I shouldn't have.
I don't know what you expect me to say.
Everything has been so chaotic since the moment I met you this summer.
And even though we're together and we have these amazing moments, it's become nothing
but toxic.
No.
We can make this work.
We'll figure it out as we have been.
Right tomorrow morning, you and Tal, you're going to be back in Miami.
I've done a lot about things in my life, Becca.
One of them was making shady deals to build my empire, illegal things, that caused people
to get hurt.
Okay.
I mean, I knew you did things that was obvious, but why not explain that to me to help me understand?
I made deals with a Russian leader named Sperda who heard some years ago when I was just
a young man trying to build my empire.
My business with him led me to do very shady deals, mix with the wrong people, and make
a lot of enemies.
Now that I'm older, I try to pull away from the business dealings I did before, but now
I've created an enemy of Sir Dave.
Wait, do you mean like the mafia?
Yes.
I mean the mafia, because I'm refusing to re-sign a deal, say I'm making threats that
they could potentially risk the safety of the people around me.
I wouldn't allow them to get anywhere near you.
I can spend some time together, not fun.
James, please, just go take care of yourself, maybe we can talk in the future.
This better be good for you to call me right now.
It's nice to talk to you as well.
I just wanted to call to see if you've heard anything about Becca.
Come on James, that's not what you want to know now, is it?
I haven't spoken to her in a bit.
We've traded some texts, however.
I hear studying can be torturous.
I've been friends for some time.
I get what you're putting down, James.
You're a wonderful cook, Becca.
Thank you.
Maybe next time I can cook something you like.
I'll eat your wonderful cooking after I age out of modeling.
I imagine James has been busy.
He's been caring for Tali, which is a full-time job.
Now that he's out of the way, I can fairly compete for you.
You need to see a doctor.
Now we've been after Sergey for 10 years now,
but no matter what we do, we can't seem to get close enough to him.
However, he's made a point multiple times
to get a hold of you, so we want to strike a deal,
because we could put you away for 15, 20 years with everything
we have on you.
Oh, that is unless Sergey kills you first.
I'd under one condition.
I want to make sure that my family,
my daughter, all of them are protected and kept safe.
That pretty girl up in New York?
I want her protected, too.
We get a call soon.
Sure.
Have a good night, Mr. Valentino.
Tali needs me.
Tali doesn't need a mother in your condition.
Her daughter needs her mother.
Leave, Allison.
No, James, you can't.
I'm praying.
Allison, it's OK.
Becca, just in case you don't read my texts,
Tali needs you.
She's gone into a premature labor.
You don't have to go, Becca.
Don't influence her, Neil.
It's her choice.
It's too early for Tali to give birth.
She must be freaking out.
She has parents that type of situation is for family only.
We can see why you're still single, Neil.
You have a good life here.
New York's been good to you.
Tali needs me.
After I help her, I'm going to tell James that I'm pregnant.
How long have you been standing there?
More enough.
I can tell you've gotten the hang of it.
Did I hear the phone earlier?
Becca, I know how much you've been missing her.
I'm unhappy you are.
I'm sure she's moved on, Tali.
Well, hello there, Rebecca.
It's funny seeing you in these parks.
What the fuck are you doing here?
You better watch yourself, Rebecca.
You're sadly mistaken if you think you can get James,
or that he walks you.
He's already been with me twice since you've been out of the picture.
And he was more than satisfied both times.
Go to hell.
You know Rebecca.
Well, I think it's happened to people who don't know how to mind their business.
You better watch her back.
Enjoy New York train.
I hope this is the last time we'll see each other.
What are you doing in my office?
Oh, James.
Is that any way to greet no lover?
I know you missed me.
I thought I'd clarify that I didn't want to see you in my office again.
Oh, well, it isn't like you have a chance here, is it?
Daddy wanted to come kill you.
But I persuaded him to let me see you instead.
Why would your father want to kill me over not giving him a contract?
Oh, that isn't why.
He thinks you're doing deals with the Feds.
I told him you must be mistaken.
We all know what kind of man you really are.
So, he sent me here to talk sex in here.
The Feds?
Why the fuck would he think that?
Get back with me, James.
Father will forgive you if you do.
Thanks.
Good note, thanks.
Security.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I can't wait to see Becca dad.
Christmas, my dog.
Merry Christmas and Happy New Year.
It's, um...
He uses me.
I can't believe it.
I did so many horrible things.
No doubt.
Do not think about the past.
He is healthy, he's beautiful, he's perfect.
Yeah, he is, because he has always been such a good friend to me through everything, even
when I didn't deserve a...
Tell you the past is the past.
Follow me.
I want to show you something.
Did you put the nursery in here, James' room?
Something like that.
Don't you think my dad would be the best person to watch after him in the middle of the night?
Alright.
Are you really Becca?
I'm not sure.
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
Disturfing me.
I'm so happy you're back.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
I thought it would be later.
It now seems better than later.
You're pregnant?
I think you know how someone gets pregnant, James.
May I?
I didn't walk us.
There's so much to talk, James.
You've known about this pregnancy longer than I have.
May I have some time to enjoy the moment, please?
Yeah.
I'm Mr. Valentino.
This just came for you.
It wouldn't hurt her.
My grandchild.
Shh!
No!
You brought it!
No, I was seeing it.
You all need for all the emotions.
You all this?
You all the consequences of dealing with the devil.
Did I miss something?
Yeah.
Our entire dinner.
Keep thinking you're going to shoot anyone that walks past the table.
I hope you understand that you're pregnant and I've put you in a very dangerous issue.
I understand, James.
But can we please enjoy our dinner?
At this rate, I think I'm going to get sour lemons for dessert.
I must protect you.
I have never felt more protected.
Give us some more time, Mr. Valentino.
Everything's going to work out.
No, I have no more time.
We've done everything we promised, Mr. Valentino, and everything should be over at a few weeks
at best.
I have a pregnant girlfriend.
Do something to capture a surrogate.
Becca, I'm not angry that you're pregnant with my future brother or sister.
You're going to make an amazing mother.
You're already an amazing person already.
So you don't hate me?
Because I don't hate you.
I hate what got us to this point, you know?
Ever since having a baby, I'm a changed woman.
And so what that brings me to my next point is, if anything would ever happen to me, you
want you to take full custody over my son.
My dad would be a wreck, and my mother is obviously out of the question, so I hope that's
okay.
Tell me, if anything ever happens to you, I promise you, I will take care of your son.
But enough of the heavy stuff, okay?
Tell me what else is going on.
Well, okay, mom, mom journeys, you know?
Nancy, take my son to the panic room.
Okay, we have to get up.
I can help you.
Come on.
Let's go.
You finally return my call.
Mr. Valentino.
It's my ass on the line, Greg.
It's my ass.
I need your help.
Mr. Valentino, FBI's operation is my...
Do it, Greg.
Tonight, no excuses.
Mr. Valentino, big timeless car.
Oh, my daughter's love.
There's no match for a man's desire for his womb.
We go home.
Greg, this is James Valentino.
Sergey has Talia and Becca tied up at my home.
We're leaving.
No, no.
Lower your hands.
I'm not the cops.
Worse.
No, no.
Forget about me.
Hmm?
Oh.
What's your choice, James?
Hmm?
This could have been so easy.
All you had to do was continue your relationship with Khatsui.
The chosen one means what?
Sergey!
The target, repeat.
I lost sight of targets.
I need a bus to the Valentino house.
Victims appear fine.
One of them appears pregnant and he transports to the hospital.
Taking Miss Valentino to the ambulance.
I need Miss Wood soon, all right?