in the arraignment.
Meet me at Diaz Global.
What the hell were you thinking and finding Kendall to that meeting?
I was just trying to facilitate a potential partnership.
Cut the shit, Jane.
I know what you were trying to do.
Fine, you caught me.
I just can't stand seeing you with that hag.
Is there a better way?
Listen, if something happens to Kendall, I swear to God.
You'll what?
Turn your back on your dad and Diaz Global?
I've already set things in motion.
Tell my dad to sit tight and wait for me to stick it to him.
It's me.
Pick up everything you can on Kendall Riot.
Her past, her weaknesses, her affairs, anything
that we can need to cast her.