Kendall, I need to tell you something.
Yeah, I've decided to give it my right to my family fortune and step away from Diaz Global.
I'm in love with Kendall, and I'll come clean her tonight.
Confirmed, Raymond's identity.
Don't listen to a word he says, Kendall. You should know, Raymond is the heir to Diaz Global.
What the hell are you doing here?
He's a spy.
Wasn't that the signal?
Time to put the plan to action, now that you've earned her trust.
Kendall, I swear to God it's not what you think.
I was going to tell you everything about it.
I can't do my doubts about you, but I just said it's trust you.
Look, I opened up to you. I told you things. I had never shared with anyone and it was all just a big lie.
No, but please.
Don't!