So, sir, are you coming back?
Why don't you go take care of Rodney and get back to work?
Three days ago, urgently, keep the shareholders be.
I know you've been pressing your shareholders.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I mean, I'm glad you know.
You see, soon your fathers will be publicized.
And when that happens, I'm going to offer you double
to buy 15% of the company's shares.
And what if I refuse?
I am doing this for the sake of the Vanderbilt group.
After all, we can't have a blind person
like you managing it, can we?
Soon enough, you will know who owns the Vanderbilt group.
And tell me, who do you think that's going to be?
You really think a bastard like you can own the company.
You know, whether you're doing this
for the Vanderbilt group or yourself, I don't really care.
I think it's best you stay where you are.
End of discussion.