Do you not trust me?
I deleted the part where your guy changed the will and made Robin.
I don't care. Just be a good girl and give me that card.
Fine. I know you don't trust me.
Of course I trust you.
Come on.
I know you've been through so much this past half year, marrying that old man.
Shit, that was torture for me too.
Thank God he's dead, right?
Let's please leave when we get the money.
Oh, good evening Mrs. Vanderbilt.
Who are you?
You don't look like someone who just lost your husband.
You must be Emma's new body card.
Your only responsibility is to take care of her.
Your insulin may cost you your job.
Did you find her?
Looks like you got in some good fight today.
Did you get the materials?
No. Someone else got them.