I mean someone opened the safe after Rodney Day?
It looks like it.
It's getting interesting.
The person who also opened the safe is the one who killed Rodney?
Where you going?
One of the Vanderbilt House.
Watch out for Rodney's daughter. She's a piece of work.
Be careful.
Good morning, Ms. Vanderbilt.
I told you yesterday I don't need a bodyguard.
You know your situation, more than I do.
Ms. Vanderbilt, I think you should at least let me protect you until you gain your sight back.
Please come have a seat.
How did you sleep?
Very well actually.
Is Daniel here?
He went to work very early this morning.
When will he be back?
Later today.
It's probably very busy.
I made you your favorite coffee.
Thank you.
It's very hot.
Let me cool down for you a little bit.
Thank you, Larry.
Hello.
Ms. Vanderbilt.
Nate?
I've got some information about Mr. Vanderbilt that you may want to know.