With the two of them.
I'm sure what kind of crap you'd take up on me,
that her nephew pushed me away again.
A year ago,
a fandered old group was about to require my brother's company.
The night before the deal was about to go down,
he'd killed himself.
To find out what really happened,
I accepted a job offer from your father,
to become your new bodyguard.
Did you find out what happened?
Well, but I know something's up.
The night that your father died,
they were by up papers from my brother's company in the safe.
And the next day, they were gone.
What do you mean the night my father died?
What were you doing in the safe?
Daniel posted a job in the black market,
G hacked your home network,
and we intercepted that task.
I was the one that was at your house that night.
Well, if Daniel set this up,
why didn't it, why didn't it, Hannah?
I got the will, I checked it out, copied it,
and I put it back.
If I knew what was gonna happen to your father,
I would have stopped it.
I did it though, and I'm sorry, I really am.
So Daniel knew, and your dad wasn't gonna make it,
and that's where you switched the will.
I'm gonna help you nail this killer,
but there's more you have to know.
I found something at Daniel's house.
You're with him all the time,
I don't have proof that he did anything,
but you need to watch out, Emma, Emma.