You passed out. I got your meds checked. The ones you've been taking since you lost your vision.
My meds.
Yeah. Evelyn and Daniel switched him out ages ago. But we caught it and I don't think there's been
a lot of harm done. Thank you, Liam.
No more solo superhero moves, okay? I'll handle it for you.
All they're good. You have some nerve coming into my office after a swiping 50 mil for me.
I gave you a contract, Daniel. You made that call yourself. I had nothing to do with it and you
know it. So why don't you explain to me how I swiped 50 million from you?
You introduced me to that god. How am I supposed to believe you have no connection?
I've introduced a lot of people to that guy. If I was blamed every time something went wrong,
I'd be broke or dead by now. So tell me, Daniel, did I lose my cut?
Yeah. You know, I'm going to call the cops because you're setting me up right now.
All right, call the cops. Have fun explaining to them where that 50 mil came from.
And don't forget about Mr. Bannerville's death.