And I need to confess something to you.
I'm listening.
And I'm so sorry. I can't live without you.
Everything you want to know, I'll tell you.
Just give me a chance.
Evelyn, the woman's evil.
She manipulated me into taking away your property.
I didn't know what I was thinking.
I just... love you.
Since the moment we met...
Stop it, Daniel! You killed my father.
I didn't!
How many times do I have to tell you your father's death was an accident?
Then why didn't you sneak into my room to steal the hair?
Which wasn't his, by the way. I cut it from a wig.
This was Liam's idea, wasn't it?
Yeah. You two ganged up on me.
And we caught your murderer.
Are you trying to scare me?
The police don't have enough evidence, so they're not going to catch me.
But they will. It's just a matter of time.
Okay.