Okay, what are you doing here? So that's why you're trying to get him to kill you, huh?
It's the easiest way leader said you wouldn't act alone Emma. What if I didn't show up in time?
What would have happened? You have any idea? I don't want you taking these risks for me
So what other just put yourself in danger?
You have any idea how worried I was about you
So glad you're home
And why are you here? Surely you're not missing me. I wanted to thank you
For taking care of dad and that's for everything else
You know when dad met you you had
Decent job you had a wonderful life and you gave everything up for that jerk
I think he really loved you though. That means anything to you Daniel talked to me last night
He told me everything you know and said that you manipulate it. No, no, no, no
Evelyn for the record. I think it was the other way around. Yeah, it doesn't mean that I forgive you
but
You made dad very happy and it's last few years
And I do appreciate that
It's a year's worth of living expenses. I know Daniel to get what he wants. He will go to any lengths even the most extreme
Be careful
Nothing can be worse than the death of my father
I'll bring that man to justice
Even if it takes my life
Spit it out. You know who changed your father's will it was Liam
So aren't you worried he has ulterior motives? I trust him
You trust him
See that's funny cuz I thought you guys met a few days ago, you know
He took the money that you stole from me
Also, his brother lost to us in a commercial battle and lost his business
Anything else you want to tell me? I get it
You have feelings for him. What are you doing? You know what? Go ahead. Call the cops
Let's see if you can get me convicted for that shady video you took
I have your signature on the transfer agreement and as for Rodney's death
Well, the evidence got deleted
You know Liam's in pretty hot water now
You can imagine it's pretty damning evidence with him transferring money laundering it through his friend's account all the fingerprints on Rodney's will
It's enough to lock a man up for years. Don't you think?
What do you want? I want you to marry me as planned
Think about it
Not too well. I have to say your call came as a bit of a surprise
Where did you get this?
I wonder how Daniel will react when he finds out how much money you took from him
Or maybe you just don't give his shit since he basically got a gun to his head
With backup security footage from the study room surveillance camera
Where's the evidence Evelyn?
Of Daniel committing the murder. I know you know where it is
Why didn't you come here sooner? And that was the perfect time. Don't you think Daniel's a very meticulous guy?
But I don't really think he understood how valuable you really were and I do I think you'd make a great partner, right?
You're right
But why would I trust you with such a trump card? It's because you have no other option. I
Tell Daniel what you have on him. I don't think he'll let you survive the rest of tonight now granted
That's the worst case scenario, but knowing how crazy that guy is
I don't think he would let you off too easily. You just know too much
Don't you fine? I will give you the footage under two conditions
What are they one I need money
Two I need security to ensure that I get out of here safely deal
I'll come pick you up tonight
Make sure everything's ready Evelyn. She still is the footage that it was deleted. She's gonna give it to me tonight
Let me go with you
It's too dangerous
Just wait at the house and call the police when I'm down. Okay, how are you gonna pay me show me the footage
You know why are you in the morning tonight?
You're the villo that I set up for you. I'll put the security in place
Some will pick you up three hours after you arrive
What's your plan exactly?
Just do what I say
Evelyn it's all there
Good. Good. It took you over there now. They fall asleep. This is it
It's time to end
How did you find me?
Well, you don't want to invite me in
Evelyn I need your help. I'm at the end of my road here. I don't know what to do
I'm sorry, but you should have thought about that before you crossed me
Baby, you're really breaking my heart here. Don't you have a seat? Let's talk. Please
I'm so stupid to have believed you
This whole time I was just a pawn in your game. No see you're not that stupid after all
Or else you wouldn't have sighted with Liam after our little chat
I don't know what you're talking about. How did the cops know what happened with Rodney then? You know see I had this
Perfectly planned out and then you ruined it. Stop it get off me. You copied the tapes and then made a goddamn fool out of me
No, no, I didn't no you didn't like I should have known
From the very start like my suit. I'm here from the police. Yeah, or do you think Danny might have run away?
I don't think so. Got some friends in the smuggling business and they haven't found anything suspicious yet
We have helped me
Who isn't sounds like Evelyn think she's in trouble. Just stay right here. I'm gonna be right back, okay?
You say sweet soon enough. You're just gonna be a body in a bag
Before I get what I want you wish I
Could see your Liam's biggest weakness
He'll do anything I say
What did you do to him nothing yet? No, he's probably still looking for you
But now that we got some time
Figured we can talk do you have anything you want to say you know as your last words
It was all your fault Emma a
Pretty rich girl fell into my arms at my lowest point
What was I supposed to say no, I didn't feel pretty bad about Evelyn
What did you do to Evelyn? I did what I had to do. She betrayed me. You did it. You're a murderer
You see
Evelyn did so much believe when I had nothing
Okay, she cooked she cleaned she even paid off a couple of my dad's blessed her heart
But I did it anyway, but you
My dear
But you made me do it quit lying to yourself
You're using Evelyn all day a man like you doesn't deserve love so much for the chit-chat
At the time the boyfriend's gonna be here any second. Oh
And on time
Stay right there
Right on time stay right there
You let her go. I'll give you the money. Well, Liam
I don't think you're in any place to tell me what to do
Unless you want me to take her with me
far just
Tell me what to do first. I want my money back. Okay now
Gee transfer the 150 million to Daniels account. Just do it
There
What else anything else save all your first-class body mark Liam
So if I expect to get out here safe, you need to be somewhat incapacitate
Hurt yourself. No, stop it. No, don't do it. Do it. Don't you want ammo, right? Come on
We have Liam
Oh, it's okay. It's okay. All right
Stop it
It's time for you to go to the funeral