Who took these photos? Was it him? Oh, God. He secretly filmed everything
I just I had a little too much to drink
Is that what you call having a good time
Playing prostitute with the closest guy in the room
Prostitute know it. It's not like that enough with the pretense. He's already posted the photos on Instagram and bragged about it
No
No, no, that's not really he'd like I think a shame a tour fine. Go ahead
But not as a Ford
Get out of my house
me
shameless
What about you, huh?
It took not even a week after a mom passed your illegitimate love child to move in with us
So who's really the shameless one here? You?
you you
You get out of no daughter of mine
This family only has one true daughter. Oh Stella. So naive
Blinded by the genius in front of you. I got you right where I want you bitch