What's this woman's deal that Dionne Hotel is the most expensive five-star hotel in America?
Is she testing me?
I'm just a security guard.
How can I ever afford a place like that?
If you want a honeymoon there, you can just forget it.
Hey, there's a gift shop right there.
We should grab something real quick.
Already showing your true gold digging colors just after one day of marriage.
You go ahead. I'm going to park the car across the street.
A gold digger. I knew it.
Let's see how you handle things when you can't pay.
Just a matter of time before you come crawling back.
Excuse me, ma'am.
That scarf is $1,800.
Do you have a discount?
This is a luxury store, not a flea market.
If you're looking for something cheaper, there's a general store down the street.