Oh, uh, I, um, I want to bet with a friend.
You gambled our savings?
Are you kidding me? That's so risky! Why would you do that?
Don't worry, it was a one-time thing, okay?
Yesterday you were mad at me, and now you're doing this. I don't understand.
Me neither. Better yet. How about we just start over? Clean slate.
I don't think I heard you right.
Stella married who?
That bitch married my Ethan.
Same old Stella, always taking everything from me.
This can't happen. You need to win Ethan back.
Our company's feature depends on the Smith Group's investment.
Am I supposed to do that, Dad? You already made me fake a pregnancy to force Ethan into a marriage with me?
And then embezzled money from his company to cover up our debts? He won't take me back.
I'm tired of hearing excuses. Think of something.
Or do you want to get out done by Stella again?
Speak of the devil. Look who's calling. Took him long enough.
Work your magic, baby.
Hey Ethan!