I can't believe I'm the owner of my own bakery.
I was really coming up.
Someone better pinch me.
I'm a taller tip.
Okay, I'm going to start with this right away.
Make it extra special.
If I hadn't been expelled, maybe I could have worked here.
I've heard their CEO is super talented.
Let's see what this other Ethan looks like.
What a pleasant surprise.
I was unexpected for another week.
Wow, we heard from your grandmother.
You got married.
How could we keep vacationing?
Meeting our daughter-in-law, you know, that takes priority.
Well, rest for a couple days.
I'll arrange a meeting for you and meet my wife.
I promise you're going to love her.
Well, all that matters is that you love her.
True love.
Right, sweetheart, just like you and me.
Wow, Dad, okay.
Really reaching for those brownie points, aren't you?
Don't worry, son.
You'll be there soon enough.
Come in.