Mom, Dad, just look at these photos.
Press my daughter-in-law.
My real daughter-in-law.
It's not calling us Mom and Dad.
You've been divorced for two years already.
No, Mom. Ethan and I have plans to get back together.
Everything's gonna go back to normal.
What delusional world are you living in?
No way in hell would he ever get back with you.
Ruby, you're out.
Stella, you're in.
You've been through so much already.
There's no idea.
I have a home now.
It's with us.
Oh, please.
You make me want to gag.
This reject isn't worth your time.
I told you Hurdie and Stella would have its consequences.
I will see where it really hurts.
Your alimony payments.
No, you can't do this to me.
I'm your one and only wife.
Security, get this crazy woman out of the building.
Stella, you parasite.
I'll shot at your world or die trying.