Your father isn't arrested.
Charlotte, what the hell is going on?
It's all Mason's doing.
They were worth some project.
Someone had to swim wrong.
And Mason's put it all on your father.
A grateful, miserable asshole.
Her family helped build his business up from the ground.
He doesn't know, but even I met him.
Evil, disgusting bastard.
Chloe, what are you doing here?
I don't even care that you cheated on me
and immediately proposed to her.
None of that matters.
What does matter?
Very much to me, Mason is what you're doing to my father.
In every business venture, there's
a certain degree of risk involved.
Don't be quiet with me.
You know, someone has to take a blame for the losses.
Touch me, Mason.
You know, Chloe, I still think of you all the time.
How about this?
You be my mistress and I'll let your father out for a hook.
You're sick, Mason.
My hands are tied, then.
My only suggestion, hire a very good lawyer,
because your father's looking at at least a decade
behind bars.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to laugh.
It's just, who would actually dare to take your case
and stay in my way?
Remember, I'm marrying Sophia Foster, the daughter
to only the richest family in town.
Maybe her brother Ethan Foster is a brilliant attorney,
but I don't think he's going to want
to go to court against his future brother-in-law.
Ethan Foster, the guy I kissed,
is he really the only one who could help me now?