What am I doing? I've refused Mason, but now I'm begging for Ethan?
Mr. Foster, please. You're my only hope.
I'm flattered, but I'm afraid I'll have to disappoint you, Miss Gray.
My sister Sophia once tried to run away because my mother tried to break up her and Mason.
She loves the son of a bitch, and I care for her deeply.
So, I promised myself that I wouldn't intervene in her relationship, and I won't let you do that either.
Then why did you make me drink all of that whiskey?
Why save me and bring me back here?
To reject me, insult me as this kind of sick game to you?
Should I have left you in the street? If not, then you're welcome.
Don't forget your coat this time.
I wasn't. I don't want to give you any other reason to pester me.
Why can't I get you out of my mind? Chloe, you make me want to play more games with you.