Thank you mr. Foster even call me either. I think there's something going on with my brother and Chloe
Chloe
Please will you come play at our wedding? You're the best violinist. I've ever heard
Don't make me beg please please please please please I appreciate it, but I'm actually already booked that day. Oh
What a shame
Thank you so much for dessert mr. Foster, but I actually need to be getting going
I'm tutoring a student in downtown. Oh, can I join you? I've always wanted to learn to play violin
You'd be disturbing her lesson Sophia fine
Please let me drive you. I'm heading downtown. Anyway, who are you looking at Mason?
Sophia
Chloe