Chloe, you're going to regret this.
Just wait.
You're going to call right back into my arms because you know you belong to me.
Ethan, how did you get back?
Just now.
Um.
I feel like you're seducing me instead of it being the other way around.
Hmm.
You seem like you're not enjoying it.
I do enjoy your morning greetings.
It makes me want to stay in bed all day, but I have business to attend.
My father, is he?
Everything's fine.
Once the paperwork goes through, me and you can go down and visit your stepmother and him together.
Why does he want to meet them with me?
Won't it be a bit like meeting the in-laws?
You don't have to come with me. I don't want to bother you.
I'm his lawyer. What are you thinking?