What do you mean by lost?
Well clearly, somebody doesn't want the Peter Gray case to be solved.
So they broke in last night and stole the security footage.
The security footage is the most important piece of evidence.
Yeah.
My shit.
I'll look for some backups, but I don't think Mason would be so stupid as to leave any behind.
Be quick.
We need it before the trial.
This case is very important.
Make it a top priority.
Hi, Captain.
Are you sure you want me to sell all of it?
I mean, some of these pieces have some real sentimental value, especially your mother's necklace.
That's a family air loan.
I know.
But we need the money to start up our new business.
Our own music studio.
I could lend you some money.
And we could look for an investor.
Do you think Ethan Foster would be interested?
Vivian, please, I can't take your money.
Or his.
I made up my mind.
Okay.
Come to my office.
Now.