You should get some rest. I'll come back later.
Mr. Foster, what brings you here?
Wait, let me guess. You got bored and came to order Chloe around and humiliate her for fun.
That was not my intention.
I very much feel that it was. So you can forget sneaking into her room and just leave.
I'd be grateful if you could help me with that.
If you think that buying her new violin is going to erase everything, I will tell you right now, it won't.
Wait a minute. Is this handmade by Giovanni DeLuca?
There's only like, ten of these left in the world. Chloe's always dreamed of having one.
It suits her. It'd be a shame if she didn't get to try it before she sends me away. What do you think?
Try it. It's a gift for you.
I can't accept this. It's too valuable. Too precious.
Do you like it?