He also helped my mother with the board when my father passed away.
I'm sorry.
I need his father died, saving Sophia from drowning.
Ever since then, my mother has taken care of her.
So, you two are raised together, like family.
In a sense, we have the same rare blood type.
So, any time she was ill, I would donate blood.
That's how you two fell in love.
You know, some people would say that you two are destined to be together.
Sophia used to think the same thing.
And we see how that turned out.
She abandoned me at the wedding.
And I'm just not one of those people that believes in destiny or fate.
What do you believe in?
I believe in the choices that we make.
Like my choice to kiss you right now.