Don't want to do business with you, Mr. Foster.
Heard what she said. Sometimes it's just not about the money, right? Should we continue, Chloe?
I have my answer now, Chloe. I can't keep lying to you or to myself. Please.
Sorry, Taylor.
It's all right. I'll see you at the studio. Buy yourself out, Tiger.
So what did you want to tell me?
This morning when you left, I was terrified. I can't stay in the idea of losing you. I've never
met it. Anyone like you and my feelings towards you are so strange and I think I didn't know what
those feelings were until now. I love you, Chloe. Ethan, marriage and family are so incredibly
important to me. I can't be with someone who doesn't think the same. To take it back,
that's not what you're expecting.
Will you marry me?