Who are you marrying me?
Yes, I'm marrying you.
I will be the only woman you marry, Ethan.
I'm going to make sure there is no other wedding.
You have no idea what I'm cute with alone.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Is this an invitation, boy?
There's no details on it, just an address and a date.
That's for tonight?
It's a surprise.
Trying to maintain some level of mystery here.
I also have a surprise for you.
What is it?
Not until tonight.
I can be quite mysterious, too.
Do you like it?
I want to make the same cake for your wedding.
Chloe?
You okay?
Ethan is going to kill me if I got you sick.
It's not the cake.
Well, are you sure?
Maybe I should call a doctor.
I took a test last night.
I'm pregnant.