Where's Chloe?
She okay?
Not good.
She got really depressed with pregnancy.
Her condition is at risk the doctor had to do an emergency C-section and I don't know
I panicked.
You're taking away from me and this is what happens.
She insisted on keeping the baby, even though every doctor told her it was risky.
Miss Gray is out of danger, but your daughter, my daughter, it's been a tough day for all
of us.
She gets some risk, Vivian.
Call me if she wakes up.
So much Chloe.
Even.
Where's my daughter?
She's an incubator.
Under medical observation.
She's so small.
So fragile.
You need to be prepared.
Her condition's not good.
The doctor says she could leave us at any moment.