I want that child gone.
Daddy, I did the math.
A month ago, remember the night she didn't come home
and was hungover for like a week?
I just think about it.
When was the last time she had a boyfriend?
You know, usually I wouldn't care, but this could affect my reputation.
Who wants to marry the sister of a slut?
Stop, sister.
Regina is your sister and more of a daughter to me than you.
You're a disgrace to this family.
I want that child gone.
You had a bastard child of your own with your mistress.
How about this? You get rid of yours and other people.
You are no daughter of mine.
Great. That's all I ever wanted.
There are times when you don't need a passport.
She's an emergency section right there.
Stop missing.