Do you have a marriage?
Marriage? She is beautiful.
And the kids do like her.
But after Anna.
So...
I don't know.
Hey, you make some things sister cries for me.
Yay!
Are you sure about this?
I mean, I'm with a horse out. I have two kids.
And them broke.
Really?
I mean...
By the way, you're dressed. It looks like you do fine.
Oh, no, this is a company uniform.
I'm a driver.
I'm for the CEO.
You have my queen eight to nine thousand dollars a month.
Yeah, I'm broke.
Nine thousand dollars? That's way more than I do.
No, sorry. I mean, eight dollars to nine thousand dollars.
I mean, grabbing when he's in town, he, you know, he travels a lot.
It's very broke.
Where do you live?
Oh, over in a green one.
Hmm. Green one.
That's where all the old money is.
Like, the richest of the rich.
You got me.
That's where my boss lives.
I don't have a house.
Yeah.
I like to brag.
But I'm broke.
Me too.
I'm a shoe sales person.
I guess it was the top seller last month.
Me.
Yeah.
I'm broke.
Isn't it?
It's so bad.
Look at the match.
Oh.
Shh.
You know what?
Just think about it.
And talk to your kids.
It's important that they want this too.
And let me know by tomorrow.
Sure.
Thank you.