Do you need some help with that?
No.
No, I got it.
It's easy here.
Here.
It just goes here.
Here we go.
How are you so good at that?
Oh, I had to build all the furniture for my apartment.
It helps to be handy sometimes.
Oh.
What's this?
It's done to people.
It's this.
Can I have that back?
You want it?
Come here.
Throw it in your lap.
Remember that next time you taught me.
It was really good.
Any way through a fashion school?
Oh, no.
I just really like designing when I was younger.
My mom said that I was a prodigy.
Why don't you pursue me?
Life hasn't been easy for me.
Sometimes it feels like I'm all down to get me.
Not that feeling.
But sometimes life offers in front of help.
Or a husband.