Um, so your Ethan Parker's stripe?
Yep.
That's why you had that response when I called him a dog.
Oh, um, this is my mother.
She's raised three generations of the parkers, and my dad, the gardener.
And we all work Ethan Parker.
Hi mom, hi dad.
Hi.
She's very excited.
It is so nice to meet you.
Ethan, I can't believe you've been holding out for so long.
Um, what do you do for work, uh, daughter?
I work as a design assistant at OL Creative Agency.
Ah, I see my son knows how to keep it in the family.
Because we all work for the parkers.
Of course.
Yeah.
This house is really beautiful.
What do you guys love?
I thought you were at the office today.
Why are you here?
Oh, yes.
I'm here to deliver a glass art piece for Ethan Parker.
This is a Celine Perkins original.
My god, how could that have happened?
I was so careful.