Hi, Doctor.
Hey.
Thank you for meeting with me.
Um, I have a few questions about a woman, a patient from five years ago.
A woman gave birth on March 8th.
What are the medical records?
Sorry about the alcohol I just got for two days ago.
What?
Everything was destroyed.
Is there any other way to figure them out?
I'm afraid not.
Thanks.
Anyway.
Doctors have been taken care of.
Great.
I'll transfer over your little thank you reward.
It's nothing, baby.
When a woman says that nothing is always something.
I told you.
You can get it.
Daddy, come home now.
Mommy's upset.
We need you right now.
Why are you talking to your daddy like that?
If anybody makes me sad, we would take him.
We love you.