Forget it. Forget it.
You said they were, they were, you know, right?
I guess we'll just save money on flowers in the future.
I told you, stop worrying about money.
How can you say that?
We have a family to take care of.
And I will take care of them.
Like us.
And speaking of which, I have something to tell you.
Yeah, so you can investigate the grievances between you and Christina.
Here are the results.
Sketches.
Why are you showing me this?
This is a design by Christina from eight years ago.
It went on the college design gold award.
But it was flagged for plagiarism.
Not only did she lose the award, but she got expelled from the school.
That's sad, but how does that play to her, hating me?
The one who reported her was Anna, our ex-wife.
They were classmates and trials.
And she did it under your name.
Sorry.
Why would she do that?
Hi.
Please cancel all expenses for Anna's overseas adventures.
Thank you.