What are you doing here?
The kids call me mommy.
What do you think I'm doing here?
The school called me here.
Did they call you?
After all, I am their real mother.
I understand you want more time.
I'm not here just to spend more time with them.
I'm taking back what belongs to me.
And what would that be?
My husband and my children.
So you used your job to get close to me just so you can destroy my life.
I give you the opportunity to become someone great
and you're sacrificing it for what?
A divorced man and two children who aren't yours?
I'll finish that project.
Take the money and protect my family.
We'll see who they choose in the end.
May the best mother win.