I want the finished designs on my desk by Monday.
Are you serious?
It's Friday, and I'm taking the kids to the aquarium this weekend.
Funny, I was planning to take them on a yacht trip this weekend.
Tell me, do you think they'd rather go with you to a crowded aquarium to eat cheap burgers,
or with me to a private beach to enjoy a French beast?
You can't buy their love, Anna.
What are you doing here, Anna?
Can we talk?
Nothing to talk about.
Must you be so cold to me?
We weren't married at one point.
My name only.
We got married because you got pregnant.
Oh, I love little Mason Melinda.
You don't love them.
How could I not love my children?
I carried them for nine months when they're sleepless nights,
morning sickness, and pushing my organs around to give them life.
I'm asking to make amends.
Can you please fulfill the wish of a humble mother?