Did you block an Instagram?
Oh, did I?
I almost met an accident.
Oh.
Well, could you unblock me?
Maybe.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
So you're not upset?
Is there a reason for me to be?
Nope.
Then I'm not upset.
Alright.
Just had a curiosity.
Do you have any plans with the kids this weekend?
Uh...
Yeah?
I've got a few things lined up.
What plans?
Um, we're gonna go see my parents.
They miss their grandkids.
Is that your husband?
That's him.
The steak goes behind.
It's gonna be extra.
Tomorrow I'll get you a big tip.
Pretty well, miss.
Where are we?
To see a side back hotel.
Please, darling.
Oh, my goodness.
That's how I ended, right?
No, I just realized I made a really big mistake.
You think that's your miss?
No.
I...
I need to go out.
How?
How where?
To the nearest bar.
I'm gonna go find Mommy.
Can I stay here?
If anyone knocks, open the door.
Okay?
What do you do with my wife?
I'm so easy, ladies.
You all were in on it.
You told me you were going to see your parents.
But really you saw Anna.
How'd you know?
I'm not gonna stop you from talking to me.
You want to, but just stop by.
My face!
It's all you saw.
We liked it.
Look how she posts her Instagram.
So I got you a...
Look how she feasts.
And my more surprise.
The kids taught me to do it.
Our family is complete without a family pet.
Mommy, our old father was following us today.
Happy birthday, darlings.
Who wants a day on a fancy yacht with Mommy?
It's docked and ready with a French feast already prepared.
Who's hungry?
I don't want you here.
Leave us alone.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, but we didn't pay her any attention.
But she's their mother.
She was no mother at all.
She was never around.
You aren't.
You guys aren't my children.
Whether you're a biologic or not, I love you both.
Always love you.
And that's what makes a family.
Love.
You were ice.
What?
How many times do I have to tell you to stop spending money?
No, I didn't drop a dime.
I got to be collecting shells and my pounds and pearls.
Fine.
Yeah, we put it on.
It's beautiful.
But I'll come down to the necklace.
Neither.
I'm so glad that you'd rely on me about going to your parents.
I just wanted to make you happy.
I hate dishonesty.
I want to build truths between us.
I want to build trust between us.
Good?
So, if you liked me ever again,
I would have pushed you harder than you've ever been.
Thought I might find you in here.
It's a matter, bro.
You scared me?
We'll get you searching for the meaning of life.
What's on your mind?
I can't keep it a secret anymore.
I got to be honest with her.
Okay, but you have to be tactful.
Okay?
How do I do that?
In my experience, you start by telling her or sneezing or sneezing.
That way we can tell the real news.
It doesn't seem that bad.
Okay.
What could be worse than your husband lying to you and everyone else being in on it?
Useless.
Okay, how about this?
You start by telling her you've been diagnosed with a terminal illness and you've got like 10 days left to live.
On the bright side, you're a billionaire.
Her and the kids won't hear everything.
Yeah.
As I said before, useless.
You're so sharp with business, but you don't know the first thing about romance.
How about this?
You speak from your heart.
Hey, Christina.
I need to talk to you.
You need me to toss a hotel tonight.
So, what do you want to tell her?
The truth?
If I keep lying through her, she'll divorce me.
Got to be honest.
You're just quite nice.
Going somewhere?
What do you want, Emma?
That is a nice necklace.
Oxygen that saw at the last month by the Austrian royal family, I believe.
He must have spent a lot of money on that.
I don't have time to listen to you.
I have somewhere to be.
Even if I said your husband is really Ethan Parker and he's been lying to you since the beginning.
He didn't have the children involved in his little lie. Isn't that crazy?
So, he was the one who sabotaged my job.
He did whatever he could do appease me.
I'm sorry it had to be you.
I want a divorce.
What?
Why?
You've lied to me the entire time.
Your monthly salary, your job, even your parents.
What were you afraid that I was in poor gold digger?
Who told you?
No, no, but I mean, yes, but I can explain.
You couldn't just ruin my career.
You had to go and ruin my whole life.
No, Christina.
I didn't know any about the competition.
I swear.
Okay, please, you've just got to believe me, okay?
I mean, I can explain everything.
If you lied about your own name, how am I supposed to believe anything else you sang?
I'll enjoy your night, Ethan.
Yeah, please.
I'll give you anything.
Anything but a divorce.
There's no going back.
I don't care.
I've already packed the luggage.
It's dark outside.
It's an unsafe to go outside alone.
I won't let you leave.
Who said I was the one leaving?
This is your luggage.
Or dish soap?
You have gone ahead.
Absolutely mad, my friend.
What are you doing doing housework?
Don't you have a parent teacher gone from CO2?
Christina's gonna be there?
Go.
You might catch her in time.
No.
No, if I go, she will make me send a divorce papers.
I'm not going.
School of Reject returns.
Hmm.
It says the one who failed all our exams.
If your father didn't donate money to the building, you wouldn't have even graduated.
We all know about your plagiarism scandal.
I just have the adoption to share your face.
I have nothing to prove to you.
Ms. Hayes, I didn't expect to see you here.
I heard you're getting a divorce.
Yes.
I am.
And if you want my sloppy seconds, he's all yours.
Welcome, esteemed graduates of the University of Arts and Design.
I have a surprise announcement I'd like to make.
But first, allow me to introduce you to a special guest.
CEO and chairman of the Parker Corporation, Mr. Ethan Parker.
Dean Ethan Parker.
He looks so handsome a person.
Why is he here though?
Ethan was last reported to have been married to Anna Ellis before they had the twins.
He's clearly here to support his ex-wife.
Really?
Even after the divorce?
That must be true, Bob.
Years ago, our school received a generous donation from Miss Honeywell's family that became the foundation of our design program.
And now, our school will truly be the best and most complete design school in the country, if not the world.
I have the great pleasure to announce that the Parker Family Trust has just donated $1.2 billion to allow us to build our new state-of-the-art fashion design building.
Allow me to introduce the Christina Hayes School of Design coming next year.
Mr. Parker, I believe you have a theme of remarks.
Your family trust my installation because we believe that Miss Hayes is the greatest designer of your generation.
But she copied your wife's work.
That scandal was completely unfounded.
And I've prepared a statement.
This was a serious mistake made by a junior staffer, Lake Parker Corporation of Subsidaries.
And we sincerely apologize to Miss Hayes, framed Sufferin's as cause for over the years.
In the future, Lake Parker Family Trust will continue to support Miss Hayes and her designs and will allocate another million dollars to open a scholarship in her name to support future designers for the upcoming generation.
You aren't really going to reward that cheater, are you?
If anyone has any objections, we are willing to reopen the scandal for investigation.
You really are cruel, Ethan.
I don't think I can take it anymore.
Well, we really have a way with women.
It's having a rich hour for a bunch of husbands. Pretty nice, isn't it?
You're joking, right?
You're no hero.
And we weren't for you, I wouldn't have to be saved in the first place.
You're right.
You're ankle sore.
Look as wise.
We're out of ice.
Then I'll go get some.
You don't like it.
I'm going to show you why you shouldn't.
When I get home, I do the chores.
For laundry.
For floors.
I wash dishes.
And then I go upstairs and I lie next to you.
Please.
Don't divorce me.
What's the meaning of this?
This is not even a second of a purchase leading to a dark future.
That is, you didn't pay the power.
Now go do it.
Does this mean you don't look at me?
It's eagerly anticipating the upcoming wedding of Ethan Parker and Christina Hayes.
With the big day, just a few days away, the city is a bond.
This is all your fault.
I'm going to make you pay for a suffering.
The city and Christina Hayes are set to exchange vows in what promises to be a spectacular event.
Can you bother her?
We think it's leukemia.
Don't worry, we're going to test her bone marrow as he even matches his.
And I'll contact other hospitals as well.
Should we get more than a tester as well?
Yes.
Some things have a higher chance of a match.
There's no match.
Hang on the registry, but it could take some time.
Is there anything else we can do to help him?
There's always another way.
What do you want?
To save my son.
What do you suggest?
Marry me.
We have another child together and they can be tested for a bone marrow transplant.
What?
Are you crazy?
I will never marry you.
We're just going to wait and hope that something pops up on the registry.
Hello?
Speaking.
Thank you.
What is it?
Somebody responded.
We have a match.
How do you feel, sweetie?
Have you found Mommy?
Well just think about my birthday for next year.
Let's do it right without that Mom around.
Of course.
What the end do you want?
A princess thing become my sister of the princess and my mom of the princess too.
You'll always be Mommy's little prince.
You look like you can use another coat.
Let me go see if they have one.
I came for you.
I've got a sick child that's very fragile.
This is not the type that lives with me.
Five years ago I got a hold of Mr. Maynard's video from about all that.
If you then finds out that you got pregnant by a stranger and you think you can still marry into the prestigious family,
I won't change anything.
Fine.
Let's see how long you can keep up this tough girl.
Be with someone else to cancel the banquet.
You aren't dreaming of marrying into the Parker family's about to crumble.
Finish watching.
We met marrying someone with such a past.
I don't care about her past.
I love who she is now.
And it seems like you never learned your lesson.
Mark, get her out of here.
No!
Stop!
Please!
Let me go!
Stop!
His Mark canceled the wedding.
I fell asleep at home.
That night at the buzz of the hotel.
I was there too.
I was confused.
I was Hannah.
But...
It was actually you.
Me?
Of course.
Which is why.
Every time.
This is a DNA test on Mason and Melinda.
The parents said you have one that's Mason and Melinda.
But I thought I was supposed to have two boys.
Well, the parents lied.
You were born a girl.
Wait, so...
Mason and Melinda are my biological children?
Yep.
And I'm never gonna let anybody hurt you ever again.
What's the matter?
Well, tell me you're pregnant again from the other night.
Well, I mean, I have some important tell you.
So, my birthday is coming up.
And on that day, five years ago...
I gave birth to a set of twins.
Oh, a story short.
Mommy is actually your biological mommy.
Well, duh.
So, since we all share the same birthday,
who's up for a princess party?
Does that mean we got more presents?
Yes, of course.
And gentlemen, he's welcome.
The beautiful bride.
Where's your brother?
He said he turned into an angel.
Mason, just because you're better doesn't mean you won't get a spank.
Oh, come on.
You're okay.
Do not hit that chart.
May you wonder,
encountering love and beauty,
may you have a home to return to,
someone waiting,
food team,
a lamp left on, just for you.