Even your jokes are terrible. Do you really think you could afford one? Do you have that kind of money?
An international auto expo. Even though what it is, that's where the real elite's gathered.
And you'd think you'd be invited.
Actually, yes. I attended for the first time this year, and I've been invited almost every single year, but I'm just busy.
Oh! They've been invited every year.
Let me guess, and then the governor invited you to this party.
Are you talking about Henry? Yeah, Henry didn't have a party this year.
Unbelievable! This guy is such a clown.
Huh? Do you think it's a move done without a fear to us?
Okay. Caroline, there is a lot of Queen Caroline.
And I will tell you this.
Okay. I don't have time for this nonsense, Caroline.
The president of the Horton Group has just arrived and read them now.
I must help my father prepare the welcome bank. Bye, Doris.
This is all your fault. Now, Andrew's upset. Why can't you just let Caroline be with Andrew?
Mom, let's go and solve. Dad's waiting. I'm sorry. Mom's a bit hot-tempered.
I will always be both sides.
You have waited for me for three years, and I am forever grateful for that.
I just want you to know that wherever you are,
I will always be by your side. Thank you.
I missed you too.
I'm glad you're back.
Me too.
Hey, Demi.
Oh, my God. Caroline. You'll never guess how this happened.
I just saw the president of the Horton Group. He's so young. Red Sue Harrison.
He was like, I saw him love it.