It's my best friend. I'll introduce you guys later. She's the shining star of the alphabet.
Okay.
I'm excited to watch it this time.
Alright.
He's a...
That charmin, huh?
He's totally my type.
Oh, by the way, Caroline, please help me pick out a sis-lum-trow.
I must capture our young hot president's eyes at the welcome dinner tonight.
You got it, girl.
Tonight, you are a special baby boy.
Hey, Caroline, your mom lost husband and finally made it back.
Heidi, you know, Philip was just working out of time.
Oh, good for him.
I was afraid we'd see him on the news,
where I'm having a bank or getting a little rested.
Heidi, thank you very much for your concern.
Alright, alright. Heidi is just messing around.
Philip, you have any gifts for us?
Yes, Nick, go ahead and pick whichever one of you would like.
Looks like plastic broaches, some wine from a fake vineyard and cheap ceramics
that won't even sell for ten bucks.
Caroline here, are you sure your man isn't going to trick on us?