You know that for let's just the viewer talk time. I'm sure he had to pick
I know Caroline actually
These are some really expensive items, especially the wine is actually from a vineyard called tri-a vineyard
Vineyard is a top-notch vineyard
And he says Paul vineyard
Never heard of Paul's vineyard. It's probably some roadside dump
Might not even be safe for the drink. Actually Heidi Hall's vineyard was their old name
And this is actually a very rare wine. It's actually from their last batch something that money can't buy
To be honest stop making up stories
I've been drinking pry a wine for years
They've never changed their name
Even if these gifts aren't worth much, it's a big quote. We appreciate them
Thank you Caroline. You're very sweet
Let's use the wine for cooking and prawn the broaches and ceramics
There's something going on at Kesso's trading thrift store where junk like this can maybe sell them ten bucks
Now that is a good idea
You actually might be able to turn a profit on all this now
Heidi you've always been the brains of the family
You know the ignorance at this table is really starting to get to me now if mr.
Draven was here who'd be owner of that vineyard to be able to tell you the value of these items immediately
You clown are you insulting us? No
I am not strictly just telling you the facts now if mr. Draven was here
He'd probably be making you guys all crying and apologizing to me