Hey kid. What are you doing here? Should be home for Christmas?
You work here?
Yeah. I'm headed the inspection department.
My uncle gave me this note. She said I could pick out her car and get the toy model that comes with it.
Oh boy. I want to sleep pranks. But I was just as useless as...
Oh my god.
Is this real?
This has the one who's present signature on it.
Mr. Can I make my thunderblade 9x now?
Uh, sure. Funny woman.
Philip. What's the deal here?
I try to get you a job and you throw it in my face.
Someone like you should show some respect to the Bob and what I've lost.
Philip, listen.
If you care so much about your so-called dignity, then getting a job, you're the biggest fool in the world.
Mom, Dad, look!
Did you really get the same car?
In the real thunderblade 9x.
Mr. Ian drove it over for me.
A real thunderblade 9x.
Come, let's see.
Is this not good for you?
Mr.