Caroline, don't you get it?
Your husband's Philip, he is a fraud.
No.
No, guys, I don't believe that Philip would do something like this.
Well, thank you for your trust, Caroline.
You know, I hate to say this to you all, but you're over home.
Wrong.
What could we possibly hear all about?
Hm?
Explain that damn signature.
Well, I'm actually.
Caroline, I'm back.
It's Andrew.
He's back from his work.
Let's deal with Philip's issues later.
We don't want to embarrass ourselves in front of Andrew.
Doris, I have some great news for you.
I've heard that Barra, the plant manager,
is coming by to wish you all a Merry Christmas, too.
You are truly blessed.
Everyone is showing you guys so much love.
That's great.
Sure is lively out there.
I had to cut my physical therapy session short.
So I could join you guys.
Draven, perfect timing.
This is Andrew.
He's the deputy director of the Ravenham Auto Plant.
He's spending Christmas with us.
This is the new Hansel and Beyond Man.
I enjoy that.
This gift is for you, Draven.
Oh, I've got you a diamond watch.
OK, thank you.
And a top tier bottle of warring for you, baby.
Andrew, how did you know Freya wines were my fav?
Look, yes, Andrew is always a generous person,
whereas some people bring us junk to ruin the holidays.
Doris, whether you believe he or not,
the struct world is good stuff.
This can't even cover half of what I've got.