But what are you talking about?
You all have no idea how twisted this guy really is and how low he's gotten.
He forged the President's signature opportunity to be someone he's not.
He's a con artist!
Dear God, you deserve that burning hell!
Cody, we know exactly who this guy is.
He's nothing but a filthy bum.
There's no way he's a big shot in the Wharton route.
He's been tricked.
You need to shut this instance!
Sir, I know it's all I do, sir, but he's a far not you.
I'll have my man take him to the police station right now.
No, not yet!
You low life, you've made me beg for mercy in front of all these people.
Now I'm going to take your bitch!
No, I'm going to get your bitch going right.
I'm going to go with me.
I'm going to go with you.
Hey, we're just getting started.
You can thank your husband for putting you in this mess.
You know, I'm going to give you one more chance to let go of you.
I'm going to your little games so you just sit and watch as I screw your bitch right here,
but I'm never buying you.
You know what?
I think I changed my life.
I'll clean you out myself.