What would she say?
Pharaoh's going to tear into this imposter and drag him in front of the real president for a proper punishment.
What's so funny, Philip?
Fag me and I might put in a good word, but of course, Caroline would ask for mine.
Don't get it twisted.
I'm only laughing because you already got one for the grave.
What?
Don't worry, you don't have to understand what I'm saying.
Just start thinking about your last words.
Fuck you!
How about I break the nose and see how cocky you really are?
Enough!
All you fuckers are dead.
Shut up, boy!
You laid hands on my son.
I can all smug and shit.
Congratulations, Philip.
You've officially pissed me off.
Save it, Dad.
I'll teach him a lesson right now.
First, I'll shoot him in his legs, then his arms, and then when he's suffered enough, I blow his fucking hand.
I can't take this anymore!
I'm gonna know I'm in the crowd.
You don't want someone finding out that you just took this imposter for the real president.
Who you still with this boy deserves?
You getting away?
That's right.
Getting away with my think you're in on.
Fucking motherfuckers is beyond fucking saving!
What's the matter, Philip?
Wasn't it you?
It just said, what were my last words?
Maybe it should be saying that lie.
Your stupidity never disappoints me, Andrew.
Still yapping away.
Goodbye, Philip.
Andrew, stop!