What happened to her?
Alpha?
She's with some guy.
Do you win the case?
Of course.
Before the first appeal was closed, the defendant proposed a negotiation of 100 million.
I disagreeed until it's increased to 1 billion.
Can you believe it?
Where's Brian?
I want to tell him the good news.
Uh, he's not here.
I don't know why you waste your time, Jesse.
He doesn't care about you.
Do you know what they call me in the New York Times?
Legal, beauty.
If I'm not the girl in his eyes, who can it be?
You?
You can't resist me now.
Well, it seems like we'll never know if you're the girl.
But someone is.
What the fuck?
Hi, Brian.
I settled the case that you gave me.
Very well.
You dare violate our mate bond and go and find another guy.
Who do you think I am?
Who is this?
She knew.
Brian's commercial assistant.
Enough!
No, I won't be your defense lawyer.
She's only six!
How could you fucking touch her?
No!
You're a pedophile and you deserve to be executed without trial and let your body rot and mud.
So rare to see Brian being so emotional, what happens?
Well, you just got married.
It was wife's ugly.
Hey, Lisa.
As Mr. Green's assistant, you had his wedding, right?
What does his wife look like?
Well, but...
Oh.
Brian hasn't made our marriage public yet.
Maybe he doesn't want others to know.
One took me.
What?
You're the famous attorney, Brian Green.
You're so hot.
Can I have your Instagram?
I didn't realize you were such a loyal husband.
You know, I'm only your fake wife.
You can absolutely.
So, if some cute guy comes through, you're going to jump into his arms.
Girls like you are so easy.
Girls like me.
Improper to judge someone so ruthlessly did something piss you off?
Be your food slick.
Sir, I think you misjudged that girl.
Really?
Well, explain.
You're rich and handsome.
You could easily have any girl you wanted.
That girl just now, she had no idea that you were married.
Second, that she saw the ring, she backed off.
Why are you judging her?
She was brave.
Lisa's right.
I'm out of touch.
If you had misunderstood my mate as well,
I should let her tell me the truth in person.
I'm sorry, Lisa.
My bad.
I was being arbitrary.
It's fine.
I forgive you.
Thank you for enlightening me.
Why don't you come with me shopping?
Help me pick out an outfit.
As someone important, I have to meet.
Back off their heads.
I'm lying.
It's been two hours since Lisa and Brian left, and they're not back.
Lisa's such a bitch.
She knows Brian has a wife, but she's so clingy with him.
I saw how flirty she was being in his office.
Slide.
Okay.
I'll go pay for this and you can wait for me outside.
Give me your purse.
And your ring.
You can't have it.
You're gonna die.
No!
Back off their heads look alike.
Get lost.
Don't tell me you're falling in love with me now.
We are a fake couple after all.
What were you thinking, Lisa?
They can't be the same person.
My hero is much more tender than this guy.
Thank you.
Sir, I can't imagine what would have happened if you hadn't showed up.
Don't worry about it.
I mean, I didn't see you for a minute, so I had to check on you, right?
So, as a thank you, take this.
For helping me pick up clothes early.
You okay?
Sir, I really like it.
Aside from my best friend, you're the only person who's been nice to me.
I'm just deeply touched.
Well, you can repay me at work.
I expect you to be the best lawyer you can be.
I'll work like a Trojan.
You were gonna meet someone.
You should go home.
I'll do that.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Is Elizabeth home?
How do you know Elizabeth?
Where are you from?
From New Jersey.
I'm Jersey.
Jesus Christ.
Look, I'm warning you.
I'm Elizabeth's boyfriend.
Her boyfriend.
Why should I believe you?
Let her tell me herself.
You sure do have guts.
Wait here.
Hi.
I kind of came to see you.
He must be some henchmen of Paul's.
I could scare him for you.
I'm gonna need your cooperation.
Okay.
Honey, that guy came again.
He doesn't believe that I'm your boyfriend, so we're gonna have to prove it to him.
What the fuck out?
Hey, where's that coat?
Which coat?
The one my savior gave me.
Oh, you mean Mr. Wax coat?
I'm not that bold, it just throwed away.
Mr. Wax?
Her name suits him.
By the way, Paul made his way to the apartment.
Do we have to move?
We have to move?
Not a chance.
He'll find me anyway.
Hey, can I be a coward?
I'll have to confront him.
You know what?
Let's not talk about your wicked father anymore.
Let's talk about something new.
How's work in your newlywed husband?
It's good.
As for my vice, not as cold as I thought.
He's warm inside.
He's a fantastic lawyer.
Unbelievable.
You actually like him.
What about Mr. Wax?
You like him.
What's not to like?
How could I resist a haughty?
Show me a pic.
Really?
A petty woman.
You just don't want to show me.
Keep your old phone.
It's late.
Who could that be?
Hello.
You're bright like the moon in the sky.
Don't ever leave me.
No, don't go.
Oh, no, don't go.
Don't go.
Thank you.
So much.
Oh, my girl.
You're bad.
You're not.
No, I'm not strong.
Where's that?
Shagrin, you said I could still be myself after I started this contract.
But I don't think that's the case.
Why did you get so drunk?
I don't have to take care of you.
In the contract.
I have to change your shirt and you're going to get sick.
I'm your assistant at work, not at home.
Why am I taking care of you like a baby?
Why did you do that?
I'm so sorry.
I won't happen again.
Why?
Why did you reject me?
Morning.
Did you take me home yesterday?
Don't just sit there.
You're going to be late for work.
I'll talk it out of your salary.
Ready to receive.
Is it real that our mate lives with some other guy?
So sorry.
What shall we do?
I guess I'll cut the mate bond with her.
She doesn't even deserve to be our mate.
Stop acting on impulse.
If we didn't lose our sense of pheromones,
our mate never would have been able to climb up to some other guy's bed.
We should win her back.
Win her back.
You are so eager to be the first cut-golden werewolf in the whole werewolf world.
No, I'll cut the mate bond with her right now.
Hey Lisa.
Why don't you tell me what happened between you and Brian yesterday?
You guys went out to lunch and they disappeared all after noon.
Then you showed up this morning side by side.
You didn't even change your clothes.
Do you even go home last night?
You are not going to hook up with Brian.
He's married, you bitch.
What can I do?
I can't declare a marriage Mr. Green wouldn't allow it.
Jesse, when it comes to law, you are a senior.
I am nearly an assistant.
Incomparable to you.
But when you talk like that, it makes me question your professionality.
You.
Did I say it wrong?
You don't want an assistant teaching you how to be professional.
Right?
So, watch your mouth.
Hello?
I was the one who saved you a month ago in New Jersey.
You.
I want to say that.
Let's meet sometime to cut off our mate bond.
Our mate bond.
What do you mean?
12 AM tomorrow.
You'll know by then.
Just now.
I hated my heartache when he said to cut the mate bond.
What's a mate bond?
All werewolves have their mates destined by the moon goddess.
But if they don't want their mate anymore, they can cut their mate bond.
Jack their mate, and they can reject them face-to-face.
Come with me to meet a client.
I'm sorry.
There's some new game up.
Can I please be excused for the day?
What happened, honey?
I remember when I told you that it was almost violated by a werewolf.
Yeah, and Mr. Wax saved you, but what makes you so sad?
He's also a werewolf.
Oh.
You kidding?
Oh, I'm not kidding.
Oh, honey.
You said that I miss mate.
Honey, I'm confused.
What's a mate?
Like, like soul mate?
Oh, honey.
Then shouldn't you be happy?
He saved you.
And you like him.
You two are like bounded soul mates.
Why are you crying?
He wants to cut ties with me.
What?
Oh, that dumbass.
Okay.
You are a catch.
He doesn't know what he's missing.
Where is he?
I am going to teach him a lesson.
He's the one that saved me.
He has the right to not like me.
And he has the right to reject his mate.
So I agreed to cut the mate bond and we're going to meet tomorrow.
Face-to-face.
I'm glad you think that way.
But I'm going to keep you good company.
I'll be here right by your side.
And even though I can't marry you,
I'm going to protect you from up to once.
See each other.
I've got to have a trick.
Any findings?
This is Brian's green swive.
Bernadimious Lisa Sterling.
Also goes by Elizabeth.
Beautiful Lisa.
Sadly, Brian disturbed us back in New Jersey.
And since you married him,
you're going to be the one to help me defeat him.
Hey, Lisa.
I just have been thinking about you since we graduated.
I wouldn't have finished college without you.
I don't expect to see you in New York.
My dear son in policeman.
Yeah, well.
You seem to have forgotten who you really are, Mr. Dylan.
Pretty bold for you to show up in my place.
Do you know each other?
Yeah, we more than know each other.
Don't get me wrong, Lisa.
We just have known each other for quite some time.
It seems like he really misses me.
So it is rare for us to meet in a crowd like this.
Isn't that right, Mr. Green?
Do not touch my woman.
You're late for work.
You still want a salary?
I'm green.
Wait, let's see.
Tell me.
How did he find you?
Dylan?
Don't get me wrong, sir.
Dylan and I went to college together.
Or, and I helped him.
And he meant to thank me.
You seem to be getting pretty intimate with him.
Have you forgotten about your agreement between you and I?
You're not supposed to date any men within the tenure of our contract.
I don't.
I swear there's nothing between us.
I didn't expect him to show up here.
I haven't even seen him since we graduated.
So, Dylan has put his eyes on Lisa.
I'm telling the truth, sir.
Okay.
Got it?
Come back to work.
Daniel, do you remember that werewolf I met back in New Jersey?
Well, he's in New York now.
I need you to alert all HAC members.
And we need to take precaution.
Got it, Alpha.
Wait.
Arrange some bodyguards to protect Lisa secretly.
He locked his eyes on her.
It's too dangerous for a human.
And I don't want any trouble.
Brush that Alpha.
By the way, I booked a table for you sound moon restaurant.
Shameless, bitch.
You can't stop flirting, can you?
Wasn't the cop enough for you?
You can't turn your tricks on by it.
He's married, you bitch.
Jesse, you're joking, right?
No, I'm telling the truth.
You can see it on her face.
It's a vine.
Keep it cool.
You don't admit you're a whore.
Are you irritated?
I eat me.
Oh, whoa.
She told me to-
I'm gonna kill you!
Kill who now?
Brian.
She bit me.
Everyone here can testify.
She vilified me.
We're bored on my shirt.