Right, what are you doing?
Why are you here?
I'm working.
Put him down, please.
I'm helping Lisa with work.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
So you're gonna care for another man right in front of me?
Sorry.
Lisa, I wanted to help you with your work.
But obviously Brian has a problem with me being here.
So I'll leave.
Dylan.
You better stay away from him.
He's dangerous.
I told you.
He's my college buddy.
I'm not a bad person.
How do you know that?
I saw the way he looked at you.
Like he wanted to devour you.
I'm your husband after all.
It's a fake marriage.
And we don't even look together.
So don't you think you're being a little bit possessive?
So that's so.
You can move in with me.
So we can keep an eye on you.