I just had some problems with the clients, but I figured it out.
What do you mean?
Nothing important, but it is my birthday, and I've been looking for our tear gaps.
But you could send yourself to me as a gift.
I don't mind being your mistress.
I do.
Actually, I'm not going to cheat on my wife.
I'm not going to get presents for anyone except my wife either.
Brian, what's so good with that bitch?
She didn't get a present today, but I don't like that.
You got the present today?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry we missed others since before.
That's alright.
I've never brought it up.
Cheers!
And you bitch, it's my birthday today, but you've stolen my thunder.
I'll make you pay.