What's this?
Come on!
Snap out of it!
She's just a regular girl.
Not our mate.
Why are you pining over like this?
She's not like those fain girls.
They're just afraid of me.
She even hates me.
Yeah, well, the girl has no taste.
You're the Supreme Alpha.
Countless women dream of being your Luna.
She's not like those fain girls.
It just seemed her first, so it's natural for her to hate me.
How about we just stick with our mate?
We're meeting her in three days, right?
Talk nicely to her.
After all, she's the best match for us.
Geez, don't be mad, man.
I'm just joking.
Why hasn't Brian come in?
I don't know.
I call them, but he didn't answer.
Hey, why hasn't Brian come in?
Are you his wife?
Could it be that Brian is tired of her?
Is this my chance?